[
  {
    "id": "2000",
    "name": "Expedition Orientation",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9598",
        "question": "In which part of the Expedition structure will you complete hands-on activities?",
        "answer": "Resources",
        "distractor_1": "Tasks",
        "distractor_2": "Expeditions",
        "distractor_3": "Destintations"
      },
      {
        "id": "9599",
        "question": "How are grading rubrics used during the Expedition?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "to assess your performance on tasks",
        "distractor_2": "to evaluate how well you worked with your partner",
        "distractor_3": "none of the above"
      },
      {
        "id": "9600",
        "question": "Which of the following could contribute to your grade for Expeditions?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "the attention to detail and other factors for the products you made",
        "distractor_2": "the performance assessment that the teacher grades",
        "distractor_3": "none of the above"
      },
      {
        "id": "9601",
        "question": "A Resource teaches you how to complete a graph. What kind of Resource is this?",
        "answer": "Lesson Resource",
        "distractor_1": "Activity Resource",
        "distractor_2": "Task Resource",
        "distractor_3": "Destination Resource"
      },
      {
        "id": "9602",
        "question": "Tasks are broken down into _________________.",
        "answer": "Resources",
        "distractor_1": "Destinations",
        "distractor_2": "Expeditions",
        "distractor_3": "events"
      },
      {
        "id": "9603",
        "question": "At the beginning and end of every Expedition, you have the option to complete ______________.",
        "answer": "a pretest or posttest",
        "distractor_1": "a soft skills survey",
        "distractor_2": "a self-reflection rubric",
        "distractor_3": "an evaluation of your work so far"
      },
      {
        "id": "9604",
        "question": "What can you reference when asked to find a specific section in your logbook?",
        "answer": "the table of contents in your logbook",
        "distractor_1": "the menu bar in the Expedition",
        "distractor_2": "the Expeditions Career Connections in your logbook",
        "distractor_3": "the index of your logbook"
      },
      {
        "id": "9605",
        "question": "What is the purpose of the logbook?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "to record what you have learned",
        "distractor_2": "to record data, observations, and solutions",
        "distractor_3": "to take notes"
      },
      {
        "id": "9606",
        "question": "Your teacher has asked you to complete the Expedition Career Connections page. Where do you find it?",
        "answer": "in the logbook",
        "distractor_1": "in the blue bin with the materials",
        "distractor_2": "online at www.pitsco.com/careerconnections",
        "distractor_3": "by clicking the Expedition Career Connections link under Destination 1"
      },
      {
        "id": "9607",
        "question": "On the back cover of your Expedition logbook, you notice some careers listed. What are these used for?",
        "answer": "They are careers related to the Expedition.",
        "distractor_1": "They are careers that require a college degree.",
        "distractor_2": "They are careers that have a positive job outlook.",
        "distractor_3": "They are careers that require travel."
      },
      {
        "id": "9608",
        "question": "You see a lightbulb on the corner of a Resource. What does this mean about that Resource?",
        "answer": "It’s optional.",
        "distractor_1": "It’s a favorite of the teacher.",
        "distractor_2": "You must complete it before moving on.",
        "distractor_3": "It’s a Resource that you have completed."
      },
      {
        "id": "9609",
        "question": "You see a star on the corner of a task. What does this mean about that task?",
        "answer": "You must complete it before moving on.",
        "distractor_1": "It’s optional.",
        "distractor_2": "It’s a task that you have completed.",
        "distractor_3": "It’s a favorite of the teacher."
      },
      {
        "id": "9610",
        "question": "You see a check mark on the corner of a Destination. What does this mean about that Destination?",
        "answer": "It’s a Destination that you have completed.",
        "distractor_1": "It’s a favorite of the teacher.",
        "distractor_2": "You must complete it before moving on.",
        "distractor_3": "It’s optional."
      },
      {
        "id": "9611",
        "question": "You want to move on, but when you try to click the next Destination, nothing happens. Why is this?",
        "answer": "You have not completed all the tasks in the current Destination.",
        "distractor_1": "The link is broken and you need to report it to your teacher.",
        "distractor_2": "You do not need to complete that Destination.",
        "distractor_3": "Your teacher has not unlocked that Destination for you."
      },
      {
        "id": "9612",
        "question": "What will you find on the menu bar of the Expedition?",
        "answer": "the title of the Expedition",
        "distractor_1": "how much time you have spent working on that Expedition",
        "distractor_2": "your progress through the Expedition",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9613",
        "question": "In which part of the Expedition experience will you complete hands-on activities?",
        "answer": "Activity Resources",
        "distractor_1": "Tasks",
        "distractor_2": "Expeditions",
        "distractor_3": "Destinations"
      },
      {
        "id": "9614",
        "question": "How can grading rubrics be used during the Expedition?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "to assess your performance on tasks",
        "distractor_2": "to decide what grade you earned",
        "distractor_3": "to evaluate how well you worked with your partner"
      },
      {
        "id": "9615",
        "question": "The Expedition has asked you to conduct an experiment. What kind of Resource is this?",
        "answer": "Activity Resource",
        "distractor_1": "Lesson Resource",
        "distractor_2": "Task Resource",
        "distractor_3": "Destination Resource"
      },
      {
        "id": "9616",
        "question": "Destinations are broken down into ________________.",
        "answer": "Tasks",
        "distractor_1": "Intervals",
        "distractor_2": "Expeditions",
        "distractor_3": "Arrivals"
      },
      {
        "id": "9617",
        "question": "At the beginning and end of every Expedition, you might complete _____________.",
        "answer": "a pretest or posttest",
        "distractor_1": "a soft skills survey",
        "distractor_2": "a self-reflection rubric",
        "distractor_3": "an evaluation of your work so far"
      },
      {
        "id": "9618",
        "question": "Which of the following best describes the purpose of the logbook?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "to record what was learned",
        "distractor_2": "to record data, observations, and solutions",
        "distractor_3": "to take notes"
      },
      {
        "id": "9619",
        "question": "Which of the following skills will help you succeed with your Expedition?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "being creative",
        "distractor_2": "problem solving",
        "distractor_3": "cooperating"
      },
      {
        "id": "9620",
        "question": "What can you do to learn about possible careers associated with the Expedition?",
        "answer": "Complete the Expedition Career Connections in the logbook.",
        "distractor_1": "View interviews with professionals associated with that Expedition on Pitsco’s YouTube channel.",
        "distractor_2": "Go online to www.pitsco.com/careerconnections.",
        "distractor_3": "Complete the Career Connection Expedition."
      },
      {
        "id": "9621",
        "question": "Where can you find careers that are connected to your Expedition?",
        "answer": "on the back cover of the logbook",
        "distractor_1": "at the bottom of the table of contents in the logbook",
        "distractor_2": "by clicking the help button in the Expedition",
        "distractor_3": "all of the above"
      },
      {
        "id": "9622",
        "question": "What symbol do you look for on a task to know if it’s required?",
        "answer": "a star",
        "distractor_1": "a check mark",
        "distractor_2": "a lightbulb",
        "distractor_3": "a mountain"
      },
      {
        "id": "9622",
        "question": "What symbol do you look for on a task to know if it’s optional?",
        "answer": "a lightbulb",
        "distractor_1": "a check mark",
        "distractor_2": "a star",
        "distractor_3": "a mountain"
      },
      {
        "id": "9623",
        "question": "What symbol do you look for on a task to know if it’s completed?",
        "answer": "a checkmark",
        "distractor_1": "a lightbulb",
        "distractor_2": "a star",
        "distractor_3": "a mountain"
      },
      {
        "id": "9624",
        "question": "You want to move on, but when you try to click the next Destination, nothing happens and it looks grayed out. Why is this?",
        "answer": "You have not completed all the tasks in the current Destination.",
        "distractor_1": "The link is broken and you need to report it to your teacher.",
        "distractor_2": "You do not need to complete that Destination.",
        "distractor_3": "Your teacher has not unlocked that Destination for you."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2021",
    "name": "Engineering Rockets",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8711",
        "question": "An object in motion remains in motion unless acted on by an unbalanced force.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8712",
        "question": "The larger the mass of an object, the smaller its gravitational force.",
        "answer": "False",
        "distractor_1": "True",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8713",
        "question": "The unit of force is ________.",
        "answer": "N",
        "distractor_1": "kg",
        "distractor_2": "s",
        "distractor_3": "m"
      },
      {
        "id": "8714",
        "question": "A ________ is a push or pull.",
        "answer": "force",
        "distractor_1": "mass",
        "distractor_2": "speed",
        "distractor_3": "time"
      },
      {
        "id": "8715",
        "question": "A force of 10 N pulls an object to the right, and a force of 7 N pulls to the left, what is the net force?",
        "answer": "3 N to the right",
        "distractor_1": "17 N to the right",
        "distractor_2": "70 N to the left",
        "distractor_3": "1.5 N to the left"
      },
      {
        "id": "8716",
        "question": "Modifying a vehicle's engine to get better gas mileage would most likely occur at which step of the engineering design process?",
        "answer": "Improve",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Imagine"
      },
      {
        "id": "8717",
        "question": "Brainstorming usually happens in which engineering step?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Plan",
        "distractor_2": "Create",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "8718",
        "question": "Testing, evaluating, and modifying a solution or product most likely occurs at which stage of the engineering design process?",
        "answer": "Improve",
        "distractor_1": "Imagine",
        "distractor_2": "Ask",
        "distractor_3": "Plan"
      },
      {
        "id": "8719",
        "question": "What is the point in an object where all of the object's weight is concentrated?",
        "answer": "center of gravity",
        "distractor_1": "balance point",
        "distractor_2": "drag point",
        "distractor_3": "apogee"
      },
      {
        "id": "8720",
        "question": "What is the sum of the forces acting on an object?",
        "answer": "resultant force",
        "distractor_1": "summative force",
        "distractor_2": "drag",
        "distractor_3": "weight"
      },
      {
        "id": "8721",
        "question": "Which of these is not a force that acts on a rocket?",
        "answer": "mass",
        "distractor_1": "crosswind",
        "distractor_2": "weight",
        "distractor_3": "drag"
      },
      {
        "id": "8722",
        "question": "What kind of stability is needed for a rocket to achieve its maximum altitude?",
        "answer": "positive stability",
        "distractor_1": "neutral stability",
        "distractor_2": "negative stability",
        "distractor_3": "pressure stability"
      },
      {
        "id": "8723",
        "question": "What is the study of how objects move through the air?",
        "answer": "aerodynamics",
        "distractor_1": "thermodynamics",
        "distractor_2": "propulsion mechanics",
        "distractor_3": "motion mechanics"
      },
      {
        "id": "8724",
        "question": "A rocket is launched and the observer measuring the rocket altitude is standing at a distance of 200 feet from the launcher. When the rocket reaches apogee, the observer measures an angle of 45° using an altitude scope. Calculate the altitude of the rocke",
        "answer": "200 feet",
        "distractor_1": "45 feet",
        "distractor_2": "245 feet",
        "distractor_3": "155 feet"
      },
      {
        "id": "8725",
        "question": "What is a constraint?",
        "answer": "a restriction or boundary that helps limit what solutions are available",
        "distractor_1": "a group of parts that work together for a common purpose",
        "distractor_2": "the exclusive right to manufacture and sell an invention",
        "distractor_3": "a solution to a problem"
      },
      {
        "id": "8726",
        "question": "What is an ideation technique used by groups to solve problems, generate ideas, and create designs and where people present ideas in an open forum?",
        "answer": "brainstorming",
        "distractor_1": "innovation",
        "distractor_2": "design",
        "distractor_3": "systems thinking"
      },
      {
        "id": "8727",
        "question": "Gravity is the force that pulls everything toward the center of Earth.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8728",
        "question": "What is a Newton?",
        "answer": "a unit of measure for force",
        "distractor_1": "a unit of measure for mass",
        "distractor_2": "a unit of measure for distance",
        "distractor_3": "a unit of measure for weight"
      },
      {
        "id": "8729",
        "question": "An object is moving with 2000 N force to the right, what is the minimum force needed to stop the object?",
        "answer": "2000 N to the left",
        "distractor_1": "2000 N to the right",
        "distractor_2": "8000 N to the left",
        "distractor_3": "4000 N to the right"
      },
      {
        "id": "8730",
        "question": "Which of the listed engineering steps would you use to brainstorm ways to use series circuits in a building?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Ask",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "8731",
        "question": "After testing a prototype in relation to its requirements, which of the following engineering steps would you do next if you wanted to refine it?",
        "answer": "Improve",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Imagine",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "8732",
        "question": "Engineers often design and use tools and instruments for which of the following activities?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "creating a prototype",
        "distractor_2": "testing a product or solution",
        "distractor_3": "gathering data"
      },
      {
        "id": "8733",
        "question": "What is ideation?",
        "answer": "the process of coming up with new ideas and ways to solve problems",
        "distractor_1": "the process of breaking a system down into subsystems",
        "distractor_2": "the process of gathering feedback to improve a system",
        "distractor_3": "the process of patenting a product"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2022",
    "name": "Urban Wind Farm",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8738",
        "question": "How many independent variables can be tested at one time during an experiment?",
        "answer": "1",
        "distractor_1": "2",
        "distractor_2": "As many as you would like",
        "distractor_3": "The same amount as the number of controlled variables"
      },
      {
        "id": "8739",
        "question": "A ________ observation deals with descriptions that cannot be expressed in numbers.",
        "answer": "qualitative",
        "distractor_1": "quantitative",
        "distractor_2": "investigation",
        "distractor_3": "science"
      },
      {
        "id": "8740",
        "question": "Modifying a vehicle's engine to get better gas mileage would most likely occur at which step of the engineering design process?",
        "answer": "Improve",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Imagine"
      },
      {
        "id": "8741",
        "question": "'The solar panel cannot exceed 2 m x 4 m' is a statement that describes which of the following?",
        "answer": "constraint",
        "distractor_1": "specification",
        "distractor_2": "both",
        "distractor_3": "neither"
      },
      {
        "id": "8742",
        "question": "Moving air causing propellers to turn a turbine is converted to electricity that powers a microwave oven. Which of the following energy sources best describes this example?",
        "answer": "wind",
        "distractor_1": "geothermal",
        "distractor_2": "hydro",
        "distractor_3": "solar"
      },
      {
        "id": "8743",
        "question": "In which of the following configurations would you expect the highest voltage? Assume the output from each power source is equal.",
        "answer": "three solar panels in a series circuit",
        "distractor_1": "three wind generators in a parallel circuit",
        "distractor_2": " one solar panel in a parallel circuit",
        "distractor_3": "one wind generator in a series circuit"
      },
      {
        "id": "8744",
        "question": "In which of the following configurations would you expect the highest current? Assume the output from each power source is equal.",
        "answer": "three wind generators in a parallel circuit",
        "distractor_1": "one solar panel in a parallel circuit",
        "distractor_2": "three solar panels in a series circuit",
        "distractor_3": "one wind generator in a series circuit"
      },
      {
        "id": "8745",
        "question": "Based on wind direction analysis, from which direction is the wind least likely coming in Chicago?",
        "answer": "southeast",
        "distractor_1": "northeast",
        "distractor_2": "northwest",
        "distractor_3": "southwest"
      },
      {
        "id": "8746",
        "question": "Of the following, which is most likely a constraint and not a criteria?",
        "answer": "maximum height of 3 in.",
        "distractor_1": "must be painted",
        "distractor_2": "must be able to be operated by remote control",
        "distractor_3": "vehicle must roll on wheels"
      },
      {
        "id": "8747",
        "question": "Brainstorming usually happens in which engineering step?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Improve",
        "distractor_2": "Create",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "8748",
        "question": "Which of the following activities would most likely not be used in the Improve engineering step?",
        "answer": "creating",
        "distractor_1": "evaluating",
        "distractor_2": "testing",
        "distractor_3": "modeling"
      },
      {
        "id": "8749",
        "question": "At which of the following heights would you expect the average wind speed in Chicago to be the least?",
        "answer": "10 m",
        "distractor_1": "80 m",
        "distractor_2": "100 m",
        "distractor_3": "140 m"
      },
      {
        "id": "8750",
        "question": "Of the following circuits, which type will show an increase in current when additional generators are added?",
        "answer": "parallel",
        "distractor_1": "series",
        "distractor_2": "open",
        "distractor_3": "closed"
      },
      {
        "id": "8751",
        "question": "Which of the following statements regarding the relationship between science and technology is false?",
        "answer": "Both scientists and technologists keep new knowledge and ideas secret so they can patent their ideas and make money.",
        "distractor_1": "The goal of science is to understand the natural world, while the goal of technology is to meet human needs or solve human problems.",
        "distractor_2": "Technologists use science to meet human needs.",
        "distractor_3": "Scientists use technology to find answers to questions."
      },
      {
        "id": "8734",
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a part of a well-designed experiment?",
        "answer": "small sample size",
        "distractor_1": "a reproducible procedure",
        "distractor_2": "multiple trials",
        "distractor_3": "a control"
      },
      {
        "id": "8735",
        "question": "John wanted to find out which laundry soap was best for removing grass stains. Each soap was mixed with warm water. It was then used to scrub a piece of grass-stained cloth for 1 minute. Then the amount of stain left on the cloth was measured. What is the",
        "answer": "type of laundry soap",
        "distractor_1": "amount of water",
        "distractor_2": "water temperature",
        "distractor_3": "scrubbing time"
      },
      {
        "id": "8736",
        "question": "Which of the following is a quantitative observation?",
        "answer": "My waist size is 31 inches.",
        "distractor_1": "Chemistry is an easy subject.",
        "distractor_2": "The flame is flickering.",
        "distractor_3": "My eyes are blue."
      },
      {
        "id": "8737",
        "question": "For an experiment, a scientist put lime at the base of tomato plant A and baking soda at the base of tomato plant B. She then sealed the plants in plastic bags. Tomato plant A eventually died, and tomato plant B stayed healthy. What was the dependent vari",
        "answer": "the response of the plants to each substance",
        "distractor_1": "the substance at the base of each plant",
        "distractor_2": "the types of plant grown for the test",
        "distractor_3": "the plastic bags wrapped around each plant"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2023",
    "name": "Building Bridges",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8752",
        "question": "Friction in which two surfaces are not moving past each other.",
        "answer": "Static",
        "distractor_1": "Rolling",
        "distractor_2": "Sliding",
        "distractor_3": "Fluid"
      },
      {
        "id": "8753",
        "question": "The unit of force is ________.",
        "answer": "N",
        "distractor_1": "m",
        "distractor_2": "s",
        "distractor_3": "kg"
      },
      {
        "id": "8754",
        "question": "A ________ is a push or pull.",
        "answer": "force",
        "distractor_1": "time",
        "distractor_2": "speed",
        "distractor_3": "mass"
      },
      {
        "id": "8755",
        "question": "If the forces acting on an object are unbalanced, what happens?",
        "answer": "the object accelerates.",
        "distractor_1": "the object moves in constant motion.",
        "distractor_2": "the object will not move.",
        "distractor_3": "the object remains at rest."
      },
      {
        "id": "8756",
        "question": "Which of the following is the load on a bridge caused by a truck moving across the bridge?",
        "answer": "live load",
        "distractor_1": "dead load",
        "distractor_2": "settlement load",
        "distractor_3": "thermal load"
      },
      {
        "id": "8757",
        "question": "Which of the following is the load on a bridge caused by the weight of the bridge materials?",
        "answer": "dead load",
        "distractor_1": "thermal load",
        "distractor_2": "live load",
        "distractor_3": "settlement load"
      },
      {
        "id": "8758",
        "question": "Which bridge type consists of a platform supported by columns underneath at specific intervals?",
        "answer": "beam",
        "distractor_1": "arch",
        "distractor_2": "suspension",
        "distractor_3": "load"
      },
      {
        "id": "8759",
        "question": "Which bridge type consists of a platform supported by cables from above?",
        "answer": "suspension",
        "distractor_1": "beam",
        "distractor_2": "load",
        "distractor_3": "arch"
      },
      {
        "id": "8760",
        "question": "Which engineering step would most likely include the building of a three-dimensional prototype?",
        "answer": "Create",
        "distractor_1": "Plan",
        "distractor_2": "Ask",
        "distractor_3": "Imagine"
      },
      {
        "id": "8761",
        "question": "After testing a prototype in relation to its requirements, which of the following engineering steps would you do next if you wanted to build a new prototype?",
        "answer": "Create",
        "distractor_1": "Improve",
        "distractor_2": "Imagine",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "8762",
        "question": "Which engineering step would most likely involve each person in a group presenting his or her ideas?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Improve",
        "distractor_3": "Plan"
      },
      {
        "id": "8763",
        "question": "Testing, evaluating, and modifying a solution or product most likely occurs at which stage of the engineering design process?",
        "answer": "Improve",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Imagine"
      },
      {
        "id": "8764",
        "question": "Which of the following are used to transform ideas into practical solutions?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "evaluating",
        "distractor_2": "testing",
        "distractor_3": "modeling"
      },
      {
        "id": "8765",
        "question": "Which of the following activities would most likely not be used in the Improve engineering step?",
        "answer": "creating",
        "distractor_1": "evaluating",
        "distractor_2": "testing",
        "distractor_3": "modeling"
      },
      {
        "id": "8766",
        "question": "What is ideation?",
        "answer": "the process of coming up with new ideas and ways to solve problems",
        "distractor_1": "the process of breaking a system down into subsystems",
        "distractor_2": "the process of gathering feedback to improve a system",
        "distractor_3": "the process of patenting a product"
      },
      {
        "id": "8767",
        "question": "Ideation can occur in any step of the engineering design loop, but it most often occurs at what step?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Improve",
        "distractor_2": "Ask",
        "distractor_3": "Plan"
      },
      {
        "id": "8768",
        "question": "What is a Newton?",
        "answer": "a unit of measure for force",
        "distractor_1": "a unit of measure for mass",
        "distractor_2": "a unit of measure for distance",
        "distractor_3": "a unit of measure for volume"
      },
      {
        "id": "8769",
        "question": "If the forces acting on an object are unbalanced, what happens?",
        "answer": "the object accelerates.",
        "distractor_1": "the object moves in constant motion.",
        "distractor_2": "the object will not move.",
        "distractor_3": "the object remains at rest."
      },
      {
        "id": "8770",
        "question": "After testing a prototype in relation to its requirements, which of the following engineering steps would you do next if you wanted to refine it?",
        "answer": "Improve",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Imagine",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2024",
    "name": "Electric Tech",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8771",
        "question": "Solve for x. x/5 = 15.5",
        "answer": "77.5",
        "distractor_1": "3.1",
        "distractor_2": "20.5",
        "distractor_3": "10.5"
      },
      {
        "id": "8772",
        "question": "Solve for b. 3b=12",
        "answer": "4",
        "distractor_1": "36",
        "distractor_2": "9",
        "distractor_3": "15"
      },
      {
        "id": "8773",
        "question": "Which subatomic particles are located outside the nucleus of an atom?",
        "answer": "electrons",
        "distractor_1": "ions",
        "distractor_2": "neutrons",
        "distractor_3": "protons"
      },
      {
        "id": "8774",
        "question": "What does an atom become when it loses an electron?",
        "answer": "a positively charged ion",
        "distractor_1": "a negatively charged ion",
        "distractor_2": "a positively charged proton",
        "distractor_3": "a negatively charged electron"
      },
      {
        "id": "8775",
        "question": "According to Ohm's law, doing which of the following will cause the current through an electrical circuit to increase?",
        "answer": "decreasing the resistance",
        "distractor_1": "decreasing the voltage",
        "distractor_2": "decreasing the power",
        "distractor_3": "increasing the resistance"
      },
      {
        "id": "8776",
        "question": "Which equation correctly states the relationship between current (I), voltage (V), and resistance (R) for a circuit?",
        "answer": "I = V / R",
        "distractor_1": "R = V • I",
        "distractor_2": "V = I / R",
        "distractor_3": "I = R / V"
      },
      {
        "id": "8777",
        "question": "Use Watt's law (P = I • R²) to calculate the electrical power (P) of a circuit that has a resistance (R) of 6 ohms and a current (I) of 0.25 amps.",
        "answer": "9 watts",
        "distractor_1": "1.5 watts",
        "distractor_2": "0.375 watts",
        "distractor_3": "36 watts"
      },
      {
        "id": "8778",
        "question": "Solve for x. 3x + 5 + 6x - 7 = 25",
        "answer": "x = 3",
        "distractor_1": "x = 25",
        "distractor_2": "x = 13",
        "distractor_3": "x = 30"
      },
      {
        "id": "8779",
        "question": "What are the smallest particles of any substance?",
        "answer": "atoms",
        "distractor_1": "compounds",
        "distractor_2": "elements",
        "distractor_3": "matter"
      },
      {
        "id": "8780",
        "question": "Which of the following engineering design steps can be repeated as needed?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "Improve",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "8781",
        "question": "Which engineering step is most likely to use a brainstorming process?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Taste",
        "distractor_3": "Touch"
      },
      {
        "id": "8782",
        "question": "Testing, evaluating, and modifying a solution or product most likely occurs at which stage of the engineering design process?",
        "answer": "Improve",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Imagine"
      },
      {
        "id": "8783",
        "question": "Which engineering step is most likely to use an ideation process?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Smell",
        "distractor_3": "Test"
      },
      {
        "id": "8784",
        "question": "Which of these steps is not a part of the engineering design loop?",
        "answer": "Communicate",
        "distractor_1": "Improve",
        "distractor_2": "Ask",
        "distractor_3": "Create"
      },
      {
        "id": "8785",
        "question": "Which of the following activities would most likely not be used in the Improve engineering step?",
        "answer": "creating",
        "distractor_1": "evaluating",
        "distractor_2": "testing",
        "distractor_3": "modeling"
      },
      {
        "id": "8786",
        "question": "Which of the following best describes an electron?",
        "answer": "It has a negative charge and much less mass than a proton.",
        "distractor_1": "It has no charge and about the same mass as a proton.",
        "distractor_2": "It has a positive charge and much more mass than a neutron.",
        "distractor_3": "It has a negative charge and about the same mass as a neutron."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2025",
    "name": "Flight Dynamics",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8787",
        "question": "Which of the following forces enables a plane to stay in the air?",
        "answer": "lift",
        "distractor_1": "weight",
        "distractor_2": "thrust",
        "distractor_3": "drag"
      },
      {
        "id": "8788",
        "question": "Which of the following forces must be overcome for lift to occur?",
        "answer": "weight",
        "distractor_1": "thrust",
        "distractor_2": "drag",
        "distractor_3": "lift"
      },
      {
        "id": "8789",
        "question": "Which of the following forces is created when a plane moves through the air?",
        "answer": "drag",
        "distractor_1": "lift",
        "distractor_2": "weight",
        "distractor_3": "thrust"
      },
      {
        "id": "8790",
        "question": "According to Newton's first law of motion, a mass in motion remains in motion unless acted upon by some force.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8791",
        "question": "Colby wants to learn more about the feeding habits of ants. What steps should Colby take in order to best study the patterns of ants?",
        "answer": "form a hypothesis, conduct an experiment, record data, make a conclusion",
        "distractor_1": "conduct an experiment, form an hypothesis, make a conclusion, record data",
        "distractor_2": "form a hypothesis, record data, conduct an experiment, make a conclusion",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8792",
        "question": "What factor is not changed in an experiment?",
        "answer": "constant",
        "distractor_1": "dependent variable",
        "distractor_2": "temperature",
        "distractor_3": "independent variable"
      },
      {
        "id": "8793",
        "question": "What factors can be changed in an experiment?",
        "answer": "variables",
        "distractor_1": "standards",
        "distractor_2": "constants",
        "distractor_3": "controls"
      },
      {
        "id": "8794",
        "question": "How many independent variables can be tested at one time during an experiment?",
        "answer": "1",
        "distractor_1": "2",
        "distractor_2": "As many as you would like",
        "distractor_3": "The same amount as the number of controlled variables"
      },
      {
        "id": "8795",
        "question": "A ________ observation deals with numbers of amounts.",
        "answer": "quantitative",
        "distractor_1": "qualitative",
        "distractor_2": "process",
        "distractor_3": "mechanical"
      },
      {
        "id": "8796",
        "question": "What does an object need to change its motion?",
        "answer": "force",
        "distractor_1": "length",
        "distractor_2": "mass",
        "distractor_3": "size"
      },
      {
        "id": "8797",
        "question": "A ________ is a push or pull.",
        "answer": "force",
        "distractor_1": "time",
        "distractor_2": "speed",
        "distractor_3": "mass"
      },
      {
        "id": "8798",
        "question": "Motion is a change in ________.",
        "answer": "position over time",
        "distractor_1": "speed over time",
        "distractor_2": "velocity over time",
        "distractor_3": "acceleration over time"
      },
      {
        "id": "8799",
        "question": "'The motor must run at 1,000 rpm' is a statement that describes which of the following?",
        "answer": "specification",
        "distractor_1": "constraint",
        "distractor_2": "both",
        "distractor_3": "neither"
      },
      {
        "id": "8800",
        "question": "Brainstorming usually happens in which engineering step?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Plan",
        "distractor_2": "Ask",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "8801",
        "question": "Which of the following forces is exerted on a plane to make it move in a specific direction?",
        "answer": "thrust",
        "distractor_1": "drag",
        "distractor_2": "weight",
        "distractor_3": "lift"
      },
      {
        "id": "8802",
        "question": "Which of the following motions is controlled by an airplane's rudder?",
        "answer": "yaw",
        "distractor_1": "pitch",
        "distractor_2": "roll",
        "distractor_3": "stability"
      },
      {
        "id": "8803",
        "question": "Which of the following motions is controlled by an airplane's aileron?",
        "answer": "roll",
        "distractor_1": "stability",
        "distractor_2": "pitch",
        "distractor_3": "yaw"
      },
      {
        "id": "8804",
        "question": "Which of the following motions is controlled by an airplane's elevator?",
        "answer": "pitch",
        "distractor_1": "yaw",
        "distractor_2": "stability",
        "distractor_3": "roll"
      },
      {
        "id": "8805",
        "question": "A force can act only by touching.",
        "answer": "False",
        "distractor_1": "True",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8806",
        "question": "An object in motion remains in motion unless acted on by an unbalanced force.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8807",
        "question": "A ________ observation deals with descriptions that cannot be expressed in numbers.",
        "answer": "qualitative",
        "distractor_1": "quantitative",
        "distractor_2": "investigation",
        "distractor_3": "science"
      },
      {
        "id": "8808",
        "question": "What should you do when your data does not support your hypothesis?",
        "answer": "Modify the experiment",
        "distractor_1": "Analyze data",
        "distractor_2": "identify the experiment",
        "distractor_3": "communicate your results"
      },
      {
        "id": "8809",
        "question": "Modifying a vehicle's engine to get better gas mileage would most likely occur at which step of the engineering design process?",
        "answer": "Improve",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Imagine"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2026",
    "name": "Thermal Physics",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8810",
        "question": "Measuring temperature means that you are measuring the average speed of moving particles.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8811",
        "question": "Only very hot materials, like the lava from a volcano, are capable of transferring thermal energy through the process of radiation.",
        "answer": "False",
        "distractor_1": "True",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8812",
        "question": "A snowman has more thermal energy than a burning match.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8813",
        "question": "Gas particles move slower than liquid particles.",
        "answer": "False",
        "distractor_1": "True",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8814",
        "question": "It is a transfer of energy from one object to another due to a difference in temperature. What is it called?",
        "answer": "heat",
        "distractor_1": "compound",
        "distractor_2": "mass",
        "distractor_3": "mixture"
      },
      {
        "id": "8815",
        "question": "What is the transfer of thermal energy from one material to another by electromagnetic waves?",
        "answer": "Radiation",
        "distractor_1": "Heat",
        "distractor_2": "Temperature",
        "distractor_3": "Convection Current"
      },
      {
        "id": "8816",
        "question": "Which of the listed engineering steps would you use to brainstorm ways to use parallel circuits in a building?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Ask",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "8817",
        "question": "Brainstorming usually happens in which engineering step?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Plan",
        "distractor_2": "Create",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "8818",
        "question": "Which engineering step would most likely involve each person in a group presenting his or her ideas?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Improve",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Create"
      },
      {
        "id": "8819",
        "question": "Which of the following are used to transform ideas into practical solutions?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "evaluating",
        "distractor_2": "testing",
        "distractor_3": "modeling"
      },
      {
        "id": "8820",
        "question": "Which of the following activities would most likely not be used in the Improve engineering step?",
        "answer": "creating",
        "distractor_1": "evaluating",
        "distractor_2": "testing",
        "distractor_3": "modeling"
      },
      {
        "id": "8821",
        "question": "What is defined as 'the ability to do work'?",
        "answer": "energy",
        "distractor_1": "potential",
        "distractor_2": "voltage",
        "distractor_3": "temperature"
      },
      {
        "id": "8822",
        "question": "The average kinetic energy of the particles that make something up is called what?",
        "answer": "temperature",
        "distractor_1": "voltage",
        "distractor_2": "heat",
        "distractor_3": "resistance"
      },
      {
        "id": "8823",
        "question": "The energy something has because of the motion of its particles is called what?",
        "answer": "heat",
        "distractor_1": "resistance",
        "distractor_2": "voltage",
        "distractor_3": "temperature"
      },
      {
        "id": "8824",
        "question": "The process of measuring the temperature change in a sample of water to determine the total amount of energy lost or gained is called what?",
        "answer": "calorimetry",
        "distractor_1": "telemetry",
        "distractor_2": "microscopy",
        "distractor_3": "spectroscopy"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2027",
    "name": "Rolling Robots",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8825",
        "question": "What effects will be seen if a small gear is attached to a servo and large gear is attached to a wheel?",
        "answer": "Speed will decrease while pulling power will increase.",
        "distractor_1": "Speed will increase while pulling power will increase.",
        "distractor_2": "Speed will increase while pulling power will decrease.",
        "distractor_3": "Speed will decrease while pulling power will decrease."
      },
      {
        "id": "8826",
        "question": "Modifying a vehicle's engine to get better gas mileage would most likely occur at which step of the engineering design process?",
        "answer": "Improve",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Imagine"
      },
      {
        "id": "8827",
        "question": "Which engineering step would most likely include the building of a three-dimensional prototype?",
        "answer": "Create",
        "distractor_1": "Plan",
        "distractor_2": "Imagine",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "8828",
        "question": "After testing a prototype in relation to its requirements, which of the following engineering steps would you do next if you wanted to brainstorm ways to make it better?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Ask",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "8829",
        "question": "After testing a prototype in relation to its requirements, which of the following engineering steps would you do next if you wanted to build a new prototype?",
        "answer": "Create",
        "distractor_1": "Improve",
        "distractor_2": "Imagine",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "8830",
        "question": "Consider two production lines. Line A has 3 workers operating 15 machines. Line B has 4 workers operating 20 machines. Each line produces 100 parts per hour. What would occur if one worker on Line B did not show up for work?",
        "answer": "Line B would produce fewer parts per hour.",
        "distractor_1": "Line B would produce more parts per hour.",
        "distractor_2": "Line A would produce more parts per hour.",
        "distractor_3": "Line A would produce fewer parts per hour."
      },
      {
        "id": "8831",
        "question": "Two supply lines deliver equal amounts of Chemical A and Chemical B to a mixing container to make a compound. If a valve that controls the supply of Chemical A sticks shut, what is the result?",
        "answer": "Less Chemical A is released than is required.",
        "distractor_1": "More Chemical A is released than is required.",
        "distractor_2": "More Chemical B is released than is required.",
        "distractor_3": "Less Chemical B is released than is required."
      },
      {
        "id": "8832",
        "question": "Consider two production lines. Line A has 5 workers operating 15 machines. Line B has 4 workers operating 16 machines. Each line produces 1,250 parts per hour. What would the occur if one worker on Line A did not show up for work?",
        "answer": "Line A would produce fewer parts per hour.",
        "distractor_1": "Line A would produce more parts per hour.",
        "distractor_2": "Line B would produce fewer parts per hour.",
        "distractor_3": "Line B would produce more parts per hour."
      },
      {
        "id": "8833",
        "question": "BPF Manufacturing ships products nationwide. The products can be made from aluminum or steel and have the strength they need. Shipping weight is a concern. The aluminum is lighter in weight, but the steel is less expensive to manufacture. How should the c",
        "answer": "compare the increased cost of the part with the savings on shipping",
        "distractor_1": "look only at the cost of the material",
        "distractor_2": "look only at the cost of shipping",
        "distractor_3": "look at the strength of each material"
      },
      {
        "id": "8834",
        "question": "What is the decision process called when a company must consider competing factors to make a decision?",
        "answer": "trade-off",
        "distractor_1": "conferencing",
        "distractor_2": "competition",
        "distractor_3": "cost comparison"
      },
      {
        "id": "8835",
        "question": "In any design there is an opportunity to make it better.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8836",
        "question": "Testing, evaluating, and modifying a solution or product most likely occurs at which stage of the engineering design process?",
        "answer": "Improve",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Imagine"
      },
      {
        "id": "8837",
        "question": "When using systems thinking one must think of how every part of the system relates to the other parts of the system.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8840",
        "question": "A servo motor has a gear attached to it that has twice the number of teeth of the gear attached to a wheel. If the servo turns 50 turns per minute, how fast will the wheel turn?",
        "answer": "100 turns per minute",
        "distractor_1": "75 turns per minute",
        "distractor_2": "25 turns per minute",
        "distractor_3": "50 turns per minute"
      },
      {
        "id": "8841",
        "question": "A wheel requires 3 full rotations to travel 1 meter. How many wheel rotations are required to travel 1 meter if a 2:1 drive gear ratio is added?",
        "answer": "3 rotations",
        "distractor_1": "1 rotation",
        "distractor_2": "9 rotations",
        "distractor_3": "6 rotations"
      },
      {
        "id": "8842",
        "question": "Select the situation in which a robot would not be the best choice to use.",
        "answer": "to complete a task in which fruit is graded for quality",
        "distractor_1": "to complete a task that creates toxic fumes",
        "distractor_2": "to complete a task that is repetitious",
        "distractor_3": "to complete a task that includes heavy lifting"
      },
      {
        "id": "8843",
        "question": "When following the engineering design loop, which step usually comes after asking questions?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Communicate",
        "distractor_2": "Create",
        "distractor_3": "Plan"
      },
      {
        "id": "8844",
        "question": "In engineering, this happens when one attribute or quality is sacrificed for the sake of another.",
        "answer": "trade-off",
        "distractor_1": "ideation",
        "distractor_2": "substitution",
        "distractor_3": "subsystem"
      },
      {
        "id": "8845",
        "question": "Which is an example of an engineering trade-off?",
        "answer": "sacrificing strength to make a product weigh less",
        "distractor_1": "making a product safer",
        "distractor_2": "reducing the cost of a product",
        "distractor_3": "building a prototype of a product"
      },
      {
        "id": "8846",
        "question": "When using systems thinking one must think of each part of the system as isolated from the other parts of the system.",
        "answer": "False",
        "distractor_1": "True",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2028",
    "name": "Contraptions",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8847",
        "question": "As the height of an inclined plane is decreased, what would you expect to happen to the effort force required to move the load up the inclined plane?",
        "answer": "The effort force will decrease.",
        "distractor_1": "The effort force will equal the mechanical advantage.",
        "distractor_2": "The effort force will stay the same.",
        "distractor_3": "The effort force will increase."
      },
      {
        "id": "8848",
        "question": "A first-class lever has a resistance arm of 3 inches and an effort arm of 12 inches. What is the mechanical advantage of the lever?",
        "answer": "4",
        "distractor_1": "0.24",
        "distractor_2": "9",
        "distractor_3": "15"
      },
      {
        "id": "8849",
        "question": "For a lever, which of the following statements is true?",
        "answer": "The load can be moved with less effort if the length of the resistance arm decreases.",
        "distractor_1": "The load requires more effort to move if the length of the effort arm increases.",
        "distractor_2": "The mechanical advantage of the lever decreases if the length of the effort arm increases.",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8850",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a simple machine?",
        "answer": "hammer",
        "distractor_1": "screw",
        "distractor_2": "wheel and axle",
        "distractor_3": "pulley"
      },
      {
        "id": "8851",
        "question": "What is the relationship between the work (W) done to move an object, the force (F) acting on the object, and the distance (D) the object is moved?",
        "answer": "W = F • D",
        "distractor_1": "W = F / D",
        "distractor_2": "D = F / W²",
        "distractor_3": "F = W / D²"
      },
      {
        "id": "8852",
        "question": "Which of the following engineering design steps can be repeated as needed?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "8853",
        "question": "Which engineering step would most likely involve each person in a group presenting his or her ideas?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Plan",
        "distractor_2": "Ask",
        "distractor_3": "Create"
      },
      {
        "id": "8854",
        "question": "'The motor must run at 1,000 rpm' is a statement that describes which of the following?",
        "answer": "specification",
        "distractor_1": "constraint",
        "distractor_2": "both",
        "distractor_3": "neither"
      },
      {
        "id": "8855",
        "question": "Which engineering step would most likely include the building of a three-dimensional prototype?",
        "answer": "Create",
        "distractor_1": "Plan",
        "distractor_2": "Imagine",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "8856",
        "question": "Which of the following is one of the six classical simple machines?",
        "answer": "screw",
        "distractor_1": "nail",
        "distractor_2": "hammer",
        "distractor_3": "saw"
      },
      {
        "id": "8857",
        "question": "After testing a prototype in relation to its requirements, which of the following engineering steps would you do next if you wanted to refine it?",
        "answer": "Improve",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Imagine",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "8858",
        "question": "Which of these steps is not a part of the engineering design loop?",
        "answer": "Communicate",
        "distractor_1": "Improve",
        "distractor_2": "Create",
        "distractor_3": "Plan"
      },
      {
        "id": "8859",
        "question": "When following the engineering design loop, which step usually comes after asking questions?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Plan",
        "distractor_2": "Improve",
        "distractor_3": "Create"
      },
      {
        "id": "8860",
        "question": "There is no perfect design for a process or product.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8861",
        "question": "A second-class lever has a resistance arm of 5 inches and an effort arm of 15 inches. What is the mechanical advantage of the lever?",
        "answer": "3",
        "distractor_1": ".33",
        "distractor_2": "10",
        "distractor_3": "5"
      },
      {
        "id": "8862",
        "question": "Which engineering step is most likely to use a brainstorming process?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Taste",
        "distractor_2": "Ask",
        "distractor_3": "Touch"
      },
      {
        "id": "8863",
        "question": "In any design there is an opportunity to make it better.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8864",
        "question": "Modifying a vehicle's engine to get better gas mileage would most likely occur at which step of the engineering design process?",
        "answer": "Improve",
        "distractor_1": "Imagine",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "8865",
        "question": "'The motor cannot exceed 1,000 rpm' is a statement that describes which of the following?",
        "answer": "constraint",
        "distractor_1": "specification",
        "distractor_2": "both",
        "distractor_3": "neither"
      },
      {
        "id": "8866",
        "question": "After testing a prototype in relation to its requirements, which of the following engineering steps would you do next if you wanted to brainstorm ways to make it better?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Create",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2029",
    "name": "Transportation Stations",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8867",
        "question": "Alyssa has 4 pairs of low-top sneakers, 7 pairs of high-top sneakers, 3 pairs of sandals, and 1 pair of boots. What is the ratio of the pairs of low-top sneakers to the total number of pairs of shoes?",
        "answer": "4 to 15",
        "distractor_1": "7 to 15",
        "distractor_2": "4 to 3",
        "distractor_3": "1 to 3"
      },
      {
        "id": "8868",
        "question": "A class of 32 students has 12 girls. What is the ratio of girls to boys?",
        "answer": "3 to 5",
        "distractor_1": "5 to 3",
        "distractor_2": "8 to 3",
        "distractor_3": "3 to 8"
      },
      {
        "id": "8869",
        "question": "How many independent variables can be tested at one time during an experiment?",
        "answer": "1",
        "distractor_1": "2",
        "distractor_2": "The same amount as the number of controlled variables",
        "distractor_3": "As many as you would like"
      },
      {
        "id": "8870",
        "question": "The primary function of a sports car is to transport which of the following?",
        "answer": "people",
        "distractor_1": "goods",
        "distractor_2": "both",
        "distractor_3": "neither"
      },
      {
        "id": "8871",
        "question": "The primary function of a cargo ship is to transport which of the following?",
        "answer": "goods",
        "distractor_1": "people",
        "distractor_2": "both",
        "distractor_3": "neither"
      },
      {
        "id": "8872",
        "question": "The primary function of a commercial airline is to transport which of the following?",
        "answer": "both",
        "distractor_1": "people",
        "distractor_2": "goods",
        "distractor_3": "neither"
      },
      {
        "id": "8873",
        "question": "To which of the following subsystems would a car's engine belong?",
        "answer": "propulsion",
        "distractor_1": "suspension",
        "distractor_2": "guidance",
        "distractor_3": "control"
      },
      {
        "id": "8874",
        "question": "To which of the following subsystems would a car's steering wheel belong?",
        "answer": "control",
        "distractor_1": "guidance",
        "distractor_2": "suspension",
        "distractor_3": "propulsion"
      },
      {
        "id": "8875",
        "question": "To which of the following subsystems would a car's chassis belong?",
        "answer": "support",
        "distractor_1": "control",
        "distractor_2": "guidance",
        "distractor_3": "suspension"
      },
      {
        "id": "8876",
        "question": "If a tanker truck were hauling gasoline, which of the following would the government require to be placed on the vehicle?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "license plate",
        "distractor_2": "hazmat placard",
        "distractor_3": "reflectors"
      },
      {
        "id": "8877",
        "question": "Which of the following traffic signs would require a transportation vehicle to have brakes installed?",
        "answer": "stop sign",
        "distractor_1": "speed limit sign",
        "distractor_2": "mileage sign",
        "distractor_3": "all of the above"
      },
      {
        "id": "8878",
        "question": "Which of the following processes would you expect to happen at a shipping port?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "moving",
        "distractor_2": "storing",
        "distractor_3": "unloading"
      },
      {
        "id": "8879",
        "question": "Which of the following processes would you expect to happen at a transportation hub?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "moving",
        "distractor_2": "unloading",
        "distractor_3": "loading"
      },
      {
        "id": "8880",
        "question": "According to historical documentation, which of the following transportation technologies have been used the longest?",
        "answer": "skis",
        "distractor_1": "railroads",
        "distractor_2": "airplanes",
        "distractor_3": "hot-air balloons"
      },
      {
        "id": "8881",
        "question": "At the same rpm, which of the following gear ratios for a bicycle would make the wheel turn slowest?",
        "answer": "10 to 1",
        "distractor_1": "5 to 1",
        "distractor_2": "2 to 7",
        "distractor_3": "1 to 11"
      },
      {
        "id": "8882",
        "question": "A youth soccer league has 60 players for 5 teams. The league then adds 1 more soccer team and divides the players equally among the teams. Which statement is true?",
        "answer": "For every 1 team, there are 10 players.",
        "distractor_1": "For every 1 team, there are 11 players.",
        "distractor_2": "For every 1 team, there are 12 players.",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8883",
        "question": "A ________ observation deals with descriptions that cannot be expressed in numbers.",
        "answer": "qualitative",
        "distractor_1": "quantitative",
        "distractor_2": "investigation",
        "distractor_3": "science"
      },
      {
        "id": "8884",
        "question": "At the same rpm, which of the following gear ratios for a bicycle would make the wheel turn fastest?",
        "answer": "1 to 11",
        "distractor_1": "2 to 7",
        "distractor_2": "5 to 1",
        "distractor_3": "10 to 1"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2030",
    "name": "Bio Research",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8885",
        "question": "If one parent is homozygous dominant and the other is homozygous recessive for the same trait, what is the probable genotype for all the offspring?",
        "answer": "heterozygous dominant",
        "distractor_1": "homozygous dominant",
        "distractor_2": "heterozygous recessive",
        "distractor_3": "homozygous recessive."
      },
      {
        "id": "8886",
        "question": "A pea plant with two tall genes is said to be:",
        "answer": "homozygous tall",
        "distractor_1": "heterozygous tall",
        "distractor_2": "homozygous short",
        "distractor_3": "heterozygous short"
      },
      {
        "id": "8887",
        "question": "The twisted shape of DNA is called a ________.",
        "answer": "double helix",
        "distractor_1": "double ladder",
        "distractor_2": "nucleotide",
        "distractor_3": "base pair"
      },
      {
        "id": "8888",
        "question": "How are specialized breeds of dogs, cats, horses, and other animals produced?",
        "answer": "selective breeding",
        "distractor_1": "budding",
        "distractor_2": "regeneration",
        "distractor_3": "asexual reproduction"
      },
      {
        "id": "8889",
        "question": "A homozygous recessive genotype is shown by which of the following?",
        "answer": "tt",
        "distractor_1": "TT",
        "distractor_2": "Tt",
        "distractor_3": "TS"
      },
      {
        "id": "8890",
        "question": "In guinea pigs, short fur (S) is dominant, and long fur (s) is recessive. A female guinea pig with short fur is mated with a male long fur. Half of the guinea pigs in the litter have short fur, and the other half have long fur. What are the genotypes of t",
        "answer": "Ss and ss",
        "distractor_1": "ss and ss",
        "distractor_2": "Ss and Ss",
        "distractor_3": "SS and ss"
      },
      {
        "id": "8891",
        "question": "In Mendel's garden peas, round peas (R) are dominant to wrinkled peas (r). If two heterozygous round pea plants are crossed, what are the possible genotypes of the offspring?",
        "answer": "RR, Rr and rr",
        "distractor_1": "Rr and rr only",
        "distractor_2": "RR and rr only",
        "distractor_3": "Rr only"
      },
      {
        "id": "8892",
        "question": "When is a recessive allele for a trait expressed in the phenotype of an individual?",
        "answer": "when it is paired with another recessive allele",
        "distractor_1": "when it is paired with a dominant allele",
        "distractor_2": "when it occurs in a heterozygous individual",
        "distractor_3": "when it occurs in a homozygous dominant individual"
      },
      {
        "id": "8893",
        "question": "Which of the following genotypes would be present if a recessive trait is expressed in the phenotype?",
        "answer": "bb",
        "distractor_1": "BB",
        "distractor_2": "Bb",
        "distractor_3": "bB"
      },
      {
        "id": "8894",
        "question": "Which of these choices describes a segment of DNA that determines a specific trait in a person, such as attached earlobes?",
        "answer": "a gene",
        "distractor_1": "a phenotype",
        "distractor_2": "a chromosome",
        "distractor_3": "a characteristic"
      },
      {
        "id": "8895",
        "question": "Which of these choices describes the purpose of a Punnett square?",
        "answer": "to illustrate how the alleles of parents might be passed on to their offspring",
        "distractor_1": "to compare inherited traits to acquired traits",
        "distractor_2": "to explain why some genes are recessive and others are dominant",
        "distractor_3": "to diagram family relationships that include several generations"
      },
      {
        "id": "8896",
        "question": "When you evaluate an Internet resource for validity, which of the following criteria should be used to help you in your evaluation?",
        "answer": "the domain of the site",
        "distractor_1": "whether or not you agree with the site",
        "distractor_2": "the amount of money spent on the site",
        "distractor_3": "the color scheme"
      },
      {
        "id": "8897",
        "question": "What base pairs with adenine in a strand of DNA?",
        "answer": "thymine",
        "distractor_1": "adenine",
        "distractor_2": "cytosine",
        "distractor_3": "guanine"
      },
      {
        "id": "8898",
        "question": "What is used to splice genes in order to make recombinant DNA?",
        "answer": "restriction enzyme",
        "distractor_1": "recombinant marker",
        "distractor_2": "laser scissors",
        "distractor_3": "acid"
      },
      {
        "id": "8899",
        "question": "What term is used to describe an organism that is created when a gene from a different organism is inserted into its genome?",
        "answer": "transgenic organism",
        "distractor_1": "mutant",
        "distractor_2": "clone",
        "distractor_3": "anomaly"
      },
      {
        "id": "8900",
        "question": "Transgenic corn that incorporates genes to shorten growing time would increase total food production for which of the following reasons?",
        "answer": "allows more crops to be planted on the same ground over time",
        "distractor_1": "reduces use of pesticides",
        "distractor_2": "increases yield per harvest",
        "distractor_3": "increases total nutritional value of the harvest"
      },
      {
        "id": "8901",
        "question": "The application of biology to create commercial products or processes is called what?",
        "answer": "biotechnology",
        "distractor_1": "bioengineering",
        "distractor_2": "market biology",
        "distractor_3": "microbiology"
      },
      {
        "id": "8902",
        "question": "Use of transgenic organisms such as E. coli to produce commercial pharmaceuticals is one of the applications of which of the following?",
        "answer": "biotechnology",
        "distractor_1": "microscopy",
        "distractor_2": "bioengineering",
        "distractor_3": "organic production"
      },
      {
        "id": "8903",
        "question": "Biotechnology applies the principles of biology to create which of the following?",
        "answer": "commercial products",
        "distractor_1": "lifelike robots",
        "distractor_2": "organic computers",
        "distractor_3": "robotic prosthetics"
      },
      {
        "id": "8904",
        "question": "Which of the following is the best example of biotechnology being used on a farm?",
        "answer": "modifying a plant's DNA to produce larger and sweeter fruits",
        "distractor_1": "using self-driving combines to harvest a corn field",
        "distractor_2": "using a wind generator to power cow milking machines on a dairy farm",
        "distractor_3": "using a greenhouse to keep tomato plants from freezing in late fall"
      },
      {
        "id": "8905",
        "question": "Each rung of the DNA ladder is made of ________.",
        "answer": "a pair of nitrogen bases",
        "distractor_1": "a single nitrogen base",
        "distractor_2": "three nitrogen bases",
        "distractor_3": "four nitrogen bases"
      },
      {
        "id": "8906",
        "question": "Which of the following technologies has contributed to increasing food production for the world's ever-increasing population?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "chemical pesticides",
        "distractor_2": "GPS-guided tractors and combines",
        "distractor_3": "biotechnology"
      },
      {
        "id": "8907",
        "question": "Transgenic wheat that incorporates genes to increase the size of the seeds would increase total food production for which of the following reasons?",
        "answer": "increases yield per harvest",
        "distractor_1": "increases total nutritional value of the harvest",
        "distractor_2": "reduces use of pesticides",
        "distractor_3": "allows more crops to be planted on the same ground over time"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2031",
    "name": "Dragster Design",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8908",
        "question": "Which of the following is the best technology for an inventor to use as documentation for an invention?",
        "answer": "logbook",
        "distractor_1": "phone call",
        "distractor_2": "text message",
        "distractor_3": "sticky notes"
      },
      {
        "id": "8909",
        "question": "Which of the following is the best product for an inventor to provide as documentation for an invention?",
        "answer": "prototype",
        "distractor_1": "sketch",
        "distractor_2": "photograph",
        "distractor_3": "diary"
      },
      {
        "id": "8910",
        "question": "Of the following, which is most likely a criteria and not a constraint?",
        "answer": "vehicle must roll on wheels",
        "distractor_1": "no more than two axles",
        "distractor_2": "cannot exceed 10 m/s",
        "distractor_3": "maximum height of 3 in."
      },
      {
        "id": "8911",
        "question": "Of the following, which is most likely a constraint and not a criteria?",
        "answer": "maximum height of 3 in.",
        "distractor_1": "must be painted",
        "distractor_2": "must be able to be operated by remote control",
        "distractor_3": "vehicle must roll on wheels"
      },
      {
        "id": "8912",
        "question": "Which factor plays the most important role in the speed of a CO2 dragster?",
        "answer": "mass of the car",
        "distractor_1": "guide string used",
        "distractor_2": "type of paint",
        "distractor_3": "color"
      },
      {
        "id": "8913",
        "question": "A rough sketch contains detailed dimensions.",
        "answer": "False",
        "distractor_1": "True",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8914",
        "question": "What is the formula for acceleration?",
        "answer": "Acceleration = Force / Mass",
        "distractor_1": "Acceleration = Force • Mass",
        "distractor_2": "Acceleration = Distance / Time",
        "distractor_3": "Acceleration = Mass / Force"
      },
      {
        "id": "8915",
        "question": "What is the purpose of a thumbnail sketch?",
        "answer": "to quickly show ideas",
        "distractor_1": "to provide accurate measurements",
        "distractor_2": "to give accurate details of the dragster shape",
        "distractor_3": "to show refinements in the design"
      },
      {
        "id": "8916",
        "question": "What is a constraint?",
        "answer": "a restriction or boundary that helps limit what solutions are available",
        "distractor_1": "a solution to a problem",
        "distractor_2": "a group of parts that work together for a common purpose",
        "distractor_3": "the exclusive right to manufacture and sell an invention"
      },
      {
        "id": "8917",
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a factor in the speed of a CO2 dragster?",
        "answer": "color",
        "distractor_1": "mass",
        "distractor_2": "friction",
        "distractor_3": "aerodynamics"
      },
      {
        "id": "8918",
        "question": "Which law is demonstrated by the movement of a CO2 car?",
        "answer": "Newton's third law",
        "distractor_1": "Galileo's first law",
        "distractor_2": "law of conservation of energy",
        "distractor_3": "Pythagorean law"
      },
      {
        "id": "8919",
        "question": "Rolling friction is most closely related to which of Newton's laws?",
        "answer": "Newton's first law",
        "distractor_1": "Newton's third law",
        "distractor_2": "Newton's zero law",
        "distractor_3": "Newton's second law"
      },
      {
        "id": "8920",
        "question": "Which of the following is a manufactured abrasive material?",
        "answer": "aluminum oxide",
        "distractor_1": "flint",
        "distractor_2": "garnet",
        "distractor_3": "emery"
      },
      {
        "id": "8921",
        "question": "When you compare the numbers on the back of abrasive paper, what does a larger number tell you about the abrasive material?",
        "answer": "It is a finer grit.",
        "distractor_1": "It is more expensive.",
        "distractor_2": "It lasts longer.",
        "distractor_3": "It is a coarser grit."
      },
      {
        "id": "8922",
        "question": "A CO2 car is placed at the top of a ramp and released without a push. A car that rolls farther has which of the following?",
        "answer": "less rolling friction",
        "distractor_1": "better color",
        "distractor_2": "larger wheels",
        "distractor_3": "smaller wheels"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2032",
    "name": "Innovating Solutions",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8923",
        "question": "Developing new products and systems to solve problems and meet needs is the goal of what?",
        "answer": "technology",
        "distractor_1": "history",
        "distractor_2": "science",
        "distractor_3": "math"
      },
      {
        "id": "8924",
        "question": "Technological systems have all of the following except what?",
        "answer": "throughputs",
        "distractor_1": "processes",
        "distractor_2": "inputs",
        "distractor_3": "outputs"
      },
      {
        "id": "8925",
        "question": "What is the difference between an open-loop and a closed-loop system?",
        "answer": "An open-loop system does not have feedback and a closed-loop system does.",
        "distractor_1": "An open-loop system does not have processes and a closed-loop system does.",
        "distractor_2": "An open-loop system does not have inputs and a closed-loop system does.",
        "distractor_3": "An open-loop system does not have outputs and a closed-loop system does."
      },
      {
        "id": "8926",
        "question": "Which of the following is an example of a closed-loop system?",
        "answer": "a security light that turns on when it senses motion",
        "distractor_1": "an MP3 player that plays when the play button is pushed",
        "distractor_2": "a showerhead that sprays water when the shower knob is turned",
        "distractor_3": "a stove burner that heats up when turned on"
      },
      {
        "id": "8927",
        "question": "Which is the best example of technological systems interacting with each other?",
        "answer": "a toilet flushing sewage into the city sewer system",
        "distractor_1": "a flag waving in the wind",
        "distractor_2": "a severe weather system canceling a baseball game",
        "distractor_3": "a flashlight turning on"
      },
      {
        "id": "8928",
        "question": "What factor will most likely determine whether a new invention or innovation will be accepted by society?",
        "answer": "if it meets society's expectations",
        "distractor_1": "if it does not function correctly",
        "distractor_2": "if it is unsafe",
        "distractor_3": "if it is priced higher than it is worth"
      },
      {
        "id": "8929",
        "question": "What is a constraint?",
        "answer": "a restriction or boundary that helps limit what solutions are available",
        "distractor_1": "a solution to a problem",
        "distractor_2": "a group of parts that work together for a common purpose",
        "distractor_3": "the exclusive right to manufacture and sell an invention"
      },
      {
        "id": "8930",
        "question": "What is ideation?",
        "answer": "the process of coming up with new ideas and ways to solve problems",
        "distractor_1": "the process of breaking a system down into subsystems",
        "distractor_2": "the process of gathering feedback to improve a system",
        "distractor_3": "the process of patenting a product"
      },
      {
        "id": "8931",
        "question": "When following the engineering design loop, which step usually comes after asking questions?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "8932",
        "question": "Which of these discoveries would you be able to obtain a patent for?",
        "answer": "discovering how to build an artificial eye",
        "distractor_1": "discovering how the Egyptian pyramids were built",
        "distractor_2": "discovering a new comet",
        "distractor_3": "discovering a new species of insect"
      },
      {
        "id": "8933",
        "question": "Which is an example of an engineering trade-off?",
        "answer": "sacrificing strength to make a product weigh less",
        "distractor_1": "making a product safer",
        "distractor_2": "reducing the cost of a product",
        "distractor_3": "building a prototype of a product"
      },
      {
        "id": "8934",
        "question": "Which of the following statements regarding the relationship between science and technology is true?",
        "answer": "Scientists use technology to study the natural world.",
        "distractor_1": "Scientists use technology to build new inventions in order to make money.",
        "distractor_2": "Scientists use technology to meet human needs.",
        "distractor_3": "Scientists do not use technology."
      },
      {
        "id": "8935",
        "question": "What is the process of turning new ideas into new products and systems?",
        "answer": "invention",
        "distractor_1": "innovation",
        "distractor_2": "ideation",
        "distractor_3": "imagination"
      },
      {
        "id": "8936",
        "question": "What is the order of the Universal Systems Model?",
        "answer": "inputs -> processes -> outputs -> feedback",
        "distractor_1": "inputs -> outputs -> feedback -> processes",
        "distractor_2": "inputs -> feedback -> outputs -> processes",
        "distractor_3": "inputs -> processes -> feedback -> outputs"
      },
      {
        "id": "8937",
        "question": "Which field of study has no effect on the development of technological products?",
        "answer": "none of the above",
        "distractor_1": "mathematics",
        "distractor_2": "history",
        "distractor_3": "science"
      },
      {
        "id": "8938",
        "question": "When using systems thinking one must think of how every part of the system relates to the other parts of the system.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8939",
        "question": "The goal of technology is to develop new products and systems that do what?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "satisfy wants",
        "distractor_2": "meet needs",
        "distractor_3": "solve problems"
      },
      {
        "id": "8940",
        "question": "All of these have inputs, processes, outputs, and, sometimes, feedback.",
        "answer": "systems",
        "distractor_1": "ideas",
        "distractor_2": "plans",
        "distractor_3": "prototypes"
      },
      {
        "id": "8941",
        "question": "Is the following statement true or false? Technological systems do not interact with each other.",
        "answer": "False",
        "distractor_1": "True",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8942",
        "question": "Which is most likely to determine whether a new product will be used by society?",
        "answer": "if it meets society's expectations",
        "distractor_1": "if it does not function correctly",
        "distractor_2": "if it is priced higher than it is worth",
        "distractor_3": "if it is unsafe"
      },
      {
        "id": "8943",
        "question": "Which of these discoveries would you be able to obtain a patent for?",
        "answer": "discovering how a car engine can run on water",
        "distractor_1": "discovering a new buried civilization",
        "distractor_2": "discovering a new species of fish",
        "distractor_3": "discovering an asteroid"
      },
      {
        "id": "8944",
        "question": "Ideation can occur in any step of the engineering design loop, but it most often occurs at what step?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Create"
      },
      {
        "id": "8945",
        "question": "Which of these steps is not a part of the engineering design loop?",
        "answer": "Communicate",
        "distractor_1": "Plan",
        "distractor_2": "Create",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "8946",
        "question": "In engineering, this happens when one attribute or quality is sacrificed for the sake of another.",
        "answer": "trade-off",
        "distractor_1": "ideation",
        "distractor_2": "substitution",
        "distractor_3": "patent"
      },
      {
        "id": "8947",
        "question": "Which of the following statements regarding the relationship between science and technology is false?",
        "answer": "Both scientists and technologists keep new knowledge and ideas secret so they can patent their ideas and make money.",
        "distractor_1": "The goal of science is to understand the natural world, while the goal of technology is to meet human needs or solve human problems.",
        "distractor_2": "Technologists use science to meet human needs.",
        "distractor_3": "Scientists use technology to find answers to questions."
      },
      {
        "id": "8948",
        "question": "What is the difference between invention and innovation?",
        "answer": "Invention is turning a new idea into a new product; innovation is modifying an existing product to improve it.",
        "distractor_1": "Invention is developing a new product; innovation is testing the product to determine its usefulness.",
        "distractor_2": "Invention is coming up with a new idea for a product; innovation is turning the idea into a new product.",
        "distractor_3": "Invention is modifying an existing product to improve it; innovation is turning a new idea into a new product."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2033",
    "name": "Design Time",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8949",
        "question": "A regular item costs $2.50 and there is a price increase of 10%, what is the new cost of the item?",
        "answer": "$2.75 ",
        "distractor_1": "$2.50 ",
        "distractor_2": "$2.70 ",
        "distractor_3": "$2.60 "
      },
      {
        "id": "8950",
        "question": "Serena used the expression 8 + 25 • 2 - 45 to find out how many pennies she has. How many pennies does she have?",
        "answer": "13",
        "distractor_1": "21",
        "distractor_2": "1",
        "distractor_3": "6"
      },
      {
        "id": "8951",
        "question": "Question",
        "answer": "Answer",
        "distractor_1": "Distractor 1",
        "distractor_2": "Distractor 2",
        "distractor_3": "Distractor 3"
      },
      {
        "id": "8952",
        "question": "Which of the following was most likely to happen as people began building steel skyscrapers?",
        "answer": "Cities became larger in population.",
        "distractor_1": "Cities became smaller in population.",
        "distractor_2": "Cities remained the same size.",
        "distractor_3": "Cities moved location."
      },
      {
        "id": "8953",
        "question": "Which of these steps is not a part of the engineering design loop?",
        "answer": "Communicate",
        "distractor_1": "Improve",
        "distractor_2": "Ask",
        "distractor_3": "Create"
      },
      {
        "id": "8954",
        "question": "Which engineering step would most likely include the building of a three-dimensional prototype?",
        "answer": "Create",
        "distractor_1": "Plan",
        "distractor_2": "Imagine",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "8955",
        "question": "After testing a prototype in relation to its requirements, which of the following engineering steps would you do next if you wanted to brainstorm ways to make it better?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Create",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "8956",
        "question": "Which engineering step is most likely to use an ideation process?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Smell",
        "distractor_2": "Ask",
        "distractor_3": "Test"
      },
      {
        "id": "8957",
        "question": "Which of the following was most likely to happen as people began using modern clocks?",
        "answer": "People wanted unique clock designs.",
        "distractor_1": "People wanted more entertainment choices.",
        "distractor_2": "People wanted to go on vacations.",
        "distractor_3": "People wanted new places to live."
      },
      {
        "id": "8958",
        "question": "What is the process humans use to develop new products to meet their needs and wants called?",
        "answer": "Technology",
        "distractor_1": "Engineering",
        "distractor_2": "Inovation",
        "distractor_3": "Invention"
      },
      {
        "id": "8959",
        "question": "Which of the following is an example of a corporation creating demand for a product through advertising?",
        "answer": "a commercial that shows how much fun kids can have with a talking doll",
        "distractor_1": "a blacksmith who makes horseshoes for the horses of local ranchers",
        "distractor_2": "a local puzzle maker who makes puzzles from pictures that people give him",
        "distractor_3": "a farmer selling produce at the side of a road"
      },
      {
        "id": "8960",
        "question": "Which of the following would be the best example of a technology being developed as the result of a need to reduce costs in mass production of products?",
        "answer": "assembly lines",
        "distractor_1": "automobiles",
        "distractor_2": "bicycles",
        "distractor_3": "airplanes"
      },
      {
        "id": "8961",
        "question": "Which of the following technologies would provide the most accurate measurement of time?",
        "answer": "atomic clock",
        "distractor_1": "gravity clock",
        "distractor_2": "calendar",
        "distractor_3": "fire clock"
      },
      {
        "id": "8962",
        "question": "Which of the following technologies was developed because of a need for building a strong shelter?",
        "answer": "ax",
        "distractor_1": "plow",
        "distractor_2": "truck",
        "distractor_3": "steam engine"
      },
      {
        "id": "8963",
        "question": "Which of the following would be the best example of a technology being developed as the result of a need to cross bodies of water?",
        "answer": "boats",
        "distractor_1": "shoes",
        "distractor_2": "automobiles",
        "distractor_3": "tractors"
      },
      {
        "id": "8964",
        "question": "Which of the following technologies was most likely developed without knowledge of science?",
        "answer": "boats",
        "distractor_1": "dialysis machines",
        "distractor_2": "genetically modified foods",
        "distractor_3": "microscopes"
      },
      {
        "id": "8965",
        "question": "Which of the following technologies would provide the least accurate measurement of time?",
        "answer": "calendar",
        "distractor_1": "fire clock",
        "distractor_2": "atomic clock",
        "distractor_3": "gravity clock"
      },
      {
        "id": "8966",
        "question": "Having five different sizes of hammers affects which of the following human uses of technology?",
        "answer": "choice",
        "distractor_1": "attitude",
        "distractor_2": "comfort",
        "distractor_3": "safety"
      },
      {
        "id": "8967",
        "question": "Having an adjustable back support for a car seat affects which of the following human uses of technology?",
        "answer": "comfort",
        "distractor_1": "safety",
        "distractor_2": "choice",
        "distractor_3": "attitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "8968",
        "question": "Which of the following would be the best example of a technology being developed as the result of a need to synchronize shipping routes around the world?",
        "answer": "international time zones",
        "distractor_1": "clocks",
        "distractor_2": "steam engines",
        "distractor_3": "cargo ships"
      },
      {
        "id": "8969",
        "question": "Which of the following would be an example of using creativity to innovate the design of a car?",
        "answer": "light sensors",
        "distractor_1": "steering wheel",
        "distractor_2": "tires",
        "distractor_3": "windshield"
      },
      {
        "id": "8970",
        "question": "Which of the following is the best technology for an inventor to use as documentation for an invention?",
        "answer": "logbook",
        "distractor_1": "phone call",
        "distractor_2": "text message",
        "distractor_3": "sticky notes"
      },
      {
        "id": "8971",
        "question": "Which of the following technologies was developed because of a need for growing large amounts of wheat?",
        "answer": "plow",
        "distractor_1": "airplane",
        "distractor_2": "truck",
        "distractor_3": "clock"
      },
      {
        "id": "8972",
        "question": "Which of the following technologies most represents a society's desire to use electrical equipment?",
        "answer": "power plants",
        "distractor_1": "roads",
        "distractor_2": "public transportation",
        "distractor_3": "water treatment"
      },
      {
        "id": "8973",
        "question": "Which of the following components of a marketing program involves the calculation of markup?",
        "answer": "price",
        "distractor_1": "distribution",
        "distractor_2": "promotion",
        "distractor_3": "products and services"
      },
      {
        "id": "8974",
        "question": "Which of the following components of a marketing program involves the creation of a prototype?",
        "answer": "products and services",
        "distractor_1": "promotion",
        "distractor_2": "price",
        "distractor_3": "distribution"
      },
      {
        "id": "8975",
        "question": "Identify the type of observation made in the following sentence: The clouds are very dark.",
        "answer": "qualitative",
        "distractor_1": "quantitative",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8976",
        "question": "A ________ observation deals with numbers of amounts.",
        "answer": "quantitative",
        "distractor_1": "qualitative",
        "distractor_2": "process",
        "distractor_3": "mechanical"
      },
      {
        "id": "8977",
        "question": "Using a power saw without a finger guard affects which of the following human uses of technology?",
        "answer": "safety",
        "distractor_1": "comfort",
        "distractor_2": "choice",
        "distractor_3": "attitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "8978",
        "question": "Which of the following would be an example of using creativity to innovate the design of a laptop computer?",
        "answer": "touch screen",
        "distractor_1": "headphone jack",
        "distractor_2": "keyboard",
        "distractor_3": "power cord"
      },
      {
        "id": "8979",
        "question": "Which of the following technologies was developed because of a need for making waterproof material?",
        "answer": "vinyl",
        "distractor_1": "plow",
        "distractor_2": "truck",
        "distractor_3": "paper"
      },
      {
        "id": "8980",
        "question": "Which of the following technologies most represents a society's desire to reduce the risk of disease?",
        "answer": "water treatment",
        "distractor_1": "power plants",
        "distractor_2": "roads",
        "distractor_3": "public transportation"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2034",
    "name": "Creative Composites",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8988",
        "question": "A electrical appliance is not running when the switch is turned on. You check several things before finding the problem and fixing it. What is this procedure called?",
        "answer": "troubleshooting",
        "distractor_1": "problem finding",
        "distractor_2": "problem solving",
        "distractor_3": "trouble location"
      },
      {
        "id": "8989",
        "question": "Two supply lines deliver equal amounts of Chemical A and Chemical B to a mixing container to make a compound. If a valve that controls the supply of Chemical A sticks shut, what is the result?",
        "answer": "Less Chemical A is released than is required.",
        "distractor_1": "More Chemical A is released than is required.",
        "distractor_2": "More Chemical B is released than is required.",
        "distractor_3": "Less Chemical B is released than is required."
      },
      {
        "id": "8990",
        "question": "A city needs a new electrical supply line installed. The line must be capable of carrying 25,000 volts and 15 megawatts of power. Due to the possibility of weather damage, the lines must be placed underground. Cost is a factor, so both aluminum and copper",
        "answer": "All of the above.",
        "distractor_1": "The power line must carry 15 megawatts of power.",
        "distractor_2": "The power line must carry 25,000 volts.",
        "distractor_3": "The power line must be placed underground."
      },
      {
        "id": "8991",
        "question": "BPF Manufacturing ships products nationwide. The products can be made from aluminum or steel and have the strength they need. Shipping weight is a concern. The aluminum is lighter in weight, but the steel is less expensive to manufacture. How should the c",
        "answer": "compare the increased cost of the part with the savings on shipping",
        "distractor_1": "look only at the cost of the material",
        "distractor_2": "look only at the cost of shipping",
        "distractor_3": "look at the strength of each material"
      },
      {
        "id": "8992",
        "question": "What is the decision process called when a company must consider competing factors to make a decision?",
        "answer": "trade-off",
        "distractor_1": "conferencing",
        "distractor_2": "competition",
        "distractor_3": "cost comparison"
      },
      {
        "id": "8993",
        "question": "Acme Manufacturing is designing a new product. They have the choice of making the parts lighter in weight or stronger. How will they make their decision?",
        "answer": "compromise by making trade-offs",
        "distractor_1": "make the least expensive part",
        "distractor_2": "make the strongest part possible",
        "distractor_3": "make the parts as light as possible to save on shipping"
      },
      {
        "id": "8994",
        "question": "There is no perfect design for a process or product.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "8995",
        "question": "In engineering, this happens when one attribute or quality is sacrificed for the sake of another.",
        "answer": "trade-off",
        "distractor_1": "subsystem",
        "distractor_2": "ideation",
        "distractor_3": "substitution"
      },
      {
        "id": "8996",
        "question": "Which is an example of an engineering trade-off?",
        "answer": "sacrificing strength to make a product weigh less",
        "distractor_1": "making a product safer",
        "distractor_2": "reducing the cost of a product",
        "distractor_3": "building a prototype of a product"
      },
      {
        "id": "8981",
        "question": "The R & D department is working on a new part for a robotic arm. The part must be made from aluminum, must attach to previous parts, and must be completed by September 1. The length may vary, and the part might be used in other places. Prototypes can be m",
        "answer": "must be aluminum • must fit previous parts • must be completed by September 1",
        "distractor_1": "must be completed by September 1 • must have prototypes 3-D printed • must be aluminum",
        "distractor_2": "must fit previous parts • must be made of steel • must be completed as soon as possible",
        "distractor_3": "must be aluminum • must have prototypes 3-D printed • must cost less than $2"
      },
      {
        "id": "8982",
        "question": "Which of the following is classified as a random arrangement composite?",
        "answer": "concrete",
        "distractor_1": "wood lamination",
        "distractor_2": "sandwich composite",
        "distractor_3": "hand lay-up composite"
      },
      {
        "id": "8983",
        "question": "Which product is made using the hand lay-up process?",
        "answer": "fiberglass boat",
        "distractor_1": "aircraft door",
        "distractor_2": "wooden arch beam",
        "distractor_3": "bridge floor"
      },
      {
        "id": "8984",
        "question": "Within a composite material, which component holds the composite together?",
        "answer": "matrix",
        "distractor_1": "fiber strands",
        "distractor_2": "adhesive",
        "distractor_3": "reinforcement"
      },
      {
        "id": "8985",
        "question": "Within a composite material, what type of bond holds the parts together?",
        "answer": "physical",
        "distractor_1": "chemical",
        "distractor_2": "electron",
        "distractor_3": "molecular"
      },
      {
        "id": "8986",
        "question": "Which term describes the problem-solving method used to identify the cause of a malfunction in a technological system?",
        "answer": "troubleshooting",
        "distractor_1": "checklisting",
        "distractor_2": "conflict resolution",
        "distractor_3": "function listing"
      },
      {
        "id": "8987",
        "question": "Troubleshooting the cause of a malfunction would not include which of the following?",
        "answer": "submitting a repair order",
        "distractor_1": "testing the equipment and comparing the results to a chart",
        "distractor_2": "turning the equipment off and then restarting",
        "distractor_3": "reading the operation manual to ensure proper use of the equipment"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2035",
    "name": "Safe Food",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8997",
        "question": "What is chemical digestion?",
        "answer": "The physical breakdown of food through chewing and churning, making digestion easier",
        "distractor_1": "An organism’s ability to keep the proper conditions inside no matter what is going on outside of the organism",
        "distractor_2": "The breakdown of food through compounds such as acids and enzymes, making it possible for the body to absorb nutrients",
        "distractor_3": "Process that releases energy by breaking down glucose and other food molecules in the presence of oxygen"
      },
      {
        "id": "8998",
        "question": "Where does the digestive system begin?",
        "answer": "Mouth",
        "distractor_1": "Feet",
        "distractor_2": "Stomach",
        "distractor_3": "Esophagus"
      },
      {
        "id": "8999",
        "question": "What is a muscular tube that connects the mouth to the stomach?",
        "answer": "esophagus",
        "distractor_1": "duodenum",
        "distractor_2": "digestive tract",
        "distractor_3": "trachea"
      },
      {
        "id": "9000",
        "question": "Where is hydrochloric acid added to the food mass?",
        "answer": "stomach",
        "distractor_1": "mouth",
        "distractor_2": "small intestine",
        "distractor_3": "large intestine"
      },
      {
        "id": "9001",
        "question": "________ are large molecules that are made of amino acids. These molecules are important building blocks for living things.",
        "answer": "Proteins",
        "distractor_1": "Carbohydrates",
        "distractor_2": "Monomers",
        "distractor_3": "Chloroplasts"
      },
      {
        "id": "9002",
        "question": "Some ________, like fats and oils, are used by organisms to store energy.",
        "answer": "lipids",
        "distractor_1": "carbohydrates",
        "distractor_2": "proteins",
        "distractor_3": "chromosomes"
      },
      {
        "id": "9003",
        "question": "Water (H2O) and salt (NaCl) are what?",
        "answer": "Compounds",
        "distractor_1": "Elements",
        "distractor_2": "Mixtures",
        "distractor_3": "Solutions"
      },
      {
        "id": "9004",
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a physical change?",
        "answer": "developing film",
        "distractor_1": "shredding cheese",
        "distractor_2": "boiling water",
        "distractor_3": "painting a wall"
      },
      {
        "id": "9005",
        "question": "What do enzymes do?",
        "answer": "act as catalysts",
        "distractor_1": "add acid",
        "distractor_2": "add base",
        "distractor_3": "produce proteins"
      },
      {
        "id": "9006",
        "question": "Which of the following would result in chemical change?",
        "answer": "burning wood",
        "distractor_1": "boiling water",
        "distractor_2": "tearing paper",
        "distractor_3": "melting wax"
      },
      {
        "id": "9007",
        "question": "During science lab, some students added small pieces of magnesium (Mg) to hydrochloric acid (HCl). They noticed that bubbles formed, the test tube got hot, and the magnesium disappeared. Which of the following is a sign that a chemical reaction has taken ",
        "answer": "formation of a gas",
        "distractor_1": "odor",
        "distractor_2": "decrease in temperature",
        "distractor_3": "formation of a precipitate"
      },
      {
        "id": "9008",
        "question": "What type of change does an odor being given off indicate?",
        "answer": "chemical change",
        "distractor_1": "change of density",
        "distractor_2": "physical change",
        "distractor_3": "change of state"
      },
      {
        "id": "9009",
        "question": "Which of the following engineering design steps can be repeated as needed?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "9010",
        "question": "Which type of scientific test can separate the colors of dyes used in food?",
        "answer": "chromotography",
        "distractor_1": "spectography",
        "distractor_2": "calorimetry",
        "distractor_3": "dye sublimation"
      },
      {
        "id": "9011",
        "question": "What is the main molecule used by your body for energy?",
        "answer": "glucose",
        "distractor_1": "amino acid",
        "distractor_2": "hydrochloric acid",
        "distractor_3": "protein"
      },
      {
        "id": "9012",
        "question": "The four classes of organic macromolecules include which of the following?",
        "answer": "lipids",
        "distractor_1": "vitamins",
        "distractor_2": "salt",
        "distractor_3": "phosphates"
      },
      {
        "id": "9013",
        "question": "Which structure in the digestive system is the longest?",
        "answer": "small intestine",
        "distractor_1": "large intestine",
        "distractor_2": "esophagus",
        "distractor_3": "pharynx"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2036",
    "name": "Everyday Electricity",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9014",
        "question": "Francis wonders where his dog is getting through the fence. He found a spot behind a bush where the fence is rotted away. What is his next step?",
        "answer": "infer",
        "distractor_1": "draw a conclusion",
        "distractor_2": "test the hypothesis",
        "distractor_3": "form a hypothesis"
      },
      {
        "id": "9015",
        "question": "What factor is not changed in an experiment?",
        "answer": "constant",
        "distractor_1": "dependent variable",
        "distractor_2": "temperature",
        "distractor_3": "independent variable"
      },
      {
        "id": "9016",
        "question": "What factors can be changed in an experiment?",
        "answer": "variables",
        "distractor_1": "standards",
        "distractor_2": "constants",
        "distractor_3": "controls"
      },
      {
        "id": "9017",
        "question": "What is the one variable that is purposely changed to test a hypothesis called?",
        "answer": "manipulated variable",
        "distractor_1": "constant",
        "distractor_2": "responding variable",
        "distractor_3": "operational variable"
      },
      {
        "id": "9018",
        "question": "Identify the type of observation made in the following sentence: The clouds are very dark.",
        "answer": "qualitative",
        "distractor_1": "quantitative",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9019",
        "question": "Which of the following is a quantitative observation?",
        "answer": "My waist size is 31 inches.",
        "distractor_1": "Chemistry is an easy subject.",
        "distractor_2": "The flame is flickering.",
        "distractor_3": "My eyes are blue."
      },
      {
        "id": "9020",
        "question": "What is using one or more of your senses to gather information called?",
        "answer": "Observing",
        "distractor_1": "Inferring",
        "distractor_2": "Predicting",
        "distractor_3": "Classifying"
      },
      {
        "id": "9021",
        "question": "How many independent variables can be tested at one time during an experiment?",
        "answer": "1",
        "distractor_1": "2",
        "distractor_2": "As many as you would like",
        "distractor_3": "The same amount as the number of controlled variables"
      },
      {
        "id": "9022",
        "question": "Which wire is the ground wire?",
        "answer": "bare",
        "distractor_1": "black",
        "distractor_2": "white",
        "distractor_3": "red"
      },
      {
        "id": "9023",
        "question": "What is the wire used to carry current to a second switch in a three-way light switch called?",
        "answer": "traveler",
        "distractor_1": "ground",
        "distractor_2": "neutral",
        "distractor_3": "source"
      },
      {
        "id": "9024",
        "question": "Which action occurs when a transformer is used to increase voltage?",
        "answer": "voltage increases and current decreases",
        "distractor_1": "voltage increases and current increases",
        "distractor_2": "voltage increases and current remains constant",
        "distractor_3": "voltage decreases and current decreases"
      },
      {
        "id": "9025",
        "question": "For a circuit to be complete, which wires are required?",
        "answer": "source and neutral",
        "distractor_1": "source and ground",
        "distractor_2": "neutral and ground",
        "distractor_3": "source and traveler"
      },
      {
        "id": "9026",
        "question": "If your hypothesis was proven incorrect at the end of your experiment trials, your experiment was a failure.",
        "answer": "False",
        "distractor_1": "True",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9027",
        "question": "Identify the type of observation made in the following sentence: He ate twenty-five french fries today.",
        "answer": "quantitative",
        "distractor_1": "qualitative",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2037",
    "name": "Future Footprints",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9028",
        "question": "Which is the best example of a human impact on the geosphere?",
        "answer": "mining for mineral ores",
        "distractor_1": "burning fossil fuels",
        "distractor_2": "building a dam for hydroelectric energy",
        "distractor_3": "hunting passenger pigeons to extinction"
      },
      {
        "id": "9029",
        "question": "Which is the best example of a human impact on the hydrosphere?",
        "answer": "building a dam for hydroelectric energy",
        "distractor_1": "burning fossil fuels",
        "distractor_2": "mining for mineral ores",
        "distractor_3": "hunting passenger pigeons to extinction"
      },
      {
        "id": "9030",
        "question": "Increase in human population impacts which of earth's spheres?",
        "answer": "biosphere, hydrosphere, atmosphere, and geosphere",
        "distractor_1": "biosphere, hydrosphere, and atmosphere only",
        "distractor_2": "biosphere and hydrosphere only",
        "distractor_3": "biosphere only"
      },
      {
        "id": "9031",
        "question": "Before any new scientific information can be accepted there is a great deal of ________ confirming its accuracy.",
        "answer": "debate",
        "distractor_1": "steps",
        "distractor_2": "hypothesis",
        "distractor_3": "analyze"
      },
      {
        "id": "9032",
        "question": "Which of the following is an example of a renewable resource?",
        "answer": "corn",
        "distractor_1": "gold",
        "distractor_2": "coal",
        "distractor_3": "diamonds"
      },
      {
        "id": "9033",
        "question": "Which of the following is an example of a nonrenewable resource?",
        "answer": "silver",
        "distractor_1": "wheat",
        "distractor_2": "fish",
        "distractor_3": "wood"
      },
      {
        "id": "9034",
        "question": "Which of the following is an example of a perpetual resource?",
        "answer": "sunlight",
        "distractor_1": "salt",
        "distractor_2": "oil",
        "distractor_3": "oranges"
      },
      {
        "id": "9035",
        "question": "Water leaving a power plant that heats lake water drastically, killing fish and plants, is an example of what type of pollution?",
        "answer": "thermal",
        "distractor_1": "radioactive",
        "distractor_2": "chemical",
        "distractor_3": "nonpoint"
      },
      {
        "id": "9036",
        "question": "Pesticides sprayed on crops that contaminate the water table below the dirt are examples of what type of pollution?",
        "answer": "chemical",
        "distractor_1": "point",
        "distractor_2": "radioactive",
        "distractor_3": "thermal"
      },
      {
        "id": "9037",
        "question": "Which of the following is a possible consequence of rapid population growth?",
        "answer": "water shortage",
        "distractor_1": "less pollution",
        "distractor_2": "increased land availability",
        "distractor_3": "no species extinction"
      },
      {
        "id": "9038",
        "question": "Which of the following is a possible consequence of rapid population growth?",
        "answer": "wildlife habitat destruction",
        "distractor_1": "less pollution",
        "distractor_2": "increased land availability",
        "distractor_3": "no species extinction"
      },
      {
        "id": "9039",
        "question": "A waste-management company wants to place a garbage dump near a small town. The community not wanting the dump located next to their town is an example of which type of issue?",
        "answer": "societal",
        "distractor_1": "economic",
        "distractor_2": "governmental",
        "distractor_3": "criminal"
      },
      {
        "id": "9040",
        "question": "A mining company located in a small town decides to create large piles of slag on its property. Slag is the waste from refining ore. The community not wanting the unsightly piles of slag in their town is an example of which type of issue?",
        "answer": "societal",
        "distractor_1": "economic",
        "distractor_2": "governmental",
        "distractor_3": "criminal"
      },
      {
        "id": "9041",
        "question": "A mining company is trying to decide whether to put its waste matter back in the ground after the refinement process. It would cost considerably more to do so, but it would be better for the environment. Which two concerns are in direct competition with e",
        "answer": "economic and environmental",
        "distractor_1": "economic and governmental",
        "distractor_2": "environmental and governmental",
        "distractor_3": "criminal and civil"
      },
      {
        "id": "9042",
        "question": "A power plant is trying to decide whether to cool its wastewater below government requirements because it would be better for the river. It would cost considerably more to do so, but it would be better for the environment. Which two concerns are in direct",
        "answer": "economic and environmental",
        "distractor_1": "economic and governmental",
        "distractor_2": "environmental and governmental",
        "distractor_3": "criminal and civil"
      },
      {
        "id": "9043",
        "question": "Which is the best example of a human impact on the biosphere?",
        "answer": "hunting passenger pigeons to extinction",
        "distractor_1": "building a dam for hydroelectric energy",
        "distractor_2": "mining for mineral ores",
        "distractor_3": "burning fossil fuels"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2039",
    "name": "Tower Power",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9044",
        "question": "Friction in which two surfaces are not moving past each other.",
        "answer": "Static",
        "distractor_1": "Rolling",
        "distractor_2": "Sliding",
        "distractor_3": "Fluid"
      },
      {
        "id": "9045",
        "question": "What is a Newton?",
        "answer": "a unit of measure for force",
        "distractor_1": "a unit of measure for mass",
        "distractor_2": "a unit of measure for distance",
        "distractor_3": "a unit of measure for weight"
      },
      {
        "id": "9046",
        "question": "The unit of force is ________.",
        "answer": "N",
        "distractor_1": "s",
        "distractor_2": "kg",
        "distractor_3": "m"
      },
      {
        "id": "9047",
        "question": "If the forces acting on an object are unbalanced, what happens?",
        "answer": "the object accelerates.",
        "distractor_1": "the object moves in constant motion.",
        "distractor_2": "the object will not move.",
        "distractor_3": "the object remains at rest."
      },
      {
        "id": "9048",
        "question": "Which of the listed engineering steps would you use to brainstorm ways to use series circuits in a building?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Create",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "9049",
        "question": "Which of the following engineering design steps can be repeated as needed?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "9050",
        "question": "Which of the following engineering design steps can be completed out of sequence?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "9051",
        "question": "Brainstorming usually happens in which engineering step?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "9052",
        "question": "Which engineering step would most likely involve each person in a group presenting his or her ideas?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "9053",
        "question": "Which of the following are used to transform ideas into practical solutions?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "modeling",
        "distractor_2": "testing",
        "distractor_3": "evaluating"
      },
      {
        "id": "9054",
        "question": "Which of the following activities would most likely not be used in the Improve engineering step?",
        "answer": "creating",
        "distractor_1": "modeling",
        "distractor_2": "testing",
        "distractor_3": "evaluating"
      },
      {
        "id": "9055",
        "question": "Which of the following is the load on a tower caused by an antenna mounted on the top of the tower?",
        "answer": "live load",
        "distractor_1": "wind load",
        "distractor_2": "dead load",
        "distractor_3": "thermal load"
      },
      {
        "id": "9056",
        "question": "Which of the following is the load on a tower caused by the weight of the tower materials?",
        "answer": "dead load",
        "distractor_1": "live load",
        "distractor_2": "settlement load",
        "distractor_3": "thermal load"
      },
      {
        "id": "9057",
        "question": "Which tower type consists of a single pole that goes straight up?",
        "answer": "monopole",
        "distractor_1": "guyed",
        "distractor_2": "lattice",
        "distractor_3": "concealed"
      },
      {
        "id": "9058",
        "question": "Which tower type consists of a tower supported by cables anchored to the ground?",
        "answer": "guyed",
        "distractor_1": "monopole",
        "distractor_2": "lattice",
        "distractor_3": "concealed"
      },
      {
        "id": "9059",
        "question": "Which of the listed engineering steps would you use to brainstorm ways to use parallel circuits in a building?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Create",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2038",
    "name": "Cultivating Our Future",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9060",
        "question": "Which of the following technologies has contributed to increasing food production for the world's ever-increasing population?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "biotechnology",
        "distractor_2": "GPS-guided tractors and combines",
        "distractor_3": "chemical pesticides"
      },
      {
        "id": "9061",
        "question": "Which of these farming practices has helped improve the production of food?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "using genetically modified organisms",
        "distractor_2": "hydroponics",
        "distractor_3": "sustainable farming"
      },
      {
        "id": "9062",
        "question": "Which of these farming technologies have had the least effect on improving the production of food?",
        "answer": "drones",
        "distractor_1": "chemical pesticides and herbicides",
        "distractor_2": "biotechnology",
        "distractor_3": "tractors and machines that perform multiple jobs"
      },
      {
        "id": "9063",
        "question": "What is an example of an artificial ecosystem that replicates some aspects of the natural environment?",
        "answer": "vertical farm",
        "distractor_1": "organic farm",
        "distractor_2": "aquifer",
        "distractor_3": "a farm using genetically modified corn"
      },
      {
        "id": "9064",
        "question": "Transgenic wheat that incorporates genes to increase the size of the seeds would increase total food production for which of the following reasons?",
        "answer": "increases yield per harvest",
        "distractor_1": "increases total nutritional value of the harvest",
        "distractor_2": "reduces use of pesticides",
        "distractor_3": "allows more crops to be planted on the same ground over time"
      },
      {
        "id": "9065",
        "question": "The application of biology to create commercial products or processes is called what?",
        "answer": "biotechnology",
        "distractor_1": "market biology",
        "distractor_2": "microbiology",
        "distractor_3": "bioengineering"
      },
      {
        "id": "9066",
        "question": "What is the process of a seed starting to grow called?",
        "answer": "germination",
        "distractor_1": "emergence",
        "distractor_2": "pollination",
        "distractor_3": "fertilization"
      },
      {
        "id": "9067",
        "question": "Which of the following is true of organic farming?",
        "answer": "Organic farms tend to have less food production but a higher variety of foods compared to traditional farms.",
        "distractor_1": "Organic farms tend to grow healthier plants through the use of chemical fertilizers.",
        "distractor_2": "On organic farms, pests and weeds are controlled by chemical pesticides and herbicides.",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9068",
        "question": "Which of the following is the best example of biotechnology being used on a farm?",
        "answer": "modifying a plant's DNA to produce larger and sweeter fruits",
        "distractor_1": "using self-driving combines to harvest a corn field",
        "distractor_2": "using a wind generator to power cow milking machines on a dairy farm",
        "distractor_3": "using a greenhouse to keep tomato plants from freezing in late fall"
      },
      {
        "id": "9069",
        "question": "Growing food in community gardens, on building rooftops, in backyard gardens, and on window ledges are all examples of what type of farming?",
        "answer": "urban farming",
        "distractor_1": "organic farming",
        "distractor_2": "traditional farming",
        "distractor_3": "sustainable farming"
      },
      {
        "id": "9070",
        "question": "What is an aquifer?",
        "answer": "an underground area of permeable rock that is saturated with groundwater",
        "distractor_1": "a hydroponic system for growing food inside a greenhouse or building",
        "distractor_2": "a naturally occurring spring where water flows out of the ground",
        "distractor_3": "an irrigation system used to water crops"
      },
      {
        "id": "9071",
        "question": "In the water cycle, which process involves the release of water into the atmosphere by plants?",
        "answer": "transpiration",
        "distractor_1": "precipitation",
        "distractor_2": "evaporation",
        "distractor_3": "condensation"
      },
      {
        "id": "9072",
        "question": "Testing, evaluating, and modifying a solution or product most likely occurs at which stage of the engineering design process?",
        "answer": "Improve",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "9073",
        "question": "When following the engineering design loop, which step usually comes after asking questions?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "9074",
        "question": "Which of these farming practices has had little or no effect on improving the production of food?",
        "answer": "virtual reality farming",
        "distractor_1": "using genetically modified organisms",
        "distractor_2": "soil conservation",
        "distractor_3": "sustainable farming"
      },
      {
        "id": "9075",
        "question": "What is an example of an artificial ecosystem that replicates some aspects of the natural environment?",
        "answer": "greenhouse",
        "distractor_1": "a farm using genetically modified wheat",
        "distractor_2": "organic farm",
        "distractor_3": "aquifer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9076",
        "question": "Transgenic corn that incorporates genes to shorten growing time would increase total food production for which of the following reasons?",
        "answer": "allows more crops to be planted on the same ground over time",
        "distractor_1": "reduces use of pesticides",
        "distractor_2": "increases yield per harvest",
        "distractor_3": "increases total nutritional value of the harvest"
      },
      {
        "id": "9077",
        "question": "In the water cycle, which process changes water vapor in the atmosphere to small water droplets, forming clouds?",
        "answer": "condensation",
        "distractor_1": "transpiration",
        "distractor_2": "evaporation",
        "distractor_3": "precipitation"
      },
      {
        "id": "9078",
        "question": "Which of these steps is not a part of the engineering design loop?",
        "answer": "Communicate",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Create",
        "distractor_3": "Plan"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2040",
    "name": "Fueling the Future",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9079",
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a part of a well-designed experiment?",
        "answer": "small sample size",
        "distractor_1": "a reproducible procedure",
        "distractor_2": "multiple trials",
        "distractor_3": "a control"
      },
      {
        "id": "9080",
        "question": "How many independent variables can be tested at one time during an experiment?",
        "answer": "1",
        "distractor_1": "2",
        "distractor_2": "As many as you would like",
        "distractor_3": "The same amount as the number of controlled variables"
      },
      {
        "id": "9081",
        "question": "In which order do the four strokes in a four-stroke internal combustion engine occur?",
        "answer": "intake • compression • power • exhaust",
        "distractor_1": "compression • power • intake • exhaust",
        "distractor_2": "exhaust • compression • power • intake",
        "distractor_3": "intake • exhaust • compression • power"
      },
      {
        "id": "9082",
        "question": "What is the international unit of measurement for energy and work?",
        "answer": "joule",
        "distractor_1": "watt",
        "distractor_2": "kilohm",
        "distractor_3": "horsepower"
      },
      {
        "id": "9083",
        "question": "Which form of energy is defined as energy in motion?",
        "answer": "kinetic",
        "distractor_1": "electrical",
        "distractor_2": "potential",
        "distractor_3": "static"
      },
      {
        "id": "9084",
        "question": "What is the energy source in a geothermal heating system?",
        "answer": "earth",
        "distractor_1": "Sun",
        "distractor_2": "wind",
        "distractor_3": "water"
      },
      {
        "id": "9085",
        "question": "Photovoltaic energy is obtained from what resource?",
        "answer": "sunlight",
        "distractor_1": "natural gas",
        "distractor_2": "coal",
        "distractor_3": "oil"
      },
      {
        "id": "9086",
        "question": "Which engineering step is most likely to use a creative planning process?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Listen",
        "distractor_3": "Watch"
      },
      {
        "id": "9087",
        "question": "Which engineering step is most likely to use a brainstorming process?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Taste",
        "distractor_3": "Touch"
      },
      {
        "id": "9088",
        "question": "Which engineering step is most likely to use an ideation process?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Smell",
        "distractor_3": "Test"
      },
      {
        "id": "9089",
        "question": "In any design there is an opportunity to make it better.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9090",
        "question": "There is no perfect design for a process or product.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9091",
        "question": "A perfect design is usually obtained on the third try.",
        "answer": "False",
        "distractor_1": "True",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9092",
        "question": "Which of these steps is not a part of the engineering design loop?",
        "answer": "Communicate",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Create"
      },
      {
        "id": "9093",
        "question": "When following the engineering design loop, which step usually comes after asking questions?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Improve",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Create"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2041",
    "name": "Beyond Earth",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9094",
        "question": "How would the force of gravity between Neptune and the sun be affected if Neptune were closer to the sun?",
        "answer": "The force between the two would be greater",
        "distractor_1": "The force between the two would be less",
        "distractor_2": "The force between the two would disappear",
        "distractor_3": "The force between the two would not change"
      },
      {
        "id": "9095",
        "question": "Complete the sentence. Gravitational forces cause ________ to orbit planets, planets to orbit ________, and stars to orbit the centers of ________.",
        "answer": "moons; stars; galaxies",
        "distractor_1": "galaxies; stars; moons",
        "distractor_2": "moons; galaxies; stars",
        "distractor_3": "stars; moons; galaxies"
      },
      {
        "id": "9096",
        "question": "Imagine that gravitational force suddenly disappeared. Which best describes what Earth's path through space would look like?",
        "answer": "Earth would move in a straight line through space.",
        "distractor_1": "Earth would stop moving.",
        "distractor_2": "Earth would stop orbiting the sun and start orbiting the other planets.",
        "distractor_3": "There would be no change in Earth's path through space."
      },
      {
        "id": "9097",
        "question": "Put the following in order from biggest to smallest:",
        "answer": "Universe, Galaxy, Solar System, Star, Planet",
        "distractor_1": "Solar System, Universe, Galaxy, Star, Planet",
        "distractor_2": "Universe, Solar System, Galaxy, Planet, Star",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9098",
        "question": "Which statement about the outer planets is TRUE?",
        "answer": "The atmosphere of the outer planets are made of thick and swirling gases.",
        "distractor_1": "The outer planets do not have many moons.",
        "distractor_2": "The outer planets are all very warm and have volcanoes.",
        "distractor_3": "Saturn is the only outer planet that has rings."
      },
      {
        "id": "9099",
        "question": "Pluto is an example of a(n)",
        "answer": "dwarf planet",
        "distractor_1": "inner planet",
        "distractor_2": "outer planet",
        "distractor_3": "planetesimal"
      },
      {
        "id": "9100",
        "question": "About how many times farther from the Sun is Mars than Earth?",
        "answer": "1.5",
        "distractor_1": ".5",
        "distractor_2": "3",
        "distractor_3": "4"
      },
      {
        "id": "9101",
        "question": "One astronomical unit is about 150 million kilometers. Jupiter is 778 million kilometers from the Sun. What is the distance from the Sun to Jupiter in astronomical units?",
        "answer": "5.2",
        "distractor_1": ".2",
        "distractor_2": "2.2",
        "distractor_3": "6.3"
      },
      {
        "id": "9102",
        "question": "The force of gravity between two objects is determined by the mass of the first object, the mass of the second object, and the distance between the two objects. Which of these three things has the greatest effect of the total amount of force?",
        "answer": "the distance between the two objects",
        "distractor_1": "the mass of the second object",
        "distractor_2": "the mass of the first object",
        "distractor_3": "the combined mass of the two objects"
      },
      {
        "id": "9103",
        "question": "The shortest path between two astronomical bodies, such as Earth and Mars, is defined by which of the following?",
        "answer": "Hohman transfer orbit",
        "distractor_1": "Einstein-Rosen bridge",
        "distractor_2": "interstellar highway",
        "distractor_3": "Voyager path"
      },
      {
        "id": "9104",
        "question": "About how many times farther from the Sun is Venus than Earth?",
        "answer": "0.7",
        "distractor_1": "1.4",
        "distractor_2": "3",
        "distractor_3": "4"
      },
      {
        "id": "9105",
        "question": "One astronomical unit is about 150 million kilometers. Mercury is 58 million kilometers from the Sun. What is the distance from the Sun to Mercury in astronomical units?",
        "answer": "0.4",
        "distractor_1": "1.4",
        "distractor_2": "2.8",
        "distractor_3": "5.6"
      },
      {
        "id": "9106",
        "question": "Which of the following engineering design steps can be repeated as needed?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "9107",
        "question": "Which engineering step would most likely involve each person in a group presenting his or her ideas?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Create"
      },
      {
        "id": "9108",
        "question": "Which of the following are used to transform ideas into practical solutions?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "modeling",
        "distractor_2": "testing",
        "distractor_3": "evaluating"
      },
      {
        "id": "9109",
        "question": "How is a moon different than a planet?",
        "answer": "a moon is in orbit around a planet",
        "distractor_1": "a moon is unable to have an atmosphere",
        "distractor_2": "a moon is less massive than any planet.",
        "distractor_3": "a moon is smaller than any planet."
      },
      {
        "id": "9110",
        "question": "Brainstorming usually happens in which engineering step?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Create"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2042",
    "name": "Making Waves",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9111",
        "question": "Alyssa has 4 pairs of low-top sneakers, 7 pairs of high-top sneakers, 3 pairs of sandals, and 1 pair of boots. What is the ratio of the pairs of low-top sneakers to the total number of pairs of shoes?",
        "answer": "4 to 15",
        "distractor_1": "7 to 15",
        "distractor_2": "4 to 3",
        "distractor_3": "1 to 3"
      },
      {
        "id": "9112",
        "question": "There are 21 sedans and 12 sports utility vehicles on the lot of a car dealership. Which ratio is equivalent to 21/12?",
        "answer": "7/4",
        "distractor_1": "24/12",
        "distractor_2": "21/9",
        "distractor_3": "7/2"
      },
      {
        "id": "9113",
        "question": "Which of the listed engineering steps would you use to brainstorm ways to use parallel circuits in a building?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Create",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "9114",
        "question": "'The solar panel cannot exceed 2 m x 4 m' is a statement that describes which of the following?",
        "answer": "constraint",
        "distractor_1": "specification",
        "distractor_2": "both",
        "distractor_3": "neither"
      },
      {
        "id": "9115",
        "question": "Which of the following is most responsible for determining the pitch of a note?",
        "answer": "frequency",
        "distractor_1": "amplitude",
        "distractor_2": "resonance",
        "distractor_3": "tone"
      },
      {
        "id": "9116",
        "question": "Which of the following is most responsible for determining the loudness of a sound?",
        "answer": "amplitude",
        "distractor_1": "frequency",
        "distractor_2": "resonance",
        "distractor_3": "tone"
      },
      {
        "id": "9117",
        "question": "Which type of instrument produces a sound by striking, shaking, scraping, or rubbing?",
        "answer": "percussion",
        "distractor_1": "string",
        "distractor_2": "brass",
        "distractor_3": "woodwind"
      },
      {
        "id": "9118",
        "question": "Which type of instrument produces a sound by buzzing lips in a mouthpiece?",
        "answer": "brass",
        "distractor_1": "woodwind",
        "distractor_2": "string",
        "distractor_3": "percussion"
      },
      {
        "id": "9119",
        "question": "Which type of instrument produces a sound by blowing air across a reed?",
        "answer": "woodwind",
        "distractor_1": "brass",
        "distractor_2": "string",
        "distractor_3": "percussion"
      },
      {
        "id": "9120",
        "question": "Which type of instrument produces a sound by plucking, strumming, or using a bow?",
        "answer": "string",
        "distractor_1": "brass",
        "distractor_2": "woodwind",
        "distractor_3": "percussion"
      },
      {
        "id": "9121",
        "question": "Which of the following mediums would a sound wave travel through the fastest?",
        "answer": "solid",
        "distractor_1": "liquid",
        "distractor_2": "gas",
        "distractor_3": "plasma"
      },
      {
        "id": "9122",
        "question": "Which of the listed engineering steps would you use to brainstorm ways to use series circuits in a building?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Create",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "9123",
        "question": "'The motor cannot exceed 1,000 rpm' is a statement that describes which of the following?",
        "answer": "constraint",
        "distractor_1": "specification",
        "distractor_2": "both",
        "distractor_3": "neither"
      },
      {
        "id": "9124",
        "question": "A class of 32 students has 12 girls. What is the ratio of girls to boys?",
        "answer": "3 to 5",
        "distractor_1": "8 to 3",
        "distractor_2": "3 to 8",
        "distractor_3": "5 to 3"
      },
      {
        "id": "9125",
        "question": "There are 30 red marbles and 150 blue marbles in a box. What is the ratio of blue marbles to red marbles?",
        "answer": "150 to 30",
        "distractor_1": "30 to 150",
        "distractor_2": "30 to 80",
        "distractor_3": "180 to 30"
      },
      {
        "id": "9126",
        "question": "A youth soccer league has 60 players for 5 teams. The league then adds 1 more soccer team and divides the players equally among the teams. Which statement is true?",
        "answer": "For every 1 team, there are 10 players.",
        "distractor_1": "For every 1 team, there are 11 players.",
        "distractor_2": "For every 1 team, there are 12 players.",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9127",
        "question": "'The motor must run at 1,000 rpm' is a statement that describes which of the following?",
        "answer": "specification",
        "distractor_1": "constraint",
        "distractor_2": "both",
        "distractor_3": "neither"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2043",
    "name": "Projecting Light",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9128",
        "question": "What is the relationship between a wave's frequency and wavelength?",
        "answer": "A wave's frequency increases while its wavelength decreases.",
        "distractor_1": "A wave's frequency increases while its wavelength increases.",
        "distractor_2": "A wave's frequency remains constant while its wavelength changes.",
        "distractor_3": "A wave's wavelength changes while its frequency remains constant."
      },
      {
        "id": "9129",
        "question": "Which of the waves listed is considered a transverse wave?",
        "answer": "radio wave",
        "distractor_1": "light wave",
        "distractor_2": "shock wave",
        "distractor_3": "sound wave"
      },
      {
        "id": "9130",
        "question": "Which of the waves listed is considered a longitudinal wave?",
        "answer": "sound wave",
        "distractor_1": "light wave",
        "distractor_2": "radio wave",
        "distractor_3": "x-ray wave"
      },
      {
        "id": "9131",
        "question": "Which statement is true of laser light?",
        "answer": "Laser light is made up of all wavelengths of light.",
        "distractor_1": "Laser light is made up of all frequencies of light.",
        "distractor_2": "Laser light is monochromatic and is made of light waves of the same frequency and wavelength.",
        "distractor_3": "Laser light has waves that travel perpendicular to each other."
      },
      {
        "id": "9132",
        "question": "Which equation is the correct form of the wave equation?",
        "answer": "speed = frequency • wavelength",
        "distractor_1": "speed = amplitude • wavelength",
        "distractor_2": "frequency = speed • wavelength",
        "distractor_3": "frequency = amplitude • wavelength"
      },
      {
        "id": "9133",
        "question": "What is the distance from one trough of a wave to the next trough of the wave?",
        "answer": "wavelength",
        "distractor_1": "amplitude",
        "distractor_2": "frequency",
        "distractor_3": "equilibrium point"
      },
      {
        "id": "9134",
        "question": "What wave feature relates to the amount of energy being carried by the light wave?",
        "answer": "amplitude",
        "distractor_1": "wavelength",
        "distractor_2": "frequency",
        "distractor_3": "wave speed"
      },
      {
        "id": "9135",
        "question": "Which is the best description of why an apple appears red?",
        "answer": "The apple absorbs all wavelengths of light except red. Red wavelengths are reflected by the apple.",
        "distractor_1": "The apple reflects all wavelengths of light except red. Red wavelengths are transmitted by the apple.",
        "distractor_2": "The apple transmits all wavelengths of light except red. Red wavelengths are absorbed by the apple.",
        "distractor_3": "The apple reflects all wavelengths of light except red. Red wavelengths are absorbed by the apple."
      },
      {
        "id": "9136",
        "question": "Why does freshly fallen snow appear white?",
        "answer": "The snow reflects all wavelengths of light.",
        "distractor_1": "The snow reflects white wavelengths of light and absorbs all other colors.",
        "distractor_2": "The snow absorbs all wavelengths of light.",
        "distractor_3": "The snow absorbs white wavelengths of light and reflects all other colors."
      },
      {
        "id": "9137",
        "question": "What is the highest point on a wave?",
        "answer": "crest",
        "distractor_1": "wave",
        "distractor_2": "trough",
        "distractor_3": "bones"
      },
      {
        "id": "9138",
        "question": "You can see your image in a shiny, flat surface because light waves bounce directly back at you and your eyes. This is an example of",
        "answer": "reflection",
        "distractor_1": "diffraction",
        "distractor_2": "refraction",
        "distractor_3": "transparency"
      },
      {
        "id": "9139",
        "question": "A disturbance that travels through a medium, transporting energy from one location to another location is ________.",
        "answer": "a wave",
        "distractor_1": "a sound",
        "distractor_2": "light",
        "distractor_3": "frequency"
      },
      {
        "id": "9140",
        "question": "Both sound and light travel in waves.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9141",
        "question": "What is the distance between to consecutive crests or troughs called?",
        "answer": "wavelength",
        "distractor_1": "amplitude",
        "distractor_2": "speed",
        "distractor_3": "frequency"
      },
      {
        "id": "9142",
        "question": "What happens to green light and red light when they shine on a green leaf?",
        "answer": "Both are absorbed.",
        "distractor_1": "Both are reflected.",
        "distractor_2": "Green light is absorbed, and red light is reflected.",
        "distractor_3": ""
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2044",
    "name": "Communications",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9143",
        "question": "Why are drawings that display views in a standard arrangement so important in manufacturing?",
        "answer": "to describe the product clearly",
        "distractor_1": "to show the correct material to use",
        "distractor_2": "to describe how to build the product",
        "distractor_3": "to show the correct color to use"
      },
      {
        "id": "9144",
        "question": "Which views are the most common views in a multiview drawing?",
        "answer": "top • front • right side",
        "distractor_1": "top • bottom • left side",
        "distractor_2": "front • back • top",
        "distractor_3": "top • front • left side"
      },
      {
        "id": "9145",
        "question": "Which of these would be the best conductor of electricity?",
        "answer": "copper",
        "distractor_1": "hydrogen",
        "distractor_2": "chloride",
        "distractor_3": "neon"
      },
      {
        "id": "9146",
        "question": "Which factor does not influence the design of a message?",
        "answer": "cost of the message",
        "distractor_1": "intended audience",
        "distractor_2": "purpose of the message",
        "distractor_3": "message medium"
      },
      {
        "id": "9147",
        "question": "Which device in a communications system sends a message?",
        "answer": "transmitter",
        "distractor_1": "receiver",
        "distractor_2": "decoder",
        "distractor_3": "encoder"
      },
      {
        "id": "9148",
        "question": "When designing a message, what factors are considered?",
        "answer": "intended audience • medium • purpose • and nature of the message",
        "distractor_1": "intended audience • medium • purpose • and cost of the message",
        "distractor_2": "method of delivery • purpose • language • and cost of delivery",
        "distractor_3": "nature • purpose • audience • and whether the delivery will be analog or digital"
      },
      {
        "id": "9149",
        "question": "When an FM signal is transmitted, how is the sound created?",
        "answer": "The frequency of the signal is changed which produces the sound.",
        "distractor_1": "The force of the signal is changed which produces the sound.",
        "distractor_2": "The amplitude of the signal is changed which produces the sound.",
        "distractor_3": "The frequency is kept the same while the strength is changed to produce the sound."
      },
      {
        "id": "9150",
        "question": "What types of systems enable information to be transferred from machine to human?",
        "answer": "information and communications",
        "distractor_1": "digital and analog",
        "distractor_2": "sound and light",
        "distractor_3": "computer and fax"
      },
      {
        "id": "9151",
        "question": "What types of systems enable information to be transferred from human to machine?",
        "answer": "information and communications",
        "distractor_1": "digital and analog",
        "distractor_2": "sound and light",
        "distractor_3": "computer and fax"
      },
      {
        "id": "9152",
        "question": "What types of systems enable information to be transferred from human to human?",
        "answer": "information and communications",
        "distractor_1": "digital and analog",
        "distractor_2": "sound and light",
        "distractor_3": "computer and fax"
      },
      {
        "id": "9153",
        "question": "What is the best way to clearly communicate a design idea?",
        "answer": "use standard symbols and dimensions in a drawing",
        "distractor_1": "use a detailed description of the process to create the design",
        "distractor_2": "use digital delivery",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9154",
        "question": "The intended audience, medium, purpose, and nature of the message are all factors in what part of a message?",
        "answer": "message design",
        "distractor_1": "message cost",
        "distractor_2": "message language",
        "distractor_3": "method of delivery"
      },
      {
        "id": "9155",
        "question": "Question",
        "answer": "Answer",
        "distractor_1": "Distractor 1",
        "distractor_2": "Distractor 2",
        "distractor_3": "Distractor 3"
      },
      {
        "id": "9156",
        "question": "In a communications system, which device changes the source information into a signal that can be transmitted?",
        "answer": "encoder",
        "distractor_1": "decoder",
        "distractor_2": "receiver",
        "distractor_3": "transmitter"
      },
      {
        "id": "9157",
        "question": "In a communications system, which device changes the signal's information into a message that can be understood by a human?",
        "answer": "decoder",
        "distractor_1": "encoder",
        "distractor_2": "receiver",
        "distractor_3": "transmitter"
      },
      {
        "id": "9158",
        "question": "How many dimensions are shown in an isometric drawing?",
        "answer": "three",
        "distractor_1": "two",
        "distractor_2": "one",
        "distractor_3": "Dimensions are not shown in an isometric drawing."
      },
      {
        "id": "9159",
        "question": "How do symbols, measurements, and drawings promote clear communication in expressing ideas?",
        "answer": "remove the language barrier",
        "distractor_1": "display all information in the same format",
        "distractor_2": "describe the shape of the idea",
        "distractor_3": "show the colors and how they blend together"
      },
      {
        "id": "9160",
        "question": "Because light waves travel in straight lines, how does fiber-optic cable transmit light through a curved cable?",
        "answer": "Total internal reflection bounces the light waves through the cable.",
        "distractor_1": "Electrons carry the light waves.",
        "distractor_2": "Transmitters resend the waves around turns.",
        "distractor_3": ""
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2045",
    "name": "Mining Mechanics",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9161",
        "question": "The Ring of Fire is a ring of volcanoes that surrounds the Atlantic.",
        "answer": "False",
        "distractor_1": "True",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9162",
        "question": "A mineral resource that can be mined for profit is an ore.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9163",
        "question": "Who proposed the theory of continental drift?",
        "answer": "Alfred Wegener",
        "distractor_1": "Harry Hess",
        "distractor_2": "Gregor Mendel",
        "distractor_3": "Charles Darwin"
      },
      {
        "id": "9164",
        "question": "Which is a theory that the Earth's crust and upper mantle are broken into sections?",
        "answer": "Plate Tectonics",
        "distractor_1": "Rock Cycle",
        "distractor_2": "Earthquakes",
        "distractor_3": "Continental Drift"
      },
      {
        "id": "9165",
        "question": "The Himalayas were formed by what process?",
        "answer": "Convergent boundary",
        "distractor_1": "Divergent boundary",
        "distractor_2": "Transform boundary",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9166",
        "question": "Which statement best describes the Earth's global distribution of natural resources?",
        "answer": "Natural resources are distributed unevenly around the Earth because natural formation processes occur at different rates depending on location and conditions.",
        "distractor_1": "Natural resources are distributed evenly around the Earth because natural formation processes occur at different rates depending on location and conditions.",
        "distractor_2": "Natural resources are distributed unevenly around the Earth because natural formation processes occur at the same rate everywhere.",
        "distractor_3": "Natural resources are distributed evenly around the Earth because natural formation processes occur at the same rate everywhere."
      },
      {
        "id": "9167",
        "question": "The first step in the process of mining materials from the earth is what?",
        "answer": "locating the material",
        "distractor_1": "obtaining legal rights to the land",
        "distractor_2": "obtaining permits",
        "distractor_3": "digging through the earth's crust"
      },
      {
        "id": "9168",
        "question": "Which of the following is usually the most time-consuming part of the mining process?",
        "answer": "locating the material",
        "distractor_1": "obtaining legal rights to the land",
        "distractor_2": "obtaining permits",
        "distractor_3": "digging through the earth's crust"
      },
      {
        "id": "9169",
        "question": "Two supply lines deliver equal amounts of Chemical A and Chemical B to a mixing container to make a compound. If a valve that controls the supply of Chemical A sticks shut, what is the result?",
        "answer": "Less Chemical A is released than is required.",
        "distractor_1": "More Chemical A is released than is required.",
        "distractor_2": "More Chemical B is released than is required.",
        "distractor_3": "Less Chemical B is released than is required."
      },
      {
        "id": "9170",
        "question": "When using systems thinking one must think of each part of the system as isolated from the other parts of the system.",
        "answer": "False",
        "distractor_1": "True",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9171",
        "question": "If a hydraulic system has a drive piston that is larger in diameter than the actuator piston, which of the following statements would be true?",
        "answer": "The force applied to the drive piston would be greater than the force supplied by the actuator piston.",
        "distractor_1": "The force applied to the drive piston would be the same as the force supplied by the actuator piston.",
        "distractor_2": "The force applied to the drive piston would be less than the force supplied by the actuator piston.",
        "distractor_3": "The two pistons are not connected and would not affect one another."
      },
      {
        "id": "9172",
        "question": "If a hydraulic system has a drive piston that is smaller in diameter than the actuator piston, which of the following statements would be true?",
        "answer": "The force applied to the drive piston would be less than the force supplied by the actuator piston.",
        "distractor_1": "The two pistons are not connected and would not affect one another.",
        "distractor_2": "The force applied to the drive piston would be the same as the force supplied by the actuator piston.",
        "distractor_3": "The force applied to the drive piston would be greater than the force supplied by the actuator piston."
      },
      {
        "id": "9173",
        "question": "Where are the most likely places to find mineral deposits on Earth?",
        "answer": "plate boundaries",
        "distractor_1": "mountaintops",
        "distractor_2": "rivers",
        "distractor_3": "islands"
      },
      {
        "id": "9174",
        "question": "Which of the following geologic formations are likely to have large mineral deposits?",
        "answer": "subduction zones",
        "distractor_1": "mountaintops",
        "distractor_2": "plains",
        "distractor_3": "hot springs"
      },
      {
        "id": "9175",
        "question": "In engineering, this happens when one attribute or quality is sacrificed for the sake of another.",
        "answer": "trade-off",
        "distractor_1": "ideation",
        "distractor_2": "substitution",
        "distractor_3": "patent"
      },
      {
        "id": "9176",
        "question": "Which is an example of an engineering trade-off?",
        "answer": "sacrificing strength to make a product weigh less",
        "distractor_1": "making a product safer",
        "distractor_2": "reducing the cost of a product",
        "distractor_3": "building a prototype of a product"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2046",
    "name": "Looks Like Rain",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9177",
        "question": "Which term refers to the amount of water vapor in the air?",
        "answer": "relative humidity",
        "distractor_1": "humidity",
        "distractor_2": "precipitation",
        "distractor_3": "dew point"
      },
      {
        "id": "9178",
        "question": "Which statement is an explanation rather than a description?",
        "answer": "The pond became smaller from evaporation.",
        "distractor_1": "The bird flaps its wings while it is flying.",
        "distractor_2": "The rock has many crystals in it.",
        "distractor_3": "The elephant weighs over 5 tons."
      },
      {
        "id": "9179",
        "question": "Which of the following makes up the greatest percentage of Earth's atmosphere?",
        "answer": "nitrogen and oxygen",
        "distractor_1": "oxygen and carbon",
        "distractor_2": "argon and oxygen",
        "distractor_3": "carbon and nitrogen"
      },
      {
        "id": "9180",
        "question": "Which of the following instruments would be best for measuring atmospheric pressure?",
        "answer": "barometer",
        "distractor_1": "thermometer",
        "distractor_2": "anemometer",
        "distractor_3": "rain gage"
      },
      {
        "id": "9181",
        "question": "Which index would be best to use for finding how relative humidity and temperature affect our comfort level?",
        "answer": "heat index",
        "distractor_1": "windchill index",
        "distractor_2": "S & P index",
        "distractor_3": "global index"
      },
      {
        "id": "9182",
        "question": "Which index would be best to use for finding how moving air and temperature affect our comfort level?",
        "answer": "windchill index",
        "distractor_1": "heat index",
        "distractor_2": "S & P index",
        "distractor_3": "global index"
      },
      {
        "id": "9183",
        "question": "When two air masses of different densities collide, it's called________.",
        "answer": "a front",
        "distractor_1": "a hurricane",
        "distractor_2": "a storm",
        "distractor_3": "a high pressure zone"
      },
      {
        "id": "9184",
        "question": "When the north end of the Earth's axis is tilted toward the sun, what will North America experience?",
        "answer": "more direct rays and longer days",
        "distractor_1": "more direct rays and shorter days",
        "distractor_2": "more indirect rays and longer days",
        "distractor_3": "more indirect rays and shorter days"
      },
      {
        "id": "9185",
        "question": "What types of clouds are the low clouds? (Up to 6,500 feet)",
        "answer": "Stratus",
        "distractor_1": "Alto",
        "distractor_2": "Cirrus",
        "distractor_3": "Mammatus"
      },
      {
        "id": "9186",
        "question": "What is the unit rate? $200 in 8 hours",
        "answer": "25 dollars per hour",
        "distractor_1": "1,600 dollars per hour",
        "distractor_2": "40 dollars per hour",
        "distractor_3": "16 dollars per hour"
      },
      {
        "id": "9187",
        "question": "What is the first layer of the atmosphere where most of our weather occurs called?",
        "answer": "Troposphere",
        "distractor_1": "Exosphere",
        "distractor_2": "Stratosphere",
        "distractor_3": "Mesosphere"
      },
      {
        "id": "9188",
        "question": "What is formed when southerly winds bring warm, moist air into a region, possibly ending a cold outbreak?",
        "answer": "fog",
        "distractor_1": "tornadoes",
        "distractor_2": "hurricanes",
        "distractor_3": "wind"
      },
      {
        "id": "9189",
        "question": "What does an anemometer measure?",
        "answer": "wind speed",
        "distractor_1": "precipitation",
        "distractor_2": "air pressure",
        "distractor_3": "relative humidity"
      },
      {
        "id": "9190",
        "question": "There are 30 red marbles and 150 blue marbles in a box. What is the ratio of blue marbles to red marbles?",
        "answer": "150 to 30",
        "distractor_1": "30 to 150",
        "distractor_2": "30 to 80",
        "distractor_3": "180 to 30"
      },
      {
        "id": "9191",
        "question": "The wind vane is used to measure air pressure.",
        "answer": "False",
        "distractor_1": "True",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9192",
        "question": "The disc used in a dog competition has a radius of 6 inches. Which of the following is closest to the circumference of the disc?",
        "answer": "36 inches",
        "distractor_1": "108 inches",
        "distractor_2": "18 inches",
        "distractor_3": "9 inches"
      },
      {
        "id": "9193",
        "question": "The best way to measure the volume of an irregular shaped solid is to",
        "answer": "the water displacement method",
        "distractor_1": "a triple beam balance",
        "distractor_2": "a spring scale",
        "distractor_3": "a ruler to measure the length of each side of the object"
      },
      {
        "id": "9194",
        "question": "Setting an outdoor rain gage under a tree will affect which of the following the most?",
        "answer": "accuracy",
        "distractor_1": "reliability",
        "distractor_2": "precision",
        "distractor_3": "significance"
      },
      {
        "id": "9195",
        "question": "Precipitation consisting of generally transparent frozen or partially frozen raindrops is called ________.",
        "answer": "sleet",
        "distractor_1": "hail",
        "distractor_2": "rain",
        "distractor_3": "snow"
      },
      {
        "id": "9196",
        "question": "Portland, Oregon is located along the coast of the northwestern United States. Several famous volcanoes, including Mount St. Helens and Mount Rainier, are located nearby. Portland normally has rainy, but mild winters. Yesterday, it rained 0.75 inch in Por",
        "answer": "Portland, Oregon is located along the coast of the northwestern United States.",
        "distractor_1": "Several famous volcanoes, including Mount St. Helens and Mount Rainier, are located nearby.",
        "distractor_2": "Portland normally has rainy, but mild winters.",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9197",
        "question": "In which atmospheric layer do meteors burn up?",
        "answer": "mesosphere",
        "distractor_1": "thermosphere",
        "distractor_2": "stratosphere",
        "distractor_3": "troposphere"
      },
      {
        "id": "9198",
        "question": "In Allen's last basketball game of the season, the ratio of free throws he made to the free throws he attempted was 12/18. Which is an equivalent ratio?",
        "answer": "4 to 6",
        "distractor_1": "12 to 9",
        "distractor_2": "6 to 12",
        "distractor_3": "2 to 18"
      },
      {
        "id": "9199",
        "question": "Imperial County, California earned the distinction of being the sunniest place in the United States based on data collected between 1979 - 2011. Does this statement describe weather or climate?",
        "answer": "climate",
        "distractor_1": "weather",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9200",
        "question": "How many cm are in a meter stick?",
        "answer": "100",
        "distractor_1": "50",
        "distractor_2": "10",
        "distractor_3": "1000"
      },
      {
        "id": "9201",
        "question": "How do you write 5% as a decimal number?",
        "answer": ".05",
        "distractor_1": ".5",
        "distractor_2": "5",
        "distractor_3": ".005"
      },
      {
        "id": "9202",
        "question": "Engineers often design and use tools and instruments for which of the following activities?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "creating a prototype",
        "distractor_2": "testing a product or solution",
        "distractor_3": "gathering data"
      },
      {
        "id": "9203",
        "question": "Earth rotates on its axis from",
        "answer": "west to east",
        "distractor_1": "east to west",
        "distractor_2": "north to south",
        "distractor_3": "south to north"
      },
      {
        "id": "9204",
        "question": "Car A travels 27 miles on 1.5 gallons of gas. Car B travels 35 miles on 2 gallons of gas. Which car gets the better mileage?",
        "answer": "Car A",
        "distractor_1": "Car B",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9205",
        "question": "Alyssa has 4 pairs of low-top sneakers, 7 pairs of high-top sneakers, 3 pairs of sandals, and 1 pair of boots. What is the ratio of the pairs of low-top sneakers to the total number of pairs of shoes?",
        "answer": "4 to 15",
        "distractor_1": "7 to 15",
        "distractor_2": "4 to 3",
        "distractor_3": "1 to 3"
      },
      {
        "id": "9206",
        "question": "A stationary front is when warm and cold air meet and neither mass has enough force to move the other.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9207",
        "question": "A class of 32 students has 12 girls. What is the ratio of girls to boys?",
        "answer": "3 to 5",
        "distractor_1": "8 to 3",
        "distractor_2": "3 to 8",
        "distractor_3": "5 to 3"
      },
      {
        "id": "9208",
        "question": "A _______________ measures the amount of rain that has fallen over a specific time period.",
        "answer": "rain gauge",
        "distractor_1": "thermometer",
        "distractor_2": "anemometer",
        "distractor_3": "wind vane"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2047",
    "name": "Optical Solutions",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9209",
        "question": "A reflecting telescope has a concave mirror that focuses light onto the focal plane.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9210",
        "question": "What is the highest point on a wave?",
        "answer": "crest",
        "distractor_1": "bones",
        "distractor_2": "wave",
        "distractor_3": "trough"
      },
      {
        "id": "9211",
        "question": "When a wave enters a new medium at an angle, what type of interaction occurs?",
        "answer": "refraction",
        "distractor_1": "reflection",
        "distractor_2": "diffraction",
        "distractor_3": "infraction"
      },
      {
        "id": "9212",
        "question": "You can see your image in a shiny, flat surface because light waves bounce directly back at you and your eyes. This is an example of",
        "answer": "reflection",
        "distractor_1": "refraction",
        "distractor_2": "diffraction",
        "distractor_3": "transparency"
      },
      {
        "id": "9213",
        "question": "What is the change in direction of a wave as the wave travels from one medium to another?",
        "answer": "refraction",
        "distractor_1": "reflection",
        "distractor_2": "absorption",
        "distractor_3": "interference"
      },
      {
        "id": "9214",
        "question": "What is the distance from one crest of a wave to the next crest of the wave?",
        "answer": "wavelength",
        "distractor_1": "amplitude",
        "distractor_2": "frequency",
        "distractor_3": "equilibrium point"
      },
      {
        "id": "9215",
        "question": "What light wave feature relates to the intensity of the light and also the amount of energy being carried by the light wave?",
        "answer": "amplitude",
        "distractor_1": "wavelength",
        "distractor_2": "frequency",
        "distractor_3": "crest"
      },
      {
        "id": "9216",
        "question": "Which is the best description of why a leaf appears green?",
        "answer": "The leaf absorbs all wavelengths of light except green. Green wavelengths are reflected by the leaf.",
        "distractor_1": "The leaf reflects all wavelengths of light except green. Green wavelengths are transmitted by the leaf.",
        "distractor_2": "The leaf transmits all wavelengths of light except green. Green wavelengths are absorbed by the leaf.",
        "distractor_3": "The leaf reflects all wavelengths of light except green. Green wavelengths are absorbed by the leaf."
      },
      {
        "id": "9217",
        "question": "Why does a black object appear black?",
        "answer": "The object absorbs all wavelengths of light.",
        "distractor_1": "The object transmits all wavelengths of light.",
        "distractor_2": "The object reflects all wavelengths of light.",
        "distractor_3": "The object reflects black light and absorbs all other colors."
      },
      {
        "id": "9218",
        "question": "It is a mixture of all the colors of the rainbow, different colors are the result of different wavelengths. What is it called?",
        "answer": "visible light",
        "distractor_1": "infrared radiation",
        "distractor_2": "ultraviolet radiation",
        "distractor_3": "scattering"
      },
      {
        "id": "9219",
        "question": "What is the distance between two consecutive crests or troughs called?",
        "answer": "wavelength",
        "distractor_1": "amplitude",
        "distractor_2": "frequency",
        "distractor_3": "speed"
      },
      {
        "id": "9220",
        "question": "A disturbance that travels through a medium, transporting energy from one location to another location is ________.",
        "answer": "a wave",
        "distractor_1": "a sound",
        "distractor_2": "light",
        "distractor_3": "frequency"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2048",
    "name": "Ahead of the Game",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9221",
        "question": "A force can act only by touching.",
        "answer": "False",
        "distractor_1": "True",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9222",
        "question": "The greater the mass of an object the greater the momentum.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9223",
        "question": "________ is done on an object when the object moves in the same direction in which the force is exerted.",
        "answer": "work",
        "distractor_1": "force",
        "distractor_2": "distance",
        "distractor_3": "power"
      },
      {
        "id": "9224",
        "question": "Which of the following illustrates the usefulness of friction?",
        "answer": "Friction helps us to walk on ground.",
        "distractor_1": "Friction can damage car wheels.",
        "distractor_2": "Friction can cause burnings.",
        "distractor_3": "Friction helps machines to do work."
      },
      {
        "id": "9225",
        "question": "What does an object need to change its motion?",
        "answer": "force",
        "distractor_1": "mass",
        "distractor_2": "size",
        "distractor_3": "length"
      },
      {
        "id": "9226",
        "question": "Which of the following forces stops an object from moving at constant speed continually?",
        "answer": "friction",
        "distractor_1": "gravity",
        "distractor_2": "magnetism",
        "distractor_3": "sliding force"
      },
      {
        "id": "9227",
        "question": "________is the tendency of an object to remain at rest or in constant motion unless a force acts on it.",
        "answer": "inertia",
        "distractor_1": "gravity",
        "distractor_2": "friction",
        "distractor_3": "acceleration"
      },
      {
        "id": "9228",
        "question": "Which cart needs the smallest force to move?",
        "answer": "A 1 kg cart",
        "distractor_1": "A 150 kg cart",
        "distractor_2": "A 40 kg cart",
        "distractor_3": "A 10 kg cart"
      },
      {
        "id": "9229",
        "question": "What kind of force makes it difficult to start moving an object?",
        "answer": "static friction",
        "distractor_1": "heat friction",
        "distractor_2": "rolling friction",
        "distractor_3": "sliding friction"
      },
      {
        "id": "9230",
        "question": "When a ball hits the ground it bounces. What is this an example of?",
        "answer": "Newton's Third Law",
        "distractor_1": "Newton's Second Law",
        "distractor_2": "Newton's First Law",
        "distractor_3": "Gravitational Law"
      },
      {
        "id": "9231",
        "question": "The larger the mass of an object, the greater ________there is between the object and the surface the object is pressing on.",
        "answer": "friction",
        "distractor_1": "repulsion",
        "distractor_2": "gravity",
        "distractor_3": "mass"
      },
      {
        "id": "9232",
        "question": "When you are pulling a sheet of paper from under a cup, what property is exhibited by the cup not moving?",
        "answer": "inertia",
        "distractor_1": "momentum",
        "distractor_2": "friction",
        "distractor_3": "mass"
      },
      {
        "id": "9233",
        "question": "When you are pulling a sheet of paper from under a cup, what is increased when mass is added to the cup?",
        "answer": "inertia",
        "distractor_1": "gravity",
        "distractor_2": "volume",
        "distractor_3": "static electricity"
      },
      {
        "id": "9234",
        "question": "What reasons can be given for the increase in size of athletes?",
        "answer": "nutrition and training",
        "distractor_1": "genetics and training",
        "distractor_2": "nutrition and genetics",
        "distractor_3": "equipment and training"
      },
      {
        "id": "9235",
        "question": "How does traumatic brain injury occur?",
        "answer": "the brain striking the inside of the skull",
        "distractor_1": "a high-speed impact on the head",
        "distractor_2": "a car accident",
        "distractor_3": "a severe blow to the head"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2049",
    "name": "Artificial Ecosystems",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9237",
        "question": "What is an ecosystem composed of?",
        "answer": "living and nonliving matter",
        "distractor_1": "only nonliving matter",
        "distractor_2": "only living matter",
        "distractor_3": "neither living nor nonliving matter"
      },
      {
        "id": "9238",
        "question": "What do plants use to trap the sun's energy for photosynthesis?",
        "answer": "chlorophyll",
        "distractor_1": "glucose",
        "distractor_2": "oxygen",
        "distractor_3": "carbon dioxide"
      },
      {
        "id": "9239",
        "question": "Where do plants get water from?",
        "answer": "rain, transpiration, and absorption",
        "distractor_1": "rain and absorption",
        "distractor_2": "transpiration and evaporation",
        "distractor_3": "rain and transpiration"
      },
      {
        "id": "9240",
        "question": "What does photosynthesis convert carbon dioxide and water into?",
        "answer": "glucose and oxygen",
        "distractor_1": "carbon monoxide and water",
        "distractor_2": "acids and bases",
        "distractor_3": "sodium bicarbonate"
      },
      {
        "id": "9241",
        "question": "What is the interaction among organisms in an ecosystem?",
        "answer": "Organisms depend on each other to support life.",
        "distractor_1": "There is no interaction.",
        "distractor_2": "Plants grow independent of any animal activity in the ecosystem.",
        "distractor_3": "Animals eat plants, but plants do not need animals for survival."
      },
      {
        "id": "9242",
        "question": "What does acidity of soil do?",
        "answer": "It has a different impact based on the type and nutritional needs of the plant.",
        "distractor_1": "It changes the colors of the flowers on plants.",
        "distractor_2": "It enables all plants to exceed normal growth.",
        "distractor_3": "It has no impact on the growth of plant matter."
      },
      {
        "id": "9243",
        "question": "Which of these statements best describes contents of soil that encourage good plant growth?",
        "answer": "Rich soil has rock and clay particles, decaying plants and animals, and trace minerals.",
        "distractor_1": "There is no matter contained in soil that is beneficial for plants.",
        "distractor_2": "The only nutritional value in soil is from man-made fertilizers.",
        "distractor_3": "Large limestone chunks are the most nutrient-rich soil material to grow plants."
      },
      {
        "id": "9244",
        "question": "How does photosynthesis use energy?",
        "answer": "Energy from the sun is part of the chemical reaction converting carbon dioxide and water to glucose and oxygen.",
        "distractor_1": "Energy from the soil is used to create plant growth.",
        "distractor_2": "Energy is a by-product of photosynthesis to create more leaves.",
        "distractor_3": "Photosynthesis does not use energy."
      },
      {
        "id": "9245",
        "question": "Plant water needs are determined by which of the following conditions?",
        "answer": "Plants have differing needs for water based on the type of plant, soil, and exposure to the sun.",
        "distractor_1": "The type of plant does not matter – all plants have the same need for water.",
        "distractor_2": "All plants need water that has been filtered through plant and animal matter.",
        "distractor_3": "Water that has been exposed to mass amounts of ultraviolet light is the only water plants need."
      },
      {
        "id": "9246",
        "question": "How are minerals in the soil absorbed into plants?",
        "answer": "The minerals are dissolved and carried into the plant cells through the absorption of water.",
        "distractor_1": "They remain in one state and plant roots grow into the mineral to get the nourishment.",
        "distractor_2": "They are in a constant liquid state to be absorbed by the plant.",
        "distractor_3": "They undergo large amounts of heat and pressure to be forced into the plant roots."
      },
      {
        "id": "9247",
        "question": "A successful artificial ecosystem would require which of the following?",
        "answer": "a correct balance of producers and consumers to allow for proper cycling of nutrients and raw materials",
        "distractor_1": "Nothing; an artificial ecosystem cannot be built.",
        "distractor_2": "large buildings and water refinement plants to support human lifestyles",
        "distractor_3": "a carefully controlled light, temperature, and moisture environment"
      },
      {
        "id": "9248",
        "question": "How do dying plants affect ecosystems?",
        "answer": "by decaying and replenishing nutrients in the soil",
        "distractor_1": "by removing oxygen from the environment",
        "distractor_2": "Plants dying have no effect on the system.",
        "distractor_3": "Plants do not die in ecosystems."
      },
      {
        "id": "9249",
        "question": "How large can an ecosystem be?",
        "answer": "The term ecosystem does not apply to biological interactions.",
        "distractor_1": "An ecosystem can vary in size from very small to very large.",
        "distractor_2": "An ecosystem is measured only in microscopic terms.",
        "distractor_3": "An area must be large to be classified as an ecosystem."
      },
      {
        "id": "9250",
        "question": "What is a quality of soil that does not contain decaying plant matter or living organisms?",
        "answer": "It lacks the nutrients and minerals for good plant growth.",
        "distractor_1": "It makes it easier for plants to absorb minerals.",
        "distractor_2": "It makes it easier for plants to absorb minerals.",
        "distractor_3": "It provides the best medium for tree growth."
      },
      {
        "id": "9251",
        "question": "Which of these statements about water is true?",
        "answer": "Water is required for photosynthesis.",
        "distractor_1": "Water is a by-product of photosynthesis.",
        "distractor_2": "Water is not required to maintain plant life.",
        "distractor_3": "Water is gathered by the plant only from the air."
      },
      {
        "id": "9252",
        "question": "How do cellular respiration and photosynthesis compare?",
        "answer": "Cellular respiration is chemically the opposite of photosynthesis, producing water and carbon dioxide.",
        "distractor_1": "Cellular respiration has no chemical reaction, and photosynthesis uses energy gained through glucose absorption.",
        "distractor_2": "Photosynthesis has no chemical reaction, and cellular respiration uses energy gained through glucose absorption.",
        "distractor_3": "Neither cellular respiration nor photosynthesis use sunlight for the reaction."
      },
      {
        "id": "9253",
        "question": "In plant growth, how is matter generated?",
        "answer": "photosynthesis and the carbon cycle",
        "distractor_1": "dirt-generated magnesium deposits",
        "distractor_2": "sodium immersion",
        "distractor_3": "water deprivation"
      },
      {
        "id": "9254",
        "question": "What is the relationship between an ecosystem and a biome?",
        "answer": "There can be multiple ecosystems in a biome.",
        "distractor_1": "They are totally different and one does not have a relationship to the other.",
        "distractor_2": "A biome contains a planet, that planet's moon, and the two neighboring planets.",
        "distractor_3": "There is only one biome in an ecosystem."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2050",
    "name": "Growing Up",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9255",
        "question": "Where does all energy for life on Earth originate?",
        "answer": "sunlight",
        "distractor_1": "water",
        "distractor_2": "animals",
        "distractor_3": "plants"
      },
      {
        "id": "9256",
        "question": "Which of the following building subsystems would you not expect to find in a bathroom?",
        "answer": "gas",
        "distractor_1": "sewer",
        "distractor_2": "electric",
        "distractor_3": "water"
      },
      {
        "id": "9257",
        "question": "Which of the following activities would have the greatest effect on the Japanese spruce population?",
        "answer": "deforestation",
        "distractor_1": "hunting",
        "distractor_2": "one week of rain",
        "distractor_3": "one week of no rain"
      },
      {
        "id": "9258",
        "question": "A shrimp eats plankton and is eaten by a fish. The fish is eaten by a bird. Which of these events would be most likely to interrupt this food chain?",
        "answer": "fishing by a human",
        "distractor_1": "a bird eating a worm",
        "distractor_2": "one week of rain",
        "distractor_3": "one week of no rain"
      },
      {
        "id": "9259",
        "question": "A government uses kudzu plants to help with soil erosion. The kudzu begins growing so rapidly that it kills all the native plants and trees in the area. This is an example of ____.",
        "answer": "an invasive species",
        "distractor_1": "deforestation",
        "distractor_2": "overhunting",
        "distractor_3": "mutualism"
      },
      {
        "id": "9260",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a basic requirement for plant growth?",
        "answer": "pollution",
        "distractor_1": "air",
        "distractor_2": "water",
        "distractor_3": "light"
      },
      {
        "id": "9261",
        "question": "Which of the following statements is true for flow rate as it relates to the diameter of a pipe?",
        "answer": "As diameter increases, the flow rate increases.",
        "distractor_1": "As diameter increases, the flow rate decreases.",
        "distractor_2": "As diameter increases, the flow rate stays the same.",
        "distractor_3": "There is no relationship between flow rate and pipe diameter."
      },
      {
        "id": "9262",
        "question": "What is the unit rate? $200 in 8 hours",
        "answer": "25 dollars per hour",
        "distractor_1": "1,600 dollars per hour",
        "distractor_2": "40 dollars per hour",
        "distractor_3": "16 dollars per hour"
      },
      {
        "id": "9263",
        "question": "Which of the following best describes the relationship between ants who eat the nectar from an acacia tree and the tree that benefits from the protection by the ants?",
        "answer": "mutualism",
        "distractor_1": "commensalism",
        "distractor_2": "parasitism",
        "distractor_3": "competition"
      },
      {
        "id": "9264",
        "question": "There are 30 red marbles and 150 blue marbles in a box. What is the ratio of blue marbles to red marbles?",
        "answer": "150/30",
        "distractor_1": "30/150",
        "distractor_2": "30/80",
        "distractor_3": "180/30"
      },
      {
        "id": "9265",
        "question": "Which of the following best describes the relationship between ticks that receive blood from a dog and the dog that becomes irritated or infected?",
        "answer": "parasitism",
        "distractor_1": "competition",
        "distractor_2": "commensalism",
        "distractor_3": "mutualism"
      },
      {
        "id": "9266",
        "question": "Which of the following building subsystems would you not expect to find in an aquaponic vertical farm?",
        "answer": "security",
        "distractor_1": "air",
        "distractor_2": "electric",
        "distractor_3": "water"
      },
      {
        "id": "9267",
        "question": "A shrimp eats plankton and is eaten by a fish. The fish is eaten by a bird. If 100 units of energy are supplied to the plankton, how many units will be supplied to the bird?",
        "answer": "1 unit",
        "distractor_1": "10 units",
        "distractor_2": "100 units",
        "distractor_3": "1,000 units"
      },
      {
        "id": "9268",
        "question": "Which of the following activities would have the greatest effect on the African elephant population?",
        "answer": "hunters killing elephants for their tusks",
        "distractor_1": "one week of rain",
        "distractor_2": "field mice eating wheat",
        "distractor_3": "gold mining"
      },
      {
        "id": "9269",
        "question": "Alyssa has 4 pairs of low-top sneakers, 7 pairs of high-top sneakers, 3 pairs of sandals, and 1 pair of boots. What is the ratio of the pairs of low-top sneakers to the total number of pairs of shoes?",
        "answer": "4 to 15",
        "distractor_1": "7 to 15",
        "distractor_2": "4 to 3",
        "distractor_3": "1 to 3"
      },
      {
        "id": "9270",
        "question": "A zebra mussel attaches itself to the hull of a boat and is transported to another lake. It detaches at the next lake and begins to multiply so much that the mussels clog drainage pipes into the lake. This is an example of ____.",
        "answer": "an invasive species",
        "distractor_1": "deforestation",
        "distractor_2": "overhunting",
        "distractor_3": "mutualism"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2051",
    "name": "Body Blueprint",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9271",
        "question": "If an image on a micrograph is 125 pixels wide and the conversion factor for a micrograph at that magnification is 0.1 mm = 100 pixels, what is the width of the image in mm?",
        "answer": "0.125 mm",
        "distractor_1": "1.25 mm",
        "distractor_2": "12.5 mm",
        "distractor_3": "125 mm"
      },
      {
        "id": "9272",
        "question": "Which of the listed engineering steps would you use to brainstorm ways to use series circuits in a building?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Create",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "9273",
        "question": "'The motor cannot exceed 1,000 rpm' is a statement that describes which of the following?",
        "answer": "constraint",
        "distractor_1": "specification",
        "distractor_2": "both",
        "distractor_3": "neither"
      },
      {
        "id": "9274",
        "question": "What is the name for a group of cells that work together to perform a similar function?",
        "answer": "Tissue",
        "distractor_1": "Molecule",
        "distractor_2": "Organelle",
        "distractor_3": "Cell"
      },
      {
        "id": "9275",
        "question": "All matter is made up of tiny particles that cannot be divided any smaller andmaintain their unique properties. These particles are called?",
        "answer": "Atoms",
        "distractor_1": "Neutrons",
        "distractor_2": "Protons",
        "distractor_3": "Electrons"
      },
      {
        "id": "9276",
        "question": "Which engineering step would most likely include the building of a three-dimensional prototype?",
        "answer": "Create",
        "distractor_1": "Plan",
        "distractor_2": "Imagine",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "9277",
        "question": "After testing a prototype in relation to its requirements, which of the following engineering steps would you do next if you wanted to build a new prototype?",
        "answer": "Create",
        "distractor_1": "Imagine",
        "distractor_2": "Ask",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "9278",
        "question": "Which list contains the levels of organization in order from largest to smallest?",
        "answer": "Organism, organ systems, organs, tissues, cells, organelles, molecules, atoms",
        "distractor_1": "Organism, organ systems, organs, organelles, tissues, cells, molecules, atoms",
        "distractor_2": "Atoms, molecules, cells, tissues, organelles, organs, organ systems, organism",
        "distractor_3": "Atoms, molecules, organelles, cells, tissues, organs, organ systems, organism"
      },
      {
        "id": "9279",
        "question": "Which of the macromolecules provides a long-term storage form for energy and structurally is glycerol and three fatty acid chains?",
        "answer": "Lipids",
        "distractor_1": "Proteins",
        "distractor_2": "Nucleic Acids",
        "distractor_3": "Carbohydrates"
      },
      {
        "id": "9280",
        "question": "Modifying a vehicle's engine to get better gas mileage would most likely occur at which step of the engineering design process?",
        "answer": "Improve",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Imagine",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "9281",
        "question": "After testing a prototype in relation to its requirements, which of the following engineering steps would you do next if you wanted to refine it?",
        "answer": "Improve",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Imagine",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "9282",
        "question": "After testing a prototype in relation to its requirements, which of the following engineering steps would you do next if you wanted to brainstorm ways to make it better?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Improve",
        "distractor_2": "Create",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "9283",
        "question": "The body system that gathers and interprets information from internal and external environments and responds to that information is called the ________.",
        "answer": "Nervous System",
        "distractor_1": "Skeletal System",
        "distractor_2": "Digestive System",
        "distractor_3": "Circulatory System"
      },
      {
        "id": "9284",
        "question": "The smallest unit of life is called what?",
        "answer": "Cell",
        "distractor_1": "Organelle",
        "distractor_2": "Molecule",
        "distractor_3": "Atom"
      },
      {
        "id": "9285",
        "question": "Which list contains the levels of organization in order from smallest to largest?",
        "answer": "Atoms, molecules, cells, tissues, organelles, organs, organ systems, organism",
        "distractor_1": "Atoms, molecules, organelles, cells, tissues, organs, organ systems, organism",
        "distractor_2": "Organism, organ systems, organs, tissues, cells, organelles, molecules, atoms",
        "distractor_3": "Organism, organ systems, organs, organelles, tissues, cells, molecules, atoms"
      },
      {
        "id": "9286",
        "question": "Which of the macromolecules is responsible for passing genetic information from one generation to the next?",
        "answer": "Nucleic Acids",
        "distractor_1": "Carbohydrates",
        "distractor_2": "Lipids",
        "distractor_3": "Proteins"
      },
      {
        "id": "9287",
        "question": "Which list contains all four of the major classes of macromolecules?",
        "answer": "Lipids, Nucleic Acids, Proteins, Carbohydrates",
        "distractor_1": "Proteins, Water, Nucleic Acids, Lipids",
        "distractor_2": "Carbohydrates, Water, Proteins, Lipids",
        "distractor_3": "Nucleic Acids, Carbohydrates, Proteins, Water"
      },
      {
        "id": "9288",
        "question": "Which of the following activities would be best used to justify an answer to the question, 'What effect does load have on a motor?'",
        "answer": "experimentation",
        "distractor_1": "innovation",
        "distractor_2": "research",
        "distractor_3": "troubleshooting"
      },
      {
        "id": "9289",
        "question": "If an image on a micrograph is 145 pixels wide and the conversion factor for a micrograph at that magnification is 1 mm = 100 pixels, what is the width of the image in mm?",
        "answer": "1.45 mm",
        "distractor_1": "0.145 mm",
        "distractor_2": "14.5 mm",
        "distractor_3": "145 mm"
      },
      {
        "id": "9290",
        "question": "Which of the macromolecules are the building blocks of all living things and can also act as enzymes in chemical reactions?",
        "answer": "Proteins",
        "distractor_1": "Lipids",
        "distractor_2": "Nucleic Acids",
        "distractor_3": "Carbohydrates"
      },
      {
        "id": "9291",
        "question": "'The solar panel cannot exceed 2 m x 4 m' is a statement that describes which of the following?",
        "answer": "constraint",
        "distractor_1": "specification",
        "distractor_2": "both",
        "distractor_3": "neither"
      },
      {
        "id": "9292",
        "question": "Which engineering step would most likely include the making of a two-dimensional route on a map for a truck to follow?",
        "answer": "Create",
        "distractor_1": "Plan",
        "distractor_2": "Imagine",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "9293",
        "question": "Which of the macromolecules functions to provide a usable form and energy for cells and as support in some plant cells?",
        "answer": "Carbohydrates",
        "distractor_1": "Nucleic Acids",
        "distractor_2": "Lipids",
        "distractor_3": "Proteins"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2052",
    "name": "A Closer Look",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9294",
        "question": "Why did Whittaker believe fungi belonged in a separate kingdom?",
        "answer": "because they do not contain chlorophyll and cannot create their own food",
        "distractor_1": "because they are decomposers",
        "distractor_2": "because they contain chlorophyll and can produce their own food",
        "distractor_3": "because they all have pseudopods"
      },
      {
        "id": "9295",
        "question": "Which characteristic separates prokaryotes from eukaryotes?",
        "answer": "Eukaryotes contain organelles surrounded by a membrane.",
        "distractor_1": "Prokaryotes contain organelles surrounded by a membrane.",
        "distractor_2": "Eukaryotes are multicellular.",
        "distractor_3": "Prokaryotes are multicellular."
      },
      {
        "id": "9296",
        "question": "What is a pseudopod?",
        "answer": "false foot on an organism",
        "distractor_1": "location of food storage for bacteria",
        "distractor_2": "location of the seed in a plant organism",
        "distractor_3": "duplicate foot on an organism"
      },
      {
        "id": "9297",
        "question": "Members of which phylum of algae have complex two-part shells made of reflective silica?",
        "answer": "diatoms",
        "distractor_1": "euglenas",
        "distractor_2": "dinoflagellates",
        "distractor_3": "green algae"
      },
      {
        "id": "9298",
        "question": "To make it easy to find your files, save them to a ________.",
        "answer": "folder or directory on your hard drive",
        "distractor_1": "disk on hard drive",
        "distractor_2": "drawer on your hard drive",
        "distractor_3": "cabinet on your hard drive"
      },
      {
        "id": "9299",
        "question": "What was the main contribution of Carolus Linnaeus to taxonomy?",
        "answer": "He developed binomial nomenclature.",
        "distractor_1": "He made great improvements in microscopes.",
        "distractor_2": "He developed the two-kingdom classification system.",
        "distractor_3": "He developed the five-kingdom classification system."
      },
      {
        "id": "9300",
        "question": "________ is a structure in the nucleus that contains hereditary material.",
        "answer": "Chromosome",
        "distractor_1": "Protein",
        "distractor_2": "Enzyme",
        "distractor_3": "DNA"
      },
      {
        "id": "9301",
        "question": "Aristotle classified animals using which of the following factors?",
        "answer": "habitat and type of movement",
        "distractor_1": "size and color",
        "distractor_2": "type of skin and hair",
        "distractor_3": "type of movement and method of obtaining food"
      },
      {
        "id": "9302",
        "question": "What term is described as classifying organisms?",
        "answer": "taxonomy",
        "distractor_1": "taxidermy",
        "distractor_2": "classonomy",
        "distractor_3": "orgonomy"
      },
      {
        "id": "9303",
        "question": "The ________ are responsible for transporting materials around the cell. They often have ribosomes attached to them.",
        "answer": "endoplasmic reticulum",
        "distractor_1": "chloroplasts",
        "distractor_2": "mitochondria",
        "distractor_3": "cell membrane"
      },
      {
        "id": "9304",
        "question": "Bacteria is never beneficial to humans.",
        "answer": "False",
        "distractor_1": "True",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9305",
        "question": "Bacteria are not useful in the production of food products.",
        "answer": "False",
        "distractor_1": "True",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9306",
        "question": "What is the total magnification of a compound microscope with a 10X eyepiece and a 40X objective lens?",
        "answer": "400X",
        "distractor_1": "4X",
        "distractor_2": "40X",
        "distractor_3": "50X"
      },
      {
        "id": "9307",
        "question": "How is the total magnification of a compound microscope determined?",
        "answer": "by multiplying the magnification of the objective lens by the magnification of the eyepiece lens",
        "distractor_1": "by dividing the magnification of the objective lens by the magnification of the eyepiece lens",
        "distractor_2": "by subtracting the magnification of the eyepiece lens from the magnification of the objective lens",
        "distractor_3": "by adding the magnification of the eyepiece lens to the magnification of the objective lens"
      },
      {
        "id": "9308",
        "question": "Antibiotics kill bacteria in different ways. Which is not a method used by antibiotics to kill bacteria?",
        "answer": "interfere with the ability of the nucleus to split",
        "distractor_1": "interfere with the building and repair of DNA chains",
        "distractor_2": "interfere with creating proteins",
        "distractor_3": "interfere with creating a strong cell wall"
      },
      {
        "id": "9309",
        "question": "Binomial nomenclature uses two names to identify an organism. Which two classifications are used in binomial nomenclature?",
        "answer": "genus and species",
        "distractor_1": "class and order",
        "distractor_2": "domain and class",
        "distractor_3": "kingdom and species"
      },
      {
        "id": "9310",
        "question": "All animal and plant cells are the same.",
        "answer": "False",
        "distractor_1": "True",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9311",
        "question": "Bacteria are tiny living creatures which are smaller than human body cells and less than 1 thousandth of a millimeter long.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9312",
        "question": "Which tool would you use to label the photo you took using the microscope you built?",
        "answer": "text tool",
        "distractor_1": "focus tool",
        "distractor_2": "arrow tool",
        "distractor_3": "circle tool"
      },
      {
        "id": "9313",
        "question": "What was the main contribution of Carolus Linnaeus to taxonomy?",
        "answer": "He developed binomial nomenclature.",
        "distractor_1": "He made great improvements in microscopes.",
        "distractor_2": "He developed the two-kingdom classification system.",
        "distractor_3": "He developed the five-kingdom classification system."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2053",
    "name": "Dynamic Disasters",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9314",
        "question": "Building designers will often sacrifice design for what reason?",
        "answer": "to save money on the project",
        "distractor_1": "to make the building look boring",
        "distractor_2": "to keep the skyline looking natural",
        "distractor_3": "An artistic design does not allow for function in a building."
      },
      {
        "id": "9315",
        "question": "When should you plan for a disaster?",
        "answer": "You should plan and practice for a disaster before a disaster happens so you know what to do.",
        "distractor_1": "You should plan as the disaster happens.",
        "distractor_2": "You should plan after the damage is done. Any earlier and you don't know what you are planning for.",
        "distractor_3": "Listen to the news and plan to take action just prior to the disaster striking."
      },
      {
        "id": "9316",
        "question": "What is the fastest calculated wind speed for tornadoes?",
        "answer": "The fastest calculated wind speed for a tornado is more than 300 miles per hour.",
        "distractor_1": "Tornado wind speeds are not calculated but are measured with simple instruments.",
        "distractor_2": "Calculated wind speeds for tornadoes have been measured at no more than 150 miles per hour.",
        "distractor_3": "Tornadoes have calculated wind speeds similar to light breezes."
      },
      {
        "id": "9317",
        "question": "What is a leading cause of earthquakes?",
        "answer": "shifting tectonic plates",
        "distractor_1": "excess underground coal mining",
        "distractor_2": "snow avalanches",
        "distractor_3": "failure of large industrial engines"
      },
      {
        "id": "9318",
        "question": "To turn off the gas to a house that has been damaged by a disaster, which tool mustyou have?",
        "answer": "adjustable wrench",
        "distractor_1": "chisel",
        "distractor_2": "screwdriver",
        "distractor_3": "hammer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9319",
        "question": "The time it takes to form a mountain through tectonic plate movement is measured in what units?",
        "answer": "thousands of years",
        "distractor_1": "centuries",
        "distractor_2": "weeks",
        "distractor_3": "days"
      },
      {
        "id": "9320",
        "question": "Which of the following affects climate patterns?",
        "answer": "ocean currents",
        "distractor_1": "oil well production",
        "distractor_2": "tectonic plate movement",
        "distractor_3": "underground salt mines"
      },
      {
        "id": "9321",
        "question": "What is the difference between a hurricane, cyclone, and typhoon?",
        "answer": "The structure of each is the same; their location on Earth is different.",
        "distractor_1": "Hurricanes cause damage; cyclones and typhoons do not.",
        "distractor_2": "Typhoon is the term used for a storm at Earth's poles.",
        "distractor_3": "Cyclone is another term for a tropical storm with light breezes."
      },
      {
        "id": "9322",
        "question": "Which factor is identified as a major contributor to the rise in CO2 levels in the 20th century?",
        "answer": "fossil fuel power",
        "distractor_1": "solar power",
        "distractor_2": "wind power",
        "distractor_3": "nuclear power"
      },
      {
        "id": "9323",
        "question": "A building is supported in strong winds by which system?",
        "answer": "foundation",
        "distractor_1": "electrical",
        "distractor_2": "plumbing",
        "distractor_3": "HVAC"
      },
      {
        "id": "9324",
        "question": "How does a tuned mass dampener help a building avoid earthquake damage?",
        "answer": "A tuned mass dampener counteracts the vibration of the building, reducing stress on the supporting structure.",
        "distractor_1": "A tuned mass dampener is only effective against hurricane force winds.",
        "distractor_2": "A tuned mass dampener absorbs the vibrations like a sponge so the vibrations are not carried through the cable to the foundation.",
        "distractor_3": "A tuned mass dampener is a fictional device."
      },
      {
        "id": "9325",
        "question": "When a building is struck by wind or an earthquake, what destructive event happens that can cause the building to fall?",
        "answer": "harmonic vibrations",
        "distractor_1": "flexible construction",
        "distractor_2": "a sturdy foundation",
        "distractor_3": "a tuned mass dampener"
      },
      {
        "id": "9326",
        "question": "Where is the best place to take shelter if you are under a tornado warning?",
        "answer": "a basement or tornado shelter",
        "distractor_1": "outside watching so you know when the damage will happen",
        "distractor_2": "the uppermost story of your house near a window",
        "distractor_3": "the largest room of a trailer house"
      },
      {
        "id": "9327",
        "question": "A storm shelter is designed to withstand the damage of what kind of wind?",
        "answer": "an EF-5 tornado",
        "distractor_1": "a New England summer gale",
        "distractor_2": "a tropical breeze",
        "distractor_3": "a solar wind"
      },
      {
        "id": "9328",
        "question": "What do dam failures and mudslides have in common?",
        "answer": "A large amount of rain or snow melt in a short time creates excessive water pressure and flooding, causing the event.",
        "distractor_1": "Cyclic periods of average rainfall followed by a continued lack of rainfall weakens thesubsoil, causing the event.",
        "distractor_2": "There is nothing in common between dam failures and mudslides.",
        "distractor_3": "Both are strictly a man-made phenomenon."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2054",
    "name": "Get a Grip",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9329",
        "question": "Which of the following technologies was developed because of a need for building astrong shelter?",
        "answer": "ax",
        "distractor_1": "plow",
        "distractor_2": "truck",
        "distractor_3": "steam engine"
      },
      {
        "id": "9330",
        "question": "A plastic bottle is manufactured using petroleum products through a process thatuses chemical reactions. If the bottle is not recycled and is thrown away with regular trash, it is placed in a dump or burned. What would the petroleum be considered in this",
        "answer": "a natural resource",
        "distractor_1": "an element",
        "distractor_2": "a synthetic material",
        "distractor_3": "an atom"
      },
      {
        "id": "9331",
        "question": "Which of the following technologies was developed because of a need for makingwaterproof material?",
        "answer": "vinyl",
        "distractor_1": "plow",
        "distractor_2": "truck",
        "distractor_3": "paper"
      },
      {
        "id": "9332",
        "question": "Who invented the moveable printing press?",
        "answer": "Johan Gutenberg",
        "distractor_1": "Benjamin Franklin",
        "distractor_2": "Thomas Edison",
        "distractor_3": "Albert Einstein"
      },
      {
        "id": "9333",
        "question": "Developing new products and systems to solve problems and meet needs is the goalof what?",
        "answer": "technology",
        "distractor_1": "math",
        "distractor_2": "science",
        "distractor_3": "government"
      },
      {
        "id": "9334",
        "question": "Which of the following technologies was developed because of a need for growinglarge amounts of wheat?",
        "answer": "plow",
        "distractor_1": "airplane",
        "distractor_2": "truck",
        "distractor_3": "clock"
      },
      {
        "id": "9335",
        "question": "If three carbon atoms chemically react with six oxygen atoms, how many totalatoms will there be after the reaction?",
        "answer": "9",
        "distractor_1": "2",
        "distractor_2": "3",
        "distractor_3": "6"
      },
      {
        "id": "9336",
        "question": "After tennis shoes have been used, some are recycled to make rubberized playgrounds or tracks. Others are thrown in the trash to be dumped in a landfill. Which use would be considered a desirable outcome?",
        "answer": "recycling",
        "distractor_1": "dumping",
        "distractor_2": "both",
        "distractor_3": "neither"
      },
      {
        "id": "9337",
        "question": "Which of the following would be an example of using creativity to innovate thedesign of a laptop computer?",
        "answer": "touch screen",
        "distractor_1": "headphone jack",
        "distractor_2": "keyboard",
        "distractor_3": "power cord"
      },
      {
        "id": "9338",
        "question": "Which of the following statements is true?",
        "answer": "Historical knowledge has a direct effect on the development of technological products.",
        "distractor_1": "Scientific knowledge has a direct effect on the development of technological products.",
        "distractor_2": "Historical knowledge has no effect on the development of technological products.",
        "distractor_3": "Scientific knowledge has no effect on the development of technological products."
      },
      {
        "id": "9339",
        "question": "What is a new product, system, or process that has never existed before, created by study and experimentation called?",
        "answer": "Invention",
        "distractor_1": "Innovation",
        "distractor_2": "Technology",
        "distractor_3": "Engineer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9340",
        "question": "Glass has been around since ancient times and has recently seen innovations thatenable it to be made in ways that can bend and withstand extreme high or lowtemperatures. The first hot-air balloons were launched in the 1700s and have seeninnovations tha",
        "answer": "hot-air balloon",
        "distractor_1": "glass",
        "distractor_2": "They have both progressed at the same rate.",
        "distractor_3": "They have not progressed."
      },
      {
        "id": "9341",
        "question": "What is the process of designing solutions to technical problems to improve people's lives called?",
        "answer": "Engineering",
        "distractor_1": "Inventing",
        "distractor_2": "Innovating",
        "distractor_3": "Formatting"
      },
      {
        "id": "9342",
        "question": "Which of the following statements regarding the relationship between science and technology is true?",
        "answer": "Scientists use technology to study the natural world.",
        "distractor_1": "Scientists use technology to build new inventions in order to make money.",
        "distractor_2": "Scientists use technology to meet human needs.",
        "distractor_3": "Scientists do not use technology."
      },
      {
        "id": "9343",
        "question": "Which field of study has no effect on the development of technological products?",
        "answer": "none of the above",
        "distractor_1": "mathematics",
        "distractor_2": "society and culture",
        "distractor_3": "science"
      },
      {
        "id": "9344",
        "question": "Which of the following would be an example of using creativity to innovate thedesign of a car?",
        "answer": "light sensors",
        "distractor_1": "steering wheel",
        "distractor_2": "tires",
        "distractor_3": "windshield"
      },
      {
        "id": "9345",
        "question": "If eight hydrogen atoms chemically react with four oxygen atoms, how many totalatoms will there be after the reaction?",
        "answer": "12",
        "distractor_1": "2",
        "distractor_2": "4",
        "distractor_3": "7"
      },
      {
        "id": "9346",
        "question": "New products and systems can be developed to _______ that could not be done without the help of technology?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "meet needs",
        "distractor_2": "solve problems",
        "distractor_3": "satisfy wants"
      },
      {
        "id": "9347",
        "question": "After tennis shoes have been used, some are recycled to make rubberized playgrounds or tracks. Others are thrown in the trash to be dumped in a landfill. Which use would be considered an undesirable outcome?",
        "answer": "dumping",
        "distractor_1": "recycling",
        "distractor_2": "both",
        "distractor_3": "neither"
      },
      {
        "id": "9348",
        "question": "Which of the following statements regarding the relationship between science andtechnology is false?",
        "answer": "Both scientists and technologists keep new knowledge and ideas secret so they canpatent their ideas and make money.",
        "distractor_1": "The goal of science is to understand the natural world, while the goal of technology is to meet human needs or solve human problems.",
        "distractor_2": "Technologists use science to meet human needs.",
        "distractor_3": "Scientists use technology to find answers to questions."
      },
      {
        "id": "9349",
        "question": "Glass has been around since ancient times and has recently seen innovations thatenable it to be made in ways that can bend and withstand extreme high or lowtemperatures. The first hot-air balloons were launched in the 1700s and have seeninnovations tha",
        "answer": "We cannot tell based on the information presented.",
        "distractor_1": "They have not had any innovations.",
        "distractor_2": "glass",
        "distractor_3": "hot-air balloon"
      },
      {
        "id": "9350",
        "question": "Which of the following would be an example of using creativity to innovate thedesign of a television?",
        "answer": "curved screen",
        "distractor_1": "speaker",
        "distractor_2": "antenna",
        "distractor_3": "power cord"
      },
      {
        "id": "9351",
        "question": "If four sodium atoms chemically react with two chlorine atoms, how many total atoms will there be after the reaction?",
        "answer": "6",
        "distractor_1": "2",
        "distractor_2": "3",
        "distractor_3": "4"
      },
      {
        "id": "9352",
        "question": "A plastic bottle is manufactured using petroleum products through a process that uses chemical reactions. If the bottle is not recycled and is thrown away with regular trash, it is placed in a dump or burned. What would the bottle be considered in this sc",
        "answer": "a societal impact",
        "distractor_1": "an atom",
        "distractor_2": "a natural resource",
        "distractor_3": "an element"
      },
      {
        "id": "9353",
        "question": "Innovative means:",
        "answer": "creative and newly invented",
        "distractor_1": "to be able to be invented",
        "distractor_2": "to be immune to a disease",
        "distractor_3": "when the body is hydrated"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2055",
    "name": "Taking Control",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9354",
        "question": "Which type of signal is either on or off?",
        "answer": "digital signal",
        "distractor_1": "optic signal",
        "distractor_2": "auditory signal",
        "distractor_3": "analog signal"
      },
      {
        "id": "9355",
        "question": "Which term describes the problem-solving method used to identify the cause of amalfunction in a technological system?",
        "answer": "troubleshooting",
        "distractor_1": "conflict resolution",
        "distractor_2": "checklisting",
        "distractor_3": "function listing"
      },
      {
        "id": "9356",
        "question": "When the value of 3 is entered for A, what occurs following the statement 'If A isequal to or less than five, print Low, else print High.'?",
        "answer": "Low will be printed.",
        "distractor_1": "High will be printed.",
        "distractor_2": "5 will be printed.",
        "distractor_3": "3 will be printed."
      },
      {
        "id": "9357",
        "question": "What is one method of slowing down the processor when writing Arduino Software(IDE) coding?",
        "answer": "Insert a delay statement.",
        "distractor_1": "Insert a pause statement.",
        "distractor_2": "There is no way to slow it down.",
        "distractor_3": "Install a 14-volt battery."
      },
      {
        "id": "9358",
        "question": "How many times does the setup function repeat?",
        "answer": "It does not repeat.",
        "distractor_1": "It does not repeat.",
        "distractor_2": "It runs until the count exceeds a set value.",
        "distractor_3": "It runs five times."
      },
      {
        "id": "9359",
        "question": "When you create a flowchart, what does the diamond shape represent?",
        "answer": "program decision",
        "distractor_1": "program start",
        "distractor_2": "program end",
        "distractor_3": "program output"
      },
      {
        "id": "9360",
        "question": "What does the word void tell the Arduino program?",
        "answer": "No output is expected.",
        "distractor_1": "Ignore the step.",
        "distractor_2": "Do not perform the step.",
        "distractor_3": "Delete the following steps."
      },
      {
        "id": "9361",
        "question": "Which punctuation mark is used to end a line of Arduino code?",
        "answer": "semicolon",
        "distractor_1": "period",
        "distractor_2": "colon",
        "distractor_3": "comma"
      },
      {
        "id": "9362",
        "question": "What term describes the order of words and the punctuation used in programminga controller?",
        "answer": "syntax",
        "distractor_1": "coding",
        "distractor_2": "language",
        "distractor_3": "programming"
      },
      {
        "id": "9363",
        "question": "Which is the best example of technological systems interacting with each other?",
        "answer": "a toilet flushing sewage into the city sewer system",
        "distractor_1": "a flag waving in the wind",
        "distractor_2": "a severe weather system canceling a baseball game",
        "distractor_3": "a flashlight turning on"
      },
      {
        "id": "9364",
        "question": "Is the following statement true or false? Technological systems often interact witheach other.",
        "answer": "True",
        "distractor_1": "False",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9365",
        "question": "How does a moisture sensor work?",
        "answer": "A moisture sensor works by measuring electrical resistance.",
        "distractor_1": "A moisture sensor works by measuring the ratio of hydrogen atoms to oxygen atoms.",
        "distractor_2": "A moisture sensor works by measuring the intensity of sound vibrations.",
        "distractor_3": "A moisture sensor works by measuring the intensity of light passing through the air."
      },
      {
        "id": "9366",
        "question": "It is the simplest type of system and requires human action to be regulated. What is it called?",
        "answer": "Open-loop system",
        "distractor_1": "Automation",
        "distractor_2": "Mechanical system",
        "distractor_3": "Closed-loop system"
      },
      {
        "id": "9367",
        "question": "When the value of 13 is entered for A, what occurs following the statement 'If A isequal to or less than five, print Low, else print High'?",
        "answer": "High will be printed.",
        "distractor_1": "Low will be printed.",
        "distractor_2": "5 will be printed.",
        "distractor_3": "13 will be printed."
      },
      {
        "id": "9368",
        "question": "What is an Arduino library?",
        "answer": "a file used to make programming simpler",
        "distractor_1": "a program to change text to speech",
        "distractor_2": "a file that lists all functions a microprocessor can complete",
        "distractor_3": "a list of all the programs stored in Arduino"
      },
      {
        "id": "9369",
        "question": "How many batteries should be connected to PRIZM®?",
        "answer": "one",
        "distractor_1": "two",
        "distractor_2": "12",
        "distractor_3": "nine"
      },
      {
        "id": "9370",
        "question": "What does two slash marks before a line of Arduino code signify?",
        "answer": "The text after the slashes is ignored.",
        "distractor_1": "The text after the slashes is processed last.",
        "distractor_2": "The text after the slashes has first priority.",
        "distractor_3": "The slashes are ignored."
      },
      {
        "id": "9371",
        "question": "How many times does the loop function repeat?",
        "answer": "There is no limit.",
        "distractor_1": "It does not repeat.",
        "distractor_2": "It runs until the count exceeds a set value.",
        "distractor_3": "It runs five times."
      },
      {
        "id": "9372",
        "question": "Troubleshooting the cause of a malfunction would not include which of the following?",
        "answer": "submitting a repair order",
        "distractor_1": "turning the equipment off and then restarting",
        "distractor_2": "reading the operation manual to ensure proper use of the equipment",
        "distractor_3": "testing the equipment and comparing the results to a chart"
      },
      {
        "id": "9373",
        "question": "What name is used for a simple computer placed on a single small integratedcircuit that consumes only a very small amount of power and accomplishes alimited number of tasks?",
        "answer": "microcontroller",
        "distractor_1": "macrocomputer",
        "distractor_2": "microscope",
        "distractor_3": "miniscope"
      },
      {
        "id": "9374",
        "question": "What is the difference between an open-loop and a closed-loop system?",
        "answer": "An open-loop system does not have feedback and a closed-loop system does.",
        "distractor_1": "An open-loop system does not have processes and a closed-loop system does.",
        "distractor_2": "An open-loop system does not have inputs and a closed-loop system does.",
        "distractor_3": "An open-loop system does not have outputs and a closed-loop system does."
      },
      {
        "id": "9375",
        "question": "What does two slash marks before a line of Arduino code signify?",
        "answer": "The text after the slashes is ignored.",
        "distractor_1": "The text after the slashes is processed last.",
        "distractor_2": "The slashes are ignored.",
        "distractor_3": "The text after the slashes has first priority."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2056",
    "name": "Animals, Plants, and Populations",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9588",
        "question": "Which of these statements is true about DNA and evolution?",
        "answer": "Two species with very similar DNA likely evolved from a common ancestor.",
        "distractor_1": "Two species that have the same DNA provide evidence that evolution has taken place.",
        "distractor_2": "Each living species has DNA made from different ingredients, showing that organisms have evolved.",
        "distractor_3": "DNA from related species is identical, providing evidence that all organisms have evolved in the same way"
      },
      {
        "id": "9589",
        "question": "Which type of microscope magnifies an object by passing light through the object and then using lenses to magnify it?",
        "answer": "Compound light microscope",
        "distractor_1": "Transmission electron microscope",
        "distractor_2": "Scanning electron microscope",
        "distractor_3": "Ultrasonic microscope"
      },
      {
        "id": "9590",
        "question": "The process of dividing a cell into four gametes, sperm cells or egg cells, to create haploid cells that fuse to form new organisms, is called what?",
        "answer": "Meiosis",
        "distractor_1": "Mitosis",
        "distractor_2": "Alternation of generations",
        "distractor_3": "Dichotomy of individuals"
      },
      {
        "id": "9591",
        "question": "Which engineering step would most likely include the making of a two-dimensional route on a map for a truck to follow?",
        "answer": "Create",
        "distractor_1": "Plan",
        "distractor_2": "Imagine",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "9592",
        "question": "The process of cell division that creates two new cells genetically identical to the parent cell is called what?",
        "answer": "Mitosis",
        "distractor_1": "Meiosis",
        "distractor_2": "Alternation of generations",
        "distractor_3": "Dichotomy of individuals"
      },
      {
        "id": "9593",
        "question": "'The solar panel cannot exceed 2 m x 4 m' is a statement that describes which of the following?",
        "answer": "constraint",
        "distractor_1": "specification",
        "distractor_2": "both",
        "distractor_3": "neither"
      },
      {
        "id": "9594",
        "question": "After testing a prototype in relation to its requirements, which of the following engineering steps would you do next if you wanted to brainstorm ways to make it better?",
        "answer": "Imagine",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Create",
        "distractor_3": "Improve"
      },
      {
        "id": "9595",
        "question": "Which of the following activities would be best used to justify an answer to the question, 'What effect does load have on a motor?'",
        "answer": "experimentation",
        "distractor_1": "innovation",
        "distractor_2": "research",
        "distractor_3": "troubleshooting"
      },
      {
        "id": "9596",
        "question": "What is the vascular tissue in plants that carries food down from the leaves to the rest of the plant?",
        "answer": "Phloem",
        "distractor_1": "Xylem",
        "distractor_2": "Stem",
        "distractor_3": "Roots"
      },
      {
        "id": "9597",
        "question": "Which type of microscope magnifies an object by passing a beam of electrons across the surface of an object and then measuring how the beam interacts with the surface?",
        "answer": "Scanning electron microscope",
        "distractor_1": "Transmission electron microscope",
        "distractor_2": "Compound light microscope",
        "distractor_3": "Ultrasonic microscope"
      },
      {
        "id": "9572",
        "question": "The process by which living things arise from living things is called ________.",
        "answer": "Reproduction",
        "distractor_1": "Perspiration",
        "distractor_2": "Classification",
        "distractor_3": "Respiration"
      },
      {
        "id": "9573",
        "question": "What is using one or more of your senses to gather information called?",
        "answer": "Observing",
        "distractor_1": "Inferring",
        "distractor_2": "Predicting",
        "distractor_3": "Classifying"
      },
      {
        "id": "9574",
        "question": "After testing a prototype in relation to its requirements, which of the following engineering steps would you do next if you wanted to build a new prototype?",
        "answer": "Create",
        "distractor_1": "Ask",
        "distractor_2": "Improve",
        "distractor_3": "Imagine"
      },
      {
        "id": "9575",
        "question": "Which of the following activities would be best used to justify an answer to the question, 'What effect does load have on a motor?'",
        "answer": "experimentation",
        "distractor_1": "innovation",
        "distractor_2": "troubleshooting",
        "distractor_3": "research"
      },
      {
        "id": "9576",
        "question": "After testing a prototype in relation to its requirements, which of the following engineering steps would you do next if you wanted to refine it?",
        "answer": "Improve",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Imagine",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "9577",
        "question": "Which situation described is most likely to cause a population to increase in size?",
        "answer": "High immigration rate + low death rate + high birth rate + low emigration rate",
        "distractor_1": "Low immigration rate + high death rate + low birth rate + high emigration rate",
        "distractor_2": "Static rates of immigration and emigration + high death rate + low birth rate",
        "distractor_3": "Static rates of immigration, emigration, death rate, and birth rate"
      },
      {
        "id": "9578",
        "question": "Why do scientists communicate different results about the same topic?",
        "answer": "scientific data can be interpreted in different ways",
        "distractor_1": "scientists support only their own opinions",
        "distractor_2": "the results of scientific experiments can never be reproduced",
        "distractor_3": "not all scientists use scientific methods"
      },
      {
        "id": "9579",
        "question": "Which type of microscope magnifies an object by passing electrons through an object and then using electromagnets to focus it?",
        "answer": "Transmission electron microscope",
        "distractor_1": "Scanning electron microscope",
        "distractor_2": "Compound light microscope",
        "distractor_3": "Laser microscope"
      },
      {
        "id": "9580",
        "question": "What is the vascular tissue in plants that carries water up from the roots to the rest of the plant?",
        "answer": "Xylem",
        "distractor_1": "Phloem",
        "distractor_2": "Stems",
        "distractor_3": "Roots"
      },
      {
        "id": "9581",
        "question": "Which engineering step would most likely include the building of a three-dimensional prototype?",
        "answer": "Create",
        "distractor_1": "Plan",
        "distractor_2": "Imagine",
        "distractor_3": "Ask"
      },
      {
        "id": "9582",
        "question": "What term is used to describe when an organism has two different stages in a life cycle, one gametophyte and the other sporophyte?",
        "answer": "Alternation of generations",
        "distractor_1": "Meiosis",
        "distractor_2": "Dichotomy of individuals",
        "distractor_3": "Mitosis"
      },
      {
        "id": "9583",
        "question": "'The motor cannot exceed 1,000 rpm' is a statement that describes which of the following?",
        "answer": "constraint",
        "distractor_1": "specification",
        "distractor_2": "both",
        "distractor_3": "neither"
      },
      {
        "id": "9584",
        "question": "A group of individuals living in the same location and defined by that location is called what?",
        "answer": "Population",
        "distractor_1": "Family",
        "distractor_2": "Species",
        "distractor_3": "State"
      },
      {
        "id": "9585",
        "question": "What is the period of time during which a mammal develops inside its mother's body called?",
        "answer": "gestation",
        "distractor_1": "germination",
        "distractor_2": "regeneration",
        "distractor_3": "pollination"
      },
      {
        "id": "9586",
        "question": "Modifying a vehicle's engine to get better gas mileage would most likely occur at which step of the engineering design process?",
        "answer": "Improve",
        "distractor_1": "Create",
        "distractor_2": "Plan",
        "distractor_3": "Imagine"
      },
      {
        "id": "9587",
        "question": "The method of determining population size that is counting every individual directly is called what?",
        "answer": "Census",
        "distractor_1": "Survey",
        "distractor_2": "Random Sampling",
        "distractor_3": "Determining Density"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2057",
    "name": "Theme Park Physics",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9376",
        "question": "What two things do you need to know in order to calculate work?",
        "answer": "force and distance",
        "distractor_1": "force and time",
        "distractor_2": "force and power",
        "distractor_3": "energy and distance"
      },
      {
        "id": "9377",
        "question": "What is the SI unit for energy?",
        "answer": "joules",
        "distractor_1": "newtons",
        "distractor_2": "kilograms",
        "distractor_3": "ergs"
      },
      {
        "id": "9378",
        "question": "A 75-kilogram mechanic pushes against a 1,500-kilogram car, but the car doesn't budge. How much work has the mechanic done?",
        "answer": "0 joules of work",
        "distractor_1": "20 joules of work",
        "distractor_2": "1,500 joules of work",
        "distractor_3": "1,575 joules of work"
      },
      {
        "id": "9379",
        "question": "Which equation can be used to calculate work?",
        "answer": "Work = Force • Distance",
        "distractor_1": "Work = Mass • Distance",
        "distractor_2": "Work = Force • Mass",
        "distractor_3": "Work = Mass • Height"
      },
      {
        "id": "9380",
        "question": "A person mowing a yard pushes a 40-kilogram lawn mower a distance of 1,500 meters. How much work has the person done?",
        "answer": "60,000 joules of work",
        "distractor_1": "1,500 joules of work",
        "distractor_2": "60 joules of work",
        "distractor_3": "37.5 joules of work"
      },
      {
        "id": "9381",
        "question": "What is the form of energy related to an object's movement?",
        "answer": "kinetic energy",
        "distractor_1": "frictional energy",
        "distractor_2": "thermal energy",
        "distractor_3": "potential energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "9382",
        "question": "Which equation best represents an object's kinetic energy?",
        "answer": "KE = 0.5 • m • v²",
        "distractor_1": "KE =  m • g • h",
        "distractor_2": "KE = F • d",
        "distractor_3": "KE = 0.5 • m • v • h"
      },
      {
        "id": "9383",
        "question": "What factor affects an object's kinetic energy?",
        "answer": "mass",
        "distractor_1": "height",
        "distractor_2": "acceleration due to gravity",
        "distractor_3": "force"
      },
      {
        "id": "9384",
        "question": "A car traveling at a constant velocity loses mass as it uses up fuel. As long as the car's velocity stays the same, what happens to the car's kinetic energy as it loses mass?",
        "answer": "As mass decreases, the car's kinetic energy will decrease.",
        "distractor_1": "As mass decreases, the car's kinetic energy will stay the same.",
        "distractor_2": "As mass decreases, the car's kinetic energy will increase.",
        "distractor_3": "It is impossible to tell because we don't know the mass of the car."
      },
      {
        "id": "9385",
        "question": "A cheetah chasing an antelope increases its velocity to catch the antelope. Assuming the mass of the cheetah stays the same, what happens to the cheetah's kinetic energy as it increases velocity?",
        "answer": "As velocity increases, the cheetah's kinetic energy will increase.",
        "distractor_1": "As velocity increases, the cheetah's kinetic energy will stay the same.",
        "distractor_2": "As velocity increases, the cheetah's kinetic energy will decrease.",
        "distractor_3": "It is impossible to tell because we don't know the mass of the cheetah."
      },
      {
        "id": "9386",
        "question": "What is the form of energy related to an object's position (height)?",
        "answer": "potential energy",
        "distractor_1": "kinetic energy",
        "distractor_2": "frictional energy",
        "distractor_3": "electrical energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "9387",
        "question": "What factor affects an object's gravitational potential energy?",
        "answer": "acceleration due to gravity",
        "distractor_1": "velocity",
        "distractor_2": "force",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9388",
        "question": "What kind of energy is considered stored energy?",
        "answer": "potential energy",
        "distractor_1": "kinetic energy",
        "distractor_2": "frictional energy",
        "distractor_3": "electrical energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "9389",
        "question": "Which equation best represents an object's potential energy?",
        "answer": "PE =  m • g • h",
        "distractor_1": "PE = F • d",
        "distractor_2": "PE = 0.5 • m • v • h",
        "distractor_3": "PE = v² • F"
      },
      {
        "id": "9390",
        "question": "A mountain climber is climbing up a rock wall. Assuming the climber's mass stays the same, what happens to the climber's potential energy as his height increases?",
        "answer": "As height increases, the climber's potential energy will increase.",
        "distractor_1": "As height increases, the climber's potential energy will stay the same.",
        "distractor_2": "As height increases, the climber's potential energy will decrease.",
        "distractor_3": "It is impossible to tell because we don't know the mass of the climber."
      },
      {
        "id": "9391",
        "question": "A woman gets in an elevator at the top of the Empire State Building and descends toward the ground floor. What happens to the woman's potential energy as she descends?",
        "answer": "As height decreases, the woman's potential energy will decrease.",
        "distractor_1": "As height decreases, the woman's potential energy will increase.",
        "distractor_2": "As height decreases, the woman's potential energy will stay the same.",
        "distractor_3": "It is impossible to tell because we don't know the mass of the woman."
      },
      {
        "id": "9392",
        "question": "An airplane traveling at a constant altitude loses mass as it uses up jet fuel. What happens to the plane's potential energy as it uses up fuel?",
        "answer": "As mass decreases, the plane's potential energy will decrease.",
        "distractor_1": "As mass decreases, the plane's potential energy will increase.",
        "distractor_2": "As mass decreases, the plane's potential energy will stay the same.",
        "distractor_3": "It is impossible to tell because we don't know the height of the plane."
      },
      {
        "id": "9393",
        "question": "What is the best representation of the law of conservation of energy?",
        "answer": "Energy can not be created or destroyed. It can only change forms.",
        "distractor_1": "Potential energy is always conserved.",
        "distractor_2": "Energy can only change between potential and kinetic forms of energy.",
        "distractor_3": "Energy is conserved when forces are balanced."
      },
      {
        "id": "9394",
        "question": "A person sits at the top of a waterslide. Which of the following is the best description of the person's energy as he or she travels down the slide?",
        "answer": "Potential energy is converted to kinetic energy.Total energy remains constant.",
        "distractor_1": "Kinetic energy is converted to potential energy.Total energy increases.",
        "distractor_2": "Potential energy is converted to kinetic energy.Total energy increases.",
        "distractor_3": "Kinetic energy is converted to potential energy.Total energy decreases."
      },
      {
        "id": "9395",
        "question": "If the velocity of an object increases, what is happening to the object's kinetic energy?",
        "answer": "Kinetic energy is being transferred to the object.",
        "distractor_1": "Kinetic energy is staying the same because energy is conserved.",
        "distractor_2": "Kinetic energy is being transferred away from the object.",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "9396",
        "question": "When an object spins or rotates, what is the force that acts toward the center of rotation?",
        "answer": "centripetal force",
        "distractor_1": "centrifugal force",
        "distractor_2": "g-force",
        "distractor_3": "frictional force"
      },
      {
        "id": "9397",
        "question": "What is the difference between centripetal force and centrifugal force for a rotating object?",
        "answer": "Centripetal force is an actual force acting toward the center of rotation. Centrifugal force is an apparent force acting away from the center of rotation.",
        "distractor_1": "Centripetal force is an apparent force acting away from the center of rotation. Centrifugal force is an actual force acting toward the center of rotation.",
        "distractor_2": "Centripetal force causes objects to rotate clockwise.Centrifugal force causes objects to rotate counterclockwise.",
        "distractor_3": "Centripetal force causes objects to rotate counterclockwise.Centrifugal force causes objects to rotate clockwise."
      },
      {
        "id": "9398",
        "question": "Which of these statements are true about energy and work?",
        "answer": "Energy is the ability to do work.",
        "distractor_1": "Energy is measured in joules; work is measured in newtons.",
        "distractor_2": "Energy is work acting at a distance.",
        "distractor_3": "Energy is stored; work is used."
      },
      {
        "id": "9399",
        "question": "Which situation is an example of increasing potential energy?",
        "answer": "pulling a wagon uphill",
        "distractor_1": "a bicyclist stopping at a stop sign",
        "distractor_2": "a cat jumping from a tree",
        "distractor_3": "emptying a bucket of water"
      },
      {
        "id": "9400",
        "question": "Noah carried a skateboard up a hill and then rode the skateboard down the hill. When Noah reached the bottom of the hill, he rolled to a stop. When did Noah have the most potential energy?",
        "answer": "while standing on the skateboard at the top of the hill",
        "distractor_1": "while carrying the skateboard up the hill",
        "distractor_2": "while riding the skateboard down the hill",
        "distractor_3": "while standing on the skateboard at the bottom of the hill"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2058",
    "name": "Special Delivery",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9401",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Warehousing and Distribution Center Operations pathway?",
        "answer": "ship loader",
        "distractor_1": "rail car repairer",
        "distractor_2": "logistician",
        "distractor_3": "sales manager"
      },
      {
        "id": "9402",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Logistics Planning and Management Services pathway?",
        "answer": "logistics engineer",
        "distractor_1": "sales manager",
        "distractor_2": "rail car repairer",
        "distractor_3": "ship loader"
      },
      {
        "id": "9403",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Health, Safety, and Environmental Management pathway?",
        "answer": "environmental compliance inspector",
        "distractor_1": "ship loader",
        "distractor_2": "customer service manager",
        "distractor_3": "rail car repairer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9404",
        "question": "Which of the following is the act of spreading people or objects over an area?",
        "answer": "distribution",
        "distractor_1": "logistics",
        "distractor_2": "transportation",
        "distractor_3": "purchasing"
      },
      {
        "id": "9405",
        "question": "Which of the following pallet sizes would not be reasonable to load on a truck?",
        "answer": "2' x 4'",
        "distractor_1": "42' x 42'",
        "distractor_2": "48' x 48'",
        "distractor_3": "48' x 40'"
      },
      {
        "id": "9406",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Sales and Service pathway?",
        "answer": "customer service manager",
        "distractor_1": "ship loader",
        "distractor_2": "auto mechanic",
        "distractor_3": "rail car repairer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9407",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Transportation Systems/ Infrastructure Planning, Management, and Regulation pathway?",
        "answer": "civil engineer",
        "distractor_1": "ship loader",
        "distractor_2": "customer service manager",
        "distractor_3": "rail car repairer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9408",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technologist career level?",
        "answer": "electrician",
        "distractor_1": "logistician",
        "distractor_2": "environmental compliance inspector",
        "distractor_3": "truck loader"
      },
      {
        "id": "9409",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Facility and Mobile Equipment pathway?",
        "answer": "rail car repairer",
        "distractor_1": "sales manager",
        "distractor_2": "commercial pilot",
        "distractor_3": "logistician"
      },
      {
        "id": "9410",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the professional career level?",
        "answer": "logistician",
        "distractor_1": "packer",
        "distractor_2": "electronic repairer",
        "distractor_3": "truck loader"
      },
      {
        "id": "9411",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Transportation Operations pathway?",
        "answer": "commercial pilot",
        "distractor_1": "logistician",
        "distractor_2": "sales manager",
        "distractor_3": "auto mechanic"
      },
      {
        "id": "9412",
        "question": "Which of the following is the act of moving people or objects from one location to another?",
        "answer": "transportation",
        "distractor_1": "distribution",
        "distractor_2": "logistics",
        "distractor_3": "purchasing"
      },
      {
        "id": "9413",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technician career level?",
        "answer": "packer",
        "distractor_1": "urban planner",
        "distractor_2": "traffic manager",
        "distractor_3": "electronic repairer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9414",
        "question": "Which of the following is the act of coordinating the movement or spread of people or objects?",
        "answer": "logistics",
        "distractor_1": "purchasing",
        "distractor_2": "distribution",
        "distractor_3": "transportation"
      },
      {
        "id": "9415",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Transportation Operations pathway?",
        "answer": "locomotive engineer",
        "distractor_1": "auto mechanic",
        "distractor_2": "sales manager",
        "distractor_3": "logistician"
      },
      {
        "id": "9416",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the professional career level?",
        "answer": "urban planner",
        "distractor_1": "packer",
        "distractor_2": "electronic repairer",
        "distractor_3": "truck loader"
      },
      {
        "id": "9417",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Transportation Systems/ Infrastructure Planning, Management, and Regulation pathway?",
        "answer": "motor vehicle inspector",
        "distractor_1": "ship loader",
        "distractor_2": "customer service manager",
        "distractor_3": "rail car repairer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9418",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technician career level?",
        "answer": "cashier",
        "distractor_1": "urban planner",
        "distractor_2": "traffic manager",
        "distractor_3": "electronic repairer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9419",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Facility and Mobile Equipment pathway?",
        "answer": "auto mechanic",
        "distractor_1": "sales manager",
        "distractor_2": "logistician",
        "distractor_3": "commercial pilot"
      },
      {
        "id": "9420",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Sales and Service pathway?",
        "answer": "sales manager",
        "distractor_1": "rail car repairer",
        "distractor_2": "logistics engineer",
        "distractor_3": "ship loader"
      },
      {
        "id": "9421",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Health, Safety, and Environmental Management pathway?",
        "answer": "safety analyst",
        "distractor_1": "ship loader",
        "distractor_2": "rail car repairer",
        "distractor_3": "auto mechanic"
      },
      {
        "id": "9422",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Warehousing and Distribution Center Operations pathway?",
        "answer": "shipping clerk",
        "distractor_1": "logistician",
        "distractor_2": "rail car repairer",
        "distractor_3": "sales manager"
      },
      {
        "id": "9423",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Logistics Planning and Management Services pathway?",
        "answer": "logistician",
        "distractor_1": "ship loader",
        "distractor_2": "sales manager",
        "distractor_3": "rail car repairer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9424",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technologist career level?",
        "answer": "ship captain",
        "distractor_1": "logistician",
        "distractor_2": "environmental compliance inspector",
        "distractor_3": "truck loader"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2059",
    "name": "Vital Signs",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9425",
        "question": "Which value represents a healthy human blood pressure?",
        "answer": "125/70",
        "distractor_1": "70/125",
        "distractor_2": "300/20",
        "distractor_3": "1/100"
      },
      {
        "id": "9426",
        "question": "Which value represents a healthy human pulse?",
        "answer": "68 bpm",
        "distractor_1": "6 bpm",
        "distractor_2": "168 bpm",
        "distractor_3": "300 bpm"
      },
      {
        "id": "9427",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Health Informatics pathway?",
        "answer": "medical records technician",
        "distractor_1": "pharmacy aide",
        "distractor_2": "hospitalist",
        "distractor_3": "nursing assistant"
      },
      {
        "id": "9428",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Support Services pathway?",
        "answer": "phlebotomist",
        "distractor_1": "medical scientist",
        "distractor_2": "biomedical engineer",
        "distractor_3": "physical therapist"
      },
      {
        "id": "9429",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Biotechnology Research and Development pathway?",
        "answer": "biomedical engineer",
        "distractor_1": "epidemiologist",
        "distractor_2": "radiological technician",
        "distractor_3": "clinical laboratory technician"
      },
      {
        "id": "9430",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technologist career level?",
        "answer": "MRI technologist",
        "distractor_1": "radiological technician",
        "distractor_2": "nursing assistant",
        "distractor_3": "physical therapist"
      },
      {
        "id": "9431",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Therapeutic Services pathway?",
        "answer": "hospitalist",
        "distractor_1": "biomedical engineer",
        "distractor_2": "phlebotomist",
        "distractor_3": "medical secretary"
      },
      {
        "id": "9432",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Diagnostic Services pathway?",
        "answer": "epidemiologist",
        "distractor_1": "orderly",
        "distractor_2": "phlebotomist",
        "distractor_3": "medical transcriptionist"
      },
      {
        "id": "9433",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Diagnostic Services pathway?",
        "answer": "clinical laboratory technician",
        "distractor_1": "medical secretary",
        "distractor_2": "medical records technician",
        "distractor_3": "physical therapist"
      },
      {
        "id": "9434",
        "question": "Which value represents a healthy human body temperature?",
        "answer": "98.6°F",
        "distractor_1": "198.6°F",
        "distractor_2": "9.6°F",
        "distractor_3": "8.6°F"
      },
      {
        "id": "9435",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technician career level?",
        "answer": "radiological technician",
        "distractor_1": "MRI technologist",
        "distractor_2": "registered nurse",
        "distractor_3": "physical therapist"
      },
      {
        "id": "9436",
        "question": "Which value represents a healthy human blood oxygen level?",
        "answer": "0.98",
        "distractor_1": "0.25",
        "distractor_2": "0.49",
        "distractor_3": "1.5"
      },
      {
        "id": "9437",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the professional career level?",
        "answer": "physical therapist",
        "distractor_1": "MRI technologist",
        "distractor_2": "nursing assistant",
        "distractor_3": "radiological technician"
      },
      {
        "id": "9438",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Diagnostic Services pathway?",
        "answer": "diagnostic medical sonographer",
        "distractor_1": "phlebotomist",
        "distractor_2": "medical transcriptionist",
        "distractor_3": "orderly"
      },
      {
        "id": "9439",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Health Informatics pathway?",
        "answer": "medical secretary",
        "distractor_1": "physical therapist",
        "distractor_2": "phlebotomist",
        "distractor_3": "orderly"
      },
      {
        "id": "9440",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Diagnostic Services pathway?",
        "answer": "radiological technician",
        "distractor_1": "pharmacy aide",
        "distractor_2": "hospitalist",
        "distractor_3": "nursing assistant"
      },
      {
        "id": "9441",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the professional career level?",
        "answer": "hospitalist",
        "distractor_1": "MRI technologist",
        "distractor_2": "radiological technician",
        "distractor_3": "nursing assistant"
      },
      {
        "id": "9442",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Biotechnology Research and Development pathway?",
        "answer": "medical scientist",
        "distractor_1": "diagnostic medical sonographer",
        "distractor_2": "medical records technician",
        "distractor_3": "medical secretary"
      },
      {
        "id": "9443",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Support Services pathway?",
        "answer": "orderly",
        "distractor_1": "nursing assistant",
        "distractor_2": "hospitalist",
        "distractor_3": "epidemiologist"
      },
      {
        "id": "9444",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Therapeutic Services pathway?",
        "answer": "nursing assistant",
        "distractor_1": "clinical laboratory technician",
        "distractor_2": "radiological technician",
        "distractor_3": "biomedical engineer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9445",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technologist career level?",
        "answer": "registered nurse",
        "distractor_1": "nursing assistant",
        "distractor_2": "physical therapist",
        "distractor_3": "hospitalist"
      },
      {
        "id": "9446",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technician career level?",
        "answer": "nursing assistant",
        "distractor_1": "physical therapist",
        "distractor_2": "registered nurse",
        "distractor_3": "MRI technologist"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2060",
    "name": "Mechanical Makers",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9447",
        "question": "Which of the following is the act of turning raw materials into usable goods?",
        "answer": "manufacturing",
        "distractor_1": "robotics",
        "distractor_2": "assembly",
        "distractor_3": "welding"
      },
      {
        "id": "9448",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technologist career level?",
        "answer": "industrial machine mechanic",
        "distractor_1": "design engineer",
        "distractor_2": "foundry worker",
        "distractor_3": "assembler"
      },
      {
        "id": "9449",
        "question": "Which of the following commands would move a standard servo from its neutral position?",
        "answer": "set servo position to 135",
        "distractor_1": "set servo position to 90",
        "distractor_2": "wait 1,000 milliseconds",
        "distractor_3": "set servo speed to 50"
      },
      {
        "id": "9450",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Logistics and Inventory Control pathway?",
        "answer": "traffic manager",
        "distractor_1": "rail car repairer",
        "distractor_2": "environmental inspector",
        "distractor_3": "ship loader"
      },
      {
        "id": "9451",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Production pathway?",
        "answer": "machine operator",
        "distractor_1": "sales manager",
        "distractor_2": "logistician",
        "distractor_3": "commercial pilot"
      },
      {
        "id": "9452",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Maintenance, Installation, and Repair pathway?",
        "answer": "major appliance technician",
        "distractor_1": "sales manager",
        "distractor_2": "logistics engineer",
        "distractor_3": "ship loader"
      },
      {
        "id": "9453",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Quality Assurance pathway?",
        "answer": "calibration technician",
        "distractor_1": "rail car repairer",
        "distractor_2": "logistics engineer",
        "distractor_3": "ship loader"
      },
      {
        "id": "9454",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Health, Safety, and Environmental Assurance pathway?",
        "answer": "safety engineer",
        "distractor_1": "rail car repairer",
        "distractor_2": "civil engineer",
        "distractor_3": "ship loader"
      },
      {
        "id": "9455",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Manufacturing Production Process Development pathway?",
        "answer": "industrial engineer",
        "distractor_1": "sales manager",
        "distractor_2": "logistician",
        "distractor_3": "ship loader"
      },
      {
        "id": "9456",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the professional career level?",
        "answer": "safety coordinator",
        "distractor_1": "bookbinder",
        "distractor_2": "foundry worker",
        "distractor_3": "assembler"
      },
      {
        "id": "9457",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technician career level?",
        "answer": "assembler",
        "distractor_1": "millwright",
        "distractor_2": "safety coordinator",
        "distractor_3": "design engineer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9458",
        "question": "Which of the following processes would a military ship builder most likely use?",
        "answer": "fixed position",
        "distractor_1": "custom manufacturing",
        "distractor_2": "continuous flow",
        "distractor_3": "production line"
      },
      {
        "id": "9459",
        "question": "Which of the following processes would a bread baker most likely use?",
        "answer": "continuous flow",
        "distractor_1": "production line",
        "distractor_2": "custom manufacturing",
        "distractor_3": "fixed position"
      },
      {
        "id": "9460",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Health, Safety, and Environmental Assurance pathway?",
        "answer": "environmental engineer",
        "distractor_1": "ship loader",
        "distractor_2": "customer service manager",
        "distractor_3": "rail car repairer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9461",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Quality Assurance pathway?",
        "answer": "inspector",
        "distractor_1": "sales manager",
        "distractor_2": "logistics engineer",
        "distractor_3": "ship loader"
      },
      {
        "id": "9462",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the professional career level?",
        "answer": "production manager",
        "distractor_1": "bookbinder",
        "distractor_2": "foundry worker",
        "distractor_3": "assembler"
      },
      {
        "id": "9463",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technologist career level?",
        "answer": "facility electrician",
        "distractor_1": "design engineer",
        "distractor_2": "foundry worker",
        "distractor_3": "assembler"
      },
      {
        "id": "9464",
        "question": "Which of the following processes would a car manufacturer most likely use?",
        "answer": "production line",
        "distractor_1": "continuous flow",
        "distractor_2": "custom manufacturing",
        "distractor_3": "fixed position"
      },
      {
        "id": "9465",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Logistics and Inventory Control pathway?",
        "answer": "logistician",
        "distractor_1": "rail car repairer",
        "distractor_2": "safety analyst",
        "distractor_3": "ship loader"
      },
      {
        "id": "9466",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Production pathway?",
        "answer": "assembler",
        "distractor_1": "sales manager",
        "distractor_2": "logistician",
        "distractor_3": "commercial pilot"
      },
      {
        "id": "9467",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technician career level?",
        "answer": "foundry worker",
        "distractor_1": "millwright",
        "distractor_2": "safety coordinator",
        "distractor_3": "design engineer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9468",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Maintenance, Installation, and Repair pathway?",
        "answer": "facility electrician",
        "distractor_1": "sales manager",
        "distractor_2": "logistician",
        "distractor_3": "ship loader"
      },
      {
        "id": "9469",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Manufacturing Production Process Development pathway?",
        "answer": "design engineer",
        "distractor_1": "sales manager",
        "distractor_2": "logistician",
        "distractor_3": "shipping clerk"
      },
      {
        "id": "9470",
        "question": "Which of the following processes would a personal seamstress most likely use?",
        "answer": "custom manufacturing",
        "distractor_1": "fixed position",
        "distractor_2": "continuous flow",
        "distractor_3": "production line"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2061",
    "name": "Under Pressure",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9471",
        "question": "What property of liquids is the reason hydraulic systems work?",
        "answer": "They are not compressible.",
        "distractor_1": "They are ionic.",
        "distractor_2": "They are cohesive.",
        "distractor_3": "They have adhesive properties."
      },
      {
        "id": "9472",
        "question": "Which job would require the most training and education among these three: recyclable materials collector, wastewater treatment plant operator, or wastewater engineer?",
        "answer": "wastewater engineer",
        "distractor_1": "recyclable materials collector",
        "distractor_2": "wastewater treatment plant operator",
        "distractor_3": "All require about the same training and education."
      },
      {
        "id": "9473",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Power, Structural & Technical Systems pathway?",
        "answer": "farm equipment mechanic and service technician",
        "distractor_1": "biological technician",
        "distractor_2": "water resource specialist",
        "distractor_3": "food scientist and technologist"
      },
      {
        "id": "9474",
        "question": "What would the mechanical advantage of a hydraulic system be if the pumpcylinder had a diameter of 8 inches and the actuator cylinder had a diameter of 24inches? Surface area of a circle  SA =  p • r²",
        "answer": "9",
        "distractor_1": "192",
        "distractor_2": "3",
        "distractor_3": "6"
      },
      {
        "id": "9475",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Animal Systems pathway?",
        "answer": "nonfarm animal caretaker",
        "distractor_1": "aquacultural manager",
        "distractor_2": "pest control worker",
        "distractor_3": "fisher and related fishing worker"
      },
      {
        "id": "9476",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Food Products and Processing Systems pathway?",
        "answer": "grader and sorter, agricultural products",
        "distractor_1": "agricultural equipment operator",
        "distractor_2": "animal breeder",
        "distractor_3": "farmworker and laborer, crop"
      },
      {
        "id": "9477",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Environmental Service Systems pathway?",
        "answer": "hazardous materials removal worker",
        "distractor_1": "pesticide handler, sprayer, and applicator, vegetation",
        "distractor_2": "fisher and related fishing worker",
        "distractor_3": "farm and ranch manager"
      },
      {
        "id": "9478",
        "question": "What is the mechanical advantage of a hydraulic system if it takes four strokes of the pump cylinder for one complete stroke of the actuator cylinder?",
        "answer": "4",
        "distractor_1": "40",
        "distractor_2": "1",
        "distractor_3": "0.25"
      },
      {
        "id": "9479",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the professional career level?",
        "answer": "environmental engineer",
        "distractor_1": "farmworker",
        "distractor_2": "farm equipment service technician",
        "distractor_3": "recyclable material collector"
      },
      {
        "id": "9480",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Agribusiness Systems pathway?",
        "answer": "aquacultural manager",
        "distractor_1": "log grader and scaler",
        "distractor_2": "biological technician",
        "distractor_3": "agricultural engineer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9481",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Natural Resources Systems pathway?",
        "answer": "geophysical data technician",
        "distractor_1": "farm labor contractor",
        "distractor_2": "first-line supervisor of farming, fishing, and forestry worker",
        "distractor_3": "soil and plant scientist"
      },
      {
        "id": "9482",
        "question": "A pump cylinder with a surface area of 4 cm² is used to push an actuator cylinder with a surface area of 20 cm². What is the mechanical advantage of this hydraulic system?",
        "answer": "5",
        "distractor_1": "4",
        "distractor_2": "20",
        "distractor_3": "80"
      },
      {
        "id": "9483",
        "question": "Which actuator cylinder surface area would have a mechanical advantage of four with a pump cylinder surface area of 40 mm²?",
        "answer": "160 mm²",
        "distractor_1": "40 mm²",
        "distractor_2": "10 mm²",
        "distractor_3": "4 mm²"
      },
      {
        "id": "9484",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technician career level?",
        "answer": "farmworker",
        "distractor_1": "farm equipment service technician",
        "distractor_2": "environmental engineer",
        "distractor_3": "wastewater engineer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9485",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Plant Systems pathway?",
        "answer": "farmworker and laborer, crop, nursery, and greenhouse",
        "distractor_1": "forest and conservation worker",
        "distractor_2": "animal breeder",
        "distractor_3": "buyer and purchasing agent, farm products"
      },
      {
        "id": "9486",
        "question": "What was the trend for technologist-level jobs in the agriculture field during the 20th century?",
        "answer": "generally decreased",
        "distractor_1": "generally increased",
        "distractor_2": "stayed about the same",
        "distractor_3": "No data is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "9487",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technologist career level?",
        "answer": "farm equipment service technician",
        "distractor_1": "recyclable material collector",
        "distractor_2": "environmental engineer",
        "distractor_3": "farmworker"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2062",
    "name": "Top Dog Architecture",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9488",
        "question": "Which of the following elements describes a curved structure that can support an elevated space?",
        "answer": "arch",
        "distractor_1": "eaves",
        "distractor_2": "chimney",
        "distractor_3": "ridge"
      },
      {
        "id": "9489",
        "question": "Which of the following elements describes the part of the roof that extends out past the walls?",
        "answer": "eaves",
        "distractor_1": "dormer",
        "distractor_2": "ridge",
        "distractor_3": "column"
      },
      {
        "id": "9490",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the professional career level?",
        "answer": "project manager",
        "distractor_1": "elevator installer",
        "distractor_2": "regional and urban renderer",
        "distractor_3": "carpet installer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9491",
        "question": "Which of the following elements describes a decorative molding at the edge of a roof or over a door or window?",
        "answer": "cornice",
        "distractor_1": "ridge",
        "distractor_2": "eaves",
        "distractor_3": "dormer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9492",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Design/Pre-Construction pathway?",
        "answer": "drafter",
        "distractor_1": "mason",
        "distractor_2": "plumber",
        "distractor_3": "heavy equipment operator"
      },
      {
        "id": "9493",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a common truss design?",
        "answer": "circular",
        "distractor_1": "queen post",
        "distractor_2": "king post",
        "distractor_3": "Pratt"
      },
      {
        "id": "9494",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technician career level?",
        "answer": "carpet installer",
        "distractor_1": "project inspector",
        "distractor_2": "construction engineer",
        "distractor_3": "project manager"
      },
      {
        "id": "9495",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a common architectural style?",
        "answer": "city",
        "distractor_1": "prairie",
        "distractor_2": "colonial",
        "distractor_3": "art deco"
      },
      {
        "id": "9496",
        "question": "Which of the following elements describes the edge created by the top of two intersecting rooflines?",
        "answer": "ridge",
        "distractor_1": "chimney",
        "distractor_2": "eaves",
        "distractor_3": "dormer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9497",
        "question": "Which of the following was originally a covering for a window opening?",
        "answer": "shutter",
        "distractor_1": "chimney",
        "distractor_2": "eaves",
        "distractor_3": "arch"
      },
      {
        "id": "9498",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Construction pathway?",
        "answer": "carpenter",
        "distractor_1": "planner",
        "distractor_2": "drafter",
        "distractor_3": "architect"
      },
      {
        "id": "9499",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technologist career level?",
        "answer": "environmental designer",
        "distractor_1": "project inspector",
        "distractor_2": "construction engineer",
        "distractor_3": "project manager"
      },
      {
        "id": "9500",
        "question": "Which of the following elements describes a fire-resistant structure that forms a vent for smoke?",
        "answer": "chimney",
        "distractor_1": "eaves",
        "distractor_2": "dormer",
        "distractor_3": "ridge"
      },
      {
        "id": "9501",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Maintenance/Operations pathway?",
        "answer": "facilities engineer",
        "distractor_1": "planner",
        "distractor_2": "drafter",
        "distractor_3": "architect"
      },
      {
        "id": "9502",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Construction pathway?",
        "answer": "electrician",
        "distractor_1": "planner",
        "distractor_2": "drafter",
        "distractor_3": "architect"
      },
      {
        "id": "9503",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technologist career level?",
        "answer": "regional and urban renderer",
        "distractor_1": "project inspector",
        "distractor_2": "construction engineer",
        "distractor_3": "project manager"
      },
      {
        "id": "9504",
        "question": "Which of the following elements describes a vertical window that extends from a sloped roof?",
        "answer": "dormer",
        "distractor_1": "eaves",
        "distractor_2": "chimney",
        "distractor_3": "ridge"
      },
      {
        "id": "9505",
        "question": "Which of the following elements describes a support structure used in place of a solid wall?",
        "answer": "column",
        "distractor_1": "ridge",
        "distractor_2": "eaves",
        "distractor_3": "dormer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9506",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technician career level?",
        "answer": "elevator installer",
        "distractor_1": "project inspector",
        "distractor_2": "construction engineer",
        "distractor_3": "project manager"
      },
      {
        "id": "9507",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the professional career level?",
        "answer": "construction engineer",
        "distractor_1": "elevator installer",
        "distractor_2": "regional and urban renderer",
        "distractor_3": "carpet installer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9508",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a common truss design?",
        "answer": "dot matrix",
        "distractor_1": "queen post",
        "distractor_2": "king post",
        "distractor_3": "Pratt"
      },
      {
        "id": "9509",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a common architectural style?",
        "answer": "rural",
        "distractor_1": "prairie",
        "distractor_2": "colonial",
        "distractor_3": "art deco"
      },
      {
        "id": "9510",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Design/Pre-Construction pathway?",
        "answer": "architect",
        "distractor_1": "mason",
        "distractor_2": "plumber",
        "distractor_3": "heavy equipment operator"
      },
      {
        "id": "9511",
        "question": "Which of the following describes the view of a building from the front, back, or sides?",
        "answer": "elevation",
        "distractor_1": "chimney",
        "distractor_2": "eaves",
        "distractor_3": "arch"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2063",
    "name": "Now Hiring",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9512",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the professional career level?",
        "answer": "human resource manager",
        "distractor_1": "human resource assistant",
        "distractor_2": "human resource specialist",
        "distractor_3": "labor relations manager"
      },
      {
        "id": "9513",
        "question": "What type of survey assesses whether you like to work with others or by yourself?",
        "answer": "personality",
        "distractor_1": "attitude",
        "distractor_2": "interest",
        "distractor_3": "cognitive ability"
      },
      {
        "id": "9514",
        "question": "How is a career defined?",
        "answer": "the general path taken in one's professional life",
        "distractor_1": "an activity done to earn an income",
        "distractor_2": "the hobbies participated in during a lifetime",
        "distractor_3": "a single work assignment"
      },
      {
        "id": "9515",
        "question": "How are careers listed in a cluster?",
        "answer": "Workers' interests and aptitudes are similar.",
        "distractor_1": "Workers are all employed by the same company.",
        "distractor_2": "All the careers have the same median pay.",
        "distractor_3": "All the careers need the same level of education."
      },
      {
        "id": "9516",
        "question": "Which of the following is an inappropriate use of social networking?",
        "answer": "posting critical comments about your current employer",
        "distractor_1": "posting conservative videos that you have created",
        "distractor_2": "posting conservative photos from your vacation",
        "distractor_3": "posting original poetry that you have written"
      },
      {
        "id": "9517",
        "question": "What types of questions will appear on an interest survey?",
        "answer": "questions about how much you enjoy specific activities",
        "distractor_1": "questions about your physical abilities",
        "distractor_2": "questions about your grades in classes associated with specific careers",
        "distractor_3": "questions about your mental abilities"
      },
      {
        "id": "9518",
        "question": "What is the common purpose of a letter of application and a résumé?",
        "answer": "to convince an employer to interview you",
        "distractor_1": "to provide proof of your skills",
        "distractor_2": "to raise your salary",
        "distractor_3": "to brag about your education"
      },
      {
        "id": "9519",
        "question": "What document is a summary of your education, skills, and work experience?",
        "answer": "résumé",
        "distractor_1": "personnel file",
        "distractor_2": "resignation",
        "distractor_3": "letter of introduction"
      },
      {
        "id": "9520",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technologist career level?",
        "answer": "human resource specialist",
        "distractor_1": "human resource assistant",
        "distractor_2": "interviewer",
        "distractor_3": "compensation, benefits, and job analysis specialist"
      },
      {
        "id": "9521",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technician career level?",
        "answer": "human resource assistant",
        "distractor_1": "human resource manager",
        "distractor_2": "compensation, benefits, and job analysis specialist",
        "distractor_3": "labor relations manager"
      },
      {
        "id": "9522",
        "question": "What is an aptitude?",
        "answer": "your natural ability to complete a task",
        "distractor_1": "your enjoyment or dislike of a task",
        "distractor_2": "your knowledge about how to complete a task",
        "distractor_3": "your positive or negative feeling about a task"
      },
      {
        "id": "9523",
        "question": "What term is used to describe a source of income that is one step in one's professional life?",
        "answer": "job",
        "distractor_1": "career",
        "distractor_2": "profession",
        "distractor_3": "vocation"
      },
      {
        "id": "9524",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technologist career level?",
        "answer": "labor relations manager",
        "distractor_1": "human resource specialist",
        "distractor_2": "compensation, benefits, and job analysis specialist",
        "distractor_3": "interviewer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9525",
        "question": "What types of questions will appear on an interest survey?",
        "answer": "questions about how much you enjoy specific activities",
        "distractor_1": "questions about your physical abilities",
        "distractor_2": "questions about your grades in classes associated with specific careers",
        "distractor_3": "questions about your mental abilities"
      },
      {
        "id": "9526",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technician career level?",
        "answer": "interviewer",
        "distractor_1": "compensation, benefits, and job analysis specialist",
        "distractor_2": "human resource manager",
        "distractor_3": "labor relations manager"
      },
      {
        "id": "9527",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the professional career level?",
        "answer": "compensation, benefits, and job analysis specialist",
        "distractor_1": "interviewer",
        "distractor_2": "human resource specialist",
        "distractor_3": "human resource assistant"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2064",
    "name": "Artistic Communication",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9528",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Audio and Video Technology and Film pathway?",
        "answer": "audio/video designer",
        "distractor_1": "fashion designer",
        "distractor_2": "dancer",
        "distractor_3": "musician"
      },
      {
        "id": "9529",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Printing Technology pathway?",
        "answer": "webpage designer",
        "distractor_1": "audio/video designer",
        "distractor_2": "video systems technician",
        "distractor_3": "dancer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9530",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the professional career level?",
        "answer": "director",
        "distractor_1": "sound engineer",
        "distractor_2": "video editor",
        "distractor_3": "audio support"
      },
      {
        "id": "9531",
        "question": "Which of the following is not one of the five Ws?",
        "answer": "whose",
        "distractor_1": "when",
        "distractor_2": "what",
        "distractor_3": "who"
      },
      {
        "id": "9532",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Telecommunications pathway?",
        "answer": "cable installer",
        "distractor_1": "video systems technician",
        "distractor_2": "dancer",
        "distractor_3": "musician"
      },
      {
        "id": "9533",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technologist career level?",
        "answer": "video editor",
        "distractor_1": "screenwriter",
        "distractor_2": "producer",
        "distractor_3": "director"
      },
      {
        "id": "9534",
        "question": "Which of the following describes the act of shortening a video clip for length?",
        "answer": "trim",
        "distractor_1": "stretch",
        "distractor_2": "splice",
        "distractor_3": "contour"
      },
      {
        "id": "9535",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Journalism and Broadcasting pathway?",
        "answer": "radio announcer",
        "distractor_1": "video systems technician",
        "distractor_2": "dancer",
        "distractor_3": "curator"
      },
      {
        "id": "9536",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Performing Arts pathway?",
        "answer": "costume designer",
        "distractor_1": "audio/video designer",
        "distractor_2": "video systems technician",
        "distractor_3": "curator"
      },
      {
        "id": "9537",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Visual Arts pathway?",
        "answer": "commercial photographer",
        "distractor_1": "video systems technician",
        "distractor_2": "dancer",
        "distractor_3": "musician"
      },
      {
        "id": "9538",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a common camera angle shot?",
        "answer": "small",
        "distractor_1": "medium",
        "distractor_2": "close-up",
        "distractor_3": "wide"
      },
      {
        "id": "9539",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a common camera motion?",
        "answer": "hop",
        "distractor_1": "tilt",
        "distractor_2": "pan",
        "distractor_3": "dolly"
      },
      {
        "id": "9540",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technician career level?",
        "answer": "video support",
        "distractor_1": "screenwriter",
        "distractor_2": "producer",
        "distractor_3": "director"
      },
      {
        "id": "9541",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a common story element?",
        "answer": "comedy",
        "distractor_1": "action",
        "distractor_2": "wants",
        "distractor_3": "hero"
      },
      {
        "id": "9542",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Performing Arts pathway?",
        "answer": "stage manager",
        "distractor_1": "audio/video designer",
        "distractor_2": "video systems technician",
        "distractor_3": "curator"
      },
      {
        "id": "9543",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Printing Technology pathway?",
        "answer": "tile setter",
        "distractor_1": "audio/video designer",
        "distractor_2": "video systems technician",
        "distractor_3": "dancer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9544",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a common story element?",
        "answer": "drama",
        "distractor_1": "resolution",
        "distractor_2": "climax",
        "distractor_3": "conflict"
      },
      {
        "id": "9545",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Telecommunications pathway?",
        "answer": "systems analyst",
        "distractor_1": "musician",
        "distractor_2": "dancer",
        "distractor_3": "video systems technician"
      },
      {
        "id": "9546",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Journalism and Broadcasting pathway?",
        "answer": "station manager",
        "distractor_1": "curator",
        "distractor_2": "video systems technician",
        "distractor_3": "dancer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9547",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Visual Arts pathway?",
        "answer": "interior designer",
        "distractor_1": "musician",
        "distractor_2": "dancer",
        "distractor_3": "video systems technician"
      },
      {
        "id": "9548",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a common camera motion?",
        "answer": "wobble",
        "distractor_1": "zoom",
        "distractor_2": "tilt",
        "distractor_3": "truck"
      },
      {
        "id": "9549",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the professional career level?",
        "answer": "producer",
        "distractor_1": "sound engineer",
        "distractor_2": "video editor",
        "distractor_3": "audio support"
      },
      {
        "id": "9550",
        "question": "Which of the following careers would you most likely find in the Audio and Video Technology and Film pathway?",
        "answer": "video systems technician",
        "distractor_1": "musician",
        "distractor_2": "dancer",
        "distractor_3": "fashion designer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9551",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technologist career level?",
        "answer": "sound engineer",
        "distractor_1": "screenwriter",
        "distractor_2": "producer",
        "distractor_3": "director"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "2065",
    "name": "Remote Aquabotics",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "9552",
        "question": "What is the upward force that a fluid exerts on an object that is either completely or partially submerged in that fluid?",
        "answer": "buoyancy",
        "distractor_1": "lift",
        "distractor_2": "drag",
        "distractor_3": "hydrodynamics"
      },
      {
        "id": "9553",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the professional career level?",
        "answer": "marine engineer",
        "distractor_1": "commercial diver",
        "distractor_2": "photographer",
        "distractor_3": "product test specialist"
      },
      {
        "id": "9554",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technologist career level?",
        "answer": "commercial diver",
        "distractor_1": "electrical and electronic equipment assembler",
        "distractor_2": "photographer",
        "distractor_3": "marine engineer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9555",
        "question": "Which term applies to workers who are specialists in their field because of their experience, training, and possible associate’s degrees?",
        "answer": "technologist",
        "distractor_1": "professional",
        "distractor_2": "expert",
        "distractor_3": "technician"
      },
      {
        "id": "9556",
        "question": "Which of these careers would you expect to have an annual salary above $60,000?",
        "answer": "marine engineer",
        "distractor_1": "commercial diver",
        "distractor_2": "photographer",
        "distractor_3": "product test specialist"
      },
      {
        "id": "9557",
        "question": "Which of these careers would you expect to have an annual salary between $40,000 and $60,000?",
        "answer": "commercial diver",
        "distractor_1": "electrical and electronic equipment assembler",
        "distractor_2": "photographer",
        "distractor_3": "marine engineer"
      },
      {
        "id": "9558",
        "question": "Which term applies to workers who specialize in a discipline and will usually have at least a four-year degree?",
        "answer": "professional",
        "distractor_1": "expert",
        "distractor_2": "technician",
        "distractor_3": "technologist"
      },
      {
        "id": "9559",
        "question": "Which of these careers would you expect to have an annual salary below $40,000?",
        "answer": "electrical and electronic equipment assembler",
        "distractor_1": "commercial diver",
        "distractor_2": "hydrologist",
        "distractor_3": "product test specialist"
      },
      {
        "id": "9560",
        "question": "When using an ROV to complete inspections underwater, you would want the buoyancy of an ROV to be which of the following to conserve battery power?",
        "answer": "low",
        "distractor_1": "high",
        "distractor_2": "neutral",
        "distractor_3": "none"
      },
      {
        "id": "9561",
        "question": "Which term applies to workers who are skilled at a task or specific job but don’t have a great deal of education?",
        "answer": "technician",
        "distractor_1": "expert",
        "distractor_2": "professional",
        "distractor_3": "technologist"
      },
      {
        "id": "9562",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technician career level?",
        "answer": "electrical and electronic equipment assembler",
        "distractor_1": "commercial diver",
        "distractor_2": "hydrologist",
        "distractor_3": "product test specialist"
      },
      {
        "id": "9563",
        "question": "Which term describes the “global aspects of work that are important to a person’s satisfaction”?",
        "answer": "work values",
        "distractor_1": "work context",
        "distractor_2": "work skills",
        "distractor_3": "work activities"
      },
      {
        "id": "9564",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technologist career level?",
        "answer": "product test specialist",
        "distractor_1": "marine engineer",
        "distractor_2": "photographer",
        "distractor_3": "electrical and electronic equipment assembler"
      },
      {
        "id": "9565",
        "question": "Which of these careers would you expect to have an annual salary above $60,000?",
        "answer": "hydrologist",
        "distractor_1": "photographer",
        "distractor_2": "commercial diver",
        "distractor_3": "electrical and electronic equipment assembler"
      },
      {
        "id": "9566",
        "question": "When retrieving items from the bottom of a body of water, you would want the buoyancy of an ROV to be which of the following to conserve battery power?",
        "answer": "high",
        "distractor_1": "low",
        "distractor_2": "neutral",
        "distractor_3": "none"
      },
      {
        "id": "9567",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the technician career level?",
        "answer": "photographer",
        "distractor_1": "product test specialist",
        "distractor_2": "commercial diver",
        "distractor_3": "hydrologist"
      },
      {
        "id": "9568",
        "question": "Which of these careers would you expect to have an annual salary between $40,000and $60,000?",
        "answer": "product test specialist",
        "distractor_1": "photographer",
        "distractor_2": "marine engineer",
        "distractor_3": "electrical and electronic equipment assembler"
      },
      {
        "id": "9569",
        "question": "When using an ROV to complete a task at a specific depth for a long period of time,you would want the buoyancy of an ROV to be which of the following to conservebattery power?",
        "answer": "neutral",
        "distractor_1": "high",
        "distractor_2": "low",
        "distractor_3": "none"
      },
      {
        "id": "9570",
        "question": "Which of the following careers is most likely at the professional career level?",
        "answer": "hydrologist",
        "distractor_1": "commercial diver",
        "distractor_2": "photographer",
        "distractor_3": "electrical and electronic equipment assembler"
      },
      {
        "id": "9571",
        "question": "Which of these careers would you expect to have an annual salary below $40,000?",
        "answer": "photographer",
        "distractor_1": "product test specialist",
        "distractor_2": "hydrologist",
        "distractor_3": "commercial diver"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "101",
    "name": "BioEngineering",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1794",
        "question": "Choose the device that is used to measure range of motion or the angle of a joint.",
        "answer": "goniometer",
        "distractor_1": "compass",
        "distractor_2": "dynamometer",
        "distractor_3": "thermometer"
      },
      {
        "id": "1795",
        "question": "Which term best defines an angle with a size between 0 degrees and 90 degrees?",
        "answer": "acute",
        "distractor_1": "straight",
        "distractor_2": "obtuse",
        "distractor_3": "right"
      },
      {
        "id": "1798",
        "question": "What is the sum of 8 + 16 + (-24) +  (-8)?",
        "answer": "-8",
        "distractor_1": "8",
        "distractor_2": "56",
        "distractor_3": "40"
      },
      {
        "id": "1800",
        "question": "Which term is used to describe objects that fly through the air, including a discus, Frisbee™, and baseball?",
        "answer": "projectiles",
        "distractor_1": "trajectories",
        "distractor_2": "velocities",
        "distractor_3": "torques"
      },
      {
        "id": "1801",
        "question": "Which term is used to describe the flexibility of a joint?",
        "answer": "range of motion",
        "distractor_1": "extension",
        "distractor_2": "flexion",
        "distractor_3": "hyperextension"
      },
      {
        "id": "1803",
        "question": "Choose the term that best defines a number's distance from zero on the number line.",
        "answer": "absolute value",
        "distractor_1": "opposite",
        "distractor_2": "total value",
        "distractor_3": "positive or negative value"
      },
      {
        "id": "1804",
        "question": "What is the sum of two angles that are said to be complementary?",
        "answer": "90º",
        "distractor_1": "180º",
        "distractor_2": "360º",
        "distractor_3": "45º"
      },
      {
        "id": "1805",
        "question": "What is the average of 11, -14, and 10?",
        "answer": "2.33",
        "distractor_1": "7",
        "distractor_2": "11.67",
        "distractor_3": "35"
      },
      {
        "id": "1806",
        "question": "Name the apparatus used to measure joint range of motion.",
        "answer": "goniometer",
        "distractor_1": "compass",
        "distractor_2": "thermometer",
        "distractor_3": "dynamometer"
      },
      {
        "id": "1807",
        "question": "What is the sum of two angles that are supplementary?",
        "answer": "180º",
        "distractor_1": "360º",
        "distractor_2": "45º",
        "distractor_3": "90º"
      },
      {
        "id": "1808",
        "question": "What are the four classifications of angles?",
        "answer": "obtuse, acute, straight, right",
        "distractor_1": "supplementary, complementary, straight, right",
        "distractor_2": "obtuse, acute, supplementary, right",
        "distractor_3": "acute, supplementary, straight, right"
      },
      {
        "id": "1809",
        "question": "What is the average of 11 3/4, 6 1/4, and -2?",
        "answer": "5.33",
        "distractor_1": "-16",
        "distractor_2": "-5.33",
        "distractor_3": "16"
      },
      {
        "id": "1810",
        "question": "What is the sum of -15 and 6?",
        "answer": "-9",
        "distractor_1": "-21",
        "distractor_2": "21",
        "distractor_3": "9"
      },
      {
        "id": "1811",
        "question": "Identify the obtuse angle measurement.",
        "answer": "135º",
        "distractor_1": "30º",
        "distractor_2": "90º",
        "distractor_3": "180º"
      },
      {
        "id": "1814",
        "question": "Identify the acute angle.",
        "answer": "30º",
        "distractor_1": "135º",
        "distractor_2": "90º",
        "distractor_3": "180º"
      },
      {
        "id": "6897",
        "question": "Name the only biological tissue capable of developing tension.",
        "answer": "muscle",
        "distractor_1": "bone",
        "distractor_2": "cartilage",
        "distractor_3": "skin"
      },
      {
        "id": "6898",
        "question": "Find the average of the following numbers: 5 1/4, -5 1/4, 11 3/4, and -6.",
        "answer": "1.4375",
        "distractor_1": "5.75",
        "distractor_2": "7.0625",
        "distractor_3": "28.25"
      },
      {
        "id": "6899",
        "question": "Choose the term that is best defined as range of motion or degree of movement within a joint.",
        "answer": "flexibility",
        "distractor_1": "coefficient",
        "distractor_2": "extension",
        "distractor_3": "hyperextension"
      },
      {
        "id": "6900",
        "question": "What are the three basic body shapes?",
        "answer": "mesomorph, endomorph, and ectomorph",
        "distractor_1": "endomorph, ligaments, and mesomorph",
        "distractor_2": "ectomorph, mesomorph, and muscles",
        "distractor_3": "tendons, muscles, and ligaments"
      },
      {
        "id": "6901",
        "question": "What is the supplementary angle to an 85° angle?",
        "answer": "95°",
        "distractor_1": "5°",
        "distractor_2": "90°",
        "distractor_3": "100°"
      },
      {
        "id": "6902",
        "question": "Name the force created by spin, such as with a properly hit golf ball or properly thrown curve ball.",
        "answer": "magnus force",
        "distractor_1": "propulsive force",
        "distractor_2": "laminar force",
        "distractor_3": "momentum"
      },
      {
        "id": "6903",
        "question": "Which of the following angles is the angle complementary to a 45° angle?",
        "answer": "45°",
        "distractor_1": "315°",
        "distractor_2": "135°",
        "distractor_3": "55°"
      },
      {
        "id": "1815",
        "question": "What is the name of an angle that measures between 90 and 180 degrees?",
        "answer": "obtuse",
        "distractor_1": "acute",
        "distractor_2": "straight",
        "distractor_3": "right"
      },
      {
        "id": "1816",
        "question": "Choose the term that is best described by the following items: things that move through the air unassisted, including a basketball, a discus, and a high jumper.",
        "answer": "projectiles",
        "distractor_1": "trajectories",
        "distractor_2": "torques",
        "distractor_3": "velocities"
      },
      {
        "id": "8260",
        "question": "Which of the following defines absolute value?",
        "answer": "the distance a number is from zero on a number line",
        "distractor_1": "the product of two numbers",
        "distractor_2": "the sum of two numbers",
        "distractor_3": "the square root of a number"
      },
      {
        "id": "5436",
        "question": "What does it mean to separate into parts or basic principles?",
        "answer": "analyze",
        "distractor_1": "inspect",
        "distractor_2": "dissect",
        "distractor_3": "observe"
      },
      {
        "id": "5437",
        "question": "Which of the following terms is defined as a close or exact reproduction?",
        "answer": "image",
        "distractor_1": "mirror image",
        "distractor_2": "duplicate",
        "distractor_3": "copy"
      },
      {
        "id": "5438",
        "question": "Which term refers to one's ability to be physically strong, muscular, or active?",
        "answer": "athleticism",
        "distractor_1": "athletic ability",
        "distractor_2": "super human",
        "distractor_3": "powerful"
      },
      {
        "id": "5439",
        "question": "What is a number within the set of positive and negative whole numbers and zero?",
        "answer": "integer",
        "distractor_1": "absolute value",
        "distractor_2": "exponent",
        "distractor_3": "whole number"
      },
      {
        "id": "5440",
        "question": "What is defined as a point where two sides meet?",
        "answer": "vertex",
        "distractor_1": "right angle",
        "distractor_2": "corner",
        "distractor_3": "segment"
      },
      {
        "id": "5441",
        "question": "Which term is defined as the extension of a body limb beyond normal limits?",
        "answer": "hyperextension",
        "distractor_1": "overextension",
        "distractor_2": "flexibility",
        "distractor_3": "rotation"
      },
      {
        "id": "5442",
        "question": "What is a number that when added to another number equals zero?",
        "answer": "additive inverse",
        "distractor_1": "binomial",
        "distractor_2": "absolute value",
        "distractor_3": "integer"
      },
      {
        "id": "5443",
        "question": "What is the unit of angle measurement?",
        "answer": "degree",
        "distractor_1": "inch",
        "distractor_2": "meter",
        "distractor_3": "centimeter"
      },
      {
        "id": "5444",
        "question": "Which of the following acronyms stands for range of motion?",
        "answer": "ROM",
        "distractor_1": "RAOM",
        "distractor_2": "RM",
        "distractor_3": "Rm"
      },
      {
        "id": "5445",
        "question": "Which of the following are described as two angles with a sum that equals 90º?",
        "answer": "complementary angle",
        "distractor_1": "supplementary angle",
        "distractor_2": "obtuse angle",
        "distractor_3": "right angle"
      },
      {
        "id": "5446",
        "question": "Which of the following is described as two angles with a sum that equals 180º?",
        "answer": "supplementary angle",
        "distractor_1": "obtuse angle",
        "distractor_2": "acute angle",
        "distractor_3": "straight angle"
      },
      {
        "id": "5447",
        "question": "What is defined as the ability of something to be bent or stretched?",
        "answer": "flexibility",
        "distractor_1": "elasticity",
        "distractor_2": "athleticism",
        "distractor_3": "hyperextension"
      },
      {
        "id": "5448",
        "question": "Which of the following is an angle with a measurement of 180º?",
        "answer": "straight angle",
        "distractor_1": "obtuse angle",
        "distractor_2": "acute angle",
        "distractor_3": "complementary angle"
      },
      {
        "id": "5449",
        "question": "Which of the following angles is a 90º angle?",
        "answer": "right angle",
        "distractor_1": "straight angle",
        "distractor_2": "obtuse angle ",
        "distractor_3": "acute angle"
      },
      {
        "id": "5450",
        "question": "Which of the following is referred to as a device for firing objects?",
        "answer": "launcher",
        "distractor_1": "projectile",
        "distractor_2": "arm",
        "distractor_3": "ejector"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "102",
    "name": "Confident Consumer",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2256",
        "question": "The 'Percent Daily Values' of a certain substance per serving is required to appear on nutrition labels for food products. What is that substance?",
        "answer": "fat",
        "distractor_1": "calories",
        "distractor_2": "sugar",
        "distractor_3": "protein"
      },
      {
        "id": "2257",
        "question": "What is the price of an item divided by its number of units, its weight, or its volume?",
        "answer": "unit price",
        "distractor_1": "dividend",
        "distractor_2": "value price",
        "distractor_3": "content price"
      },
      {
        "id": "2259",
        "question": "How many calories are in each gram of fat?",
        "answer": "9",
        "distractor_1": "7",
        "distractor_2": "4",
        "distractor_3": "3"
      },
      {
        "id": "2262",
        "question": "On a nutrition label, what is based on a 2,000-calorie diet?",
        "answer": "Percent Daily Values",
        "distractor_1": "Recommended Dietary Allowances",
        "distractor_2": "serving sizes",
        "distractor_3": "total calories"
      },
      {
        "id": "2263",
        "question": "The FDA requires that nutrition labels contain the 'Percent Daily Values' of what substance?",
        "answer": "fat",
        "distractor_1": "calories",
        "distractor_2": "sugar",
        "distractor_3": "protein"
      },
      {
        "id": "2267",
        "question": "The 'Percent Daily Values' printed on food labels are based on a certain number of calories in a diet. What is the number of calories?",
        "answer": "2,000",
        "distractor_1": "1,500",
        "distractor_2": "2,500",
        "distractor_3": "3,000"
      },
      {
        "id": "2268",
        "question": "What is the date on a food item that indicates the last date the item should be sold called?",
        "answer": "pull date",
        "distractor_1": "open date",
        "distractor_2": "last chance date",
        "distractor_3": "expiration date"
      },
      {
        "id": "2269",
        "question": "What is a ratio that compares a number to 100 called?",
        "answer": "percentage",
        "distractor_1": "proportion",
        "distractor_2": "rate",
        "distractor_3": "metric"
      },
      {
        "id": "2272",
        "question": "Unit price is determined by dividing what two factors?",
        "answer": "price ÷ size",
        "distractor_1": "size ÷ price",
        "distractor_2": "units ÷ price",
        "distractor_3": "price x units"
      },
      {
        "id": "2273",
        "question": "How many calories are used in the diet on which nutrition labels on food products are generally based?",
        "answer": "2,000",
        "distractor_1": "1,500",
        "distractor_2": "2,500",
        "distractor_3": "3,000"
      },
      {
        "id": "2276",
        "question": "Trading stamps, coupons, contests, rebates, and prizes are all forms of what?",
        "answer": "buying incentives",
        "distractor_1": "puffery",
        "distractor_2": "clearance sales",
        "distractor_3": "packaging"
      },
      {
        "id": "2280",
        "question": "The maximum Recommended Dietary Allowance (RDA) of fat in a 2,000-calorie diet is 65 grams. What would the maximum RDA of fat be for a 2,500-calorie diet, if the recommended ratio of fat to calories were the same?",
        "answer": "about 81 grams",
        "distractor_1": "about 49 grams",
        "distractor_2": "about 52 grams",
        "distractor_3": "about 78 grams"
      },
      {
        "id": "2283",
        "question": "The RDA of carbohydrates in a 2,000-calorie diet is 300 grams. What would the RDA of carbohydrates be for a 2,500-calorie diet, if the recommended ratio of carbohydrates to calories were the same?",
        "answer": "375 grams",
        "distractor_1": "350 grams",
        "distractor_2": "400 grams",
        "distractor_3": "240 grams"
      },
      {
        "id": "5121",
        "question": "What is a mathematical way of comparing the relationship between two numbers that is expressed as a fraction?",
        "answer": "ratio",
        "distractor_1": "unit price",
        "distractor_2": "diameter",
        "distractor_3": "variable"
      },
      {
        "id": "5122",
        "question": "What is the price of a single unit of a product?  The formula is the unit price = price divided by size",
        "answer": "unit price",
        "distractor_1": "diameter",
        "distractor_2": "discount",
        "distractor_3": "subtotal"
      },
      {
        "id": "5123",
        "question": "What is a straight line segment that passes through the center of a circle or sphere from one side to the other?",
        "answer": "diameter",
        "distractor_1": "ray",
        "distractor_2": "radius",
        "distractor_3": "arc"
      },
      {
        "id": "5124",
        "question": "What is a line segment that joins the center of a circle with any point on the circumference?",
        "answer": "radius",
        "distractor_1": "diameter",
        "distractor_2": "arc",
        "distractor_3": "circle"
      },
      {
        "id": "5125",
        "question": "What does not resemble a straight line?",
        "answer": "nonlinear",
        "distractor_1": "linear",
        "distractor_2": "point",
        "distractor_3": "ray"
      },
      {
        "id": "5126",
        "question": "What resembles a straight line?",
        "answer": "linear",
        "distractor_1": "nonlinear",
        "distractor_2": "circular",
        "distractor_3": "ray"
      },
      {
        "id": "5127",
        "question": "Which is an equation that shows two equal ratios?",
        "answer": "proportion",
        "distractor_1": "nonlinear",
        "distractor_2": "variable",
        "distractor_3": "subtotal"
      },
      {
        "id": "5128",
        "question": "What is to take in or soak up?",
        "answer": "absorb",
        "distractor_1": "reflect",
        "distractor_2": "distract",
        "distractor_3": "embark"
      },
      {
        "id": "5129",
        "question": "What is the price of a product divided by the amount used?",
        "answer": "usable unit price",
        "distractor_1": "unit price",
        "distractor_2": "subtotal",
        "distractor_3": "taxable price"
      },
      {
        "id": "5130",
        "question": "What is not packaged or considered loose?",
        "answer": "bulk",
        "distractor_1": "prepackaged",
        "distractor_2": "free agent",
        "distractor_3": "premeasured"
      },
      {
        "id": "5131",
        "question": "What procedure is measured before it was packaged?",
        "answer": "premeasured",
        "distractor_1": "prepackaged",
        "distractor_2": "preabsorbed",
        "distractor_3": "prepriced"
      },
      {
        "id": "5132",
        "question": "What is suited or favorable to one's comfort, needs, or purpose?",
        "answer": "convenient",
        "distractor_1": "efficient",
        "distractor_2": "sufficient",
        "distractor_3": "expedient"
      },
      {
        "id": "5133",
        "question": "What is a symbol used in math that is not fixed in value?",
        "answer": "variable",
        "distractor_1": "unit price",
        "distractor_2": "discount",
        "distractor_3": "function"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "103",
    "name": "Digital Design",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2285",
        "question": "What is the first step in the design process?",
        "answer": "defining a goal",
        "distractor_1": "developing thumbnail sketches",
        "distractor_2": "brainstorming",
        "distractor_3": "creating a rough layout"
      },
      {
        "id": "2287",
        "question": "What is a formally balanced design called?",
        "answer": "symmetrical",
        "distractor_1": "asymmetrical",
        "distractor_2": "proportional",
        "distractor_3": "orthogonal"
      },
      {
        "id": "2289",
        "question": "Which step in the design process is defining a goal?",
        "answer": "first",
        "distractor_1": "second",
        "distractor_2": "third",
        "distractor_3": "fourth"
      },
      {
        "id": "2290",
        "question": "A formal design is a balanced design on what format?",
        "answer": "central axis",
        "distractor_1": "white background",
        "distractor_2": "page",
        "distractor_3": "classical presentation"
      },
      {
        "id": "2291",
        "question": "After brainstorming design ideas, the next step in the design process is to create something. What needs to be created?",
        "answer": "thumbnail sketch",
        "distractor_1": "rough layout",
        "distractor_2": "comprehensive layout",
        "distractor_3": "pasteup"
      },
      {
        "id": "2293",
        "question": "Which design principle's function is to pull the total design together?",
        "answer": "unity",
        "distractor_1": "proportion",
        "distractor_2": "contrast",
        "distractor_3": "rhythm"
      },
      {
        "id": "2294",
        "question": "Two identical objects lie horizontal to one another 5.37 centimeters apart. The design is formally balanced, and the center lies between the two objects. How far is the center from each object?",
        "answer": "2.685 cm",
        "distractor_1": "2.185 cm",
        "distractor_2": "3.185 cm",
        "distractor_3": "5.37 cm"
      },
      {
        "id": "2295",
        "question": "In communication, after a message has been designed, it must be coded. In a printed visual message, what is the coding called?",
        "answer": "layout",
        "distractor_1": "thumbnails",
        "distractor_2": "comprehensives",
        "distractor_3": "rhythm"
      },
      {
        "id": "2297",
        "question": "A balanced design on what format is a formal design?",
        "answer": "central axis",
        "distractor_1": "white background",
        "distractor_2": "page",
        "distractor_3": "classical presentation"
      },
      {
        "id": "2298",
        "question": "After brainstorming design ideas, the next step in the design process is creation. What should be created?",
        "answer": "thumbnail sketch",
        "distractor_1": "rough layout",
        "distractor_2": "comprehensive layout",
        "distractor_3": "pasteup"
      },
      {
        "id": "2299",
        "question": "What is a tertiary color?",
        "answer": "the combination of a secondary and a primary color",
        "distractor_1": "a color on the lower third of the color wheel",
        "distractor_2": "the third color in a triad",
        "distractor_3": "the combination of two primary colors"
      },
      {
        "id": "2300",
        "question": "What is the principle of design that uses colors, texture, and lines to provide a point of emphasis in a layout?",
        "answer": "contrast",
        "distractor_1": "balance",
        "distractor_2": "rhythm",
        "distractor_3": "proportion"
      },
      {
        "id": "2301",
        "question": "Which of the following is a principle of design?",
        "answer": "proportion",
        "distractor_1": "shape",
        "distractor_2": "color",
        "distractor_3": "texture"
      },
      {
        "id": "2302",
        "question": "What are two colors opposite one another on the color wheel called?",
        "answer": "complementary",
        "distractor_1": "warm",
        "distractor_2": "secondary",
        "distractor_3": "formal"
      },
      {
        "id": "2304",
        "question": "What is the principle of design that uses colors, texture, and lines to provide a point of emphasis in a layout?",
        "answer": "contrast",
        "distractor_1": "balance",
        "distractor_2": "rhythm",
        "distractor_3": "proportion"
      },
      {
        "id": "2305",
        "question": "Proportion is an important part of design. What is proportion considered?",
        "answer": "principle",
        "distractor_1": "shape",
        "distractor_2": "type",
        "distractor_3": "element"
      },
      {
        "id": "2306",
        "question": "Where are complementary colors located on the color wheel?",
        "answer": "opposite one another on",
        "distractor_1": "beside one another on",
        "distractor_2": "on the same side of",
        "distractor_3": "on top of"
      },
      {
        "id": "2307",
        "question": "Color is an important part of design. What part of design is color considered?",
        "answer": "element",
        "distractor_1": "principle",
        "distractor_2": "type",
        "distractor_3": "contrast"
      },
      {
        "id": "2308",
        "question": "What is the color yellow considered?",
        "answer": "primary",
        "distractor_1": "secondary",
        "distractor_2": "tertiary",
        "distractor_3": "complementary"
      },
      {
        "id": "2309",
        "question": "Identify the two calming or mild colors.",
        "answer": "blue, green",
        "distractor_1": "green, red",
        "distractor_2": "yellow, blue",
        "distractor_3": "yellow, red"
      },
      {
        "id": "2310",
        "question": "Which of the following is an element of design?",
        "answer": "color",
        "distractor_1": "rhythm",
        "distractor_2": "unity",
        "distractor_3": "contrast"
      },
      {
        "id": "2311",
        "question": "Which of the following is a primary color?",
        "answer": "yellow",
        "distractor_1": "orange",
        "distractor_2": "green",
        "distractor_3": "purple"
      },
      {
        "id": "6247",
        "question": "What is a distinctive arrangement of words and/or symbols for the name of a publication, business, or organization?",
        "answer": "Logo",
        "distractor_1": "Trademark",
        "distractor_2": "Copyright",
        "distractor_3": "Symbol"
      },
      {
        "id": "6248",
        "question": "What is the result of placing elements on a page so that they appear secure and natural, either formally or informally?",
        "answer": "Balance",
        "distractor_1": "Contrast",
        "distractor_2": "Harmony",
        "distractor_3": "Rhythm"
      },
      {
        "id": "6249",
        "question": "What is uneven in reference to balance of elements; tone, size, and shape play major parts?",
        "answer": "Asymmetrical",
        "distractor_1": "Symmetrical",
        "distractor_2": "Off-balance",
        "distractor_3": "Balance"
      },
      {
        "id": "6250",
        "question": "What is all elements are in precise relationship to one another?",
        "answer": "Formal balance",
        "distractor_1": "Informal balance",
        "distractor_2": "Negative space",
        "distractor_3": "Rhythm"
      },
      {
        "id": "6251",
        "question": "What are elements of similar weight are placed in relationship so that stability is achieved through dynamic rather than static control?",
        "answer": "Informal balance",
        "distractor_1": "Formal balance",
        "distractor_2": "Harmony ",
        "distractor_3": "Contrast"
      },
      {
        "id": "6252",
        "question": "What is also called white space; usually the empty space surrounding the elements in a design?",
        "answer": "Negative space",
        "distractor_1": "Harmony",
        "distractor_2": "Informal balance",
        "distractor_3": "Balance"
      },
      {
        "id": "6253",
        "question": "What are dividing lines, usually termed x and y, that split a space into four quadrants?",
        "answer": "Axis",
        "distractor_1": "Color wheel",
        "distractor_2": "Balance",
        "distractor_3": "Proportion"
      },
      {
        "id": "6254",
        "question": "What is a tool that organizes colors by how they are made; for example, orange is between red and yellow; the color wheel also allows the artist to pick complementary and contrasting colors easily?",
        "answer": "Color Wheel",
        "distractor_1": "Logo",
        "distractor_2": "Complimentary colors",
        "distractor_3": "Rhythm"
      },
      {
        "id": "6255",
        "question": "What is created by adding light tints (addition of white) or shades (addition of black) to a color, difference is emphasized; for example, by adding light green text to a dark green background, you will grab the reader's attention?",
        "answer": "Contrasting colors",
        "distractor_1": "Complimentary colors",
        "distractor_2": "Negative space",
        "distractor_3": "Informal balance"
      },
      {
        "id": "6257",
        "question": "What is when all parts of a layout work together to achieve their intended messages?",
        "answer": "Harmony",
        "distractor_1": "Rhythm",
        "distractor_2": "Balance",
        "distractor_3": "Proportion"
      },
      {
        "id": "6258",
        "question": "What is the result when a layout incorporates points, lines, shapes, textures, tones, and colors in a pleasing fashion?",
        "answer": "rhythm",
        "distractor_1": "harmony",
        "distractor_2": "balance",
        "distractor_3": "proportion"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "104",
    "name": "Digital Manufacturing",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2312",
        "question": "What term is defined as changing materials to make them more useful?",
        "answer": "manufacturing",
        "distractor_1": "construction",
        "distractor_2": "fabrication",
        "distractor_3": "modification"
      },
      {
        "id": "2313",
        "question": "This method is defined as locating addresses or locations identified by X, Y, and Z values.",
        "answer": "Cartesian coordinate system",
        "distractor_1": "XYZ system",
        "distractor_2": "computer numerical control",
        "distractor_3": "binary system"
      },
      {
        "id": "2314",
        "question": "You have been asked to provide 18 pieces of plywood that measure 16 inches by 32 inches each. How many sheets of plywood will you need? A sheet of plywood measures 4 feet by 8 feet.",
        "answer": "2",
        "distractor_1": "3",
        "distractor_2": "4",
        "distractor_3": "5"
      },
      {
        "id": "2315",
        "question": "Which of the following terms is defined as natural resources found in or on the Earth and in the oceans?",
        "answer": "raw materials",
        "distractor_1": "engineering",
        "distractor_2": "secondary",
        "distractor_3": "primary"
      },
      {
        "id": "2316",
        "question": "What term is defined as the process of taking a material and changing it to make it more useful?",
        "answer": "manufacturing",
        "distractor_1": "construction",
        "distractor_2": "fabrication",
        "distractor_3": "modification"
      },
      {
        "id": "2317",
        "question": "In order to turn raw materials into useful products, what two processes need to occur?",
        "answer": "primary and secondary",
        "distractor_1": "chemical and mechanical",
        "distractor_2": "forming and assembling",
        "distractor_3": "forming and finishing"
      },
      {
        "id": "2318",
        "question": "What are natural resources found in or on the Earth and in the oceans called?",
        "answer": "raw materials",
        "distractor_1": "engineering materials",
        "distractor_2": "standard stock",
        "distractor_3": "primary materials"
      },
      {
        "id": "2319",
        "question": "A system that links all departments of a manufacturing plant using computer software.",
        "answer": "computer-integrated manufacturing (CIM)",
        "distractor_1": "computer-aided drafting (CAD)",
        "distractor_2": "computer-aided machining (CAM)",
        "distractor_3": "computer numerical control (CNC)"
      },
      {
        "id": "2320",
        "question": "This process is defined as the changing of raw materials, such as plants, animals, and minerals, into engineering materials or standard stock.",
        "answer": "primary processing",
        "distractor_1": "conditioning",
        "distractor_2": "secondary processing",
        "distractor_3": "manufacturing"
      },
      {
        "id": "2321",
        "question": "Which axis on a milling machine travels in a vertical direction?",
        "answer": "z",
        "distractor_1": "x",
        "distractor_2": "y",
        "distractor_3": "Cartesian"
      },
      {
        "id": "2322",
        "question": "Raw materials are either renewable or exhaustible. Renewable means there is a limitless supply if managed properly. Exhaustible means that when we use all of the material available, there will be no more. Which of these materials is/are renewable?",
        "answer": "trees",
        "distractor_1": "oil",
        "distractor_2": "coal",
        "distractor_3": "metal ores"
      },
      {
        "id": "2323",
        "question": "What is the system in which all steps in producing a product are computer controlled?",
        "answer": "computer-integrated manufacturing (CIM)",
        "distractor_1": "computer-aided drafting (CAD)",
        "distractor_2": "computer-aided machining (CAM)",
        "distractor_3": "computer numerical control (CNC)"
      },
      {
        "id": "2324",
        "question": "Which axis on a milling machine travels in a vertical direction?",
        "answer": "z",
        "distractor_1": "x",
        "distractor_2": "y",
        "distractor_3": "Cartesian"
      },
      {
        "id": "2325",
        "question": "This program links all departments of a manufacturing facility together.",
        "answer": "Computer Integrated Manufacturing",
        "distractor_1": "Computers In Manufacturing",
        "distractor_2": "Computer Intelligence Monitoring",
        "distractor_3": "Continuous Integrated Manufacturing"
      },
      {
        "id": "2327",
        "question": "Raw materials are either renewable or exhaustible. Renewable means  there is a limitless supply if managed properly. Exhaustible means when we use all of the material available, there will be no more. Which of these materials is/are exhaustible?",
        "answer": "coal",
        "distractor_1": "oxygen",
        "distractor_2": "trees",
        "distractor_3": "leather"
      },
      {
        "id": "2328",
        "question": "What is one advantage that digital automation, or manufacturing, has over mechanical automation?",
        "answer": "reprogrammable",
        "distractor_1": "larger",
        "distractor_2": "more durable",
        "distractor_3": "stronger"
      },
      {
        "id": "2329",
        "question": "After the invention of the steam engine, machines began replacing skilled labor. What is this time period called?",
        "answer": "Industrial Revolution",
        "distractor_1": "Age of Discovery",
        "distractor_2": "Robot Revolution",
        "distractor_3": "Automation Age"
      },
      {
        "id": "2331",
        "question": "Digital automation, or manufacturing, has one large advantage over mechanical automation. What is that one large advantage?",
        "answer": "digitally controlled machines are reprogrammable",
        "distractor_1": "digitally controlled machines are larger",
        "distractor_2": "digitally controlled machines are more durable",
        "distractor_3": "digitally controlled machines are stronger"
      },
      {
        "id": "2332",
        "question": "During this time period, beginning in the late 1700s and going into the 1900s, machines began replacing skilled labor.",
        "answer": "Industrial Revolution",
        "distractor_1": "Age of Discovery",
        "distractor_2": "Robot Revolution",
        "distractor_3": "Automation Age"
      },
      {
        "id": "2333",
        "question": "Identify the continuous system that uses computers to operate machines and material handling devices. This system allows companies to produce small quantities of products and maintain high quality and low cost.",
        "answer": "flexible manufacturing",
        "distractor_1": "intermittent manufacturing",
        "distractor_2": "continuous manufacturing",
        "distractor_3": "custom manufacturing"
      },
      {
        "id": "2335",
        "question": "In the world of manufacturing, what does the acronym CNC stand for?",
        "answer": "computer numerical control",
        "distractor_1": "computer network center",
        "distractor_2": "cash-n-carry",
        "distractor_3": "cost-n-customer"
      },
      {
        "id": "2336",
        "question": "Which of the following is used to turn raw materials into useful products?",
        "answer": "primary and secondary processing",
        "distractor_1": "automation",
        "distractor_2": "manufacturing",
        "distractor_3": "computer control"
      },
      {
        "id": "2337",
        "question": "Which process is defined as the changing of materials to make them more useful?",
        "answer": "manufacturing",
        "distractor_1": "construction",
        "distractor_2": "production",
        "distractor_3": "engineering"
      },
      {
        "id": "2338",
        "question": "In the world of manufacturing, what does the acronym CNC stand for?",
        "answer": "computer numerical control",
        "distractor_1": "computer network center",
        "distractor_2": "cash-n-carry",
        "distractor_3": "cost-n-customer"
      },
      {
        "id": "2339",
        "question": "What term is defined as the method of locating addresses or locations identified by X, Y, and Z values?",
        "answer": "Cartesian coordinate system",
        "distractor_1": "binary system",
        "distractor_2": "XYZ system",
        "distractor_3": "computer numerical control"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "105",
    "name": "Digital Transportation",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2340",
        "question": "On a map, what does the term 'legend' mean?",
        "answer": "explanation of symbols",
        "distractor_1": "mileage chart",
        "distractor_2": "mileage scale",
        "distractor_3": "arrow pointing north"
      },
      {
        "id": "2349",
        "question": "All transportation systems have a similar structure. What three things do all systems use?",
        "answer": "energy, vehicles, routes",
        "distractor_1": "computers, vehicles, power",
        "distractor_2": "people, vehicles, fuel",
        "distractor_3": "vehicles, schedules, energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "2350",
        "question": "In the world of navigation, for what do the letters 'GPS' stand?",
        "answer": "Global Positioning System",
        "distractor_1": "Geodetic Planning System",
        "distractor_2": "Geographic Places and States",
        "distractor_3": "Geographic Placing System"
      },
      {
        "id": "2355",
        "question": "Computers use a system of 1s and 0s called the binary system. Identify the synonym for the word binary.",
        "answer": "double",
        "distractor_1": "binomial",
        "distractor_2": "decimal",
        "distractor_3": "bionics"
      },
      {
        "id": "2357",
        "question": "Identify the word defined as to move people and/or products from one place to another.",
        "answer": "transportation",
        "distractor_1": "vehicular system",
        "distractor_2": "relocation",
        "distractor_3": "freight"
      },
      {
        "id": "2359",
        "question": "Maps are divided by imaginary lines that form a grid. What are these lines called?",
        "answer": "longitude and latitude",
        "distractor_1": "vertical and horizontal",
        "distractor_2": "up and down",
        "distractor_3": "primary and secondary"
      },
      {
        "id": "2361",
        "question": "What are the four areas or environments in which transportation is conducted?",
        "answer": "land, air, water, space",
        "distractor_1": "cars, trucks, planes, boats",
        "distractor_2": "wheeled, floating, flying, weightless",
        "distractor_3": "fixed, variable, linear, random"
      },
      {
        "id": "2364",
        "question": "Something invented in the 1940s has had a great influence on all forms of transportation. What was it?",
        "answer": "computer",
        "distractor_1": "rocket",
        "distractor_2": "satellite",
        "distractor_3": "fax machine"
      },
      {
        "id": "2365",
        "question": "Satellites provide the most accurate way to do what?",
        "answer": "navigate",
        "distractor_1": "fax",
        "distractor_2": "communicate",
        "distractor_3": "tell magnetic north"
      },
      {
        "id": "2366",
        "question": "What invention most affected transportation?",
        "answer": "wheel",
        "distractor_1": "steam engine",
        "distractor_2": "airplane",
        "distractor_3": "automobile"
      },
      {
        "id": "2367",
        "question": "When looking at a map, what direction is at the top of the map?",
        "answer": "north",
        "distractor_1": "west",
        "distractor_2": "east",
        "distractor_3": "south"
      },
      {
        "id": "6262",
        "question": "What is data in the form of numerical digits that are used by computers?",
        "answer": "digital",
        "distractor_1": "navigation",
        "distractor_2": "binary",
        "distractor_3": "latitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "6263",
        "question": "What is the location and guiding of a vehicle along a route?",
        "answer": "navigation",
        "distractor_1": "prime meridian",
        "distractor_2": "binary",
        "distractor_3": "route"
      },
      {
        "id": "6264",
        "question": "What is the longitudinal line running through Greenwich, England, used as the 0° reference for measuring longitude?",
        "answer": "prime meridian",
        "distractor_1": "equator",
        "distractor_2": "compass",
        "distractor_3": "route"
      },
      {
        "id": "6265",
        "question": "What is the latitudinal line that divides the Earth into the northern and southern hemispheres, used as the 0° reference for measuring latitude?",
        "answer": "equator",
        "distractor_1": "prime meridian",
        "distractor_2": "latitude",
        "distractor_3": "longitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "6268",
        "question": "What is a system of locating an unknown point from two or more known points by finding the lengths of the sides of triangles?",
        "answer": "trilateration",
        "distractor_1": "navigation",
        "distractor_2": "global positioning",
        "distractor_3": "itinerary"
      },
      {
        "id": "6270",
        "question": "What is the route or outline of a journey?",
        "answer": "itinerary",
        "distractor_1": "route",
        "distractor_2": "compass",
        "distractor_3": "trilateration"
      },
      {
        "id": "6271",
        "question": "What are the lines that run north-south on maps and are used to identify specific locations in east-west directions by degrees from the prime meridian called?",
        "answer": "longitude",
        "distractor_1": "latitude",
        "distractor_2": "elevation",
        "distractor_3": "equator"
      },
      {
        "id": "6272",
        "question": "What are the lines that run east-west on maps and are used to identify specific locations in north-south directions by degrees from the equator called?",
        "answer": "latitude",
        "distractor_1": "longitude",
        "distractor_2": "prime meridian",
        "distractor_3": "equator"
      },
      {
        "id": "6273",
        "question": "What is a height measured from a reference point, such as sea level?",
        "answer": "elevation",
        "distractor_1": "route",
        "distractor_2": "latitude",
        "distractor_3": "longitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "6275",
        "question": "What involves two or more states, such as an interstate highway?",
        "answer": "interstate",
        "distractor_1": "intrastate",
        "distractor_2": "out of state",
        "distractor_3": "in to state"
      },
      {
        "id": "6276",
        "question": "What is a course for traveling from one place to another?",
        "answer": "route",
        "distractor_1": "compass",
        "distractor_2": "line",
        "distractor_3": "navigation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6277",
        "question": "What is an instrument used to determine magnetic north?",
        "answer": "compass",
        "distractor_1": "route",
        "distractor_2": "navigation",
        "distractor_3": "global positioning"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "106",
    "name": "Digital Video",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2368",
        "question": "During which stage of video production is the storyboard created?",
        "answer": "preproduction",
        "distractor_1": "production",
        "distractor_2": "postproduction",
        "distractor_3": "editing"
      },
      {
        "id": "2369",
        "question": "Which of the following are two types of transitions?",
        "answer": "dissolves, wipes",
        "distractor_1": "wipes, flicks",
        "distractor_2": "cuts, breaks",
        "distractor_3": "dissolves, breaks"
      },
      {
        "id": "2370",
        "question": "Which of the listed items would not be included among the information listed on a storyboard?",
        "answer": "cost of production",
        "distractor_1": "video title",
        "distractor_2": "audio script",
        "distractor_3": "producers"
      },
      {
        "id": "2371",
        "question": "What is created during the video preproduction stage?",
        "answer": "storyboards",
        "distractor_1": "graphics",
        "distractor_2": "transitions",
        "distractor_3": "frames"
      },
      {
        "id": "2372",
        "question": "Which of the following is a proper SMPTE time code for a 30-frame-per-second video?",
        "answer": "10:15:20:25",
        "distractor_1": "02:15:60:20",
        "distractor_2": "1:2:3:4",
        "distractor_3": "10:20:30:40"
      },
      {
        "id": "2373",
        "question": "To create this type of video, the record rate must be faster than the playback rate.",
        "answer": "slow-motion",
        "distractor_1": "time-lapse",
        "distractor_2": "digital",
        "distractor_3": "professional"
      },
      {
        "id": "2374",
        "question": "What term is defined as one still image in a series of still images that are played very quickly to give the impression of smooth motion?",
        "answer": "frame",
        "distractor_1": "clip",
        "distractor_2": "line",
        "distractor_3": "segment"
      },
      {
        "id": "2375",
        "question": "The standard frame rate for a video is how many frames per second?",
        "answer": "30",
        "distractor_1": "15",
        "distractor_2": "45",
        "distractor_3": "60"
      },
      {
        "id": "2376",
        "question": "During which stage of the video production process is video shot and audio recorded?",
        "answer": "production",
        "distractor_1": "preproduction",
        "distractor_2": "postproduction",
        "distractor_3": "reassembly"
      },
      {
        "id": "2377",
        "question": "Which of the following is a proper SMPTE time code for a 30-frame-per-second video?",
        "answer": "02:02:02:02",
        "distractor_1": "01:15:45:30",
        "distractor_2": "05:10:20:40",
        "distractor_3": "10:75:30:15"
      },
      {
        "id": "2378",
        "question": "To create this type of video, the record rate must be slower than the playback rate.",
        "answer": "time-lapse",
        "distractor_1": "professional",
        "distractor_2": "digital",
        "distractor_3": "slow-motion"
      },
      {
        "id": "2379",
        "question": "What is achieved by ensuring a visual coherence from shot to shot in video production?",
        "answer": "continuity",
        "distractor_1": "sequence",
        "distractor_2": "pace",
        "distractor_3": "success"
      },
      {
        "id": "2380",
        "question": "What term is defined as a dissolve to or from a color?",
        "answer": "fade",
        "distractor_1": "cut",
        "distractor_2": "wipe",
        "distractor_3": "break"
      },
      {
        "id": "2381",
        "question": "If a video of a plane is recorded at 15 frames per second and played back at 30 frames per second, how fast would it appear to be flying compared to its actual speed?",
        "answer": "twice",
        "distractor_1": "half",
        "distractor_2": "15 times",
        "distractor_3": "30 times"
      },
      {
        "id": "2382",
        "question": "How many seconds will a 75-frame transition last in a 30-frame-per-second video?",
        "answer": "2.5",
        "distractor_1": "0.4",
        "distractor_2": "30",
        "distractor_3": "75"
      },
      {
        "id": "7329",
        "question": "During which stage of the video production process is video edited and special effects added?",
        "answer": "postproduction",
        "distractor_1": "preproduction",
        "distractor_2": "production",
        "distractor_3": "reassembly"
      },
      {
        "id": "2388",
        "question": "Which one of the items listed make up the rows of dots on the inside surface of the monitor to create an image on the computer screen?",
        "answer": "pixels",
        "distractor_1": "parcels",
        "distractor_2": "blips",
        "distractor_3": "microbes"
      },
      {
        "id": "2390",
        "question": "Why would the editing technique chroma keying be used in a video?",
        "answer": "to make a person or object appear in front of a fake background",
        "distractor_1": "to make sound align with video",
        "distractor_2": "as a transition from one clip to another",
        "distractor_3": "to create a slow-motion video"
      },
      {
        "id": "2391",
        "question": "What is the total number of pixels on a 640 x 480 screen?",
        "answer": "307,200",
        "distractor_1": "640",
        "distractor_2": "480",
        "distractor_3": "200,120"
      },
      {
        "id": "2393",
        "question": "The standard frame rate for a video is 30 frames per second. How many frames would be contained in a five-minute video?",
        "answer": "9,000",
        "distractor_1": "150",
        "distractor_2": "900",
        "distractor_3": "1,500"
      },
      {
        "id": "2394",
        "question": "Each frame in a video is given a SMPTE time code that tells its location in hours, minutes, seconds, and frames from the beginning of a tape. What is the SMPTE time code for a frame 184.5 seconds from the beginning of a 30-frame-per-second video?",
        "answer": "00:03:04:15",
        "distractor_1": "00:03:04:05",
        "distractor_2": "00:00:184:15",
        "distractor_3": "00:01:84:05"
      },
      {
        "id": "2395",
        "question": "What is the total number of pixels on a 1,074 x 768 screen?",
        "answer": "824,832",
        "distractor_1": "768",
        "distractor_2": "1,074",
        "distractor_3": "1,842"
      },
      {
        "id": "5360",
        "question": "Which term refers to a short segment of video?",
        "answer": "clip",
        "distractor_1": "storyboard",
        "distractor_2": "frame",
        "distractor_3": "transition"
      },
      {
        "id": "5361",
        "question": "Which of the following is a type of edit in which the video abruptly jumps from one scene to another? ",
        "answer": "cut",
        "distractor_1": "transition",
        "distractor_2": "clip",
        "distractor_3": "animation"
      },
      {
        "id": "5362",
        "question": "Which of the following is a gradual fade from one video image to another? ",
        "answer": "dissolve",
        "distractor_1": "fade-in",
        "distractor_2": "transition",
        "distractor_3": "cut"
      },
      {
        "id": "5363",
        "question": "What is referred to as the process of assembling audio and video clips into a complete video program? ",
        "answer": "editing",
        "distractor_1": "production",
        "distractor_2": "chroma keying",
        "distractor_3": "creating a storyboard"
      },
      {
        "id": "5364",
        "question": "Which of the following is a series of cartoon-like pictures that show the main elements of the story being told? ",
        "answer": "storyboard",
        "distractor_1": "script",
        "distractor_2": "outline",
        "distractor_3": "clip"
      },
      {
        "id": "5366",
        "question": "Which of the following is a type of superimposition that replaces the background color in one picture with an image of a different picture?",
        "answer": "chroma keying",
        "distractor_1": "dissolving",
        "distractor_2": "preproduction",
        "distractor_3": "editing"
      },
      {
        "id": "5368",
        "question": "Which of the following refers to the number of images or frames displayed in one second? ",
        "answer": "frame rate",
        "distractor_1": "SMPTE time code",
        "distractor_2": "chroma-keying",
        "distractor_3": "time-lapse"
      },
      {
        "id": "5369",
        "question": "Which of the following is a type of edit, sometimes referred to as a wipe, in which one clip gradually fades into the next?",
        "answer": "transition",
        "distractor_1": "slow-motion",
        "distractor_2": "time-lapse",
        "distractor_3": "fade-in"
      },
      {
        "id": "5370",
        "question": "What is the gradual brightening of an image or the increasing of a sound?",
        "answer": "fade-in",
        "distractor_1": "break",
        "distractor_2": "cut",
        "distractor_3": "slow-motion"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "107",
    "name": "Forces",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1821",
        "question": "What occurs if an unbalanced force is exerted on a mass?",
        "answer": "acceleration",
        "distractor_1": "compensation",
        "distractor_2": "condensation",
        "distractor_3": "amalgamation"
      },
      {
        "id": "1822",
        "question": "Identify the term that represents the following statement: The tendency of an object to resist changes in its motion; that is, to stay still or keep moving with constant speed unless some force acts upon it.",
        "answer": "inertia",
        "distractor_1": "cohesion",
        "distractor_2": "force",
        "distractor_3": "momentum"
      },
      {
        "id": "1823",
        "question": "The statement 'an object in motion will remain in motion unless an outside force acts upon it' defines which law of motion?",
        "answer": "Newton's First Law of Motion",
        "distractor_1": "Newton's Second Law of Motion",
        "distractor_2": "Newton's Third Law of Motion",
        "distractor_3": "Aristotle's Law of Motion"
      },
      {
        "id": "1824",
        "question": "If an object travels 30 meters north of its position in 10 seconds, what is its average speed?",
        "answer": "3 meters per second",
        "distractor_1": "6 meters per second",
        "distractor_2": "9 meters per second",
        "distractor_3": "10 meters per second"
      },
      {
        "id": "1825",
        "question": "What is another name for Newton's first law?",
        "answer": "the law of inertia",
        "distractor_1": "F = m x a",
        "distractor_2": "the law of equal actions and reactions",
        "distractor_3": "the law of conservation of momentum"
      },
      {
        "id": "1826",
        "question": "Choose the other name for Newton's first law of motion.",
        "answer": "law of inertia",
        "distractor_1": "law of conservation of momentum",
        "distractor_2": "law of thermodynamics",
        "distractor_3": "law of conservation of energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "1827",
        "question": "In Newton's second law, what happens to an object because a force acts upon it?",
        "answer": "accelerates",
        "distractor_1": "slows down",
        "distractor_2": "balances",
        "distractor_3": "responds"
      },
      {
        "id": "1828",
        "question": "The speed of an object is dependent upon what characteristic of the force acting upon it?",
        "answer": "strength",
        "distractor_1": "sound",
        "distractor_2": "alteration",
        "distractor_3": "velocity"
      },
      {
        "id": "1829",
        "question": "Which statement infers the difference between speed and velocity?",
        "answer": "velocity implies direction",
        "distractor_1": "velocity is faster than speed",
        "distractor_2": "speed is faster than velocity",
        "distractor_3": "acceleration"
      },
      {
        "id": "1830",
        "question": "Which statement defines friction?",
        "answer": "resistance to motion between two touching objects",
        "distractor_1": "support of one object by another",
        "distractor_2": "reproduction of motion between two objects",
        "distractor_3": "an object in motion remains in motion"
      },
      {
        "id": "1832",
        "question": "Which of the following terms is best defined as the resistance to motion between two bodies in contact?",
        "answer": "friction",
        "distractor_1": "inertia",
        "distractor_2": "momentum",
        "distractor_3": "gravity"
      },
      {
        "id": "1833",
        "question": "Choose the term that is best defined as the tendency of an object to resist changes in its motion; that is, to stay still or keep moving with constant speed unless some force acts upon it.",
        "answer": "inertia",
        "distractor_1": "resistance",
        "distractor_2": "momentum",
        "distractor_3": "friction"
      },
      {
        "id": "1834",
        "question": "Which of Newton's laws states that for every action there is an equal and opposite reaction?",
        "answer": "Newton's Third Law",
        "distractor_1": "Newton's Second Law",
        "distractor_2": "Newton's First Law",
        "distractor_3": "Law of Inertia"
      },
      {
        "id": "1835",
        "question": "Identify the type of energy a roller coaster going down a hill, a little boy swinging, or a girl throwing a baseball possesses.",
        "answer": "kinetic energy",
        "distractor_1": "chemical energy",
        "distractor_2": "elastic energy",
        "distractor_3": "nuclear energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "1836",
        "question": "What type of force must be exerted on a mass in order for acceleration to occur?",
        "answer": "unbalanced",
        "distractor_1": "balanced",
        "distractor_2": "pressure",
        "distractor_3": "gravitational"
      },
      {
        "id": "1837",
        "question": "The statement 'for every action there is an equal and opposite reaction' defines which law of motion?",
        "answer": "Newton's Third Law of Motion",
        "distractor_1": "Newton's First Law of Motion",
        "distractor_2": "Newton's Second Law of Motion",
        "distractor_3": "Aristotle's Law of Motion"
      },
      {
        "id": "1838",
        "question": "A 24-newton force causes an object to accelerate at a rate of 6 meters per second squared. What is the mass of the object? (Hint: Force = mass x acceleration)",
        "answer": "4 kilograms",
        "distractor_1": "2 kilograms",
        "distractor_2": "3 kilograms",
        "distractor_3": "8 kilograms"
      },
      {
        "id": "1840",
        "question": "Which statement best defines velocity?",
        "answer": "speed with direction",
        "distractor_1": "energy with direction",
        "distractor_2": "time with speed",
        "distractor_3": "motion with direction"
      },
      {
        "id": "1841",
        "question": "Choose the formula used to calculate force.",
        "answer": "mass × acceleration",
        "distractor_1": "mass × velocity",
        "distractor_2": "distance traveled ÷ time of travel",
        "distractor_3": "change in velocity ÷ the time taken for the change"
      },
      {
        "id": "1842",
        "question": "As the mass of an object increases, what outside influence must also increase to move that object?",
        "answer": "force",
        "distractor_1": "diffusion",
        "distractor_2": "tone",
        "distractor_3": "convection"
      },
      {
        "id": "1843",
        "question": "Define centripetal force.",
        "answer": "pulls an object toward the center of rotation of a curving path",
        "distractor_1": "overcomes the inertia of a body at rest",
        "distractor_2": "keeps an object moving in a straight line",
        "distractor_3": "pushes an object away from the center of rotation of a curving path"
      },
      {
        "id": "1844",
        "question": "The momentum of an object depends on two conditions acting upon the object. What are they?",
        "answer": "mass, velocity",
        "distractor_1": "speed, time",
        "distractor_2": "force, motion",
        "distractor_3": "speed, strength"
      },
      {
        "id": "1845",
        "question": "Any and all objects with any mass are attracted to one another due to what force?",
        "answer": "gravity",
        "distractor_1": "friction",
        "distractor_2": "balanced forces",
        "distractor_3": "positive attraction"
      },
      {
        "id": "1846",
        "question": "Which term is defined as the force applied to the object divided by the mass of the object?",
        "answer": "acceleration",
        "distractor_1": "speed",
        "distractor_2": "velocity",
        "distractor_3": "mass"
      },
      {
        "id": "1848",
        "question": "What is the name of the force that pulls an object toward the center of rotation of a curving path?",
        "answer": "centripetal force",
        "distractor_1": "momentum",
        "distractor_2": "conservation of energy",
        "distractor_3": "velocity"
      },
      {
        "id": "6428",
        "question": "What is change in an object’s position?",
        "answer": "Motion",
        "distractor_1": "Velocity",
        "distractor_2": "Speed",
        "distractor_3": "Momentum"
      },
      {
        "id": "6429",
        "question": "What is an object at rest?",
        "answer": "Inert object",
        "distractor_1": "Ert object",
        "distractor_2": "Centripetal force",
        "distractor_3": "Balanced force"
      },
      {
        "id": "6430",
        "question": "What is the rate at which the velocity of a moving object decreases over time?",
        "answer": "Deceleration",
        "distractor_1": "Acceleration",
        "distractor_2": "Speed",
        "distractor_3": "Momentum"
      },
      {
        "id": "6431",
        "question": "What is the amount of material that an object contains?",
        "answer": "Mass",
        "distractor_1": "Weight",
        "distractor_2": "Velocity",
        "distractor_3": "Speed"
      },
      {
        "id": "6432",
        "question": "What is the property of a moving object that determines the length of time needed to bring it to rest?",
        "answer": "Momentum",
        "distractor_1": "Speed",
        "distractor_2": "Velocity",
        "distractor_3": "Acceleration"
      },
      {
        "id": "6433",
        "question": "What is the distance an object travels per unit of time?",
        "answer": "Speed",
        "distractor_1": "Velocity",
        "distractor_2": "Force",
        "distractor_3": "Acceleration"
      },
      {
        "id": "6434",
        "question": "What is force that is counterbalanced?",
        "answer": "Balanced force",
        "distractor_1": "Unbalanced force",
        "distractor_2": "Centripetal force",
        "distractor_3": "Centrifugal force"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "108",
    "name": "Gravity",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2609",
        "question": "Which coordinate in a coordinate pair is listed last?",
        "answer": "y-coordinate",
        "distractor_1": "x-coordinate",
        "distractor_2": "larger value",
        "distractor_3": "least important number"
      },
      {
        "id": "2613",
        "question": "What is a variable?",
        "answer": "a letter, symbol, or combination of letters and symbols that represents an unknown or changing value",
        "distractor_1": "a letter, symbol, or combination of letters and symbols that represents an acceleration due to gravity",
        "distractor_2": "a letter, symbol, or combination of letters and symbols that represents time and velocity",
        "distractor_3": "a letter, symbol, or combination of letters and symbols that represents the position of a point on a plane"
      },
      {
        "id": "2615",
        "question": "What is the rate of change of velocity?",
        "answer": "acceleration",
        "distractor_1": "speed",
        "distractor_2": "gravitation",
        "distractor_3": "motion"
      },
      {
        "id": "2616",
        "question": "In a coordinate pair, which coordinate is listed first?",
        "answer": "x-coordinate",
        "distractor_1": "y-coordinate",
        "distractor_2": "larger value",
        "distractor_3": "more important number"
      },
      {
        "id": "2618",
        "question": "Which of the following is a letter, symbol, or combination of letters and symbols that represents an unknown or changing value?",
        "answer": "variable",
        "distractor_1": "coordinate",
        "distractor_2": "point",
        "distractor_3": "coefficient"
      },
      {
        "id": "2629",
        "question": "Which statement best describes the changes in energy as an object falls?",
        "answer": "Kinetic energy increases while potential energy decreases.",
        "distractor_1": "Kinetic energy increases while total energy decreases.",
        "distractor_2": "Potential energy increases while total energy decreases.",
        "distractor_3": "Potential energy increases while kinetic energy decreases."
      },
      {
        "id": "2630",
        "question": "What is a condition in which the force of gravity seems to disappear because a spaceship and its contents are free falling at the same rate?",
        "answer": "microgravity",
        "distractor_1": "orbit",
        "distractor_2": "equilibrium",
        "distractor_3": "quantum physics"
      },
      {
        "id": "8254",
        "question": "What term is defined as a proposed answer to a question?",
        "answer": "hypothesis",
        "distractor_1": "experiment",
        "distractor_2": "observation",
        "distractor_3": "variable"
      },
      {
        "id": "6459",
        "question": "What is the force of attraction between two bodies caused by the bodies' masses and is normally associated with the force a large object such as Earth exerts on objects close to it?",
        "answer": "gravity",
        "distractor_1": "magnetism",
        "distractor_2": "pressure",
        "distractor_3": "applied force"
      },
      {
        "id": "6460",
        "question": "What is the rate change in an object's position?",
        "answer": "velocity",
        "distractor_1": "vertex",
        "distractor_2": "rotation",
        "distractor_3": "acceleration"
      },
      {
        "id": "6461",
        "question": "What are a set of numbers that describes an object's position in reference to a set of axes?",
        "answer": "coordinates",
        "distractor_1": "slope",
        "distractor_2": "formula",
        "distractor_3": "location"
      },
      {
        "id": "6462",
        "question": "What is the ratio of the difference in y-values between two points divided by the difference in x-values between the same points?",
        "answer": "slope",
        "distractor_1": "velocity",
        "distractor_2": "variable",
        "distractor_3": "distance"
      },
      {
        "id": "6463",
        "question": "What is the horizontal number line in a coordinate plane?",
        "answer": "x-axis",
        "distractor_1": "y-axis",
        "distractor_2": "parallel axis",
        "distractor_3": "isometric axis"
      },
      {
        "id": "6464",
        "question": "What is the vertical number line in a coordinate plane?",
        "answer": "y-axis",
        "distractor_1": "x-axis",
        "distractor_2": "perpendicular axis",
        "distractor_3": "parallel axis"
      },
      {
        "id": "6465",
        "question": "What is a value that does not change?",
        "answer": "constant",
        "distractor_1": "coordinate",
        "distractor_2": "slope",
        "distractor_3": "formula"
      },
      {
        "id": "6466",
        "question": "What is an equation that uses variables to state how a quantity can be calculated?",
        "answer": "formula",
        "distractor_1": "expression",
        "distractor_2": "statement",
        "distractor_3": "polynomial"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "109",
    "name": "Landfills",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "3088",
        "question": "What is the slimy, noxious substance at the bottom of a landfill?",
        "answer": "leachate",
        "distractor_1": "gunk",
        "distractor_2": "sewage",
        "distractor_3": "dioxins"
      },
      {
        "id": "3089",
        "question": "Many people do not want a landfill located in their community. What is the acronym for these groups?",
        "answer": "NIMBY",
        "distractor_1": "STOP",
        "distractor_2": "COPS",
        "distractor_3": "PETS"
      },
      {
        "id": "3090",
        "question": "What is water that has been drained into a garbage dump and picks up dangerous chemicals called?",
        "answer": "leachate",
        "distractor_1": "compost",
        "distractor_2": "biodegradable",
        "distractor_3": "nonrecyclable"
      },
      {
        "id": "3092",
        "question": "In an incinerator, 80 cans of garbage produce enough energy to light a lamp, night and day, for four months. How many cans of garbage would need to be incinerated to burn the lamp for one year?",
        "answer": "240 cans of garbage",
        "distractor_1": "320 cans of garbage",
        "distractor_2": "960 cans of garbage",
        "distractor_3": "80 cans of garbage"
      },
      {
        "id": "3093",
        "question": "What is the acronym of the organization known for their strong public opposition to placing landfills and other waste-disposal facilities in a community?",
        "answer": "NIMBY",
        "distractor_1": "STOP",
        "distractor_2": "COPS",
        "distractor_3": "PETS"
      },
      {
        "id": "3094",
        "question": "Silent Spring helped to change the environmental control of our world. What is Silent Spring?",
        "answer": "book",
        "distractor_1": "river",
        "distractor_2": "nuclear power plant",
        "distractor_3": "landfill"
      },
      {
        "id": "3096",
        "question": "What term is defined as something that has the ability to rot or decompose while in a landfill?",
        "answer": "biodegradable",
        "distractor_1": "leachate",
        "distractor_2": "nonbiodegradable",
        "distractor_3": "detergent"
      },
      {
        "id": "3097",
        "question": "Which agency monitors our nation's environmental protection?",
        "answer": "EPA",
        "distractor_1": "PET",
        "distractor_2": "BACT",
        "distractor_3": "POST"
      },
      {
        "id": "3098",
        "question": "The average person in this country goes through 250 six-packs of beverages in one year. Approximately how many single cans does one person have in one year?",
        "answer": "1,500 cans",
        "distractor_1": "91,250 cans",
        "distractor_2": "3,000 cans",
        "distractor_3": "365 cans"
      },
      {
        "id": "3100",
        "question": "What term is defined as something that has the ability to rot or decompose while in a landfill?",
        "answer": "biodegradable",
        "distractor_1": "leachate",
        "distractor_2": "nonbiodegradable",
        "distractor_3": "detergent"
      },
      {
        "id": "3101",
        "question": "What type of pollution can a leak in a landfill liner create?",
        "answer": "groundwater pollution",
        "distractor_1": "air pollution",
        "distractor_2": "noise pollution",
        "distractor_3": "rainwater pollution"
      },
      {
        "id": "3103",
        "question": "What term is defined as an equation stating that two ratios are equal?",
        "answer": "proportion",
        "distractor_1": "function",
        "distractor_2": "expression",
        "distractor_3": "ratio"
      },
      {
        "id": "3104",
        "question": "What is the fastest-growing segment of waste?",
        "answer": "plastics",
        "distractor_1": "glass",
        "distractor_2": "tires",
        "distractor_3": "paper"
      },
      {
        "id": "3105",
        "question": "What is another name for the ability to do work?",
        "answer": "energy",
        "distractor_1": "oxidation",
        "distractor_2": "technology",
        "distractor_3": "radiation"
      },
      {
        "id": "3106",
        "question": "What is the fastest-growing segment of waste?",
        "answer": "plastics",
        "distractor_1": "glass",
        "distractor_2": "tires",
        "distractor_3": "paper"
      },
      {
        "id": "3107",
        "question": "What is the acronym of the organization known for their strong public opposition to placing landfills and other waste-disposal facilities in a community?",
        "answer": "NIMBY",
        "distractor_1": "BACT",
        "distractor_2": "STOP",
        "distractor_3": "COPS"
      },
      {
        "id": "3109",
        "question": "What term is defined as water drained from a garbage dump that contains dangerous chemicals?",
        "answer": "leachate",
        "distractor_1": "dioxins",
        "distractor_2": "gunk",
        "distractor_3": "sewage"
      },
      {
        "id": "3110",
        "question": "Silent Spring was important in establishing the beginning of an environmental awareness. What is Silent Spring?",
        "answer": "book",
        "distractor_1": "landfill",
        "distractor_2": "nuclear power plant",
        "distractor_3": "river"
      },
      {
        "id": "3112",
        "question": "What term is defined as two ratios stated equally in an equation?",
        "answer": "proportion",
        "distractor_1": "expression",
        "distractor_2": "ratio",
        "distractor_3": "function"
      },
      {
        "id": "3113",
        "question": "What is the fastest-growing waste category?",
        "answer": "plastics",
        "distractor_1": "paper",
        "distractor_2": "glass",
        "distractor_3": "tires"
      },
      {
        "id": "3114",
        "question": "A leak in the liner of a landfill can cause what type of pollution?",
        "answer": "groundwater pollution",
        "distractor_1": "noise pollution",
        "distractor_2": "air pollution",
        "distractor_3": "rainwater pollution"
      },
      {
        "id": "3115",
        "question": "What is another name for the ability to do work?",
        "answer": "energy",
        "distractor_1": "technology",
        "distractor_2": "oxidation",
        "distractor_3": "radiation"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "110",
    "name": "Package Design",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "3144",
        "question": "The net for a cylindrical package consists of two circles and what other shape?",
        "answer": "a rectangle",
        "distractor_1": "a triangle",
        "distractor_2": "an ellipse",
        "distractor_3": "a trapezoid"
      },
      {
        "id": "3147",
        "question": "What is a tessellation?",
        "answer": "a repeating pattern that fills a plane",
        "distractor_1": "a type of transformation",
        "distractor_2": "a pair of coordinates in a plane",
        "distractor_3": "a translation whose image overlaps the original image"
      },
      {
        "id": "5316",
        "question": "Aubrey is sending a box of pecans to her uncle. The box is 14 inches by 9 inches by 8 inches. What is the volume of the box she is sending?",
        "answer": "1,008 square inches",
        "distractor_1": "31 square inches",
        "distractor_2": " 134 square inches",
        "distractor_3": " 86 square inches"
      },
      {
        "id": "5317",
        "question": "A circle with a center point (2, 3) is reflected across the x-axis. What is the center point of the reflected image of the circle?",
        "answer": "(2, -3)",
        "distractor_1": "(-2, 3)",
        "distractor_2": "(2, 3)",
        "distractor_3": "(-2, 3)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5318",
        "question": "Grandma is mailing a box of cookies to Bill at college. The box has a length of 12 inches, a width of 9 inches, and a height of 4 inches. What is the volume of the box she is sending?",
        "answer": "432 inches cubed",
        "distractor_1": "25 inches cubed",
        "distractor_2": "432 inches squared",
        "distractor_3": "25 inches squared"
      },
      {
        "id": "5319",
        "question": "If point (11, -2) were translated three units to the left, what would be its new coordinates?",
        "answer": "(8, -2)",
        "distractor_1": "(11, 1)",
        "distractor_2": "(11, -5)",
        "distractor_3": "(14, -2)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5320",
        "question": "A circle with center point (2, 3) is reflected across the y-axis. What is the center point of the reflected image of the circle?",
        "answer": "(-2, 3)",
        "distractor_1": "(3, 2)",
        "distractor_2": "(2, -3)",
        "distractor_3": "(-3, 2)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5321",
        "question": "If point (-1, -2) were translated three units up, what would be its new coordinates?",
        "answer": "(-1, 1)",
        "distractor_1": "(2, 1)",
        "distractor_2": "(1, 2)",
        "distractor_3": "(2, -2)"
      },
      {
        "id": "3150",
        "question": "In a rotation, what does not change about the object?",
        "answer": "size and shape",
        "distractor_1": "shape and orientation",
        "distractor_2": "size and orientation",
        "distractor_3": "shape and position"
      },
      {
        "id": "3151",
        "question": "What is the term for a repetitive pattern that covers a plane, leaving no gaps?",
        "answer": "tessellation",
        "distractor_1": "translation",
        "distractor_2": "transformation",
        "distractor_3": "reflection"
      },
      {
        "id": "3157",
        "question": "How many square faces are contained in a cube?",
        "answer": "6",
        "distractor_1": "4",
        "distractor_2": "8",
        "distractor_3": "10"
      },
      {
        "id": "3163",
        "question": "What is one shape that would tessellate through a translation-based tessellation?",
        "answer": "hexagon",
        "distractor_1": "triangle",
        "distractor_2": "pentagon",
        "distractor_3": "circle"
      },
      {
        "id": "3165",
        "question": "How many triangular sections would a pattern for a pyramid with a square base contain?",
        "answer": "four",
        "distractor_1": "zero",
        "distractor_2": "two",
        "distractor_3": "three"
      },
      {
        "id": "3168",
        "question": "What is the term for a transformation that slides an object along a line in a plane?",
        "answer": "translation",
        "distractor_1": "reflection",
        "distractor_2": "rotation",
        "distractor_3": "tessellation"
      },
      {
        "id": "3169",
        "question": "From what would the net for a cylindrical package be made?",
        "answer": "a rectangle and two circles",
        "distractor_1": "two circles and an ellipse",
        "distractor_2": "a circle and a trapezoid",
        "distractor_3": "two ellipses and a rectangle"
      },
      {
        "id": "6064",
        "question": "What are the flat sides of a polyhedron called?",
        "answer": "Faces",
        "distractor_1": "Planes",
        "distractor_2": "Flats",
        "distractor_3": "Intersections"
      },
      {
        "id": "6065",
        "question": "What is a line segment that marks the border of a 2-D figure, or a line segment where two faces of a 3-D figure meet?",
        "answer": "Edge",
        "distractor_1": "Intersection",
        "distractor_2": "Point",
        "distractor_3": "Plane"
      },
      {
        "id": "6066",
        "question": "What is a transformation that turns a figure about a fixed point?",
        "answer": "Rotation",
        "distractor_1": "Revolution",
        "distractor_2": "Spiral",
        "distractor_3": "Circulate"
      },
      {
        "id": "6067",
        "question": "What is a transformation that flips an object across a line?",
        "answer": "Reflection",
        "distractor_1": "Refraction",
        "distractor_2": "Rotation",
        "distractor_3": "Radiation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6068",
        "question": "What is a movement of a figure in a plane?",
        "answer": "Transformation",
        "distractor_1": "Translation",
        "distractor_2": "Tessellation",
        "distractor_3": "Taxation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6069",
        "question": "What is a repeating pattern that fills a plane?",
        "answer": "Tessellation",
        "distractor_1": "Transformation",
        "distractor_2": "Translation",
        "distractor_3": "Reflection"
      },
      {
        "id": "6070",
        "question": "What is the horizontal number line in a coordinate plane?",
        "answer": "X-axis",
        "distractor_1": "Y-axis",
        "distractor_2": "Ordered pairs",
        "distractor_3": "Coordinate grid"
      },
      {
        "id": "6071",
        "question": "What is the vertical number line in a coordinate plane?",
        "answer": "Y-axis",
        "distractor_1": "X-axis",
        "distractor_2": "Coordinate grid",
        "distractor_3": "Ordered pairs"
      },
      {
        "id": "6072",
        "question": "What is a pair of numbers that gives the coordinates of a point on a grid in this order (horizontal coordinate, vertical coordinate)?",
        "answer": "Ordered pairs",
        "distractor_1": "Coordinate grid",
        "distractor_2": "X-axis",
        "distractor_3": "Y-axis"
      },
      {
        "id": "6073",
        "question": "What is a 2-dimensional system in which the coordinates of a point are its distances from two intersecting, usually perpendicular, straight lines called axes?",
        "answer": "Coordinate grid",
        "distractor_1": "Ordered pairs",
        "distractor_2": "X-axis",
        "distractor_3": "Y-axis"
      },
      {
        "id": "6074",
        "question": "What is the number of cubic units it takes to fill a figure?",
        "answer": "Volume",
        "distractor_1": "Mass",
        "distractor_2": "Weight",
        "distractor_3": "Liter"
      },
      {
        "id": "6075",
        "question": "What is a 2-dimensional shape that can be folded into a 3-dimensional figure is a net of that figure?",
        "answer": "Net",
        "distractor_1": "Vertex",
        "distractor_2": "Volume",
        "distractor_3": "Edge"
      },
      {
        "id": "6076",
        "question": "What is the point at which two line segments, lines, or rays meet to form an angle?",
        "answer": "Vertex",
        "distractor_1": "Net",
        "distractor_2": "Volume",
        "distractor_3": "Vortex"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "111",
    "name": "Water Management",
    "weight": "90",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "4439",
        "question": "Students floated an orange from Point A to Point B in a stream, a distance of 47 feet. It took 7.8 seconds for the orange to travel this distance. What is the flow rate of the stream?",
        "answer": "about 6 ft/sec",
        "distractor_1": "about 6 sec/ft",
        "distractor_2": "about .17 ft/sec",
        "distractor_3": "about .17 sec/ft"
      },
      {
        "id": "4445",
        "question": "What is the major purpose of our modern system of water rights?",
        "answer": "controls water use so people can share water resources",
        "distractor_1": "gives people a legal right to pollute water",
        "distractor_2": "prevents farmers and industries from diverting water from a water body",
        "distractor_3": "prevents water users from removing water if the use would pollute it"
      },
      {
        "id": "8502",
        "question": "Nearly 75% of Earth’s total freshwater supply is found in ice caps and glaciers. What fraction of Earth’s freshwater supply is this?",
        "answer": "3/4",
        "distractor_1": "1/4",
        "distractor_2": "5/7",
        "distractor_3": "2/3"
      },
      {
        "id": "8503",
        "question": "Compare the units used to express area and volume.",
        "answer": "Area is in square units; volume is in cubic units.",
        "distractor_1": "Area is in cubic units; volume is in square units.",
        "distractor_2": "Area is in square units; volume is in square units per second.",
        "distractor_3": "Area is in cubic units; volume is in cubic units per second."
      },
      {
        "id": "8504",
        "question": "A triangular-shaped lake has a base length of 300 meters and a height length of 400 meters. Calculate the surface area of the lake.",
        "answer": "60,000 square meters",
        "distractor_1": "120,000 square meters",
        "distractor_2": "700 square meters",
        "distractor_3": "240,000 square meters"
      },
      {
        "id": "8505",
        "question": "A mountain stream has a flow rate of 250 gallons per second. How many gallons of water would flow through the stream in 5 minutes?",
        "answer": "75,000 gallons",
        "distractor_1": "15,000 gallons",
        "distractor_2": "50 gallons",
        "distractor_3": "1,250 gallons"
      },
      {
        "id": "8507",
        "question": "A four-sided polygon with only two sides that are parallel is in what class?",
        "answer": "trapezoid",
        "distractor_1": "parallelogram",
        "distractor_2": "rectangle",
        "distractor_3": "regular polygon"
      },
      {
        "id": "8508",
        "question": "A triangle with three congruent sides is in which class of polygons?",
        "answer": "regular polygon",
        "distractor_1": "trapezoid",
        "distractor_2": "right triangle",
        "distractor_3": "symmetric polygon"
      },
      {
        "id": "8522",
        "question": "What is the formula for determining the area of a circle?",
        "answer": "A = Pi x r²",
        "distractor_1": "A = 2 x Pi x r",
        "distractor_2": "A = (4/3) x Pi x r³",
        "distractor_3": "A = Pi x d"
      },
      {
        "id": "4452",
        "question": "Which of the following water plants has become a nuisance because it spreads rapidly and clogs waterways?",
        "answer": "water hyacinth",
        "distractor_1": "water lily",
        "distractor_2": "water plantain ",
        "distractor_3": "duckweed"
      },
      {
        "id": "4453",
        "question": "What water-dwelling insect grows large enough to prey on tadpoles and small fish?",
        "answer": "great diving beetle",
        "distractor_1": "mayfly",
        "distractor_2": "water boatman",
        "distractor_3": "water beetle"
      },
      {
        "id": "4454",
        "question": "Which characteristic is the best indicator that sewage is polluting a stream?",
        "answer": "rotten egg smell",
        "distractor_1": "orange or red coating on the water",
        "distractor_2": "presence of  insects and fish in the water",
        "distractor_3": "shiny film on the water surface"
      },
      {
        "id": "8509",
        "question": "A plastic pipe shaped like a cylinder is 35 centimeters long and has a radius of 5 centimeters. What is the approximate volume of water the pipe will hold?",
        "answer": "2,749 cubic centimeters",
        "distractor_1": "550 cubic centimeters",
        "distractor_2": "875 cubic centimeters",
        "distractor_3": "175 cubic centimeters"
      },
      {
        "id": "8510",
        "question": "Lake Tahoe has a surface area of 122,880 acres. There are 640 acres in a square mile. What is the surface area of Lake Tahoe in square miles?",
        "answer": "192 square miles",
        "distractor_1": "154 square miles ",
        "distractor_2": "22,435 square miles",
        "distractor_3": "78,643,200 square miles"
      },
      {
        "id": "4460",
        "question": "A sewage treatment lagoon is a square 50 yards on a side. The formula for area is side times side (s x s), or side squared (s²). What is the surface area of the lagoon in square feet?",
        "answer": "22,500 sq ft",
        "distractor_1": "100 sq ft",
        "distractor_2": "600 sq ft",
        "distractor_3": "2,500 sq ft"
      },
      {
        "id": "4461",
        "question": "A small lake has two sections. One is a rectangular prism 30 feet long and 10 feet wide. The other is a cube 10 feet on a side. The average depth of the whole lake is 10 feet. What is the total volume of the lake?",
        "answer": "4,000 cu ft",
        "distractor_1": "3,000 sq ft",
        "distractor_2": "4,000 sq ft",
        "distractor_3": "3,000 cu ft"
      },
      {
        "id": "5180",
        "question": "What term refers to an entire region of land that drains into a particular water body?",
        "answer": "watershed",
        "distractor_1": "area",
        "distractor_2": "volume",
        "distractor_3": "groundwater"
      },
      {
        "id": "5181",
        "question": "What is the measure of the number of square units covering a two-dimensional surface?",
        "answer": "area",
        "distractor_1": "volume",
        "distractor_2": "perimeter",
        "distractor_3": "cubes"
      },
      {
        "id": "5182",
        "question": "What term is defined as the number of cubic units it takes to fill a figure?",
        "answer": "volume",
        "distractor_1": "area",
        "distractor_2": "blocks",
        "distractor_3": "cubes"
      },
      {
        "id": "5183",
        "question": "What term below is defined as a two-dimensional closed figure composed of joined line segments, such as a triangle or rectangle?",
        "answer": "polygon",
        "distractor_1": "sphere",
        "distractor_2": "cube",
        "distractor_3": "triangular pyramid"
      },
      {
        "id": "5184",
        "question": "Which of the following is a three-dimensional structure formed by joining several polygons along their edges, such as a cube or pyramid?",
        "answer": "polyhedron",
        "distractor_1": "face",
        "distractor_2": "edge",
        "distractor_3": "sphere"
      },
      {
        "id": "5185",
        "question": "Which of the following is defined as the value representing the constant relationship between the circumference and diameter of a circle; found by dividing circumference by diameter?",
        "answer": "pi",
        "distractor_1": "radii",
        "distractor_2": "polygon",
        "distractor_3": "area"
      },
      {
        "id": "5186",
        "question": "Which term is defined as the volume of water flowing past a certain point per unit time?",
        "answer": "flow rate",
        "distractor_1": "unit price",
        "distractor_2": "flow time",
        "distractor_3": "unit ratio"
      },
      {
        "id": "5187",
        "question": "Which of the following is the mathematical way of comparing the relationship between two numbers; expressed as a fraction?",
        "answer": "ratio",
        "distractor_1": "pi",
        "distractor_2": "coordinate grid",
        "distractor_3": "symbol"
      },
      {
        "id": "5188",
        "question": "What is referred to as water that penetrates below Earth's surface, filling spaces between soil and rock particles?",
        "answer": "groundwater",
        "distractor_1": "aquifer",
        "distractor_2": "runoff",
        "distractor_3": "filtration station"
      },
      {
        "id": "5189",
        "question": "What is referred to as an underground region of soil and rock that stores groundwater?",
        "answer": "aquifer",
        "distractor_1": "flow rate",
        "distractor_2": "runoff",
        "distractor_3": "hydrology"
      },
      {
        "id": "5190",
        "question": "What is referred to as the top of the saturated zone of groundwater; defines the height, or level, of groundwater?",
        "answer": "water table",
        "distractor_1": "stream bed",
        "distractor_2": "ground zone",
        "distractor_3": "zoning grid"
      },
      {
        "id": "5191",
        "question": "What is the circular movement of water through the Earth's system, including oceans, freshwater, atmosphere, soil, and organisms?",
        "answer": "hydrologic cycle",
        "distractor_1": "cloud formation",
        "distractor_2": "runoff",
        "distractor_3": "groundwater"
      },
      {
        "id": "5192",
        "question": "What term refers to water that runs off the land surface and flows into streams and lakes?",
        "answer": "runoff",
        "distractor_1": "groundwater",
        "distractor_2": "aquifer",
        "distractor_3": "water table"
      },
      {
        "id": "5193",
        "question": "Which of the following is a symbol, usually a letter, that stands for different values?",
        "answer": "variable",
        "distractor_1": "distracter",
        "distractor_2": "function",
        "distractor_3": "pi"
      },
      {
        "id": "5194",
        "question": "What is the applied science, or technology, dealing with water flow and quality and with regulation of water use within a watershed?",
        "answer": "water management",
        "distractor_1": "farm management",
        "distractor_2": "hydrology",
        "distractor_3": "oceanography"
      },
      {
        "id": "5195",
        "question": "Which of the following is the basic science concerned with the study of water throughout the environment, including water bodies, groundwater, and the atmosphere?",
        "answer": "hydrology",
        "distractor_1": "oceanography",
        "distractor_2": "ecology",
        "distractor_3": "farm management"
      },
      {
        "id": "8511",
        "question": "Which measurement would be most useful to determine how much water is available in a lake for irrigation?",
        "answer": "the volume of water in the lake",
        "distractor_1": "the flow rate of a stream flowing into the lake",
        "distractor_2": "the surface area of the lake",
        "distractor_3": "the average percentage of the lake that evaporates daily"
      },
      {
        "id": "8512",
        "question": "Nearly 3/4 of Earth’s total freshwater supply is found in ice caps and glaciers. What percentage of Earth’s freshwater supply is this?",
        "answer": "0.75",
        "distractor_1": "0.25",
        "distractor_2": "0.66",
        "distractor_3": "0.34"
      },
      {
        "id": "8513",
        "question": "Compare the units used to express area and volume.",
        "answer": "Area is in square units; volume is in cubic units.",
        "distractor_1": "Area is in cubic units; volume is in square units.",
        "distractor_2": "Area is in square units; volume is in square units per second.",
        "distractor_3": "Area is in cubic units; volume is in cubic units per second."
      },
      {
        "id": "8514",
        "question": "A triangular-shaped lake has a base length of 200 meters and a height length of 350 meters. Calculate the surface area of the lake.",
        "answer": "35,000 square meters",
        "distractor_1": "17,500 square meters",
        "distractor_2": "70,000 square meters",
        "distractor_3": "140,000 square meters"
      },
      {
        "id": "8515",
        "question": "The Mississippi River has a flow rate of 16,790 cubic meters of water per second. How many cubic meters of water would flow through the river in 10 minutes?",
        "answer": "10,074,000 cubic meters",
        "distractor_1": "167,900 cubic meters",
        "distractor_2": "1,007,400 cubic meters",
        "distractor_3": "1,679 cubic meters"
      },
      {
        "id": "8516",
        "question": "Multiplying Pi times the radius squared will give the area of what shape?",
        "answer": "circle",
        "distractor_1": "cylinder",
        "distractor_2": "sphere",
        "distractor_3": "triangle"
      },
      {
        "id": "8517",
        "question": "A four-sided polygon has two short sides that are parallel and two long sides that are parallel. How would this polygon be classified?",
        "answer": "parallelogram",
        "distractor_1": "regular polygon",
        "distractor_2": "rhombus",
        "distractor_3": "trapezoid"
      },
      {
        "id": "8518",
        "question": "A triangle with three congruent sides is in which class of polygons?",
        "answer": "regular polygon",
        "distractor_1": "trapezoid",
        "distractor_2": "right triangle",
        "distractor_3": "symmetric polygon"
      },
      {
        "id": "8519",
        "question": "A cylindrical water storage tank used for irrigation is 3 meters tall and has a radius of 1.5 meters. What is the approximate volume of water the tank will hold?",
        "answer": "21.2 cubic meters",
        "distractor_1": "4.5 cubic meters",
        "distractor_2": "14.1 cubic meters",
        "distractor_3": "42.4 cubic meters"
      },
      {
        "id": "8520",
        "question": "A small irrigation lake has a surface area of 0.45 square miles. There are 640 acres in a square mile. What is the surface area of the lake in acres?",
        "answer": "288 acres",
        "distractor_1": "160 acres",
        "distractor_2": "320 acres ",
        "distractor_3": "1,422 acres"
      },
      {
        "id": "8521",
        "question": "Which measurement would be most useful to determine how much water is available in a reservoir used to provide drinking water for a city?",
        "answer": "the volume of water in the reservoir",
        "distractor_1": "the average percentage of the reservoir that evaporates daily",
        "distractor_2": "the surface area of the reservoir",
        "distractor_3": "the flow rate of a stream flowing into the reservoir"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "112",
    "name": "Weather",
    "weight": "90",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "4822",
        "question": "Which of the following processes occurs in Earth’s troposphere?",
        "answer": "Clouds form.",
        "distractor_1": "Ozone forms.",
        "distractor_2": "Meteors burn up.",
        "distractor_3": "Radio waves are propagated."
      },
      {
        "id": "4823",
        "question": "Which type of cloud is most likely to produce intense storms and show great vertical development?",
        "answer": "cumulonimbus",
        "distractor_1": "stratus",
        "distractor_2": "nimbostratus",
        "distractor_3": "cirrus"
      },
      {
        "id": "4824",
        "question": "Which name and description best fits an air mass that originates over a tropical ocean and blows onto a continent?",
        "answer": "maritime; warm and moist",
        "distractor_1": "maritime; hot and dry",
        "distractor_2": "continental; warm and dry",
        "distractor_3": "continental; cool and moist"
      },
      {
        "id": "4826",
        "question": "Which of the following describes drizzle drops, as compared to raindrops?",
        "answer": "smaller and closer together",
        "distractor_1": "smaller and more separated",
        "distractor_2": "larger and closer together",
        "distractor_3": "larger and more separated"
      },
      {
        "id": "4827",
        "question": "Which type of light intensity and climate will occur on the part of Earth that receives sunlight at the most direct angle?",
        "answer": "highest intensity and warmest climate",
        "distractor_1": "highest intensity and coldest climate",
        "distractor_2": "lowest intensity and warmest climate",
        "distractor_3": "lowest intensity and coldest climate"
      },
      {
        "id": "4828",
        "question": "When the Sun beats down on sunbathers on a beach, they are receiving heat through which process?",
        "answer": "radiation",
        "distractor_1": "conduction",
        "distractor_2": "convection",
        "distractor_3": "infiltration"
      },
      {
        "id": "4829",
        "question": "What name and description best fits a high-pressure region inside an air mass that is associated with sunny, cloudless skies?",
        "answer": "anticyclone, with clockwise sinking winds",
        "distractor_1": "anticyclone, with counterclockwise sinking winds",
        "distractor_2": "cyclone, with clockwise rising winds",
        "distractor_3": "cyclone, with counterclockwise rising winds"
      },
      {
        "id": "4830",
        "question": "Which two processes in the hydrologic cycle are responsible for returning water to the atmosphere?",
        "answer": "evaporation and transpiration",
        "distractor_1": "evaporation and condensation",
        "distractor_2": "transpiration and infiltration",
        "distractor_3": "condensation and transpiration"
      },
      {
        "id": "4831",
        "question": "When a boy walks in hot sand on a beach, his feet receive heat through which process?",
        "answer": "conduction",
        "distractor_1": "radiation",
        "distractor_2": "convection",
        "distractor_3": "infiltration"
      },
      {
        "id": "4832",
        "question": "The largest hailstone ever measured in the United States was seven inches across and weighed 1.7 pounds. Where did this hailstone fall?",
        "answer": "Aurora, Nebraska",
        "distractor_1": "Coffeyville, Kansas",
        "distractor_2": "Colorado Springs, Colorado",
        "distractor_3": "Naples, Maine"
      },
      {
        "id": "4833",
        "question": "Which of the following processes occurs in Earth's stratosphere?",
        "answer": "Ozone forms.",
        "distractor_1": "Clouds form.",
        "distractor_2": "Meteors burn up.",
        "distractor_3": "Radio waves are propagated."
      },
      {
        "id": "4834",
        "question": "When air reaches its dew point temperature, which process of the hydrologic cycle occurs?",
        "answer": "condensation",
        "distractor_1": "evaporation",
        "distractor_2": "precipitation",
        "distractor_3": "convection"
      },
      {
        "id": "4835",
        "question": "A cold, dry air mass originating in Canada is described by what symbol?",
        "answer": "cP",
        "distractor_1": "cA",
        "distractor_2": "mP",
        "distractor_3": "mT"
      },
      {
        "id": "4836",
        "question": "In which of the following processes is water changed from the liquid state to the gaseous state?",
        "answer": "evaporation",
        "distractor_1": "sublimation",
        "distractor_2": "deposition",
        "distractor_3": "condensation"
      },
      {
        "id": "4837",
        "question": "Which kind of front is occurring when warm and cold air masses have winds blowing in opposite directions and parallel to each other?",
        "answer": "stationary front",
        "distractor_1": "cold front",
        "distractor_2": "warm front",
        "distractor_3": "occluded front"
      },
      {
        "id": "4838",
        "question": "In what direction does the Coriolis force deflect winds in the Northern Hemisphere?",
        "answer": "to the west",
        "distractor_1": "to the south",
        "distractor_2": "to the east",
        "distractor_3": "inconsistently, depending on the season"
      },
      {
        "id": "4839",
        "question": "The Sun's radiation is responsible for the warming of Earth. What type of electromagnetic energy is responsible for this warming?",
        "answer": "infrared radiation",
        "distractor_1": "ultraviolet radiation",
        "distractor_2": "visible light",
        "distractor_3": "nuclear radiation"
      },
      {
        "id": "4840",
        "question": "What is a line on a weather map that separates areas of equal air temperature?",
        "answer": "isotherm",
        "distractor_1": "isobar",
        "distractor_2": "isomer",
        "distractor_3": "isospin"
      },
      {
        "id": "4841",
        "question": "In which of the following processes is water changed directly from the solid state to the gaseous state?",
        "answer": "sublimation",
        "distractor_1": "evaporation",
        "distractor_2": "condensation",
        "distractor_3": "deposition"
      },
      {
        "id": "4842",
        "question": "What name is given to thick, gray, undefined clouds that produce continuous precipitation?",
        "answer": "nimbostratus",
        "distractor_1": "cirrus",
        "distractor_2": "stratus",
        "distractor_3": "cumulonimbus"
      },
      {
        "id": "4843",
        "question": "The Coriolis force, which deflects wind direction, results from which of the following?",
        "answer": "Earth's rotation under the atmosphere",
        "distractor_1": "the pressure gradient force",
        "distractor_2": "the tilt of Earth's axis",
        "distractor_3": "wind friction against Earth's surface"
      },
      {
        "id": "4844",
        "question": "Which type of light intensity and climate will occur on the part of Earth that receives sunlight at the most indirect angle?",
        "answer": "lowest intensity and coldest climate",
        "distractor_1": "highest intensity and warmest climate",
        "distractor_2": "highest intensity and coldest climate",
        "distractor_3": "lowest intensity and warmest climate"
      },
      {
        "id": "4845",
        "question": "Which name and description best fits the low-pressure region occurring at a weather front?",
        "answer": "cyclone, with counterclockwise winds",
        "distractor_1": "anticyclone, with clockwise winds",
        "distractor_2": "anticyclone, with counterclockwise winds",
        "distractor_3": "cyclone, with clockwise winds"
      },
      {
        "id": "4847",
        "question": "Which kind of front is occurring when cool, cold, and warm air masses collide, forcing the warm air mass aloft?",
        "answer": "occluded front",
        "distractor_1": "cold front",
        "distractor_2": "warm front",
        "distractor_3": "stationary front"
      },
      {
        "id": "5358",
        "question": "Which level of the atmosphere is the lowest region in which weather and most cloud formations appear?",
        "answer": "troposphere",
        "distractor_1": "stratosphere",
        "distractor_2": "mesosphere",
        "distractor_3": "thermosphere"
      },
      {
        "id": "5359",
        "question": "Which layer of the atmosphere lies above the troposphere and below the mesosphere and has a relatively even temperature throughout?",
        "answer": "stratosphere",
        "distractor_1": "troposphere",
        "distractor_2": "mesosphere",
        "distractor_3": "thermosphere"
      },
      {
        "id": "5372",
        "question": "Which type of cloud is low-lying, flat, and often covers the entire sky?",
        "answer": "stratus cloud",
        "distractor_1": "cirrus cloud",
        "distractor_2": "cumulonimbus cloud",
        "distractor_3": "nimbus cloud"
      },
      {
        "id": "5373",
        "question": "What is the type of cloud that is capable of producing rain?",
        "answer": "nimbus cloud",
        "distractor_1": "cirrus cloud",
        "distractor_2": "stratocumulus cloud",
        "distractor_3": "stratus cloud"
      },
      {
        "id": "5374",
        "question": "What type of current is the transfer of heat by the circulation of heated currents within a gas or liquid?",
        "answer": "convection current",
        "distractor_1": "conduction current",
        "distractor_2": "jet stream current",
        "distractor_3": "radiation current"
      },
      {
        "id": "5375",
        "question": "Which term combines air temperature with relative humidity to express how hot it feels?",
        "answer": "heat index",
        "distractor_1": "barometric pressure",
        "distractor_2": "latent heat of fusion",
        "distractor_3": "specific heat"
      },
      {
        "id": "5376",
        "question": "Which term refers to the boundary between two air masses that have different temperatures?",
        "answer": "front",
        "distractor_1": "isobar",
        "distractor_2": "isotherm",
        "distractor_3": "jet stream"
      },
      {
        "id": "5377",
        "question": "Which term refers to a line on a weather map connecting places that have the same average temperature?",
        "answer": "isotherm",
        "distractor_1": "front",
        "distractor_2": "isobar",
        "distractor_3": "jet stream"
      },
      {
        "id": "5378",
        "question": "Which term refers to a line on a weather map connecting places that have the same barometric pressure?",
        "answer": "isobar",
        "distractor_1": "front",
        "distractor_2": "isotherm",
        "distractor_3": "jet stream"
      },
      {
        "id": "5379",
        "question": "Which term refers to a strong wind, often reaching very high speeds, that blows from a westerly direction at altitudes of 10 to 15 miles?",
        "answer": "jet stream",
        "distractor_1": "Coriolis force",
        "distractor_2": "cyclone",
        "distractor_3": "vortex"
      },
      {
        "id": "5383",
        "question": "Which term refers to the amount of water vapor in the air divided by the maximum that the air could contain?",
        "answer": "relative humidity",
        "distractor_1": "dew point",
        "distractor_2": "heat index",
        "distractor_3": "specific heat"
      },
      {
        "id": "5386",
        "question": "Which term refers to the temperature at which water vapor begins to condense, or change from a gas into a liquid?",
        "answer": "dew point",
        "distractor_1": "latent heat of vaporization",
        "distractor_2": "relative humidity",
        "distractor_3": "windchill temperature index"
      },
      {
        "id": "5389",
        "question": "Which term refers to the amount of heat per unit mass needed to increase the temperature of a specific substance one degree Celsius?",
        "answer": "specific heat",
        "distractor_1": "latent heat of fusion",
        "distractor_2": "latent heat of vaporization",
        "distractor_3": "relative humidity"
      },
      {
        "id": "5402",
        "question": "Which term refers to the amount of energy that must be added to a substance to make it change from a solid to a liquid?",
        "answer": "latent heat of fusion",
        "distractor_1": "latent heat of vaporization",
        "distractor_2": "relative humidity",
        "distractor_3": "specific heat"
      },
      {
        "id": "5403",
        "question": "Which term refers to the rotating wind produced by a tornado?",
        "answer": "vortex",
        "distractor_1": "center",
        "distractor_2": "cyclone",
        "distractor_3": "eye"
      },
      {
        "id": "5406",
        "question": "Which term refers to how wind combines with air temperature to affect comfort level?",
        "answer": "windchill temperature index",
        "distractor_1": "dew point",
        "distractor_2": "heat index",
        "distractor_3": "relative humidity"
      },
      {
        "id": "5407",
        "question": "Which term is also known as atmospheric pressure and is measured with an instrument called a barometer?",
        "answer": "barometric pressure",
        "distractor_1": "Coriolis pressure",
        "distractor_2": "ideal pressure",
        "distractor_3": "wind pressure"
      },
      {
        "id": "5408",
        "question": "Which term refers to the deflection of winds caused by the rotation of Earth?",
        "answer": "Coriolis force",
        "distractor_1": "jet stream",
        "distractor_2": "wind speed",
        "distractor_3": "windchill factor"
      },
      {
        "id": "5409",
        "question": "Which term refers to the paths of all the convection currents on Earth that form the wind system of Earth?",
        "answer": "general circulation",
        "distractor_1": "cyclone",
        "distractor_2": "jet stream",
        "distractor_3": "wind speed"
      },
      {
        "id": "5410",
        "question": "Which term refers to a storm or winds moving around and toward a calm center of low pressure?",
        "answer": "cyclone",
        "distractor_1": "anticyclone",
        "distractor_2": "front",
        "distractor_3": "jet stream"
      },
      {
        "id": "5411",
        "question": "Which term refers to a system of winds that spiral outward around a region of high atmospheric pressure?",
        "answer": "anticyclone",
        "distractor_1": "cyclone",
        "distractor_2": "jet stream",
        "distractor_3": "wind speed"
      },
      {
        "id": "8318",
        "question": "What is the type of cloud that is capable of producing heavy rain, thunder, lightning, and hail?",
        "answer": "Cumulonimbus",
        "distractor_1": "Cirrostratus",
        "distractor_2": "Altostratus",
        "distractor_3": "Stratus"
      },
      {
        "id": "8319",
        "question": "What are lines that connect points of equal air pressure on weather maps?",
        "answer": "Isobars",
        "distractor_1": "Isotherms",
        "distractor_2": "Isometrics",
        "distractor_3": "Isolations"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "113",
    "name": "CADD",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2145",
        "question": "Engineering drawings should follow which type of standards?",
        "answer": "Geometric Dimensioning and Tolerancing",
        "distractor_1": "High-Level Architectural",
        "distractor_2": "American Drafting Association",
        "distractor_3": "Computer-Aided Drafting and Design"
      },
      {
        "id": "2146",
        "question": "Identify the two major types of drafting.",
        "answer": "architectural and engineering",
        "distractor_1": "architectural and CADD",
        "distractor_2": "CADD and engineering",
        "distractor_3": "orthogonal and perspective"
      },
      {
        "id": "2147",
        "question": "Which type of drawing would typically show the most detail?",
        "answer": "multiview drawing",
        "distractor_1": "isometric drawing",
        "distractor_2": "oblique drawing",
        "distractor_3": "perspective drawing"
      },
      {
        "id": "2150",
        "question": "Which of the following is the most basic type of a working architectural drawing?",
        "answer": "floor plan",
        "distractor_1": "orthogonal projection",
        "distractor_2": "pictorial",
        "distractor_3": "elevation"
      },
      {
        "id": "2151",
        "question": "Which of the following is a representation of a centerline?",
        "answer": "____ _ ____",
        "distractor_1": "- - - - - -",
        "distractor_2": "_______",
        "distractor_3": "========="
      },
      {
        "id": "2156",
        "question": "Select the three most common views in a multiview drawing.",
        "answer": "front, top, and right side",
        "distractor_1": "front, top, and left side",
        "distractor_2": "front, bottom, and right side",
        "distractor_3": "top, right side, and perspective"
      },
      {
        "id": "2157",
        "question": "What does the acronym CAD represent?",
        "answer": "computer-aided drafting",
        "distractor_1": "computer-aided diskette",
        "distractor_2": "computer-aided development",
        "distractor_3": "computer-aided drawing"
      },
      {
        "id": "2158",
        "question": "According to the alphabet of lines, which of the following is the thickest line?",
        "answer": "border",
        "distractor_1": "object",
        "distractor_2": "hidden",
        "distractor_3": "center"
      },
      {
        "id": "2160",
        "question": "How many sides does a cube have?",
        "answer": "6",
        "distractor_1": "3",
        "distractor_2": "4",
        "distractor_3": "8"
      },
      {
        "id": "2162",
        "question": "Dimension lines are generally drawn between which type of lines?",
        "answer": "extension",
        "distractor_1": "phantom",
        "distractor_2": "object",
        "distractor_3": "hidden"
      },
      {
        "id": "2164",
        "question": "Which line type indicates an exposed object surface in a cutaway drawing?",
        "answer": "section",
        "distractor_1": "hidden",
        "distractor_2": "cutting plane",
        "distractor_3": "phantom"
      },
      {
        "id": "2165",
        "question": "Extension lines are generally used in conjunction with which type of line?",
        "answer": "dimension",
        "distractor_1": "phantom",
        "distractor_2": "object",
        "distractor_3": "hidden"
      },
      {
        "id": "2167",
        "question": "What is the method used for developing a multiview drawing?",
        "answer": "orthographic projection",
        "distractor_1": "two-point perspective projection",
        "distractor_2": "isometric projection",
        "distractor_3": "oblique projection"
      },
      {
        "id": "2169",
        "question": "Which line type should be used to draw the outline of an object?",
        "answer": "object",
        "distractor_1": "hidden",
        "distractor_2": "border",
        "distractor_3": "outlines"
      },
      {
        "id": "2170",
        "question": "Common views shown on a multiview drawing include the front and right side of the object. What other view is most likely shown as well?",
        "answer": "top",
        "distractor_1": "back",
        "distractor_2": "left side",
        "distractor_3": "bottom"
      },
      {
        "id": "5996",
        "question": "What is known as the figure formed by two lines coming together at a point?",
        "answer": "angle",
        "distractor_1": "edge",
        "distractor_2": "line",
        "distractor_3": "object"
      },
      {
        "id": "5997",
        "question": "What is the name of a computer program that can create a drawing of an object to the correct scale?",
        "answer": "Computer-Aided Drafting and Design (CADD)",
        "distractor_1": "Computer-Aided Manufacturing (CAM)",
        "distractor_2": "Computer-Integrated Drafting (CID)",
        "distractor_3": "Computer-Assisted Design and Engineering (CADE)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5998",
        "question": "What is referred to as the length of a straight line that passes through the center of a circle and touches two points on the circle?",
        "answer": "diameter",
        "distractor_1": "radius",
        "distractor_2": "dimension",
        "distractor_3": "object line"
      },
      {
        "id": "5999",
        "question": "What is referred to as the size of a geometrical feature of an object?",
        "answer": "dimension",
        "distractor_1": "orthographic projection",
        "distractor_2": "elevation",
        "distractor_3": "radius"
      },
      {
        "id": "6000",
        "question": "What is a form of graphic communication; the language of industry?",
        "answer": "drafting",
        "distractor_1": "design",
        "distractor_2": "orthographic projection",
        "distractor_3": "pictorial communication"
      },
      {
        "id": "6001",
        "question": "What are the lines that run from side to side, parallel to the horizon?",
        "answer": "horizontal lines",
        "distractor_1": "object lines",
        "distractor_2": "parallel lines",
        "distractor_3": "drafting lines"
      },
      {
        "id": "6003",
        "question": "What are the heavy lines that represent visible edges?",
        "answer": "object lines",
        "distractor_1": "parallel lines",
        "distractor_2": "horizontal lines",
        "distractor_3": "elevation lines"
      },
      {
        "id": "6004",
        "question": "What is a multiview drawing, usually containing the top, front, and right-side views?",
        "answer": "orthographic projection",
        "distractor_1": "perspective projection",
        "distractor_2": "isometric drawing",
        "distractor_3": "floor plan"
      },
      {
        "id": "6005",
        "question": "What are referred to as lines that never will intersect?",
        "answer": "parallel lines",
        "distractor_1": "object lines",
        "distractor_2": "horizontal lines",
        "distractor_3": "perpendicular lines"
      },
      {
        "id": "6006",
        "question": "What are known as lines that intersect at right- or 90-degree angles?",
        "answer": "perpendicular lines",
        "distractor_1": "parallel lines",
        "distractor_2": "object lines",
        "distractor_3": "vertical lines"
      },
      {
        "id": "6007",
        "question": "What is the distance of a straight line from any point on a circle to the center of the circle?",
        "answer": "radius",
        "distractor_1": "diameter",
        "distractor_2": "circumference",
        "distractor_3": "height"
      },
      {
        "id": "6008",
        "question": "What are known as lines that run up and down, perpendicular to the horizon?",
        "answer": "vertical lines",
        "distractor_1": "perpendicular lines",
        "distractor_2": "object lines",
        "distractor_3": "parallel lines"
      },
      {
        "id": "6009",
        "question": "Which of the following are known as the line symbols used in drawings? ",
        "answer": "alphabet of lines",
        "distractor_1": "language of industry",
        "distractor_2": "ANSI standards",
        "distractor_3": "orthographic drawings"
      },
      {
        "id": "8099",
        "question": "A floor plan is a section drawing for each floor of the structure created at what view?",
        "answer": "as seen from above",
        "distractor_1": "at floor level",
        "distractor_2": "about one foot above the floor",
        "distractor_3": "just below floor level"
      },
      {
        "id": "8100",
        "question": "What is the area of a 16' x 12' rectangular room?",
        "answer": "192 square feet",
        "distractor_1": "192 feet",
        "distractor_2": "28 feet",
        "distractor_3": "28 square feet"
      },
      {
        "id": "8101",
        "question": "What is the third most common view (besides the front and side view) shown on a multiview drawing?",
        "answer": "top",
        "distractor_1": "bottom",
        "distractor_2": "left side",
        "distractor_3": "back"
      },
      {
        "id": "8102",
        "question": "Which line type indicates surfaces exposed by cutaway drawings?",
        "answer": "section",
        "distractor_1": "hidden",
        "distractor_2": "cutting plane",
        "distractor_3": "phantom"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "114",
    "name": "Careers",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2172",
        "question": "This term is defined as a means of making a living in a profession or job.",
        "answer": "an occupation",
        "distractor_1": "a career",
        "distractor_2": "a job",
        "distractor_3": "a vocation"
      },
      {
        "id": "2173",
        "question": "For most people, what is the single most important aspect of their job?",
        "answer": "income",
        "distractor_1": "work environment",
        "distractor_2": "travel",
        "distractor_3": "benefits"
      },
      {
        "id": "2174",
        "question": "Which of the following has/have created new jobs and changed jobs the most during the past decade?",
        "answer": "computers",
        "distractor_1": "cytotechnology",
        "distractor_2": "automobiles",
        "distractor_3": "teleconferencing"
      },
      {
        "id": "2175",
        "question": "Recently, numerous new occupations have been created and existing jobs have changed due to advancements in this area.",
        "answer": "computers",
        "distractor_1": "cytotechnology",
        "distractor_2": "microchips",
        "distractor_3": "teleconferencing"
      },
      {
        "id": "2176",
        "question": "How often does the average worker change occupations?",
        "answer": "about every seven years",
        "distractor_1": "about every five years",
        "distractor_2": "about every nine years",
        "distractor_3": "about every fifteen years"
      },
      {
        "id": "2177",
        "question": "Select the most accurate description of a career.",
        "answer": "a general path or course in one's professional life",
        "distractor_1": "a vocation",
        "distractor_2": "a job",
        "distractor_3": "an extra privilege that employers give to employees"
      },
      {
        "id": "2178",
        "question": "What is the most important factor governing the size and composition of the labor force?",
        "answer": "population",
        "distractor_1": "economic growth",
        "distractor_2": "global trading",
        "distractor_3": "government"
      },
      {
        "id": "2180",
        "question": "Which one of the following best describes a job?",
        "answer": "a position of employment that usually lasts a short period of time",
        "distractor_1": "a position of employment that is for a lifetime",
        "distractor_2": "a family business that you take over",
        "distractor_3": "a position of employment that is held for 20 years"
      },
      {
        "id": "2182",
        "question": "Some labor unions now give this aspect a higher priority in bargaining than they do traditional wage and benefit packages.",
        "answer": "job security",
        "distractor_1": "work environment",
        "distractor_2": "retirement plans",
        "distractor_3": "income"
      },
      {
        "id": "2183",
        "question": "This term is defined as the general progress, or course, of a person’s professional life.",
        "answer": "career",
        "distractor_1": "vocation",
        "distractor_2": "job",
        "distractor_3": "occupation"
      },
      {
        "id": "2184",
        "question": "What is a perk?",
        "answer": "an extra privilege that employers give to employees for compensation",
        "distractor_1": "a supervisory position",
        "distractor_2": "an opportunity to change jobs",
        "distractor_3": "ergonomically designed office furniture"
      },
      {
        "id": "2185",
        "question": "What is a position of employment that is usually for a short period of time?",
        "answer": "a job",
        "distractor_1": "an occupation",
        "distractor_2": "a career",
        "distractor_3": "a vocation"
      },
      {
        "id": "2186",
        "question": "Melissa works five days a week and receives two weeks vacation and 10 paid holidays per year. About what percentage of total days in a year does Melissa work? (Hint: 365 days in a calendar year)",
        "answer": "66 percent",
        "distractor_1": "75 percent",
        "distractor_2": "33 percent",
        "distractor_3": "50 percent"
      },
      {
        "id": "2188",
        "question": "What is the most important factor governing the size and composition of the labor force?",
        "answer": "population",
        "distractor_1": "global trading",
        "distractor_2": "government",
        "distractor_3": "economic growth"
      },
      {
        "id": "2190",
        "question": "About how often will the average worker change his or her occupation?",
        "answer": "every seven years",
        "distractor_1": "every three years",
        "distractor_2": "every five years",
        "distractor_3": "every nine years"
      },
      {
        "id": "2191",
        "question": "This term is defined as a position of employment that is usually for a short period of time.",
        "answer": "job",
        "distractor_1": "vocation",
        "distractor_2": "career",
        "distractor_3": "occupation"
      },
      {
        "id": "2192",
        "question": "What is the most important factor governing the size and composition of the labor force?",
        "answer": "population",
        "distractor_1": "global trading",
        "distractor_2": "government",
        "distractor_3": "economic growth"
      },
      {
        "id": "2194",
        "question": "For most people this is the single most important aspect of their job.",
        "answer": "income",
        "distractor_1": "travel",
        "distractor_2": "work environment",
        "distractor_3": "benefits"
      },
      {
        "id": "2195",
        "question": "Select the definition of an occupation.",
        "answer": "a means of making a living in a profession or job",
        "distractor_1": "a way to make money in the summer",
        "distractor_2": "an after-school job",
        "distractor_3": "a position with no supervisory responsibilities"
      },
      {
        "id": "2196",
        "question": "In bargaining, job security is given what priority compared to a traditional wage-and-benefits package?",
        "answer": "higher",
        "distractor_1": "none",
        "distractor_2": "lower",
        "distractor_3": "equal"
      },
      {
        "id": "2197",
        "question": "This term is defined as a means of making a living in a profession or job.",
        "answer": "an occupation",
        "distractor_1": "a vocation",
        "distractor_2": "a career",
        "distractor_3": "a job"
      },
      {
        "id": "2198",
        "question": "This term is defined as extra privileges that employers give to employees for compensation.",
        "answer": "perks",
        "distractor_1": "values",
        "distractor_2": "hourly rate of pay",
        "distractor_3": "ergonomically designed office furniture"
      },
      {
        "id": "2199",
        "question": "Three out of the four fastest growing occupational groups require high levels of what?",
        "answer": "education and skill",
        "distractor_1": "problem solving",
        "distractor_2": "concentration",
        "distractor_3": "physical strength"
      },
      {
        "id": "5561",
        "question": "What is referred to as a course that a student must take and pass in order to graduate from high school?",
        "answer": "required course",
        "distractor_1": "optional course",
        "distractor_2": "elective",
        "distractor_3": "GED"
      },
      {
        "id": "5562",
        "question": "What are advantages or something helpful?",
        "answer": "benefits",
        "distractor_1": "perks",
        "distractor_2": "income",
        "distractor_3": "interests"
      },
      {
        "id": "5570",
        "question": "What is known as an activity in which a person earns a living; a vocation or a job?",
        "answer": "occupation",
        "distractor_1": "career",
        "distractor_2": "job",
        "distractor_3": "retirement"
      },
      {
        "id": "5571",
        "question": "What are advantages that a person receives, in addition to income, from a job?",
        "answer": "perks",
        "distractor_1": "benefits",
        "distractor_2": "electives",
        "distractor_3": "retirement"
      },
      {
        "id": "5572",
        "question": "What is known as the time in a person's life when he or she has worked long enough and saved enough money to no longer need to work?",
        "answer": "retirement",
        "distractor_1": "old age",
        "distractor_2": "middle age",
        "distractor_3": "adulthood"
      },
      {
        "id": "5573",
        "question": "What high school courses, other than those required for graduation, may a student select to pursue individual areas of interest?",
        "answer": "electives",
        "distractor_1": "required courses",
        "distractor_2": "units",
        "distractor_3": "credits"
      },
      {
        "id": "5574",
        "question": "What is defined as a job in which a person usually must have specific skills?",
        "answer": "vocation",
        "distractor_1": "career",
        "distractor_2": "occupation",
        "distractor_3": "trade"
      },
      {
        "id": "5575",
        "question": "What is a general equivalency diploma given to those who successfully demonstrate through testing that they have as much knowledge as those graduating from a four-year high school?",
        "answer": "GED",
        "distractor_1": "high school diploma",
        "distractor_2": "high school education",
        "distractor_3": "degree"
      },
      {
        "id": "5563",
        "question": "What is the area of employment selected by an individual?",
        "answer": "career",
        "distractor_1": "occupation",
        "distractor_2": "job security",
        "distractor_3": "vocation"
      },
      {
        "id": "5564",
        "question": "What is the unit used to count educational requirements? You must have a certain amount of these to graduate from high school.",
        "answer": "credit",
        "distractor_1": "goal",
        "distractor_2": "interests",
        "distractor_3": "units"
      },
      {
        "id": "5565",
        "question": "What is a purpose or objective that a person tries to achieve?",
        "answer": "goal",
        "distractor_1": "target",
        "distractor_2": "retirement",
        "distractor_3": "benefit"
      },
      {
        "id": "5566",
        "question": "What is known as the amount of money a person makes doing a job?",
        "answer": "income",
        "distractor_1": "benefits",
        "distractor_2": "wage",
        "distractor_3": "hourly pay"
      },
      {
        "id": "5567",
        "question": "What are the things that a person enjoys doing?",
        "answer": "interests",
        "distractor_1": "likes",
        "distractor_2": "perks",
        "distractor_3": "electives"
      },
      {
        "id": "5568",
        "question": "What is known as an 18-week segment of a nine-month school term? ",
        "answer": "semester",
        "distractor_1": "school year",
        "distractor_2": "vacation",
        "distractor_3": "spring break"
      },
      {
        "id": "5569",
        "question": "What is known as the degree of stability when determining whether or not a person will maintain his or her job on a day-to-day basis?",
        "answer": "job security",
        "distractor_1": "occupation",
        "distractor_2": "vocation",
        "distractor_3": "career"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "115",
    "name": "Simple Machines",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "3199",
        "question": "What term is defined as a single machine consisting of two or more simple machines?",
        "answer": "compound machine",
        "distractor_1": "complex machine",
        "distractor_2": "motor",
        "distractor_3": "mechanism"
      },
      {
        "id": "3200",
        "question": "The mechanical advantage of a machine is written as what ratio?",
        "answer": "input force to the output force",
        "distractor_1": "work done to the input force",
        "distractor_2": "effort force to work",
        "distractor_3": "work to energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "3201",
        "question": "What is the mechanical advantage of a 20-meter-long inclined plane with a height of 5 meters?",
        "answer": "4",
        "distractor_1": "5",
        "distractor_2": "20",
        "distractor_3": "100"
      },
      {
        "id": "3202",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a simple machine?",
        "answer": "rope",
        "distractor_1": "wedge",
        "distractor_2": "inclined plane",
        "distractor_3": "pulley"
      },
      {
        "id": "3203",
        "question": "Which of the following describes the mechanical advantage of a machine?",
        "answer": "input force to the output force",
        "distractor_1": "work done to the input force",
        "distractor_2": "effort force to work",
        "distractor_3": "work to energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "3206",
        "question": "What is the number of threads per unit length of a screw called?",
        "answer": "pitch",
        "distractor_1": "mechanical advantage",
        "distractor_2": "circumference",
        "distractor_3": "efficiency"
      },
      {
        "id": "3207",
        "question": "What term is defined as the pivot upon which a device, such as a lever, is supported so that it can balance, tilt, or swing?",
        "answer": "fulcrum",
        "distractor_1": "simple machine",
        "distractor_2": "axle",
        "distractor_3": "base"
      },
      {
        "id": "3210",
        "question": "An inclined plane is most similar to which other simple machine?",
        "answer": "wedge",
        "distractor_1": "wheel and axle",
        "distractor_2": "lever",
        "distractor_3": "pulley"
      },
      {
        "id": "3212",
        "question": "What does the conservation of energy law state?",
        "answer": "energy can neither be created nor destroyed",
        "distractor_1": "if people do not conserve energy, it eventually will be all used",
        "distractor_2": "energy equals force times distance",
        "distractor_3": "simple machines can output more energy than is put into them"
      },
      {
        "id": "3213",
        "question": "A wedge is most similar to which other simple machine?",
        "answer": "inclined plane",
        "distractor_1": "screw",
        "distractor_2": "lever",
        "distractor_3": "pulley"
      },
      {
        "id": "3214",
        "question": "If the diameter of the axle in a wheel-and-axle system is cut in half while the diameter of the wheel does not change, what will happen to the mechanical advantage of the wheel and axle?",
        "answer": "double",
        "distractor_1": "be cut in half",
        "distractor_2": "stay the same",
        "distractor_3": "quadruple"
      },
      {
        "id": "3216",
        "question": "What does the conservation of energy law state?",
        "answer": "energy can neither be created nor destroyed",
        "distractor_1": "if people do not conserve energy, it eventually will be all used",
        "distractor_2": "energy equals force times distance",
        "distractor_3": "simple machines can output more energy than is put into them"
      },
      {
        "id": "3218",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a simple machine?",
        "answer": "wing",
        "distractor_1": "lever",
        "distractor_2": "wheel and axle",
        "distractor_3": "screw"
      },
      {
        "id": "3220",
        "question": "The mechanical advantage of a screw is its circumference divided by its pitch. If a 2-newton force were input into a screw with a diameter of 2 and pitch of 1/4, what would be the output force?",
        "answer": "about 50 newtons",
        "distractor_1": "about 8 newtons",
        "distractor_2": "about 25 newtons",
        "distractor_3": "about 16 newtons"
      },
      {
        "id": "3223",
        "question": "What happens to the mechanical advantage of the wheel and axle if the diameter of the axle in a wheel-and-axle system is cut in half while the diameter of the wheel doubles?",
        "answer": "quadruple",
        "distractor_1": "be cut in half",
        "distractor_2": "double",
        "distractor_3": "stay the same"
      },
      {
        "id": "3226",
        "question": "What term is defined as the metric unit used to express the amount of energy or work?",
        "answer": "joule",
        "distractor_1": "newton",
        "distractor_2": "horsepower",
        "distractor_3": "dyne"
      },
      {
        "id": "6483",
        "question": "What is accomplished when a force moves an object some distance?",
        "answer": "work",
        "distractor_1": "mechanical advantage",
        "distractor_2": "law",
        "distractor_3": "energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "6484",
        "question": "What is known as the push or pull that is required to change the direction of an object?",
        "answer": "effort force",
        "distractor_1": "resistant force",
        "distractor_2": "mechanical advantage",
        "distractor_3": "work"
      },
      {
        "id": "6485",
        "question": "What is known as the push or pull that resists a change in direction; usually the weight or mass of an object?",
        "answer": "resistant force",
        "distractor_1": "work",
        "distractor_2": "effort force",
        "distractor_3": "force"
      },
      {
        "id": "6486",
        "question": "What is the output or resistant force divided by the input or effort force of a machine?",
        "answer": "mechanical advantage",
        "distractor_1": "independent variable",
        "distractor_2": "dependent variable",
        "distractor_3": "force"
      },
      {
        "id": "6487",
        "question": "What is described as any one of six devices that makes work easier?",
        "answer": "simple machine",
        "distractor_1": "compound machine",
        "distractor_2": "fulcrum",
        "distractor_3": "effort"
      },
      {
        "id": "6488",
        "question": "What is known as a device made up of two or more simple machines that function as a single mechanism?",
        "answer": "compound machine",
        "distractor_1": "simple machine",
        "distractor_2": "fulcrum",
        "distractor_3": "complex machine"
      },
      {
        "id": "6489",
        "question": "What is known as a variable that you control; a manipulated variable?",
        "answer": "independent variable",
        "distractor_1": "dependent variable",
        "distractor_2": "theory",
        "distractor_3": "hypothesis"
      },
      {
        "id": "6490",
        "question": "What is a variable that changes as a response to a controlled variable; a responding variable?",
        "answer": "dependent variable",
        "distractor_1": "independent variable",
        "distractor_2": "complex variable",
        "distractor_3": "law"
      },
      {
        "id": "6491",
        "question": "What is the horizontal axis in a graph; usually labeled with the independent variable?",
        "answer": "x-axis",
        "distractor_1": "y-axis",
        "distractor_2": "z-axis",
        "distractor_3": "m-axis"
      },
      {
        "id": "6492",
        "question": "What is the vertical axis in a graph; usually labeled with the dependent variable?",
        "answer": "y-axis",
        "distractor_1": "x-axis",
        "distractor_2": "z-axis",
        "distractor_3": "m-axis"
      },
      {
        "id": "6493",
        "question": "What is described as an explanation of scientific facts?",
        "answer": "theory",
        "distractor_1": "law",
        "distractor_2": "hypothesis",
        "distractor_3": "speculation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6494",
        "question": "What is a push or a pull that has an influence on the shape or direction of an object?",
        "answer": "force",
        "distractor_1": "work",
        "distractor_2": "law of motion",
        "distractor_3": "resistance"
      },
      {
        "id": "6495",
        "question": "What is described as an educated guess?",
        "answer": "hypothesis",
        "distractor_1": "law",
        "distractor_2": "rule",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "6496",
        "question": "What is known as a fixed point on which a rigid bar rotates?",
        "answer": "fulcrum",
        "distractor_1": "lever",
        "distractor_2": "center point",
        "distractor_3": "center"
      },
      {
        "id": "6497",
        "question": "What is a theory that holds true and is accepted as fact?",
        "answer": "law",
        "distractor_1": "theory",
        "distractor_2": "hypothesis",
        "distractor_3": "educated guess"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "116",
    "name": "Food Science",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "3014",
        "question": "What is the chemical formula for sodium chloride, or table salt?",
        "answer": "NaCl",
        "distractor_1": "C",
        "distractor_2": "So",
        "distractor_3": "Sa"
      },
      {
        "id": "3016",
        "question": "What is the first step in developing an experiment?",
        "answer": "stating its purpose",
        "distractor_1": "locating the necessary equipment",
        "distractor_2": "determining the results",
        "distractor_3": "writing a conclusion"
      },
      {
        "id": "3017",
        "question": "What is the body’s most important source of energy?",
        "answer": "carbohydrates",
        "distractor_1": "protein",
        "distractor_2": "sweets",
        "distractor_3": "exercise"
      },
      {
        "id": "3018",
        "question": "What is the first step in developing an experiment?",
        "answer": "State its purpose.",
        "distractor_1": "Locate the necessary equipment.",
        "distractor_2": "Determine the results.",
        "distractor_3": "Write a conclusion."
      },
      {
        "id": "3019",
        "question": "What is the chemical symbol for carbon?",
        "answer": "C",
        "distractor_1": "N",
        "distractor_2": "Co",
        "distractor_3": "Ca"
      },
      {
        "id": "3020",
        "question": "This nutrient insulates and protects vital organs from injury and protects your body from cold temperatures.",
        "answer": "fats",
        "distractor_1": "proteins",
        "distractor_2": "carbohydrates",
        "distractor_3": "water"
      },
      {
        "id": "3021",
        "question": "What is another name for table salt?",
        "answer": "sodium chloride",
        "distractor_1": "glucose",
        "distractor_2": "carbon dioxide",
        "distractor_3": "sodium bicarbonate"
      },
      {
        "id": "3022",
        "question": "What agency is responsible for regulating all food chemical safety?",
        "answer": "Food and Drug Administration (FDA)",
        "distractor_1": "United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)",
        "distractor_2": "American Dietetic Association (ADA)",
        "distractor_3": "Center for Disease Control (CDC)"
      },
      {
        "id": "3023",
        "question": "What is the most harmful type of fat?",
        "answer": "saturated",
        "distractor_1": "unsaturated",
        "distractor_2": "polyunsaturated",
        "distractor_3": "processed"
      },
      {
        "id": "3024",
        "question": "This mineral helps carry oxygen in the blood.",
        "answer": "iron",
        "distractor_1": "calcium",
        "distractor_2": "phosphorous",
        "distractor_3": "water"
      },
      {
        "id": "3026",
        "question": "What is the chemical symbol for hydrogen?",
        "answer": "H",
        "distractor_1": "Hy",
        "distractor_2": "Hg",
        "distractor_3": "Hn"
      },
      {
        "id": "3027",
        "question": "For what did Louis Pasteur prove that microorganisms were responsible in food?",
        "answer": "fermentation",
        "distractor_1": "digestion",
        "distractor_2": "nutrients",
        "distractor_3": "cooking"
      },
      {
        "id": "3028",
        "question": "Carbohydrates are the body’s most important source of this.",
        "answer": "energy",
        "distractor_1": "protein",
        "distractor_2": "nutrients",
        "distractor_3": "fiber"
      },
      {
        "id": "3029",
        "question": "What compounds help regulate body processes?",
        "answer": "vitamins",
        "distractor_1": "atoms",
        "distractor_2": "elements",
        "distractor_3": "minerals"
      },
      {
        "id": "3030",
        "question": "Louis Pasteur proved that these were responsible for food fermentation.",
        "answer": "microorganisms",
        "distractor_1": "proteins",
        "distractor_2": "enzymes",
        "distractor_3": "minerals"
      },
      {
        "id": "3031",
        "question": "How would the chemical formula for a molecule that is made up of two atoms of the same element be written?",
        "answer": "followed by a subscript 2",
        "distractor_1": "twice",
        "distractor_2": "preceded by the numeral 2",
        "distractor_3": "followed by a superscript 2"
      },
      {
        "id": "3032",
        "question": "How would the chemical formula for a molecule that is made up of three atoms of the same element be written?",
        "answer": "chemical symbol followed by a subscript 3",
        "distractor_1": "chemical symbol three times",
        "distractor_2": "numeral 3 followed by the chemical symbol",
        "distractor_3": "chemical symbol followed by a superscript 3"
      },
      {
        "id": "3034",
        "question": "Iron helps carry this in the blood.",
        "answer": "oxygen",
        "distractor_1": "calories",
        "distractor_2": "fiber",
        "distractor_3": "minerals"
      },
      {
        "id": "6413",
        "question": "What is the scientific understanding of how food is used by the body?",
        "answer": "Nutrition",
        "distractor_1": "Sensory evaluation",
        "distractor_2": "Physical reaction",
        "distractor_3": "Chemical reaction"
      },
      {
        "id": "6414",
        "question": "What is the amount of matter in an object?",
        "answer": "Mass",
        "distractor_1": "Atom",
        "distractor_2": "Velocity",
        "distractor_3": "Weight"
      },
      {
        "id": "6415",
        "question": "What is the smallest unit of an element?",
        "answer": "Atom",
        "distractor_1": "Molecule",
        "distractor_2": "Electron",
        "distractor_3": "Nucleus"
      },
      {
        "id": "6416",
        "question": "What is a list of all the elements in order of atomic number; arrangement of elements in rows and columns is based on both physical and chemical properties?",
        "answer": "Periodic table",
        "distractor_1": "Element table",
        "distractor_2": "Table of compounds",
        "distractor_3": "Formula"
      },
      {
        "id": "6417",
        "question": "What is a group of symbols that shows the chemical makeup of a compound and the proportion of each element?",
        "answer": "Formula",
        "distractor_1": "Hypothesis",
        "distractor_2": "Equation",
        "distractor_3": "Periodic table"
      },
      {
        "id": "6418",
        "question": "What particle is made up of two or more atoms held together by forces between the atoms?",
        "answer": "molecule",
        "distractor_1": "atom",
        "distractor_2": "nucleus",
        "distractor_3": "electron"
      },
      {
        "id": "6419",
        "question": "What produces positive hydrogen (H+) ions in water solution; turns litmus paper red; and has a sour taste?",
        "answer": "Acid",
        "distractor_1": "Ph",
        "distractor_2": "Protein",
        "distractor_3": "Molecule"
      },
      {
        "id": "6420",
        "question": "What produces hydroxide (OH-) ions in water solution; turns litmus paper blue; has a bitter taste; and feels slippery?",
        "answer": "Base",
        "distractor_1": "acid",
        "distractor_2": "ph",
        "distractor_3": "chemical reaction"
      },
      {
        "id": "6421",
        "question": "What process in which a substance becomes new and different through the rearrangement of its atoms?",
        "answer": "Chemical reaction",
        "distractor_1": "Physical reaction",
        "distractor_2": "Sensory evaluation",
        "distractor_3": "Formula"
      },
      {
        "id": "6422",
        "question": "What process in which the basic nature of matter is not altered; shape, size, and physical state can be altered?",
        "answer": "Physical reaction",
        "distractor_1": "Chemical reaction",
        "distractor_2": " Psychological reaction",
        "distractor_3": "Sensory reaction"
      },
      {
        "id": "6423",
        "question": "What is a nutrient composed of large molecules made from amino acids that all organisms need, including meat, fish, poultry, dairy products, and eggs?",
        "answer": "Protein",
        "distractor_1": "Carbohydrate",
        "distractor_2": "Iron",
        "distractor_3": "Fat"
      },
      {
        "id": "6424",
        "question": "What uses our human senses – sight, smell, touch, taste, and hearing – for objective, chemical, and instrumental evaluation?",
        "answer": "Sensory evaluation",
        "distractor_1": "Sensory analysis",
        "distractor_2": "Chemical reaction",
        "distractor_3": "Physical reaction"
      },
      {
        "id": "6425",
        "question": "What is the scientific study of food?",
        "answer": "Food science",
        "distractor_1": "Agronomy",
        "distractor_2": "Producology",
        "distractor_3": "Study of production"
      },
      {
        "id": "6426",
        "question": "What is the bottom of the curve that is formed by liquid in a container caused by the relative attraction of the molecules to each other and to the surface of the container?",
        "answer": "Meniscus",
        "distractor_1": "Canines",
        "distractor_2": "Molars",
        "distractor_3": "Incisors"
      },
      {
        "id": "6427",
        "question": "What kind of a substance that cannot be decomposed further by any chemical reaction?",
        "answer": "Element",
        "distractor_1": "Compound",
        "distractor_2": "Mineral",
        "distractor_3": "Rock"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "117",
    "name": "Plastics & Polymers",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2826",
        "question": "Which of these statements must be true for a substance to be flexible?",
        "answer": "Its molecules must be able to move past one another.",
        "distractor_1": "Its molecules must be bonded tightly in place.",
        "distractor_2": "Its molecules must be long chains.",
        "distractor_3": "Its molecules must be short and straight."
      },
      {
        "id": "2827",
        "question": "What is the simplest unit of a compound that maintains all the characteristics of the compound?",
        "answer": "molecule",
        "distractor_1": "atom",
        "distractor_2": "monomer",
        "distractor_3": "polymer"
      },
      {
        "id": "2828",
        "question": "What are the three states of matter?",
        "answer": "solid, liquid, and gas",
        "distractor_1": "atom, element, and molecule",
        "distractor_2": "monomer, polymer, and plastic",
        "distractor_3": "mineral, metal, and compound"
      },
      {
        "id": "2829",
        "question": "What is the atomic symbol for carbon?",
        "answer": "C",
        "distractor_1": "Ca",
        "distractor_2": "Cn",
        "distractor_3": "H-C"
      },
      {
        "id": "2831",
        "question": "Which of the following is an example of a thermoset plastic?",
        "answer": "polyester resin",
        "distractor_1": "polystyrene",
        "distractor_2": "polyethylene",
        "distractor_3": "polyvinyl chloride"
      },
      {
        "id": "2832",
        "question": "Which of the following are examples of natural polymers?",
        "answer": "starch and DNA",
        "distractor_1": "DNA and water",
        "distractor_2": "starch and rayon",
        "distractor_3": "rubber and sugar"
      },
      {
        "id": "2836",
        "question": "Which of the following is defined as a molecule made of repeating copies of smaller molecules?",
        "answer": "polymer",
        "distractor_1": "monomer",
        "distractor_2": "plastic",
        "distractor_3": "polystyrene"
      },
      {
        "id": "2837",
        "question": "What is the simplest unit of an element that maintains all the characteristics of the element?",
        "answer": "atom",
        "distractor_1": "molecule",
        "distractor_2": "monomer",
        "distractor_3": "polymer"
      },
      {
        "id": "2839",
        "question": "What type of molecule is defined as a chain of repeating copies of smaller molecules?",
        "answer": "polymer",
        "distractor_1": "monomer",
        "distractor_2": "plastic",
        "distractor_3": "polystyrene"
      },
      {
        "id": "2841",
        "question": "In which forming process is a polymer fully melted?",
        "answer": "injection molding",
        "distractor_1": "vacuum forming",
        "distractor_2": "pressing",
        "distractor_3": "etching"
      },
      {
        "id": "2842",
        "question": "What are the repeating units that make up a polymer?",
        "answer": "monomers",
        "distractor_1": "plastics",
        "distractor_2": "atoms",
        "distractor_3": "styrenes"
      },
      {
        "id": "2843",
        "question": "Which of the following terms is defined as a large molecule that forms when many smaller molecules are linked together by covalent bonds?",
        "answer": "polymer",
        "distractor_1": "water",
        "distractor_2": "monomer",
        "distractor_3": "hydrocarbon"
      },
      {
        "id": "2844",
        "question": "What are the two basic categories of synthetic plastics?",
        "answer": "thermoplastics and thermosets",
        "distractor_1": "thermoplastics and polymers",
        "distractor_2": "thermosets and rubber",
        "distractor_3": "rubber and polymers"
      },
      {
        "id": "2847",
        "question": "What is the term for the repeating units that make up a polymer?",
        "answer": "monomers",
        "distractor_1": "plastics",
        "distractor_2": "atoms",
        "distractor_3": "styrenes"
      },
      {
        "id": "2849",
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a polymer?",
        "answer": "water",
        "distractor_1": "polyethylene",
        "distractor_2": "nylon",
        "distractor_3": "plastic"
      },
      {
        "id": "2851",
        "question": "The molecules of a substance must have which set of characteristics in order for the substance to be flexible?",
        "answer": "able to move past one another",
        "distractor_1": "short and straight",
        "distractor_2": "bonded tightly in place",
        "distractor_3": "long chains"
      },
      {
        "id": "8259",
        "question": "According to the law of conservation of mass, if 60 grams of glue were mixed with 5 grams of borax and 10 grams of water, what would be the total mass of the mixture?",
        "answer": "75 grams",
        "distractor_1": "15 grams",
        "distractor_2": "65 grams",
        "distractor_3": "70 grams"
      },
      {
        "id": "6565",
        "question": "What is the quantity of matter in a material?",
        "answer": "Mass",
        "distractor_1": "Velocity",
        "distractor_2": "Weight",
        "distractor_3": "Plasma"
      },
      {
        "id": "6566",
        "question": "What is a process during which a substance becomes new and different through the rearrangement of its atoms?",
        "answer": "Chemical reaction",
        "distractor_1": "Compound reaction",
        "distractor_2": "Injection molding",
        "distractor_3": "Polymer"
      },
      {
        "id": "6567",
        "question": "What is a process during which a thin sheet of plastic is heated and drawn by a vacuum into a mold or around an object?",
        "answer": "Vacuum forming",
        "distractor_1": "Injection molding",
        "distractor_2": "Chemical reaction",
        "distractor_3": "Polymer"
      },
      {
        "id": "6568",
        "question": "What is a substance that cannot be decomposed into a simpler substance by any chemical reaction?",
        "answer": "Element",
        "distractor_1": "Compound",
        "distractor_2": "Chemical",
        "distractor_3": "Monomer"
      },
      {
        "id": "6569",
        "question": "What is a substance composed of two or more chemically combined elements?",
        "answer": "Compound",
        "distractor_1": "Element",
        "distractor_2": "Monomer",
        "distractor_3": "Polymer"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "118",
    "name": "Video Production",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "3227",
        "question": "What are the three main stages of video production?",
        "answer": "preproduction, production, and postproduction",
        "distractor_1": "design, edit, and process",
        "distractor_2": "develop, implement, and print",
        "distractor_3": "tape, arrange, and transition"
      },
      {
        "id": "8152",
        "question": "What are the three primary colors used in a television tube?",
        "answer": "red, blue, and green",
        "distractor_1": "white, black, and red",
        "distractor_2": "red, white, and blue",
        "distractor_3": "red, blue, and yellow"
      },
      {
        "id": "3229",
        "question": "What is a pixel?",
        "answer": "picture element",
        "distractor_1": "light source",
        "distractor_2": "digital sound card",
        "distractor_3": "sound bit"
      },
      {
        "id": "3232",
        "question": "Who invented the television?",
        "answer": "John Baird",
        "distractor_1": "Benjamin Franklin",
        "distractor_2": "Thomas Edison",
        "distractor_3": "Louis Lumière"
      },
      {
        "id": "8652",
        "question": "During which stage of video production is the storyboard created?",
        "answer": "preproduction",
        "distractor_1": "production",
        "distractor_2": "postproduction",
        "distractor_3": "editing"
      },
      {
        "id": "8104",
        "question": "In video production, what is a PSA?",
        "answer": "public service announcement",
        "distractor_1": "postsecondary advancement",
        "distractor_2": "pre-studio arrangement",
        "distractor_3": "professional scenic arrangement"
      },
      {
        "id": "8154",
        "question": "Which of the following takes place when the director has actors rehearse the scene in the set?",
        "answer": "blocking out",
        "distractor_1": "dollying",
        "distractor_2": "animating",
        "distractor_3": "plotting out"
      },
      {
        "id": "8156",
        "question": "In a production, who would be responsible for lifting and fixing cameras and other equipment?",
        "answer": "grip",
        "distractor_1": "gaffer",
        "distractor_2": "camera operator",
        "distractor_3": "boom operator"
      },
      {
        "id": "3240",
        "question": "What term is defined as a signal transmitter in orbit around Earth?",
        "answer": "satellite",
        "distractor_1": "planet",
        "distractor_2": "comet",
        "distractor_3": "shuttle"
      },
      {
        "id": "3241",
        "question": "Which of the following is a tendency of an analog signal?",
        "answer": "vary constantly",
        "distractor_1": "remain constant",
        "distractor_2": "be greater than a binary signal",
        "distractor_3": "be discrete"
      },
      {
        "id": "3244",
        "question": "What is a storyboard?",
        "answer": "an outline of the production",
        "distractor_1": "a production technique",
        "distractor_2": "a producer",
        "distractor_3": "a video backdrop"
      },
      {
        "id": "3253",
        "question": "What does the word 'video' mean in Latin?",
        "answer": "I see",
        "distractor_1": "to view",
        "distractor_2": "vision",
        "distractor_3": "television"
      },
      {
        "id": "3254",
        "question": "What is the most powerful tool of mass communication known to humans?",
        "answer": "television",
        "distractor_1": "radio",
        "distractor_2": "newspaper",
        "distractor_3": "satellite"
      },
      {
        "id": "8105",
        "question": "What is the planning stage when you determine a topic and target audience, write the script, and use a storyboard to plan how it will look?",
        "answer": "preproduction ",
        "distractor_1": "production",
        "distractor_2": "postproduction",
        "distractor_3": "publication"
      },
      {
        "id": "6514",
        "question": "Which of the following is defined as moving the camera up or down?",
        "answer": "tilt",
        "distractor_1": "dolly",
        "distractor_2": "pan",
        "distractor_3": "truck"
      },
      {
        "id": "6515",
        "question": "Identify the word that means to pivot the camera from side to side.",
        "answer": "pan",
        "distractor_1": "tilt",
        "distractor_2": "dolly",
        "distractor_3": "truck"
      },
      {
        "id": "6519",
        "question": "Which of the following is a small element that makes up the picture on a television screen? These elements are made up of three colors that create the appearance of many when viewed from a distance.",
        "answer": "pixel",
        "distractor_1": "ray",
        "distractor_2": "high definition",
        "distractor_3": "plasma"
      },
      {
        "id": "8158",
        "question": "What term is defined as the process of creating the movement of an object on video?",
        "answer": "animation",
        "distractor_1": "documentation",
        "distractor_2": "commercial",
        "distractor_3": "public service announcement"
      },
      {
        "id": "8106",
        "question": "What is the stage when editing takes place and special effects, music, and narration are added?",
        "answer": "postproduction",
        "distractor_1": "preproduction",
        "distractor_2": "production",
        "distractor_3": "publication"
      },
      {
        "id": "8107",
        "question": "What is the stage when dialogue, action, sound, and scenery recording take place?",
        "answer": "production",
        "distractor_1": "preproduction",
        "distractor_2": "postproduction",
        "distractor_3": "publication"
      },
      {
        "id": "8108",
        "question": "What term is defined as the first place where words and pictures are put together in visual form? It contains areas for drawing scenes, writing dialogue, and noting where action takes place.",
        "answer": "storyboard",
        "distractor_1": "production board",
        "distractor_2": "sketch board",
        "distractor_3": "scene board"
      },
      {
        "id": "8109",
        "question": "What is a production created to inform viewers about important issues, enlighten them about the harm of certain behaviors, and encourage them to take action?",
        "answer": "public service announcement",
        "distractor_1": "news report",
        "distractor_2": "documentary",
        "distractor_3": "advertisement"
      },
      {
        "id": "8110",
        "question": "What is a device used to transfer video signals?",
        "answer": "satellite",
        "distractor_1": "video camera",
        "distractor_2": "television",
        "distractor_3": "cable box"
      },
      {
        "id": "8111",
        "question": "What is the group that is commissioned by Congress to regulate communication businesses, develop regulations and policies, and work to protect the public interest in radio, television, wire, satellite, and cable communications?",
        "answer": "Federal Communications Commission (FCC)",
        "distractor_1": "Public Access Commission (PAC)",
        "distractor_2": "Network Executive Group (NEG)",
        "distractor_3": "Cable Communications Group (CCG)"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "119",
    "name": "Music and Sound",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2801",
        "question": "Which part of the score tells you the meter of the song?",
        "answer": "time signature",
        "distractor_1": "grand staff",
        "distractor_2": "bass clef",
        "distractor_3": "measure"
      },
      {
        "id": "2802",
        "question": "Which musical instrument typically produces the beat?",
        "answer": "percussion",
        "distractor_1": "string",
        "distractor_2": "woodwind",
        "distractor_3": "voice"
      },
      {
        "id": "2803",
        "question": "What type of wave is used most often by bats for echolocation?",
        "answer": "ultrasounds",
        "distractor_1": "algorithms",
        "distractor_2": "infrasounds",
        "distractor_3": "interference"
      },
      {
        "id": "2804",
        "question": "The meter of a song is written in what part of the score?",
        "answer": "time signature",
        "distractor_1": "grand staff",
        "distractor_2": "bass clef",
        "distractor_3": "measure"
      },
      {
        "id": "2805",
        "question": "A percussion instrument typically produces which part of a song?",
        "answer": "beat",
        "distractor_1": "melody",
        "distractor_2": "interval",
        "distractor_3": "chords"
      },
      {
        "id": "2806",
        "question": "What does the pattern in a musical beat give music?",
        "answer": "rhythm",
        "distractor_1": "melody",
        "distractor_2": "ratio",
        "distractor_3": "sound"
      },
      {
        "id": "2807",
        "question": "What does a sound wave with louder amplitude indicate?",
        "answer": "a higher wave peak",
        "distractor_1": "more waves in a second",
        "distractor_2": "a shorter wave height",
        "distractor_3": "a longer wavelength"
      },
      {
        "id": "5346",
        "question": "What term refers to the tone of a musical note as heard by a listener? ",
        "answer": "pitch",
        "distractor_1": "melody",
        "distractor_2": "volume",
        "distractor_3": "chord"
      },
      {
        "id": "2810",
        "question": "What does a condenser microphone use that vibrates as sound waves strike it?",
        "answer": "diaphragm",
        "distractor_1": "air column",
        "distractor_2": "amplifier",
        "distractor_3": "electronic membrane"
      },
      {
        "id": "6915",
        "question": "To what does the key signature refer?",
        "answer": "a sharp or flat that tells which major or minor key to use",
        "distractor_1": "base or treble clef",
        "distractor_2": "the first note in a scale",
        "distractor_3": "the base key for correct finger position on a keyboard or piano"
      },
      {
        "id": "5347",
        "question": "What term refers to an instrument containing a column of air that vibrates to produce sound? ",
        "answer": "wind instrument",
        "distractor_1": "percussion instrument",
        "distractor_2": "music",
        "distractor_3": "cymbals"
      },
      {
        "id": "5348",
        "question": "What is a mixture of two or more melodies playing together or voices singing together? ",
        "answer": "polyphony",
        "distractor_1": "a chord",
        "distractor_2": "an octave",
        "distractor_3": "volume"
      },
      {
        "id": "5349",
        "question": "What is music?",
        "answer": "sound that has pitch, timbre, duration, and dynamic level",
        "distractor_1": "the tone of a musical note as heard by a listener",
        "distractor_2": "a measurement of the relative loudness of a sound compared to the loudness of other sounds",
        "distractor_3": "a harmony with three or more notes, or pitches, played at the same time"
      },
      {
        "id": "5350",
        "question": "What is a melody?",
        "answer": "a musical sentence",
        "distractor_1": "frequency in cycles per second",
        "distractor_2": "loudness of sound as perceived by the listener",
        "distractor_3": "sound that has pitch, timbre, duration, and dynamic level"
      },
      {
        "id": "2811",
        "question": "What do eight white keys in a row make?",
        "answer": "an octave",
        "distractor_1": "a measure",
        "distractor_2": "a musical scale",
        "distractor_3": "a key signature"
      },
      {
        "id": "2812",
        "question": "What term refers to the pattern of a musical beat?",
        "answer": "rhythm",
        "distractor_1": "measure",
        "distractor_2": "frequency",
        "distractor_3": "melody"
      },
      {
        "id": "2814",
        "question": "What does a higher sound wave indicate?",
        "answer": "a louder sound",
        "distractor_1": "a higher note",
        "distractor_2": "increased frequency",
        "distractor_3": "lower amplitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "2815",
        "question": "What does a sound wave with a higher frequency indicate?",
        "answer": "more waves in a second",
        "distractor_1": "a louder sound",
        "distractor_2": "a longer wavelength",
        "distractor_3": "increased amplitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "2816",
        "question": "In the world of music, what is a melody?",
        "answer": "a musical sentence",
        "distractor_1": "a happy tune",
        "distractor_2": "part of the bass clef",
        "distractor_3": "a harmonic interval"
      },
      {
        "id": "2817",
        "question": "During a hearing exam, what object creates pure tones that are used to test the range of a person's hearing?",
        "answer": "audiometer",
        "distractor_1": "oscilloscope",
        "distractor_2": "radiogram",
        "distractor_3": "ultrasound machine"
      },
      {
        "id": "2819",
        "question": "A sentence in a composition is the same as what in a musical composition?",
        "answer": "melody",
        "distractor_1": "harmony",
        "distractor_2": "score",
        "distractor_3": "lyric"
      },
      {
        "id": "2820",
        "question": "What does a sound wave with more waves per second indicate?",
        "answer": "an increased frequency",
        "distractor_1": "a louder sound",
        "distractor_2": "a longer wavelength",
        "distractor_3": "an increased amplitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "2821",
        "question": "Which of the following terms refers to the amount of time between bars on a musical scale?",
        "answer": "measure",
        "distractor_1": "composition",
        "distractor_2": "time signature",
        "distractor_3": "interval"
      },
      {
        "id": "2822",
        "question": "In what form is sound carried through the air?",
        "answer": "waves",
        "distractor_1": "harmonies",
        "distractor_2": "decibels",
        "distractor_3": "amplitudes"
      },
      {
        "id": "2823",
        "question": "What do musical instruments create that can be received and interpreted by our ears as music?",
        "answer": "vibrations",
        "distractor_1": "serial sounds",
        "distractor_2": "compressions",
        "distractor_3": "infrasounds"
      },
      {
        "id": "2824",
        "question": "Sound is carried through the air in what form?",
        "answer": "waves",
        "distractor_1": "amplitudes",
        "distractor_2": "decibels",
        "distractor_3": "harmonies"
      },
      {
        "id": "2825",
        "question": "What is a measure?",
        "answer": "time between bars in a score",
        "distractor_1": "the melody notes",
        "distractor_2": "the number of rhythm beats",
        "distractor_3": "the number of interval steps"
      },
      {
        "id": "5351",
        "question": "What is a chord? ",
        "answer": "a harmony with three or more notes, or pitches, played at the same time",
        "distractor_1": "a musical interval that contains eight white keys in a row",
        "distractor_2": "frequency in cycles per second",
        "distractor_3": "the tone of a musical note as heard by the listener"
      },
      {
        "id": "5352",
        "question": "Which of the following terms refers to the loudness of a sound as perceived by a listener?",
        "answer": "volume",
        "distractor_1": "octave",
        "distractor_2": "hertz",
        "distractor_3": "decibels"
      },
      {
        "id": "5353",
        "question": "Who discovered the mathematical relationship between string length and pitch? ",
        "answer": "Pythagoras",
        "distractor_1": "Archimedes",
        "distractor_2": "Albert Einstein",
        "distractor_3": "Aristotle"
      },
      {
        "id": "5354",
        "question": "Which term refers to the frequency of cycles per second? ",
        "answer": "hertz",
        "distractor_1": "chord",
        "distractor_2": "pitch",
        "distractor_3": "decibels"
      },
      {
        "id": "5355",
        "question": "What is the measurement of the relative loudness of a sound compared to the loudness of other sounds? ",
        "answer": "decibels",
        "distractor_1": "melody",
        "distractor_2": "octave",
        "distractor_3": "volume"
      },
      {
        "id": "5356",
        "question": "What is frequency?",
        "answer": "actual wavelength of a note or key",
        "distractor_1": "a musical sentence",
        "distractor_2": "a musical interval that contains eight white keys in a row",
        "distractor_3": "the tone of a musical note as  heard by the listener"
      },
      {
        "id": "5357",
        "question": "What type of instruments are made of solid material or material stretched over a hollow container?",
        "answer": "percussion instruments",
        "distractor_1": "string instruments",
        "distractor_2": "woodwind instruments",
        "distractor_3": "brass instruments"
      },
      {
        "id": "6916",
        "question": "What term often identifies the scale in which a piece of music is written?",
        "answer": "key signature",
        "distractor_1": "interval step",
        "distractor_2": "treble clef",
        "distractor_3": "harmonic chord"
      },
      {
        "id": "6917",
        "question": "What term means eight full tones that start at a given note and end on a note that has twice or one-half the frequency of the first note? ",
        "answer": "an octave",
        "distractor_1": "a musical scale",
        "distractor_2": "a measure",
        "distractor_3": "a key signature "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "120",
    "name": "Light and Lasers",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1655",
        "question": "If the angle of incidence of a light to a mirror is 25 degrees, what is the angle of reflection?",
        "answer": "25 degrees",
        "distractor_1": "50 degrees",
        "distractor_2": "65 degrees",
        "distractor_3": "155 degrees"
      },
      {
        "id": "1656",
        "question": "Which color of light would be absorbed the most by a green leaf?",
        "answer": "red",
        "distractor_1": "green",
        "distractor_2": "blue",
        "distractor_3": "yellow"
      },
      {
        "id": "1657",
        "question": "If the intensity of light is 900 lumens 1 foot from the source, what is the intensity 3 feet from the source?",
        "answer": "100 lumens",
        "distractor_1": "300 lumens",
        "distractor_2": "450 lumens",
        "distractor_3": "900 lumens"
      },
      {
        "id": "1658",
        "question": "What is the strength of light falling on a certain area called?",
        "answer": "intensity",
        "distractor_1": "flux",
        "distractor_2": "lumens",
        "distractor_3": "photonic charge"
      },
      {
        "id": "1659",
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a use for lasers?",
        "answer": "illuminating rooms",
        "distractor_1": "treating cancer",
        "distractor_2": "making holograms",
        "distractor_3": "carrying signals"
      },
      {
        "id": "1660",
        "question": "If the intensity of light is 1600 lumens 1 foot from the source, what is the intensity 2 feet from the source?",
        "answer": "400 lumens",
        "distractor_1": "600 lumens",
        "distractor_2": "800 lumens",
        "distractor_3": "1600 lumens"
      },
      {
        "id": "1661",
        "question": "What is the speed of light, approximately?",
        "answer": "300,000 kilometers/second",
        "distractor_1": "300,000 kilometers/hour",
        "distractor_2": "300,000 miles/hour",
        "distractor_3": "300,000 miles/second"
      },
      {
        "id": "1663",
        "question": "What is the smallest unit of light?",
        "answer": "photon",
        "distractor_1": "atom",
        "distractor_2": "electron",
        "distractor_3": "ray"
      },
      {
        "id": "1664",
        "question": "What are the names of the small cells contained in the back of the human eye that allow all people to see in black and white in dim light and in color in bright light?",
        "answer": "rods and cones",
        "distractor_1": "retinas and corneas",
        "distractor_2": "pupils and lenses",
        "distractor_3": "retinas and pupils"
      },
      {
        "id": "1665",
        "question": "The speed of light is 300,000 kilometers per second. The Sun is approximately 144 million kilometers from the Earth. Approximately how long does it take light from the Sun to reach the Earth?",
        "answer": "8 minutes",
        "distractor_1": "48 seconds",
        "distractor_2": "48 minutes",
        "distractor_3": "8 hours"
      },
      {
        "id": "1666",
        "question": "Of what are optical fibers generally made?",
        "answer": "glass",
        "distractor_1": "copper",
        "distractor_2": "linen",
        "distractor_3": "light"
      },
      {
        "id": "8256",
        "question": "This process occurs when white light separates into colors.",
        "answer": "dispersion",
        "distractor_1": "scattering",
        "distractor_2": "polarization",
        "distractor_3": "reflection"
      },
      {
        "id": "1667",
        "question": "If the angle of incidence between a light ray and a mirror is 40 degrees, what is the angle between the angle of incidence and the angle of reflection? (Hint: A straight line is a 180 degrees angle.)",
        "answer": "100 degrees ",
        "distractor_1": "140 degrees ",
        "distractor_2": "80 degrees ",
        "distractor_3": "40 degrees "
      },
      {
        "id": "1668",
        "question": "How many frequencies and energy levels of light are in each laser beam?",
        "answer": "1",
        "distractor_1": "infinitely many",
        "distractor_2": "4",
        "distractor_3": "7"
      },
      {
        "id": "1669",
        "question": "If the angle of incidence of a light to a mirror is 30 degrees, what is the angle of reflection?",
        "answer": "30 degrees",
        "distractor_1": "25 degrees",
        "distractor_2": "65 degrees",
        "distractor_3": "155 degrees"
      },
      {
        "id": "1670",
        "question": "Which color of light would be absorbed the most by a red flower?",
        "answer": "green",
        "distractor_1": "red",
        "distractor_2": "pink",
        "distractor_3": "white"
      },
      {
        "id": "1674",
        "question": "A 2-inch long object appears to be 5 inches long when viewed through a convex lens. What is the magnification of the lens?",
        "answer": "2.5",
        "distractor_1": "0.4",
        "distractor_2": "2",
        "distractor_3": "5"
      },
      {
        "id": "1675",
        "question": "What happens to light when it passes through a concave lens?",
        "answer": "It is dispersed.",
        "distractor_1": "It is reflected.",
        "distractor_2": "It is absorbed.",
        "distractor_3": "It is focused."
      },
      {
        "id": "1677",
        "question": "A photon is released by an atom when which of the following occurs?",
        "answer": "An electron moves from a higher to a lower energy level.",
        "distractor_1": "An electron is absorbed.",
        "distractor_2": "An electron is released.",
        "distractor_3": "An electron moves from a lower to a higher energy level."
      },
      {
        "id": "1679",
        "question": "Light travels at 186,282 miles per second. About how far does light travel in a year?",
        "answer": "6 trillion miles",
        "distractor_1": "600 million miles",
        "distractor_2": "6 billion miles",
        "distractor_3": "60 billion miles"
      },
      {
        "id": "1680",
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct expression of the speed of light?",
        "answer": "186,282 miles/second",
        "distractor_1": "186,282 kilometers/hour",
        "distractor_2": "186,282 kilometers/second",
        "distractor_3": "186,282 miles/hour"
      },
      {
        "id": "1681",
        "question": "What types of waves in the electromagnetic spectrum have the highest energy level?",
        "answer": "gamma rays",
        "distractor_1": "radio waves",
        "distractor_2": "infrared waves",
        "distractor_3": "visible light rays"
      },
      {
        "id": "5141",
        "question": "What term describes electromagnetic waves that an eye can detect?",
        "answer": "visible light",
        "distractor_1": "radio waves",
        "distractor_2": "ultraviolet radiation",
        "distractor_3": "infrared radiation"
      },
      {
        "id": "5142",
        "question": "What term describes the range of radiant electromagnetic energy arranged in order of frequency or wavelength?",
        "answer": "electromagnetic spectrum",
        "distractor_1": "electromagnetic field",
        "distractor_2": "electromagnetic attraction",
        "distractor_3": "electromagnetism"
      },
      {
        "id": "5143",
        "question": "What is a device that produces a very intense light made of only one wavelength; a light amplified by stimulating emission of radiation?",
        "answer": "laser",
        "distractor_1": "radar",
        "distractor_2": "speaker",
        "distractor_3": "strobe light"
      },
      {
        "id": "5144",
        "question": "What term describes a bending of rays and waves as they pass from one medium into another, such as light passing from air into glass?",
        "answer": "refraction",
        "distractor_1": "reflection",
        "distractor_2": "splitting",
        "distractor_3": "fission"
      },
      {
        "id": "5145",
        "question": "What is the term for a change in the direction of waves, or rays that bounce off an object?",
        "answer": "reflection",
        "distractor_1": "fission",
        "distractor_2": "refraction",
        "distractor_3": "diffusion"
      },
      {
        "id": "5146",
        "question": "What is the process of using mirrors to bend light and thus make objects appear larger?",
        "answer": "magnification",
        "distractor_1": "refraction",
        "distractor_2": "diffusion",
        "distractor_3": "fission"
      },
      {
        "id": "5148",
        "question": "Which term describes the number that tells how many equal factors there are",
        "answer": "exponent",
        "distractor_1": "numerator",
        "distractor_2": "denominator",
        "distractor_3": "sum"
      },
      {
        "id": "5149",
        "question": "What is the term for electromagnetic waves with a wavelength that is slightly longer than visible light?",
        "answer": "infrared light",
        "distractor_1": "ultraviolet light",
        "distractor_2": "gamma rays",
        "distractor_3": "x-ray"
      },
      {
        "id": "5150",
        "question": "What is the name of the electromagnetic waves with a wavelength that is slightly shorter than visible light?",
        "answer": "ultraviolet light",
        "distractor_1": "infrared light",
        "distractor_2": "radio waves",
        "distractor_3": "television waves"
      },
      {
        "id": "5151",
        "question": "What is the distance between a point on one wave to the same point on the next wave?",
        "answer": "wavelength",
        "distractor_1": "frequency",
        "distractor_2": "decibel",
        "distractor_3": "amplitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "5152",
        "question": "What is the number of waves in a given cycle, which is usually measured in cycles per second?",
        "answer": "frequency",
        "distractor_1": "amplitude",
        "distractor_2": "volume",
        "distractor_3": "RPM"
      },
      {
        "id": "5153",
        "question": "What is a lens that curves outward like the outer boundary of a circle or sphere?",
        "answer": "convex lens",
        "distractor_1": "concave lens",
        "distractor_2": "reflective",
        "distractor_3": "opaque"
      },
      {
        "id": "5154",
        "question": "What is a lens that curves inward like the inside of a circle or sphere?",
        "answer": "concave lens",
        "distractor_1": "convex",
        "distractor_2": "reflective ",
        "distractor_3": "translucent"
      },
      {
        "id": "5156",
        "question": "What is the term for two objects having exactly the same size and shape?",
        "answer": "congruent",
        "distractor_1": "similar",
        "distractor_2": "identical",
        "distractor_3": "vertical"
      },
      {
        "id": "5160",
        "question": "What is an equation that shows two ratios are equivalent?",
        "answer": "proportion",
        "distractor_1": "inequality",
        "distractor_2": "quadratic equation",
        "distractor_3": "polynomial equation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6061",
        "question": "What is a change in the direction of waves, or rays that bounce off an object?",
        "answer": "Reflection",
        "distractor_1": "Refraction",
        "distractor_2": "Magnification",
        "distractor_3": "Transversal"
      },
      {
        "id": "6063",
        "question": "What is the number that tells how many equal factors there are?",
        "answer": "Exponent",
        "distractor_1": "Superponent",
        "distractor_2": "Transversal",
        "distractor_3": "Congruent"
      },
      {
        "id": "6078",
        "question": "What are angles created when a transversal crosses two lines, corresponding angles are in the same position from one figure to the other. They are congruent if the two lines are parallel?",
        "answer": "Corresponding angles",
        "distractor_1": "Alternate interior angles",
        "distractor_2": "Alternate exterior angles",
        "distractor_3": "Transversal"
      },
      {
        "id": "6079",
        "question": "What are angles whose interior points are on the opposite sides of a transversal line and on the inside of the lines it intersects?",
        "answer": "Alternate interior angles",
        "distractor_1": "Transversals",
        "distractor_2": "Alternate exterior angles",
        "distractor_3": "Corresponding angles"
      },
      {
        "id": "6080",
        "question": "What are angles whose interior points are on the opposite sides of a transversal line and on the outside of the lines it intersects?",
        "answer": "Alternate exterior angles",
        "distractor_1": "Corresponding angles",
        "distractor_2": "Transversals",
        "distractor_3": "Alternating exterior angles"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "121",
    "name": "Soils",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1876",
        "question": "Which of the following items is transferred through the earth by biogeochemical cycles?",
        "answer": "an element such as nitrogen",
        "distractor_1": "the Sun's energy",
        "distractor_2": "water",
        "distractor_3": "air"
      },
      {
        "id": "1877",
        "question": "Which of the following items is added to soil to make it less acidic?",
        "answer": "lime",
        "distractor_1": "sulfur",
        "distractor_2": "nitrogen",
        "distractor_3": "potash"
      },
      {
        "id": "1878",
        "question": "Identify the major reason soil organisms are important for soil formation.",
        "answer": "decomposition of organic matter",
        "distractor_1": "removal of air pockets",
        "distractor_2": "removal of  excess water",
        "distractor_3": "decomposition of inorganic matter"
      },
      {
        "id": "1879",
        "question": "Rocks break down to form soil by what process?",
        "answer": "weathering",
        "distractor_1": "composting",
        "distractor_2": "decomposition",
        "distractor_3": "erosion"
      },
      {
        "id": "1880",
        "question": "By adding lime to a soil we decrease what quality of the soil?",
        "answer": "acidity",
        "distractor_1": "alkalinity",
        "distractor_2": "nutrient content",
        "distractor_3": "organic matter"
      },
      {
        "id": "1881",
        "question": "Which of the following land-use practices is used in sustainable agriculture?",
        "answer": "terracing to control erosion",
        "distractor_1": "planting the same crop every year",
        "distractor_2": "clear-cutting to obtain more cropland",
        "distractor_3": "using large amounts of chemical pesticides"
      },
      {
        "id": "1882",
        "question": "Parent material, or rock, is broken down to form soil by what process?",
        "answer": "weathering",
        "distractor_1": "composting",
        "distractor_2": "erosion",
        "distractor_3": "decomposition"
      },
      {
        "id": "1883",
        "question": "Which phrase best describes soil texture?",
        "answer": "the size of the particles within the soil",
        "distractor_1": "the way soil particles group together",
        "distractor_2": "the amount of organic matter within the soil",
        "distractor_3": "a cross section of a soil sample"
      },
      {
        "id": "1884",
        "question": "What is the best range for soil pH?",
        "answer": "4-9",
        "distractor_1": "5-7",
        "distractor_2": "8-10",
        "distractor_3": "2-4"
      },
      {
        "id": "1885",
        "question": "What does the size of the particles within the soil determine?",
        "answer": "texture",
        "distractor_1": "structure",
        "distractor_2": "profile",
        "distractor_3": "tilth"
      },
      {
        "id": "1886",
        "question": "Why is soil formation dependent on soil organisms?",
        "answer": "They decompose organic matter.",
        "distractor_1": "They remove excess air from the soil.",
        "distractor_2": "They add new kinds of nutrients.",
        "distractor_3": "They remove excess water from the soil."
      },
      {
        "id": "1887",
        "question": "Which one of the following plants is NOT a nitrogen-fixing plant?",
        "answer": "corn",
        "distractor_1": "soybean",
        "distractor_2": "alfalfa",
        "distractor_3": "clover"
      },
      {
        "id": "1888",
        "question": "What are the three primary nutrients required for a 'complete fertilizer'?",
        "answer": "nitrogen, phosphorus, potassium",
        "distractor_1": "nitrogen, phosphorus, calcium",
        "distractor_2": "nitrogen, potassium, carbon",
        "distractor_3": "phosphorus, carbon, calcium"
      },
      {
        "id": "1889",
        "question": "Choose the land-use practice that would NOT be recommended for sustainable agriculture.",
        "answer": "clear-cutting to obtain more cropland",
        "distractor_1": "controlling erosion by terracing",
        "distractor_2": "practicing crop rotation",
        "distractor_3": "using biological pest control methods"
      },
      {
        "id": "1890",
        "question": "Organic matter in the soil does NOT contain which of the following?",
        "answer": "clay",
        "distractor_1": "animal wastes",
        "distractor_2": "decomposing animal matter",
        "distractor_3": "decaying leaf litter"
      },
      {
        "id": "1891",
        "question": "What descriptive best characterizes a soil with a pH range of 4-9?",
        "answer": "characteristic of most soils",
        "distractor_1": "too acidic for most plants",
        "distractor_2": "too basic for most plants",
        "distractor_3": "characteristic of all soils"
      },
      {
        "id": "1892",
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT an organic matter found in soil?",
        "answer": "clay",
        "distractor_1": "decaying leaf litter",
        "distractor_2": "animal wastes",
        "distractor_3": "decomposing animals"
      },
      {
        "id": "1893",
        "question": "What is the name of the pathway that recycles elements through the earth?",
        "answer": "biogeochemical",
        "distractor_1": "energy",
        "distractor_2": "weather",
        "distractor_3": "organic"
      },
      {
        "id": "1894",
        "question": "Which of the following crops is NOT a nitrogen-fixing crop?",
        "answer": "corn",
        "distractor_1": "soybean",
        "distractor_2": "alfalfa",
        "distractor_3": "clover"
      },
      {
        "id": "1895",
        "question": "Complete fertilizers contain three elements. Nitrogen and phosphorus are two. What is the third element found in a complete fertilizer?",
        "answer": "potassium",
        "distractor_1": "carbon",
        "distractor_2": "calcium",
        "distractor_3": "sulfur"
      },
      {
        "id": "6524",
        "question": "What is known as the mass of material, such as rock, from which soil develops?",
        "answer": "parent material",
        "distractor_1": "topsoil",
        "distractor_2": "fertilizer",
        "distractor_3": "erosion"
      },
      {
        "id": "6525",
        "question": "What is defined as plant and animal matter in various stages of decay?",
        "answer": "organic matter",
        "distractor_1": "humus",
        "distractor_2": "compost",
        "distractor_3": "fertilizer"
      },
      {
        "id": "6526",
        "question": "What is known as well-decomposed organic matter?",
        "answer": "humus",
        "distractor_1": "fertilizer",
        "distractor_2": "topsoil",
        "distractor_3": "compost"
      },
      {
        "id": "6527",
        "question": "What is used to describe the makeup of various soils?",
        "answer": "soil texture triangle",
        "distractor_1": "soil pH",
        "distractor_2": "strip cropping",
        "distractor_3": "terracing"
      },
      {
        "id": "6528",
        "question": "What is known as soil containing humus, roots, and organisms?",
        "answer": "topsoil",
        "distractor_1": "fertilizer",
        "distractor_2": "compost",
        "distractor_3": "organic matter"
      },
      {
        "id": "6529",
        "question": "What is defined as the loss of topsoil due to wind, water action, or poor land-use practices?",
        "answer": "erosion",
        "distractor_1": "decomposition",
        "distractor_2": "stripping",
        "distractor_3": "terracing"
      },
      {
        "id": "6530",
        "question": "What affects what nutrients are available to plants in the soil?",
        "answer": "soil pH",
        "distractor_1": "parent material",
        "distractor_2": "biogeochemical cycle",
        "distractor_3": "decomposition"
      },
      {
        "id": "6531",
        "question": "Which of the following are added to soil to increase nutrients available for plant growth?",
        "answer": "fertilizer",
        "distractor_1": "compost",
        "distractor_2": "humus",
        "distractor_3": "topsoil"
      },
      {
        "id": "6532",
        "question": "What is defined as alternating the planting of crops that need plowing with unplowed crops?",
        "answer": "strip cropping",
        "distractor_1": "terracing ",
        "distractor_2": "contour plowing",
        "distractor_3": "weathering"
      },
      {
        "id": "6533",
        "question": "What is defined as building earthen ridges or embankments to slow water runoff?",
        "answer": "terracing",
        "distractor_1": "strip cropping",
        "distractor_2": "erosion",
        "distractor_3": "weathering"
      },
      {
        "id": "6534",
        "question": "What is defined as plowing around or across a slope?",
        "answer": "contour plowing",
        "distractor_1": "strip cropping",
        "distractor_2": "terracing",
        "distractor_3": "soil texturing"
      },
      {
        "id": "6535",
        "question": "Which of the following is defined as forming organic fertilizer from a mixture of leaf litter, manure, and household waste?",
        "answer": "composting",
        "distractor_1": "erosion",
        "distractor_2": "strip cropping",
        "distractor_3": "terracing"
      },
      {
        "id": "6536",
        "question": "What is described as forming organic fertilizer from a mixture of leaf litter, manure, and household waste?",
        "answer": "decomposition",
        "distractor_1": "composting",
        "distractor_2": "weathering",
        "distractor_3": "contour plowing"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "122",
    "name": "Early Childhood",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2881",
        "question": "What term means to turn a child’s attention toward something else?",
        "answer": "redirect",
        "distractor_1": "stifle",
        "distractor_2": "corral",
        "distractor_3": "adjust"
      },
      {
        "id": "2882",
        "question": "Which of the following describes a child when they learn to walk?",
        "answer": "toddlers",
        "distractor_1": "walkers",
        "distractor_2": "big boys and girls",
        "distractor_3": "preschoolers"
      },
      {
        "id": "4017",
        "question": "Which term refers to an automatic body response to a stimulus?",
        "answer": "reflex",
        "distractor_1": "instinct",
        "distractor_2": "knee-jerk",
        "distractor_3": "imitation"
      },
      {
        "id": "4018",
        "question": "Watching another person and then acting out that behavior is referred to as this type of form.",
        "answer": "deferred imitation",
        "distractor_1": "attachment behavior",
        "distractor_2": "temperament",
        "distractor_3": "stereotyping"
      },
      {
        "id": "4019",
        "question": "How many calories does a single gram of protein contain?",
        "answer": "4",
        "distractor_1": "6",
        "distractor_2": "9",
        "distractor_3": "12"
      },
      {
        "id": "2886",
        "question": "About how many hours of sleep each night do preschoolers need?",
        "answer": "10",
        "distractor_1": "8",
        "distractor_2": "12",
        "distractor_3": "14"
      },
      {
        "id": "2891",
        "question": "What type of development involves changes in a child’s body size and his or her ability to accomplish tasks?",
        "answer": "physical development",
        "distractor_1": "social development",
        "distractor_2": "emotional development",
        "distractor_3": "intellectual development"
      },
      {
        "id": "2892",
        "question": "Children gradually play less by themselves and more with other children during these years.",
        "answer": "preschool",
        "distractor_1": "infant",
        "distractor_2": "toddler",
        "distractor_3": "middle years"
      },
      {
        "id": "2893",
        "question": "What is the first thing you should do if the toddler you are baby-sitting begins to choke?",
        "answer": "use the Heimlich maneuver",
        "distractor_1": "give mouth-to-mouth resuscitation",
        "distractor_2": "get a neighbor",
        "distractor_3": "call 911"
      },
      {
        "id": "2898",
        "question": "To make a room appear pleasant and spacious, colors such as blue, green, and purple should be used. Which term is generally used to describe these colors?",
        "answer": "cool",
        "distractor_1": "warm",
        "distractor_2": "hot",
        "distractor_3": "cold"
      },
      {
        "id": "2899",
        "question": "Nutrition labels on food products are generally based on a diet of how many calories?",
        "answer": "2,000",
        "distractor_1": "1,000",
        "distractor_2": "1,200",
        "distractor_3": "1,500"
      },
      {
        "id": "8177",
        "question": "When a caregiver makes a suggestion to a child that requires the child to answer him or her, which of the following strategies is being used?",
        "answer": "prompt",
        "distractor_1": "feature",
        "distractor_2": "parallel play",
        "distractor_3": "toy"
      },
      {
        "id": "6010",
        "question": "What is known as placing thoughts for consideration into a child's mind?",
        "answer": "suggesting",
        "distractor_1": "encouraging",
        "distractor_2": "intimidating",
        "distractor_3": "prompting"
      },
      {
        "id": "6011",
        "question": "What is the term used to define the first month after birth?",
        "answer": "newborn",
        "distractor_1": "infant",
        "distractor_2": "toddler",
        "distractor_3": "baby"
      },
      {
        "id": "6012",
        "question": "What is the term for a guidance technique that helps children believe in themselves?",
        "answer": "encouraging",
        "distractor_1": "redirecting",
        "distractor_2": "praise",
        "distractor_3": "self motivation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6013",
        "question": "What is referred to as playing with other children in a group activity?",
        "answer": "cooperative play",
        "distractor_1": "parallel play",
        "distractor_2": "intellectual development",
        "distractor_3": "discipline"
      },
      {
        "id": "6014",
        "question": "What term describes the way that children react to their environments?",
        "answer": "temperament",
        "distractor_1": "attitude",
        "distractor_2": "body language",
        "distractor_3": "discipline"
      },
      {
        "id": "6015",
        "question": "What is known as playing near another child but not with him or her?",
        "answer": "parallel play",
        "distractor_1": "individual play",
        "distractor_2": "cooperative play",
        "distractor_3": "redirection"
      },
      {
        "id": "6016",
        "question": "What are the various methods used to teach children acceptable behavior?",
        "answer": "discipline",
        "distractor_1": "prompting",
        "distractor_2": "modeling",
        "distractor_3": "redirecting"
      },
      {
        "id": "6017",
        "question": "What is referred to as the ability to think, reason, use language, and form ideas?",
        "answer": "intellectual development",
        "distractor_1": "physical development",
        "distractor_2": "development",
        "distractor_3": "growth"
      },
      {
        "id": "6018",
        "question": "What is the name given to a child from birth through age one?",
        "answer": "infant",
        "distractor_1": "toddler",
        "distractor_2": "baby",
        "distractor_3": "newborn"
      },
      {
        "id": "8167",
        "question": "Which of the following terms is defined as change or growth in a child?",
        "answer": "development",
        "distractor_1": "temperament",
        "distractor_2": "culture",
        "distractor_3": "environment"
      },
      {
        "id": "8168",
        "question": "About how many hours of sleep each night do toddlers generally need?",
        "answer": "10-12",
        "distractor_1": "6-7",
        "distractor_2": "8-9",
        "distractor_3": "13-15"
      },
      {
        "id": "8170",
        "question": "An average baby's weight increases about 150 percent in the first nine months. If a baby weighs 8 pounds at birth, about how much will it weigh at 9 months?",
        "answer": "20 pounds",
        "distractor_1": "12 pounds",
        "distractor_2": "16 pounds",
        "distractor_3": "24 pounds"
      },
      {
        "id": "8171",
        "question": "An average-sized boy grows in length from about 53 centimeters at birth to about 98 centimeters at age three. Determine the approximate increase in height between birth and age three.",
        "answer": "85%",
        "distractor_1": "45%",
        "distractor_2": "65%",
        "distractor_3": "75%"
      },
      {
        "id": "8173",
        "question": "What is the name given to a child from about age two and one-half to about age seven?",
        "answer": "preschooler",
        "distractor_1": "infant",
        "distractor_2": "teenager",
        "distractor_3": "toddler"
      },
      {
        "id": "8174",
        "question": "What is the term that describes a substance that can provide energy and build tissue?",
        "answer": "nutrient",
        "distractor_1": "mineral",
        "distractor_2": "fluid",
        "distractor_3": "trace element"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "123",
    "name": "Practical Skills",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2581",
        "question": "Name the most commonly used hardware piece in a house that provides the first defense against intruders.",
        "answer": "lockset",
        "distractor_1": "wide-angle viewer",
        "distractor_2": "garage door opener",
        "distractor_3": "alarm"
      },
      {
        "id": "2585",
        "question": "Identify the most used hardware piece in a house that provides the first defense against intruders.",
        "answer": "locksets",
        "distractor_1": "wide-angle viewers",
        "distractor_2": "garage door openers",
        "distractor_3": "alarms"
      },
      {
        "id": "2586",
        "question": "Which plumbing fixture does NOT require a hot water supply?",
        "answer": "toilet",
        "distractor_1": "kitchen faucet",
        "distractor_2": "dishwasher",
        "distractor_3": "shower"
      },
      {
        "id": "2587",
        "question": "Which of the following tools is an example of a compound first-class lever?",
        "answer": "pliers",
        "distractor_1": "combination wrench",
        "distractor_2": "hammer",
        "distractor_3": "screwdriver"
      },
      {
        "id": "2588",
        "question": "The round prong on an electrical plug fulfills which function?",
        "answer": "ground",
        "distractor_1": "switch",
        "distractor_2": "receptacle",
        "distractor_3": "circuit"
      },
      {
        "id": "2589",
        "question": "Identify the most common household plumbing problem.",
        "answer": "leaky faucet",
        "distractor_1": "faulty water heater",
        "distractor_2": "clogged vent pipe",
        "distractor_3": "broken water line"
      },
      {
        "id": "2590",
        "question": "Which type of hammer is designed to drive and pull nails and should never be used to strike metal tools?",
        "answer": "claw",
        "distractor_1": "rip",
        "distractor_2": "shingler's",
        "distractor_3": "barrel"
      },
      {
        "id": "2591",
        "question": "Identify the receptacle used as a safety device that protects against electrical shock caused by a faulty or worn-out plug.",
        "answer": "GFCI",
        "distractor_1": "high-voltage",
        "distractor_2": "non-polarized",
        "distractor_3": "ceramic duplex"
      },
      {
        "id": "2592",
        "question": "Name the metal plate that fastens to the doorjamb which holds the bolt and secures the door.",
        "answer": "strike plate",
        "distractor_1": "rim lock",
        "distractor_2": "retaining plate",
        "distractor_3": "faceplate"
      },
      {
        "id": "2593",
        "question": "Identify the threaded fasteners used to hold objects together or hang items on a wall.",
        "answer": "screws",
        "distractor_1": "nails",
        "distractor_2": "staples",
        "distractor_3": "cotter pins"
      },
      {
        "id": "2594",
        "question": "What is the purpose of the round prong on an electrical plug?",
        "answer": "ground",
        "distractor_1": "switch",
        "distractor_2": "receptacle",
        "distractor_3": "circuit"
      },
      {
        "id": "2595",
        "question": "Which type of furniture uses individual furniture pieces that are manufactured, boxed, and shipped to the consumer for assembly?",
        "answer": "prefabricated",
        "distractor_1": "preassembled",
        "distractor_2": "prerequisite",
        "distractor_3": "premanufactured"
      },
      {
        "id": "2596",
        "question": "A regular household lightbulb is also referred to as which of the following?",
        "answer": "incandescent",
        "distractor_1": "solar",
        "distractor_2": "halogen",
        "distractor_3": "fluorescent"
      },
      {
        "id": "2597",
        "question": "Threaded fasteners, used to hold objects together or hang items on a wall, are more commonly referred to as which of the following items?",
        "answer": "screws",
        "distractor_1": "nails",
        "distractor_2": "staples",
        "distractor_3": "cotter pins"
      },
      {
        "id": "2598",
        "question": "A regular household lightbulb is also known as which type of light?",
        "answer": "incandescent",
        "distractor_1": "solar",
        "distractor_2": "halogen",
        "distractor_3": "fluorescent"
      },
      {
        "id": "2600",
        "question": "Identify the type of furniture where the individual furniture pieces are manufactured, boxed, and shipped to the consumer for assembly.",
        "answer": "prefabricated",
        "distractor_1": "preassembled",
        "distractor_2": "premanufactured",
        "distractor_3": "prerequisite"
      },
      {
        "id": "2601",
        "question": "Which tool is based upon the principle of a wheel and axle?",
        "answer": "screwdriver",
        "distractor_1": "level",
        "distractor_2": "pliers",
        "distractor_3": "hammer"
      },
      {
        "id": "2602",
        "question": "Which system carries waste, wastewater, and dangerous gases away from the home?",
        "answer": "DWV",
        "distractor_1": "WWWDG",
        "distractor_2": "PVC",
        "distractor_3": "USPS"
      },
      {
        "id": "2603",
        "question": "Which tool is an example of a compound first-class lever?",
        "answer": "pliers",
        "distractor_1": "hammer",
        "distractor_2": "screwdriver",
        "distractor_3": "combination wrench"
      },
      {
        "id": "2605",
        "question": "Which type of faucet has separate handles for hot and cold water and can be identified by a threaded stem assembly?",
        "answer": "compression",
        "distractor_1": "ball",
        "distractor_2": "cartridge",
        "distractor_3": "disc"
      },
      {
        "id": "2607",
        "question": "Which of the following is the most common household plumbing problem?",
        "answer": "leaky faucet",
        "distractor_1": "clogged vent pipe",
        "distractor_2": "broken water line",
        "distractor_3": "faulty water heater"
      },
      {
        "id": "2608",
        "question": "Name the tool that is an example of the wheel and axle.",
        "answer": "screwdriver",
        "distractor_1": "hammer",
        "distractor_2": "pliers",
        "distractor_3": "level"
      },
      {
        "id": "6539",
        "question": "What is a highly purified form of iron that is easily shaped, forged, or welded?",
        "answer": "Wrought iron",
        "distractor_1": "Iron",
        "distractor_2": "Metal",
        "distractor_3": "Copper"
      },
      {
        "id": "6541",
        "question": "What is a unit of power, especially electrical power, equal to 1,000 watts?",
        "answer": "Kilowatt",
        "distractor_1": "Wattage",
        "distractor_2": "Ohm",
        "distractor_3": "Volt"
      },
      {
        "id": "6542",
        "question": "What is a principal measurement system used in the U.S. for home maintenance and repair?",
        "answer": "English Units of Measurement",
        "distractor_1": "British Units of Measurement",
        "distractor_2": "Metric system",
        "distractor_3": "National units of measurement"
      },
      {
        "id": "6544",
        "question": "What is an amount of power, especially electrical power, expressed in watts or kilowatts?",
        "answer": "Wattage",
        "distractor_1": "Ohm",
        "distractor_2": "Volt",
        "distractor_3": "Kilowatt"
      },
      {
        "id": "6545",
        "question": "What is incapable of reacting with other elements to form chemical compounds?",
        "answer": "Inert",
        "distractor_1": "Inertia",
        "distractor_2": "Blending",
        "distractor_3": "Chemical compound"
      },
      {
        "id": "6549",
        "question": "What is the amount something is allowed to vary from the value intended?",
        "answer": "Tolerance",
        "distractor_1": "Ability",
        "distractor_2": "Forgiveness",
        "distractor_3": "Sorrow"
      },
      {
        "id": "6551",
        "question": "What is a measurement system in which all units are based upon multiples of 10?",
        "answer": "Metric system",
        "distractor_1": "English Units of Measurement",
        "distractor_2": "National metric system",
        "distractor_3": "Standardized measurements"
      },
      {
        "id": "6553",
        "question": "What is a simple machine consisting of a resistance arm, fulcrum, and an effort arm?",
        "answer": "Lever",
        "distractor_1": "Wheel and axel",
        "distractor_2": "Fulcrum",
        "distractor_3": "Wrench"
      },
      {
        "id": "6556",
        "question": "What are the pipes, fixtures, and other equipment used in a system through which liquid or gas flows?",
        "answer": "Plumbing",
        "distractor_1": "Wiring",
        "distractor_2": "Drainage system",
        "distractor_3": "Septic system"
      },
      {
        "id": "6558",
        "question": "A screwdriver is an example of this simple machine?",
        "answer": "Wheel and axle",
        "distractor_1": "Lever",
        "distractor_2": "Wrench",
        "distractor_3": "Fulcrum"
      },
      {
        "id": "6561",
        "question": "What is the main vent pipe in a drain, waste, and vent plumbing system?",
        "answer": "Soil stack",
        "distractor_1": "DWV system",
        "distractor_2": "Drainage system",
        "distractor_3": "Air vent"
      },
      {
        "id": "6562",
        "question": "What is a metal strip of wire wound in a tight coil and usually made from tungsten?",
        "answer": "Filament",
        "distractor_1": "Coil",
        "distractor_2": "Light bulb",
        "distractor_3": "Wattage"
      },
      {
        "id": "6564",
        "question": "What is an item used to hold something firmly in place?",
        "answer": "Fastener",
        "distractor_1": "Button",
        "distractor_2": "Zipper",
        "distractor_3": "Hook and eye"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "201",
    "name": "Applied Physics",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2034",
        "question": "Which of the following statements about laser light technology is true?",
        "answer": "It makes supermarket checkout quicker by scanning a bar code printed on the product package.",
        "distractor_1": "It makes printing a price on the product package possible.",
        "distractor_2": "It makes the production of composite materials possible.",
        "distractor_3": "It makes microwave transmission possible."
      },
      {
        "id": "2035",
        "question": "In which of the following situations would your weight change the most?",
        "answer": "if you were standing on the Moon",
        "distractor_1": "if you were standing in your room",
        "distractor_2": "if you were standing on a mountain",
        "distractor_3": "if you were standing on an ocean liner"
      },
      {
        "id": "2036",
        "question": "If the frequency of a sound wave is multiplied by 10, what happens to the wavelength?",
        "answer": "it is divided by 10",
        "distractor_1": "it is multiplied by 10",
        "distractor_2": "it stays the same",
        "distractor_3": "it increases by 10"
      },
      {
        "id": "2038",
        "question": "How does heat energy travel?",
        "answer": "by convection",
        "distractor_1": "by contraction",
        "distractor_2": "by isolation",
        "distractor_3": "by connection"
      },
      {
        "id": "2041",
        "question": "What happens to objects when heat energy causes them to expand?",
        "answer": "They get larger.",
        "distractor_1": "They get smaller.",
        "distractor_2": "They contract.",
        "distractor_3": "They become more dense."
      },
      {
        "id": "2042",
        "question": "Heat travels in three ways: conduction, convection, and which of the following?",
        "answer": "radiation",
        "distractor_1": "joules",
        "distractor_2": "velocity",
        "distractor_3": "contraction"
      },
      {
        "id": "2043",
        "question": "Which physical state of matter has a definite volume and takes the shape of its container?",
        "answer": "liquid",
        "distractor_1": "solid",
        "distractor_2": "gas",
        "distractor_3": "plasma"
      },
      {
        "id": "2044",
        "question": "What phenomenon do vibrating molecules create?",
        "answer": "heat",
        "distractor_1": "gravity",
        "distractor_2": "inertia",
        "distractor_3": "force"
      },
      {
        "id": "2047",
        "question": "Which of the following are properties of the liquid state of matter?",
        "answer": "a definite volume, but takes the shape of its container",
        "distractor_1": "mass, definite shape",
        "distractor_2": "a changing volume, but takes the shape of its container",
        "distractor_3": "a definite volume and a definite shape"
      },
      {
        "id": "2048",
        "question": "The law of energy conservation states that energy can be neither created nor destroyed. What is the only thing that can happen to energy?",
        "answer": "Energy can be converted.",
        "distractor_1": "Energy can be increased.",
        "distractor_2": "Energy can be decreased.",
        "distractor_3": "Energy can be unchanged."
      },
      {
        "id": "2050",
        "question": "What is the term for the length from the top of one sound wave to the top of the next?",
        "answer": "wavelength",
        "distractor_1": "aptitude",
        "distractor_2": "amplitude",
        "distractor_3": "frequency"
      },
      {
        "id": "2052",
        "question": "A red slide would filter the most light of what color?",
        "answer": "green",
        "distractor_1": "pink",
        "distractor_2": "white",
        "distractor_3": "red"
      },
      {
        "id": "2053",
        "question": "One of the most important laws of science states that energy can be neither created nor destroyed. It can only be changed from one form to another. What is this law called?",
        "answer": "conservation of energy",
        "distractor_1": "energy transfer",
        "distractor_2": "constant energy",
        "distractor_3": "motion"
      },
      {
        "id": "2054",
        "question": "Which of the following would change if you went to the Moon?",
        "answer": "your weight",
        "distractor_1": "your mass",
        "distractor_2": "your volume",
        "distractor_3": "your height"
      },
      {
        "id": "2055",
        "question": "Which of the following creates the phenomenon known as heat?",
        "answer": "vibrating molecules",
        "distractor_1": "convection",
        "distractor_2": "conduction",
        "distractor_3": "high sound"
      },
      {
        "id": "2056",
        "question": "What is the science of the relationship between matter and energy called?",
        "answer": "physics",
        "distractor_1": "technology",
        "distractor_2": "biology",
        "distractor_3": "kinesiology"
      },
      {
        "id": "2057",
        "question": "When two surfaces rub together, what is the resulting braking action called?",
        "answer": "friction",
        "distractor_1": "momentum",
        "distractor_2": "energy",
        "distractor_3": "power"
      },
      {
        "id": "2059",
        "question": "Which of the following makes automatic supermarket checkouts possible?",
        "answer": "laser light",
        "distractor_1": "biotechnology",
        "distractor_2": "microwaves",
        "distractor_3": "composites"
      },
      {
        "id": "2060",
        "question": "What is the ability of an object at rest to stay at rest and an object in motion to stay in motion known?",
        "answer": "inertia",
        "distractor_1": "mass",
        "distractor_2": "internal force",
        "distractor_3": "volume"
      },
      {
        "id": "2061",
        "question": "When heat energy causes an object to become larger, what happens to the object?",
        "answer": "It expands.",
        "distractor_1": "It radiates.",
        "distractor_2": "It conducts.",
        "distractor_3": "It contracts."
      },
      {
        "id": "6081",
        "question": "What is a change in the velocity of an object in a given amount of time?",
        "answer": "Acceleration",
        "distractor_1": "Amplitude",
        "distractor_2": "Velocity",
        "distractor_3": "Frequency"
      },
      {
        "id": "6082",
        "question": "What is the height of an electromagnetic wave?",
        "answer": "Amplitude",
        "distractor_1": "Conduction",
        "distractor_2": "Convection",
        "distractor_3": "Meter"
      },
      {
        "id": "6084",
        "question": "What is the transfer of heat or electricity through a solid?",
        "answer": "Conduction",
        "distractor_1": "Convection",
        "distractor_2": "Insulator",
        "distractor_3": "Refraction"
      },
      {
        "id": "6085",
        "question": "What is a material with low resistance to heat and electricity, allowing heat and electricity to pass through it easily?",
        "answer": "Conductor",
        "distractor_1": "Convector ",
        "distractor_2": "Conduit",
        "distractor_3": "Insulator"
      },
      {
        "id": "6087",
        "question": "What is the transfer of heat energy through gases or liquids?",
        "answer": "Convection",
        "distractor_1": "Conduction",
        "distractor_2": "Insulation",
        "distractor_3": "Refraction"
      },
      {
        "id": "6088",
        "question": "What is the entire range of radiant electromagnetic energy?",
        "answer": "Electromagnetic spectrum",
        "distractor_1": "Frequency",
        "distractor_2": "Wavelength",
        "distractor_3": "Visible light spectrum"
      },
      {
        "id": "6089",
        "question": "What is the number of waves in a given cycle, usually measured in cycles per second?",
        "answer": "Frequency",
        "distractor_1": "Volume",
        "distractor_2": "Depth",
        "distractor_3": "Velocity"
      },
      {
        "id": "6090",
        "question": "What is a material with a high resistance to heat and electricity -- a poor conductor?",
        "answer": "Insulator",
        "distractor_1": "Conductor",
        "distractor_2": "Conduit",
        "distractor_3": "Frequency"
      },
      {
        "id": "6093",
        "question": "What is a device that produces a very intense light made of only one wavelength; light amplification by stimulating emission of radiation?",
        "answer": "Laser",
        "distractor_1": "Insulator",
        "distractor_2": "Conductor",
        "distractor_3": "Accelerator "
      },
      {
        "id": "6096",
        "question": "What is the change in the direction of waves or rays due to bouncing off an object?",
        "answer": "Reflection",
        "distractor_1": "Refraction",
        "distractor_2": "Conduction",
        "distractor_3": "Retraction"
      },
      {
        "id": "6097",
        "question": "What is the bending of rays and waves as they pass from one medium into another, such as light passing from air into glass?",
        "answer": "Refraction",
        "distractor_1": "Reflection",
        "distractor_2": "Conduction",
        "distractor_3": "Convection"
      },
      {
        "id": "6099",
        "question": "What is the speed and direction of an object?",
        "answer": "Velocity",
        "distractor_1": "Acceleration",
        "distractor_2": "Mass",
        "distractor_3": "Weight"
      },
      {
        "id": "6101",
        "question": "What is electromagnetic waves that the eye can detect?",
        "answer": "Visible light spectrum",
        "distractor_1": "Electromagnetic spectrum",
        "distractor_2": "Wavelength",
        "distractor_3": "Amplitude"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "202",
    "name": "Biotechnology",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2091",
        "question": "What is a change in the DNA structure of a cell, in which the instructions for making protein are affected, called?",
        "answer": "a mutation",
        "distractor_1": "a clone",
        "distractor_2": "a misprint",
        "distractor_3": "a splice"
      },
      {
        "id": "2092",
        "question": "What is the process of removing DNA from one organism and combining it with the DNA of another organism?",
        "answer": "genetic engineering",
        "distractor_1": "mutant genealogy",
        "distractor_2": "the scientific method",
        "distractor_3": "chromosome synthesis"
      },
      {
        "id": "2094",
        "question": "What are bacteria used for in genetic engineering?",
        "answer": "hosts",
        "distractor_1": "food chains",
        "distractor_2": "models",
        "distractor_3": "predators"
      },
      {
        "id": "2095",
        "question": "How can DNA be changed artificially by scientists?",
        "answer": "splicing",
        "distractor_1": "cloning",
        "distractor_2": "mitigating",
        "distractor_3": "creating"
      },
      {
        "id": "2096",
        "question": "What is DNA?",
        "answer": "a molecule  that carries genetic information",
        "distractor_1": "an atom  that carries genetic information",
        "distractor_2": "a cell that carries genetic information",
        "distractor_3": "an enzyme  that carries genetic information"
      },
      {
        "id": "2097",
        "question": "Which of the following produces gamma radiation that may change the genetic code of cells in living organisms?",
        "answer": "radioactive elements",
        "distractor_1": "radon",
        "distractor_2": "laser rays",
        "distractor_3": "delta waves"
      },
      {
        "id": "2098",
        "question": "The structure of the DNA molecule resembles a twisted staircase. What is the name given to this structure?",
        "answer": "double helix",
        "distractor_1": "spiraling strand",
        "distractor_2": "corkscrew",
        "distractor_3": "whirligig"
      },
      {
        "id": "2100",
        "question": "Rings of DNA found in bacteria are responsible for a great deal of the exchange of genetic information that occurs in nature. What are these rings?",
        "answer": "plasmids",
        "distractor_1": "enzymes",
        "distractor_2": "strands",
        "distractor_3": "viruses"
      },
      {
        "id": "2101",
        "question": "What is the large molecule found inside a cell that contains all of the information needed for the cell to reproduce and carry out its life processes?",
        "answer": "DNA",
        "distractor_1": "ATP",
        "distractor_2": "PCP",
        "distractor_3": "RGB"
      },
      {
        "id": "2102",
        "question": "Restriction enzymes are used to cut the DNA chain at a particular site. Why?",
        "answer": "so that new genes may be inserted",
        "distractor_1": "so that new genes may be created",
        "distractor_2": "so that new genes may be developed",
        "distractor_3": "so that new genes may be removed"
      },
      {
        "id": "2103",
        "question": "In what field is genetic engineering commonly applied?",
        "answer": "agriculture",
        "distractor_1": "construction",
        "distractor_2": "education",
        "distractor_3": "physics"
      },
      {
        "id": "2104",
        "question": "Which of these may cause mutations to occur in the cell's genetic code?",
        "answer": "radiation",
        "distractor_1": "lasers",
        "distractor_2": "vibrations",
        "distractor_3": "S waves"
      },
      {
        "id": "2106",
        "question": "Where are plasmids that can exchange genetic information found?",
        "answer": "bacteria",
        "distractor_1": "viruses",
        "distractor_2": "protists",
        "distractor_3": "yeasts"
      },
      {
        "id": "2107",
        "question": "Which of the following is a combination of nitrogen, carbon, hydrogen, and oxygen atoms found in DNA?",
        "answer": "nitrogenous base",
        "distractor_1": "deoxyribose sugar",
        "distractor_2": "phosphate",
        "distractor_3": "cellulose"
      },
      {
        "id": "2109",
        "question": "What is used to cut the DNA chain so that new genes may be inserted?",
        "answer": "restriction enzymes",
        "distractor_1": "restriction plasmids",
        "distractor_2": "restriction lasers",
        "distractor_3": "restriction viruses"
      },
      {
        "id": "2110",
        "question": "What is biotechnology?",
        "answer": "the use of genetic engineering to make products",
        "distractor_1": "the creation of life in the laboratory",
        "distractor_2": "the study of all living things",
        "distractor_3": "the study of technology used in the lab"
      },
      {
        "id": "2112",
        "question": "What is the term for the use of genetic engineering on humans?",
        "answer": "biotechnology",
        "distractor_1": "biodiversity",
        "distractor_2": "paragenetics",
        "distractor_3": "technological advancements"
      },
      {
        "id": "2115",
        "question": "What are researchers developing that are capable of degrading toxic chemicals, assisting in oil spill cleanups, and decomposing grease that clogs drains?",
        "answer": "bacteria",
        "distractor_1": "viruses",
        "distractor_2": "hybrid plants",
        "distractor_3": "amoebas"
      },
      {
        "id": "2116",
        "question": "Which of these single-celled organisms are often used as hosts in genetic engineering?",
        "answer": "bacteria",
        "distractor_1": "amoebas",
        "distractor_2": "paramecia",
        "distractor_3": "euglenas"
      },
      {
        "id": "2117",
        "question": "What is a result of the practical application of genetic engineering?",
        "answer": "crops resistant to disease",
        "distractor_1": "cleaner air and water",
        "distractor_2": "smarter students",
        "distractor_3": "stronger, more durable bridges"
      },
      {
        "id": "6152",
        "question": "What is referred to as using a type of genetic scissors called restriction enzymes to cut a DNA chain at a particular point so that new genes can be inserted?",
        "answer": "gene splicing",
        "distractor_1": "splicing",
        "distractor_2": "DNA restriction",
        "distractor_3": "enzyme restriction"
      },
      {
        "id": "6153",
        "question": "What is known as any group of organic compounds composed of a sugar, a phosphate, and one of several nitrogen bases?",
        "answer": "nucleotide",
        "distractor_1": "enzyme",
        "distractor_2": "DNA",
        "distractor_3": "gene"
      },
      {
        "id": "6154",
        "question": "What is known as DNA altered through laboratory manipulation in which genes from one organism are transplanted or spliced into the genetic material of an organism of a different species?",
        "answer": "recombinant DNA",
        "distractor_1": "transgenic",
        "distractor_2": "altered DNA",
        "distractor_3": "plasmid"
      },
      {
        "id": "6155",
        "question": "What is referred to as the use of living organisms or biological substances to perform certain industrial or manufacturing processes?",
        "answer": "biotechnology",
        "distractor_1": "biology",
        "distractor_2": "life science",
        "distractor_3": "industrial technology"
      },
      {
        "id": "6156",
        "question": "What is described as a small body in all living cells, usually contained in a nucleus and composed mostly of DNA?",
        "answer": "chromosome",
        "distractor_1": "plasmid",
        "distractor_2": "enzyme",
        "distractor_3": "gene"
      },
      {
        "id": "6157",
        "question": "What is known as a segment of DNA, located at a particular point on a chromosome, that determines hereditary characteristics?",
        "answer": "gene",
        "distractor_1": "enzyme",
        "distractor_2": "nucleotide",
        "distractor_3": "plasmid"
      },
      {
        "id": "6158",
        "question": "What are referred to as any of numerous proteins produced in living cells and acting as catalysts in the chemical processes of living organisms?",
        "answer": "enzyme",
        "distractor_1": "plasmids",
        "distractor_2": "chromosomes",
        "distractor_3": "nucleotides"
      },
      {
        "id": "6173",
        "question": "Which of the following is described being used to produce an organism or cell of one species into which one or more genes of another species have been incorporated?",
        "answer": "transgenic",
        "distractor_1": "genetic engineering",
        "distractor_2": "engineering",
        "distractor_3": "genetics"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "203",
    "name": "Creative Solutions",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2230",
        "question": "Which problem-solving step is immediately prior to 'selecting a solution?'",
        "answer": "brainstorming",
        "distractor_1": "induction",
        "distractor_2": "evaluating the test",
        "distractor_3": "implementation"
      },
      {
        "id": "2231",
        "question": "What is the descriptive term used to identify a problem solver who creates and carries out plans for new products and structures?",
        "answer": "a designer",
        "distractor_1": "a programmer",
        "distractor_2": "an administrator",
        "distractor_3": "an entrepreneur"
      },
      {
        "id": "2233",
        "question": "Identify the multistep process used to reach a solution in response to a human need or want.",
        "answer": "problem solving",
        "distractor_1": "technology",
        "distractor_2": "unity",
        "distractor_3": "ergonomics"
      },
      {
        "id": "2234",
        "question": "What is the problem-solving step immediately following 'identifying the problem?'",
        "answer": "brainstorming",
        "distractor_1": "induction",
        "distractor_2": "evaluating the test",
        "distractor_3": "implementation"
      },
      {
        "id": "2235",
        "question": "With which of the following roles is George Washington Carver most identified?",
        "answer": "scientist",
        "distractor_1": "civil rights activist",
        "distractor_2": "computer programmer",
        "distractor_3": "pilot"
      },
      {
        "id": "2236",
        "question": "Which of the following rules does NOT apply when brainstorming?",
        "answer": "make fun of someone’s idea",
        "distractor_1": "involve several people",
        "distractor_2": "approach the problem differently",
        "distractor_3": "record all ideas"
      },
      {
        "id": "2237",
        "question": "Which choice best describes the problem-solving process used to reach a solution in response to a human need or want?",
        "answer": "multistep",
        "distractor_1": "one-step",
        "distractor_2": "easy",
        "distractor_3": "three-step"
      },
      {
        "id": "4765",
        "question": "This problem-solving process occurs when the solution leaps into the mind of the problem solver. ",
        "answer": "insight",
        "distractor_1": "deduction",
        "distractor_2": "induction",
        "distractor_3": "accident"
      },
      {
        "id": "2238",
        "question": "What is the name of the document that gives an inventor the exclusive right to make and sell their invention?",
        "answer": "patent",
        "distractor_1": "trademark",
        "distractor_2": "copyright",
        "distractor_3": "deed"
      },
      {
        "id": "2240",
        "question": "Name the method of solving problems in which many solutions are tried until one is found to be acceptable.",
        "answer": "trial and error",
        "distractor_1": "deduction",
        "distractor_2": "modeling",
        "distractor_3": "induction"
      },
      {
        "id": "2242",
        "question": "George Washington Carver spent most of his life solving problems related to which of the following areas?",
        "answer": "farming",
        "distractor_1": "civil rights",
        "distractor_2": "computers",
        "distractor_3": "air travel"
      },
      {
        "id": "2243",
        "question": "The results of an evaluation prove the possible solution to be correct. What step of the Synergistic Problem-solving Model should be taken next?",
        "answer": "implement the solution",
        "distractor_1": "test the solution again",
        "distractor_2": "redesign the solution",
        "distractor_3": "re-evaluation of the solution"
      },
      {
        "id": "2245",
        "question": "What solution did George Washington Carver use to address the problem of declining farm income in the South?",
        "answer": "teaching crop rotation",
        "distractor_1": "inventing crop dusters",
        "distractor_2": "inventing new uses for cotton",
        "distractor_3": "leading protests"
      },
      {
        "id": "2246",
        "question": "During which step of problem solving does implementing a possible solution immediately follow?",
        "answer": "evaluating a possible solution",
        "distractor_1": "brainstorming for a possible solution",
        "distractor_2": "testing a possible solution",
        "distractor_3": "selecting a possible solution"
      },
      {
        "id": "2247",
        "question": "When the results of an evaluation prove the possible solution wrong, what step of the Synergistic Problem-solving Model should be next?",
        "answer": "redesign the solution",
        "distractor_1": "test the solution again",
        "distractor_2": "implement the solution",
        "distractor_3": "ignore the evaluation"
      },
      {
        "id": "2248",
        "question": "What is the first step in the problem-solving process?",
        "answer": "identify the problem",
        "distractor_1": "brainstorm solutions",
        "distractor_2": "evaluate ideas",
        "distractor_3": "find a solution"
      },
      {
        "id": "2254",
        "question": "When brainstorming, how many ideas should be written down and considered?",
        "answer": "all ideas presented",
        "distractor_1": "the first five ideas",
        "distractor_2": "only good ideas",
        "distractor_3": "the five most popular ideas"
      },
      {
        "id": "2255",
        "question": "When solving a problem, which step immediately follows 'selecting a possible solution?'",
        "answer": "testing",
        "distractor_1": "brainstorming",
        "distractor_2": "implementing",
        "distractor_3": "evaluating"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "204",
    "name": "Electricity",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2690",
        "question": "When batteries are connected in a series circuit, what math function is applied to calculate the voltage available to the circuit?",
        "answer": "addition",
        "distractor_1": "subtraction",
        "distractor_2": "multiplication",
        "distractor_3": "division"
      },
      {
        "id": "2691",
        "question": "Which of the following would be a good insulator?",
        "answer": "glass",
        "distractor_1": "silver",
        "distractor_2": "brass",
        "distractor_3": "lead"
      },
      {
        "id": "2692",
        "question": "What is the unit of measure for electrical pressure?",
        "answer": "voltage",
        "distractor_1": "ampere",
        "distractor_2": "watt",
        "distractor_3": "electron"
      },
      {
        "id": "2694",
        "question": "A magnet has two poles, a north pole and a south pole. Which pole will attract a north pole?",
        "answer": "south",
        "distractor_1": "north",
        "distractor_2": "neither north nor south",
        "distractor_3": "both north and south"
      },
      {
        "id": "2695",
        "question": "What type of charge does an electron contain?",
        "answer": "negative",
        "distractor_1": "neutral",
        "distractor_2": "positive",
        "distractor_3": "light"
      },
      {
        "id": "2696",
        "question": "Which of the following terms best classifies glass and rubber?",
        "answer": "insulators",
        "distractor_1": "conductors",
        "distractor_2": "resistors",
        "distractor_3": "inductors"
      },
      {
        "id": "2697",
        "question": "What type of circuit has only one path that allows electron flow?",
        "answer": "series",
        "distractor_1": "parallel",
        "distractor_2": "open",
        "distractor_3": "neutral"
      },
      {
        "id": "2698",
        "question": "What term describes materials that have the ability to transfer electrons from one atom to another?",
        "answer": "conductors",
        "distractor_1": "protons",
        "distractor_2": "insulators",
        "distractor_3": "partners"
      },
      {
        "id": "2699",
        "question": "A magnet has two poles, a north pole and a south pole. Which pole will attract a south pole?",
        "answer": "north",
        "distractor_1": "south",
        "distractor_2": "neither north nor south",
        "distractor_3": "both north and south"
      },
      {
        "id": "2700",
        "question": "What is the negatively charged part of an atom called?",
        "answer": "electron",
        "distractor_1": "proton",
        "distractor_2": "neutron",
        "distractor_3": "omegatron"
      },
      {
        "id": "2702",
        "question": "What is the measurement of electrical pressure?",
        "answer": "voltage",
        "distractor_1": "ampere",
        "distractor_2": "watt",
        "distractor_3": "electron"
      },
      {
        "id": "2704",
        "question": "Which of the following terms best classifies copper and gold?",
        "answer": "conductors",
        "distractor_1": "insulators",
        "distractor_2": "resistors",
        "distractor_3": "inductors"
      },
      {
        "id": "2705",
        "question": "Which of the following would be a good conductor?",
        "answer": "gold",
        "distractor_1": "rubber",
        "distractor_2": "silicon",
        "distractor_3": "wood"
      },
      {
        "id": "2706",
        "question": "What describes the condition that occurs when bare wires in an electrical circuit accidentally touch, causing more current to flow than the circuit can safely carry? It will cause a fuse or circuit breaker to interrupt current flow.",
        "answer": "short circuit",
        "distractor_1": "open circuit",
        "distractor_2": "series circuit",
        "distractor_3": "parallel circuit"
      },
      {
        "id": "2708",
        "question": "Which of the following terms best describes the opposition to the flow of electricity?",
        "answer": "resistance",
        "distractor_1": "amperage",
        "distractor_2": "voltage",
        "distractor_3": "watt"
      },
      {
        "id": "2709",
        "question": "Some materials are good conductors because they are able to easily transfer what element from one atom to another?",
        "answer": "electrons",
        "distractor_1": "protons",
        "distractor_2": "neutrons",
        "distractor_3": "isotopes"
      },
      {
        "id": "2710",
        "question": "What describes the condition that occurs when bare wires in an electrical circuit accidentally touch, causing more current to flow than the circuit can safely carry? It will cause a fuse or circuit breaker to interrupt current flow.",
        "answer": "short circuit",
        "distractor_1": "open circuit",
        "distractor_2": "series circuit",
        "distractor_3": "parallel circuit"
      },
      {
        "id": "2711",
        "question": "What is the unit of measure for electrical current?",
        "answer": "ampere",
        "distractor_1": "resistance",
        "distractor_2": "voltage",
        "distractor_3": "ohms"
      },
      {
        "id": "2712",
        "question": "Voltage is the measurement of which of the following?",
        "answer": "electrical pressure",
        "distractor_1": "current",
        "distractor_2": "resistance",
        "distractor_3": "loudness of sound"
      },
      {
        "id": "2713",
        "question": "How many paths are there for electron flow in a series circuit?",
        "answer": "one",
        "distractor_1": "indefinite",
        "distractor_2": "three",
        "distractor_3": "two"
      },
      {
        "id": "2714",
        "question": "What is the unit of measure for electrical current?",
        "answer": "ampere",
        "distractor_1": "resistance",
        "distractor_2": "voltage",
        "distractor_3": "ohms"
      },
      {
        "id": "2715",
        "question": "A continuous path along which electricity flows is known as what?",
        "answer": "circuit",
        "distractor_1": "watt",
        "distractor_2": "fuse",
        "distractor_3": "volt"
      },
      {
        "id": "2717",
        "question": "What is the unit of measure for electrical current?",
        "answer": "ampere",
        "distractor_1": "resistance",
        "distractor_2": "voltage",
        "distractor_3": "ohms"
      },
      {
        "id": "6311",
        "question": "What is an electron flow that changes direction on a regular basis?",
        "answer": "Alternating current (AC)",
        "distractor_1": "Direct current (DC)",
        "distractor_2": "Parallel circuit",
        "distractor_3": "Series circuit"
      },
      {
        "id": "6312",
        "question": "What is a device that stores DC electricity?",
        "answer": "Battery",
        "distractor_1": "Insulator",
        "distractor_2": "Series circuit",
        "distractor_3": "Conductor"
      },
      {
        "id": "6313",
        "question": "What is a measurement of the flow of electricity measured in amperes?",
        "answer": "Current",
        "distractor_1": "Ground",
        "distractor_2": "Ohm",
        "distractor_3": "Schematic"
      },
      {
        "id": "6314",
        "question": "What is an electron flow that does not change direction?",
        "answer": "Direct current (DC)",
        "distractor_1": "Alternating current (AC)",
        "distractor_2": "Parallel circuit",
        "distractor_3": "Series circuit"
      },
      {
        "id": "6315",
        "question": "What is an electrical conductor that has the same potential as the Earth?",
        "answer": "Ground",
        "distractor_1": "Insulator",
        "distractor_2": "Conductor",
        "distractor_3": "Switch"
      },
      {
        "id": "6316",
        "question": "What is an electrically powered device with a rotating shaft that converts electric energy to mechanical energy?",
        "answer": "Motor",
        "distractor_1": "Schematic",
        "distractor_2": "Switch",
        "distractor_3": "Battery"
      },
      {
        "id": "6317",
        "question": "What is a unit of measurement of electrical resistance?",
        "answer": "Ohm",
        "distractor_1": "Battery",
        "distractor_2": "Switch",
        "distractor_3": "Volt"
      },
      {
        "id": "6318",
        "question": "What is a circuit that provides more than one path for electron flow?",
        "answer": "Parallel circuit",
        "distractor_1": "Series circuit",
        "distractor_2": "Switch",
        "distractor_3": "Battery"
      },
      {
        "id": "6319",
        "question": "What is a diagram containing symbols that represent components for electrical, mechanical, or other systems?",
        "answer": "Schematic",
        "distractor_1": "Switch",
        "distractor_2": "Ground",
        "distractor_3": "Conductor"
      },
      {
        "id": "6320",
        "question": "What is a circuit with one path for electricity to follow?",
        "answer": "Series circuit",
        "distractor_1": "Parallel circuit",
        "distractor_2": "Switch",
        "distractor_3": "Insulator"
      },
      {
        "id": "6321",
        "question": "What is a device used to open or close an electric circuit?",
        "answer": "Switch",
        "distractor_1": "Motor",
        "distractor_2": "Battery",
        "distractor_3": "Schematic"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "205",
    "name": "Electronics",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2902",
        "question": "Ohm's law states: voltage equals current multiplied by resistance, or V = I x R. What is the voltage in a wire if the resistance is 5 ohms and the current is 6 amperes?",
        "answer": "30 volts",
        "distractor_1": "5 volts",
        "distractor_2": "6 volts",
        "distractor_3": "61 volts"
      },
      {
        "id": "2903",
        "question": "The number of amperes of current drawn from an electrical circuit is equal to the voltage divided by the resistance. If an electric toaster has a resistance of 25 ohms, how many amperes will it draw from a 120-volt electrical line?",
        "answer": "4.8 amps",
        "distractor_1": "5.5 amps",
        "distractor_2": "6.0 amps",
        "distractor_3": "1.2 amps"
      },
      {
        "id": "2904",
        "question": "Which one of the listed electronic components limits or controls the amount of current flowing through a circuit?",
        "answer": "resistor",
        "distractor_1": "capacitor",
        "distractor_2": "transistor",
        "distractor_3": "diode"
      },
      {
        "id": "2906",
        "question": "Which of the following electronic components limits the amount of electrical current flowing through a circuit?",
        "answer": "resistor",
        "distractor_1": "capacitor",
        "distractor_2": "transistor",
        "distractor_3": "LED"
      },
      {
        "id": "2907",
        "question": "What is a single electronic component that replaces an entire group of separate components?",
        "answer": "integrated circuit",
        "distractor_1": "inverted circuit",
        "distractor_2": "complex circuit",
        "distractor_3": "integral circuit"
      },
      {
        "id": "2908",
        "question": "Identify the circuit where patterns are etched into a thin layer of copper to form conducting paths.",
        "answer": "printed circuit",
        "distractor_1": "pattern circuit",
        "distractor_2": "digital circuit",
        "distractor_3": "analog circuit"
      },
      {
        "id": "2909",
        "question": "Which electronic component is designed to hold an electric charge?",
        "answer": "capacitor",
        "distractor_1": "transistor",
        "distractor_2": "resistor",
        "distractor_3": "diode"
      },
      {
        "id": "2910",
        "question": "Modern electronics make use of semiconductor materials. Which of the following is a very common type of semiconductor material?",
        "answer": "silicon",
        "distractor_1": "carbon",
        "distractor_2": "silver",
        "distractor_3": "plastic"
      },
      {
        "id": "2911",
        "question": "Which of the following is a very common type of semiconductor material?",
        "answer": "silicon",
        "distractor_1": "carbon",
        "distractor_2": "silver",
        "distractor_3": "plastic"
      },
      {
        "id": "2912",
        "question": "Identify the electronic component that can temporarily store electricity.",
        "answer": "capacitor",
        "distractor_1": "resistor",
        "distractor_2": "transistor",
        "distractor_3": "diode"
      },
      {
        "id": "2913",
        "question": "Name the single electronic component that replaces an entire group of separate components.",
        "answer": "integrated circuit",
        "distractor_1": "inverted circuit",
        "distractor_2": "integral circuit",
        "distractor_3": "complex circuit"
      },
      {
        "id": "2914",
        "question": "Identify the electronic component which allows current flow in one direction.",
        "answer": "diode",
        "distractor_1": "capacitor",
        "distractor_2": "transistor",
        "distractor_3": "resistor"
      },
      {
        "id": "2915",
        "question": "Silicon is best described by which of the following terms?",
        "answer": "semiconductor",
        "distractor_1": "conductor",
        "distractor_2": "insulator",
        "distractor_3": "terminator"
      },
      {
        "id": "2916",
        "question": "What function does a capacitor perform within a circuit?",
        "answer": "stores electrical energy",
        "distractor_1": "amplifies electrical energy",
        "distractor_2": "eliminates electrical energy",
        "distractor_3": "elevates electrical energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "2918",
        "question": "What is the name of a single chip containing many electrical components that can replace whole systems of separate components? ",
        "answer": "integrated circuit",
        "distractor_1": "printed circuit",
        "distractor_2": "digital circuit",
        "distractor_3": "analog circuit"
      },
      {
        "id": "2919",
        "question": "What is the correct name for a thin board made of an insulating material with patterns etched in a thin layer of copper on the surface to form conducting paths?",
        "answer": "printed circuit",
        "distractor_1": "integrated circuit",
        "distractor_2": "pattern circuit",
        "distractor_3": "analog circuit"
      },
      {
        "id": "2920",
        "question": "What is the function of a transistor, which is an electronic device having three terminals and is made of semiconductor materials?",
        "answer": "switches electrical current on and off",
        "distractor_1": "tunes electrical current",
        "distractor_2": "reverses electrical current",
        "distractor_3": "amplifies electrical current"
      },
      {
        "id": "2921",
        "question": "Which of the following is the most common method of making electrical connections?",
        "answer": "soldering",
        "distractor_1": "adhesive bonding",
        "distractor_2": "crimping",
        "distractor_3": "snap joining"
      },
      {
        "id": "2922",
        "question": "What is an LED?",
        "answer": "light emitting diode",
        "distractor_1": "light energized diode",
        "distractor_2": "laser energized diode",
        "distractor_3": "laser emitting diode"
      },
      {
        "id": "2923",
        "question": "Which one of the following electronic components allows electrical current to flow within a circuit in only one direction?",
        "answer": "diode",
        "distractor_1": "capacitor",
        "distractor_2": "transistor",
        "distractor_3": "resistor"
      },
      {
        "id": "2924",
        "question": "Kirkoff's first law says the current flowing into a junction equals the current flowing out. Assume wires carrying 7, 10, and 6 amps flow into a junction, and two wires carry current away. If one wire carries 10 amps away, how much does the other carry?",
        "answer": "13 amps",
        "distractor_1": "6 amps",
        "distractor_2": "7 amps",
        "distractor_3": "10 amps"
      },
      {
        "id": "2926",
        "question": "Identify the electronic device that switches electric currents on and off, has three terminals, and is made of semiconductor materials.",
        "answer": "transistor",
        "distractor_1": "potentiometer",
        "distractor_2": "diode",
        "distractor_3": "capacitor"
      },
      {
        "id": "2927",
        "question": "Which of the following choices is the most common way of making electrical connections?",
        "answer": "soldering",
        "distractor_1": "adhesive bonding",
        "distractor_2": "snap joining",
        "distractor_3": "crimping"
      },
      {
        "id": "2928",
        "question": "What is an LED?",
        "answer": "light emitting diode",
        "distractor_1": "light energized diode",
        "distractor_2": "laser energized diode",
        "distractor_3": "laser emitting diode"
      },
      {
        "id": "6322",
        "question": "What is a closed path through which electricity can flow?",
        "answer": "Circuit",
        "distractor_1": "Circuit board",
        "distractor_2": "Light-emitting diode (LED)",
        "distractor_3": "Schematic"
      },
      {
        "id": "6323",
        "question": "What is a thin insulator on which components are mounted and connected to form a circuit?",
        "answer": "Circuit board",
        "distractor_1": "Circuit chip",
        "distractor_2": "Capacitor",
        "distractor_3": "Circuit"
      },
      {
        "id": "6324",
        "question": "What is a unit of measurement of electrical resistance?",
        "answer": "Ohm",
        "distractor_1": "Voltage",
        "distractor_2": "Circuit board",
        "distractor_3": "Capacitor"
      },
      {
        "id": "6325",
        "question": "What is an opposition to the flow of electricity?",
        "answer": "Resistance",
        "distractor_1": "Ohm",
        "distractor_2": "Voltage",
        "distractor_3": "Schematic"
      },
      {
        "id": "6326",
        "question": "What is a diagram containing symbols that represent components for electrical, mechanical, or other systems?",
        "answer": "Schematic",
        "distractor_1": "Circuit board",
        "distractor_2": "Capacitor",
        "distractor_3": "Circuit"
      },
      {
        "id": "6327",
        "question": "What is a metal alloy of tin and lead used to join metals?",
        "answer": "Solder",
        "distractor_1": "Iron",
        "distractor_2": "Metal",
        "distractor_3": "Ohm"
      },
      {
        "id": "6328",
        "question": "What is a unit of measure of electrical pressure?",
        "answer": "Voltage",
        "distractor_1": "Ohm",
        "distractor_2": "Resistance",
        "distractor_3": "Circuit"
      },
      {
        "id": "6875",
        "question": "Identify in correct order the standard units for voltage, resistance, and current.",
        "answer": "volts, ohms, and amps ",
        "distractor_1": "volts, amps, and ohms",
        "distractor_2": "watts, ohms, and joules",
        "distractor_3": "ohms, joules, and amps"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "206",
    "name": "EP&M",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2956",
        "question": "Which of the following is used to describe heat from within Earth?",
        "answer": "geothermal",
        "distractor_1": "geographical",
        "distractor_2": "thermal dynamics",
        "distractor_3": "inert gas exchange"
      },
      {
        "id": "2957",
        "question": "Which of the following can neither be created nor destroyed? It can only be changed from one form to another.",
        "answer": "energy",
        "distractor_1": "life",
        "distractor_2": "power",
        "distractor_3": "work"
      },
      {
        "id": "2958",
        "question": "Which scientific law states: Energy can neither be created nor destroyed. It can only be changed from one form to another?",
        "answer": "law of conservation of energy",
        "distractor_1": "law of thermodynamics",
        "distractor_2": "Newton's first law of motion",
        "distractor_3": "Newton's second law of motion"
      },
      {
        "id": "2959",
        "question": "A parabolic dish can affect light energy in which of the following ways?",
        "answer": "focus light energy",
        "distractor_1": "diminish light energy",
        "distractor_2": "separate light energy",
        "distractor_3": "diffuse light energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "2960",
        "question": "Which of the following uses solar energy to produce electricity?",
        "answer": "photovoltaic cell",
        "distractor_1": "dry cell",
        "distractor_2": "geothermal",
        "distractor_3": "pneumatic"
      },
      {
        "id": "2961",
        "question": "What is the reaction to the direction and speed of a machine when gears are used?",
        "answer": "change in both speed and direction",
        "distractor_1": "increase in speed",
        "distractor_2": "decrease in speed",
        "distractor_3": "no change in both speed and direction"
      },
      {
        "id": "2962",
        "question": "What is involved with the study of hydraulics?",
        "answer": "pressure on liquids",
        "distractor_1": "pressure on gases",
        "distractor_2": "energy by position",
        "distractor_3": "energy from motion"
      },
      {
        "id": "2963",
        "question": "Levers are classified by the location of the effort, the fulcrum, and the load. Which class of levers is represented by a wheelbarrow?",
        "answer": "second-class lever",
        "distractor_1": "first-class lever",
        "distractor_2": "fourth-class lever",
        "distractor_3": "third-class lever"
      },
      {
        "id": "2964",
        "question": "What is the simple machine consisting of a bar and fulcrum that can be used to increase force or decrease the effort needed to move a load?",
        "answer": "lever",
        "distractor_1": "wedge",
        "distractor_2": "inclined plane",
        "distractor_3": "pulley"
      },
      {
        "id": "2966",
        "question": "What is the ability to move a large resistance with a small effort?",
        "answer": "mechanical advantage",
        "distractor_1": "work",
        "distractor_2": "transportation",
        "distractor_3": "energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "2967",
        "question": "What term best describes an energy source that replaces itself?",
        "answer": "renewable",
        "distractor_1": "recyclable",
        "distractor_2": "parasitical",
        "distractor_3": "extinguishable"
      },
      {
        "id": "2969",
        "question": "Fusion occurs when what two parts of an atom are combined and energy is emitted?",
        "answer": "nuclei",
        "distractor_1": "neutrons",
        "distractor_2": "electrons",
        "distractor_3": "protons"
      },
      {
        "id": "2971",
        "question": "What is the study of pressure on liquids?",
        "answer": "hydraulics",
        "distractor_1": "pressurization",
        "distractor_2": "pneumatics",
        "distractor_3": "physics"
      },
      {
        "id": "2973",
        "question": "What term describes the development, production, and use of machines or mechanical structures?",
        "answer": "mechanics",
        "distractor_1": "hydraulics",
        "distractor_2": "pneumatics",
        "distractor_3": "aesthetics"
      },
      {
        "id": "2975",
        "question": "Several geometric shapes can focus light to certain points to concentrate the energy for cooking, such as is done with the solar hot dog cooker. Which three geometric figures have a point of focus?",
        "answer": "parabola, ellipse, hyperbola",
        "distractor_1": "ellipse, parabola, triangle",
        "distractor_2": "parabola, hyperbola, angle",
        "distractor_3": "triangle, acute angle, obtuse angle"
      },
      {
        "id": "2977",
        "question": "What energy source do photovoltaic cells use to produce electricity?",
        "answer": "solar",
        "distractor_1": "wind",
        "distractor_2": "geothermal",
        "distractor_3": "nuclear"
      },
      {
        "id": "2979",
        "question": "What is the name of the wheels used to change the direction or speed of a machine?",
        "answer": "gears",
        "distractor_1": "collectors",
        "distractor_2": "dynamos",
        "distractor_3": "turbines"
      },
      {
        "id": "2980",
        "question": "A lever is an example of what type of machine?",
        "answer": "simple machine",
        "distractor_1": "complex machine",
        "distractor_2": "static machine",
        "distractor_3": "perpetual motion machine"
      },
      {
        "id": "2981",
        "question": "What occurs when the nuclei of two atoms are combined and energy is given off?",
        "answer": "fusion",
        "distractor_1": "hydraulic",
        "distractor_2": "fission",
        "distractor_3": "hydroelectric"
      },
      {
        "id": "2982",
        "question": "What is the source of geothermal energy?",
        "answer": "Earth",
        "distractor_1": "Sun",
        "distractor_2": "wind",
        "distractor_3": "ocean"
      },
      {
        "id": "2983",
        "question": "Which of the following instruments is used to focus solar energy?",
        "answer": "parabolic dish",
        "distractor_1": "spectrometer",
        "distractor_2": "nanometer",
        "distractor_3": "hyperbolic dish"
      },
      {
        "id": "6329",
        "question": "What is a form of chemical energy that comes from the breakdown of plant and animal matter?",
        "answer": "Biomass energy",
        "distractor_1": "Nuclear energy",
        "distractor_2": "Geothermal energy",
        "distractor_3": "Wind energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "6330",
        "question": "What is a push or pull of one mass on another?",
        "answer": "Force",
        "distractor_1": "Velocity",
        "distractor_2": "Weight ",
        "distractor_3": "Mass"
      },
      {
        "id": "6331",
        "question": "What is an electricity produced using the force of gravity on moving water?",
        "answer": "Hydroelectricity",
        "distractor_1": "Nuclear energy",
        "distractor_2": "Tidal energy",
        "distractor_3": "Wind energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "6332",
        "question": "What is an energy that is created through fission (splitting atoms) or fusion (joining atoms)?",
        "answer": "Nuclear energy",
        "distractor_1": "Tidal energy",
        "distractor_2": "Wind energy ",
        "distractor_3": "Hydroelectricity"
      },
      {
        "id": "6333",
        "question": "What is a study of pressure on air or a system in which compressed air is used to provide force?",
        "answer": "Pneumatics",
        "distractor_1": "Nuclear energy",
        "distractor_2": "Biomass energy",
        "distractor_3": "Geology"
      },
      {
        "id": "6334",
        "question": "What is an energy produced by the rise and fall of tides in the oceans?",
        "answer": "Tidal energy",
        "distractor_1": "Hydroelectricity",
        "distractor_2": "Geothermal electricity",
        "distractor_3": "Biomass energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "6335",
        "question": "What is a form of solar energy harnessed with devices that capture wind and use it for power to do work?",
        "answer": "Wind energy",
        "distractor_1": "Tidal energy",
        "distractor_2": "Biomass energy",
        "distractor_3": "Geothermal energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "6336",
        "question": "What is a measurement of energy used to accomplish a task?",
        "answer": "Work",
        "distractor_1": "Force",
        "distractor_2": "Velocity",
        "distractor_3": "Mass"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "207",
    "name": "Engineering Towers",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2662",
        "question": "A truss is a framework made up of what type of geometric shape?",
        "answer": "triangular",
        "distractor_1": "circular",
        "distractor_2": "oval",
        "distractor_3": "elliptical"
      },
      {
        "id": "2663",
        "question": "Tension is a type of stress that occurs when members are what?",
        "answer": "pulled apart",
        "distractor_1": "twisted",
        "distractor_2": "fused together",
        "distractor_3": "sheared off"
      },
      {
        "id": "2664",
        "question": "What term refers to a structure made up of one or more triangular units made from straight members of wood or metal?",
        "answer": "truss",
        "distractor_1": "arch",
        "distractor_2": "girder",
        "distractor_3": "beam"
      },
      {
        "id": "2665",
        "question": "What type of stress occurs when members are pulled apart?",
        "answer": "tensile",
        "distractor_1": "compression",
        "distractor_2": "vertical",
        "distractor_3": "horizontal"
      },
      {
        "id": "2669",
        "question": "What is one important job that all structures have in common?",
        "answer": "to support a load",
        "distractor_1": "to withstand heat",
        "distractor_2": "to house people",
        "distractor_3": "to resist weather"
      },
      {
        "id": "2671",
        "question": "To support a load is what?",
        "answer": "a function that all structures have in common",
        "distractor_1": "the most important function of a house",
        "distractor_2": "a definition of functional stress",
        "distractor_3": "a definition of tension"
      },
      {
        "id": "2672",
        "question": "A rigid member in tension is called a tie. What is a rigid member in compression called?",
        "answer": "strut",
        "distractor_1": "diagonal",
        "distractor_2": "brace",
        "distractor_3": "pier"
      },
      {
        "id": "2673",
        "question": "What kind of brace can be added to a square or rectangle to give it strength?",
        "answer": "diagonal",
        "distractor_1": "side",
        "distractor_2": "vertical",
        "distractor_3": "horizontal"
      },
      {
        "id": "6905",
        "question": "A rigid member in tension is called a tie. A strut is a rigid member in what?",
        "answer": "compression",
        "distractor_1": "torsion",
        "distractor_2": "pier",
        "distractor_3": "tension"
      },
      {
        "id": "6906",
        "question": "What term is defined as the distance between supports?",
        "answer": "span",
        "distractor_1": "height",
        "distractor_2": "run",
        "distractor_3": "rise"
      },
      {
        "id": "2674",
        "question": "The legs of your tower will be subjected to compression, which is what kind of force?",
        "answer": "squeezing",
        "distractor_1": "twisting",
        "distractor_2": "pulling",
        "distractor_3": "dynamic"
      },
      {
        "id": "2675",
        "question": "What is another word for a load that is always moving?",
        "answer": "dynamic",
        "distractor_1": "loco",
        "distractor_2": "static",
        "distractor_3": "stationary"
      },
      {
        "id": "2676",
        "question": "For engineering purposes, the triangle is the best choice of all the geometric shapes for providing which element?",
        "answer": "strength",
        "distractor_1": "design",
        "distractor_2": "look",
        "distractor_3": "balance"
      },
      {
        "id": "2680",
        "question": "The legs of your tower will be subjected to a squeezing force that is called what?",
        "answer": "compression",
        "distractor_1": "tension",
        "distractor_2": "stress",
        "distractor_3": "dynamic"
      },
      {
        "id": "2681",
        "question": "There are two kinds of loads. A static load will be placed on your tower when you test it. Which of the following best describes a dynamic load?",
        "answer": "It is always moving.",
        "distractor_1": "It is heavy.",
        "distractor_2": "It is always pushing down.",
        "distractor_3": "It is always stationary."
      },
      {
        "id": "2682",
        "question": "What are the two most common forces that will be acting on each piece of wood in your tower?",
        "answer": "compression and tension",
        "distractor_1": "up and down",
        "distractor_2": "weight and static",
        "distractor_3": "static and dynamic"
      },
      {
        "id": "2683",
        "question": "What is another word for a force placed on a structure?",
        "answer": "load",
        "distractor_1": "covering",
        "distractor_2": "beam",
        "distractor_3": "stage"
      },
      {
        "id": "2689",
        "question": "Which geometric shape is the strongest?",
        "answer": "triangle",
        "distractor_1": "square",
        "distractor_2": "rectangle",
        "distractor_3": "circle"
      },
      {
        "id": "6343",
        "question": "What is a foundation that supports the end of a bridge?",
        "answer": "Abutment",
        "distractor_1": "Arch",
        "distractor_2": "Truss",
        "distractor_3": "Substructure"
      },
      {
        "id": "6344",
        "question": "What is a support structure that is curved?",
        "answer": "Arch",
        "distractor_1": "Truss",
        "distractor_2": "Keystone",
        "distractor_3": "Span"
      },
      {
        "id": "6345",
        "question": "What is a person who develops plans for municipal systems such as roads and bridges?",
        "answer": "Civil engineer",
        "distractor_1": "Rural engineer",
        "distractor_2": "Bridge specialist",
        "distractor_3": "Suspension structure specialist"
      },
      {
        "id": "6346",
        "question": "What is a central wedge-shaped stone of an arch that locks the other stones together?",
        "answer": "Keystone",
        "distractor_1": "Span",
        "distractor_2": "Arch",
        "distractor_3": "Truss"
      },
      {
        "id": "6347",
        "question": "What is a portion of a structure that is below ground and usually not visible?",
        "answer": "Substructure",
        "distractor_1": "Superstructure",
        "distractor_2": "Suspension structure",
        "distractor_3": "Truss"
      },
      {
        "id": "6348",
        "question": "What is a portion of a structure that is above ground and usually visible?",
        "answer": "Superstructure",
        "distractor_1": "Substructure",
        "distractor_2": "Suspension structure",
        "distractor_3": "Truss"
      },
      {
        "id": "6349",
        "question": "What is a structure held by cables anchored at the ends and supported by towers?",
        "answer": "Suspension structure",
        "distractor_1": "Superstructure",
        "distractor_2": "Substructure",
        "distractor_3": "Truss"
      },
      {
        "id": "6350",
        "question": "What is a force that tries to pull a material apart?",
        "answer": "Tension",
        "distractor_1": "Truss",
        "distractor_2": "Compression",
        "distractor_3": "Span"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "208",
    "name": "Engineering Bridges",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2478",
        "question": "What term is defined as a structural element made up of a series of triangles?",
        "answer": "truss",
        "distractor_1": "wedge",
        "distractor_2": "flying buttress",
        "distractor_3": "post and lintel"
      },
      {
        "id": "2480",
        "question": "What term is defined as the type of brace that makes squares and rectangles stronger?",
        "answer": "diagonal",
        "distractor_1": "horizontal",
        "distractor_2": "vertical",
        "distractor_3": "insider"
      },
      {
        "id": "2483",
        "question": "Which of the listed functions is common to all structures?",
        "answer": "to support a load",
        "distractor_1": "to withstand heat",
        "distractor_2": "to house people",
        "distractor_3": "to resist weather"
      },
      {
        "id": "2484",
        "question": "Which of the braces listed should be added in order to strengthen a square or rectangle?",
        "answer": "diagonal",
        "distractor_1": "side",
        "distractor_2": "top",
        "distractor_3": "bottom"
      },
      {
        "id": "2485",
        "question": "What measurement is figured when the weight required to break your bridge is divided by the weight of your bridge?",
        "answer": "efficiency",
        "distractor_1": "span",
        "distractor_2": "load",
        "distractor_3": "stress"
      },
      {
        "id": "2488",
        "question": "Which geometric shape provides the best strength and stability?",
        "answer": "triangle",
        "distractor_1": "square",
        "distractor_2": "parallelogram",
        "distractor_3": "rectangle"
      },
      {
        "id": "2489",
        "question": "Which structural element is made up of a series of triangles?",
        "answer": "truss",
        "distractor_1": "post and lintel",
        "distractor_2": "wedge",
        "distractor_3": "flying buttress"
      },
      {
        "id": "2490",
        "question": "What force is described as a sliding and separating force that causes material to break?",
        "answer": "shear",
        "distractor_1": "tension",
        "distractor_2": "compression",
        "distractor_3": "torsion"
      },
      {
        "id": "2491",
        "question": "Each piece of wood in your bridge (structure) will have one of two forces on it when a load is applied. What are the two possible forces?",
        "answer": "compression, tension",
        "distractor_1": "up, down",
        "distractor_2": "static, dynamic",
        "distractor_3": "weight, static"
      },
      {
        "id": "2492",
        "question": "A rigid member in tension is called a tie. What is a rigid member in compression called?",
        "answer": "strut",
        "distractor_1": "diagonal",
        "distractor_2": "brace",
        "distractor_3": "pier"
      },
      {
        "id": "2493",
        "question": "For engineering purposes, the triangle is the best choice of all the geometric shapes for providing which element?",
        "answer": "strength",
        "distractor_1": "design",
        "distractor_2": "look",
        "distractor_3": "balance"
      },
      {
        "id": "2494",
        "question": "Which of the listed items is an example of a dynamic load?",
        "answer": "a heavy truck crossing a bridge",
        "distractor_1": "the force that a magnet creates",
        "distractor_2": "a heavy truck parked on a bridge",
        "distractor_3": "a side force"
      },
      {
        "id": "2495",
        "question": "In engineering, what does the word 'span' describe?",
        "answer": "the length of a bridge",
        "distractor_1": "the weight of a bridge",
        "distractor_2": "the height of a bridge",
        "distractor_3": "how high the roadway of a bridge is above water"
      },
      {
        "id": "2496",
        "question": "To calculate the efficiency of your bridge, the weight required to break your bridge should be _______ the weight of your bridge.",
        "answer": "divided by",
        "distractor_1": "subtracted from",
        "distractor_2": "added to",
        "distractor_3": "multiplied by"
      },
      {
        "id": "2497",
        "question": "Who is cited as the first American to have used mathematical calculations when he designed the X truss in 1830?",
        "answer": "Stephen H. Long",
        "distractor_1": "Theodore Burr",
        "distractor_2": "Robert W. Smith",
        "distractor_3": "Reuben L. Partridge"
      },
      {
        "id": "2498",
        "question": "All structures must be able to support a load without collapsing. What are the two types of load?",
        "answer": "dead, live",
        "distractor_1": "impact, span length",
        "distractor_2": "weight, static",
        "distractor_3": "up, down"
      },
      {
        "id": "2500",
        "question": "A heavy truck crossing a bridge is an example of what type of load?",
        "answer": "dynamic",
        "distractor_1": "static",
        "distractor_2": "vertical",
        "distractor_3": "horizontal"
      },
      {
        "id": "2501",
        "question": "What are the two most common forces that will be acting on each piece of wood in your bridge?",
        "answer": "compression, tension",
        "distractor_1": "up, down",
        "distractor_2": "weight, static",
        "distractor_3": "static, dynamic"
      },
      {
        "id": "2502",
        "question": "A rigid member in compression is called a strut. What is a rigid member in tension called?",
        "answer": "tie",
        "distractor_1": "diagonal",
        "distractor_2": "pier",
        "distractor_3": "brace"
      },
      {
        "id": "2503",
        "question": "What is the term for the portion of the bridge that rests on the piers and abutments?",
        "answer": "superstructure",
        "distractor_1": "truss",
        "distractor_2": "substructure",
        "distractor_3": "span"
      },
      {
        "id": "2504",
        "question": "What term is defined as the distance covered by a bridge?",
        "answer": "span",
        "distractor_1": "racking",
        "distractor_2": "substructure",
        "distractor_3": "superstructure"
      },
      {
        "id": "6337",
        "question": "What is a  foundation that supports the end of a bridge?",
        "answer": "Abutment",
        "distractor_1": "Arch",
        "distractor_2": "Substructure",
        "distractor_3": "Suspension structure"
      },
      {
        "id": "6338",
        "question": "What is a curved support structure?",
        "answer": "Arch",
        "distractor_1": "Abutment",
        "distractor_2": "Truss",
        "distractor_3": "Suspension structure"
      },
      {
        "id": "6339",
        "question": "What is a person who develops plans for municipal systems, such as roads and bridges?",
        "answer": "Civil engineer",
        "distractor_1": "Rural engineer",
        "distractor_2": "Bridge engineer",
        "distractor_3": "Suspension structure specialist"
      },
      {
        "id": "6340",
        "question": "What is a central wedge-shaped stone of an arch that locks the other stones together?",
        "answer": "Keystone",
        "distractor_1": "Substructure",
        "distractor_2": "Arch",
        "distractor_3": "Truss"
      },
      {
        "id": "6341",
        "question": "What is a portion of a structure that is below ground and usually not visible?",
        "answer": "Substructure",
        "distractor_1": "Superstructure",
        "distractor_2": "Suspension structure",
        "distractor_3": "Tension"
      },
      {
        "id": "6342",
        "question": "What is a structure held by cables anchored at the ends and supported by towers?",
        "answer": "Suspension structure",
        "distractor_1": "Superstructure",
        "distractor_2": "Substructure",
        "distractor_3": "Abutment"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "209",
    "name": "Personal Finance",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "3171",
        "question": "Which of the following items should be done when writing a check?",
        "answer": "use the current date",
        "distractor_1": "write in cursive",
        "distractor_2": "abbreviate the date",
        "distractor_3": "write your initials"
      },
      {
        "id": "3172",
        "question": "You have an outstanding check. What happened to the check?",
        "answer": "not received by the bank",
        "distractor_1": "not balanced in the checkbook",
        "distractor_2": "not earned compounded interest",
        "distractor_3": "not been budgeted"
      },
      {
        "id": "3174",
        "question": "Identify the term for balancing an account.",
        "answer": "reconciling",
        "distractor_1": "endorsing",
        "distractor_2": "registering",
        "distractor_3": "certifying"
      },
      {
        "id": "3175",
        "question": "What should you fill out to place money in your checking account?",
        "answer": "deposit slip",
        "distractor_1": "check register",
        "distractor_2": "balance sheet",
        "distractor_3": "bank draft"
      },
      {
        "id": "3176",
        "question": "Identify what a check register is used to record.",
        "answer": "checks written",
        "distractor_1": "interest paid",
        "distractor_2": "cashier's checks",
        "distractor_3": "finance charges on credit cards"
      },
      {
        "id": "3177",
        "question": "Interest is earned on a savings account. What part of the account will grow as interest is compounded?",
        "answer": "principal",
        "distractor_1": "collateral",
        "distractor_2": "finance charges",
        "distractor_3": "budget"
      },
      {
        "id": "3178",
        "question": "A budget is used by wise people. What do they budget?",
        "answer": "wants and needs",
        "distractor_1": "collateral",
        "distractor_2": "only finance charges",
        "distractor_3": "credit limits"
      },
      {
        "id": "3179",
        "question": "What is the term for parts of a company that may be purchased by the public?",
        "answer": "stocks",
        "distractor_1": "certificates of deposit",
        "distractor_2": "mutual funds",
        "distractor_3": "bonds"
      },
      {
        "id": "3180",
        "question": "When you write a check, where should you keep a record of it?",
        "answer": "check register",
        "distractor_1": "debit sheet",
        "distractor_2": "profit and loss statement",
        "distractor_3": "financial statement"
      },
      {
        "id": "3181",
        "question": "Savings accounts earn interest. Identify the word used to describe the effect of interest added to the total principal before new interest earnings are computed.",
        "answer": "compounding",
        "distractor_1": "endorsing",
        "distractor_2": "budgeting",
        "distractor_3": "balancing"
      },
      {
        "id": "3182",
        "question": "A person has a history of paying bills on time. What is that person said to have?",
        "answer": "good credit",
        "distractor_1": "high collateral",
        "distractor_2": "bad budgeting habits",
        "distractor_3": "low interest"
      },
      {
        "id": "3183",
        "question": "The product that banks sell or loan is money. To earn a profit on their product, they charge their customers interest. What are the interest and fees on a loan called?",
        "answer": "finance charges",
        "distractor_1": "principal",
        "distractor_2": "credit charges",
        "distractor_3": "loan fees"
      },
      {
        "id": "3184",
        "question": "What term describes checks that you have written, but the bank has not yet received?",
        "answer": "outstanding",
        "distractor_1": "overdraft",
        "distractor_2": "canceled",
        "distractor_3": "cashier's"
      },
      {
        "id": "3185",
        "question": "You must first endorse a check in order to do what?",
        "answer": "cash a check",
        "distractor_1": "add it to the register",
        "distractor_2": "reconcile your account",
        "distractor_3": "balance your checking account"
      },
      {
        "id": "3186",
        "question": "Identify the term that means to reconcile your checking account each time you receive a bank statement.",
        "answer": "to balance",
        "distractor_1": "to endorse",
        "distractor_2": "to budget",
        "distractor_3": "to overdraft"
      },
      {
        "id": "3187",
        "question": "Banks earn a profit on their product by selling or loaning money. What do they charge to earn money on a loan?",
        "answer": "interest and fees",
        "distractor_1": "an overdraft",
        "distractor_2": "collateral",
        "distractor_3": "principal"
      },
      {
        "id": "3188",
        "question": "Identify the term for money used to produce more money.",
        "answer": "an investment",
        "distractor_1": "equity",
        "distractor_2": "collateral",
        "distractor_3": "an annuity"
      },
      {
        "id": "3189",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a type of checking account?",
        "answer": "mutual fund",
        "distractor_1": "regular (budget)",
        "distractor_2": "minimum balance",
        "distractor_3": "interest-bearing"
      },
      {
        "id": "3192",
        "question": "Identify what happens to the stock market during a bull market.",
        "answer": "does well and prices are up",
        "distractor_1": "does well and prices are low",
        "distractor_2": "does poorly and prices go down",
        "distractor_3": "does poorly and prices go up"
      },
      {
        "id": "3193",
        "question": "What must you have a history of doing in order to earn good credit?",
        "answer": "paying bills on time",
        "distractor_1": "overdrawing accounts",
        "distractor_2": "reconciling credit card bills",
        "distractor_3": "budgeting income"
      },
      {
        "id": "3194",
        "question": "Where is money put when a deposit slip is used?",
        "answer": "checking account",
        "distractor_1": "balance sheet",
        "distractor_2": "financial statement",
        "distractor_3": "budget"
      },
      {
        "id": "3196",
        "question": "What must you do before you can cash a check?",
        "answer": "endorse it",
        "distractor_1": "clear it",
        "distractor_2": "register it",
        "distractor_3": "balance it"
      },
      {
        "id": "3197",
        "question": "What should be done when writing checks?",
        "answer": "use ink",
        "distractor_1": "use tomorrow's date",
        "distractor_2": "abbreviate the date",
        "distractor_3": "write in cursive"
      },
      {
        "id": "3198",
        "question": "A wise spender understands the difference between wants and needs. What tool is used to help manage spending?",
        "answer": "budget",
        "distractor_1": "expense account",
        "distractor_2": "audit",
        "distractor_3": "expense estimate"
      },
      {
        "id": "6572",
        "question": "What is the term for amount of money in a bank account at any given time?",
        "answer": "account balance",
        "distractor_1": "bank statement",
        "distractor_2": "budget",
        "distractor_3": "balanced budget"
      },
      {
        "id": "6577",
        "question": "What type of  budget has money going out that is equal to or less than the money taken in?",
        "answer": "balanced budget",
        "distractor_1": "reconcile",
        "distractor_2": "account balance",
        "distractor_3": "expenses budget"
      },
      {
        "id": "6580",
        "question": "What institution holds money for withdrawal or loans to people and businesses?",
        "answer": "bank",
        "distractor_1": "checking account",
        "distractor_2": "savings account",
        "distractor_3": "market"
      },
      {
        "id": "6583",
        "question": "What is a monthly summary of a customer's bank transactions?",
        "answer": "bank statement",
        "distractor_1": "bank reconcile",
        "distractor_2": "account balance",
        "distractor_3": "balanced budget"
      },
      {
        "id": "6586",
        "question": "In which period does the stock market do poorly and prices go down?",
        "answer": "bear market",
        "distractor_1": "bull market",
        "distractor_2": "depression",
        "distractor_3": "recession"
      },
      {
        "id": "6589",
        "question": "In which period does the stock market do well and prices are up?",
        "answer": "bull market",
        "distractor_1": "bear market",
        "distractor_2": "raised market",
        "distractor_3": "inflation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6590",
        "question": "What is something owed to someone?",
        "answer": "debt",
        "distractor_1": "loan",
        "distractor_2": "expenses",
        "distractor_3": "finance charge"
      },
      {
        "id": "6591",
        "question": "What is it called when money is put into a bank account?",
        "answer": "deposit",
        "distractor_1": "savings",
        "distractor_2": "account balance",
        "distractor_3": "currency"
      },
      {
        "id": "6592",
        "question": "What are fixed, flexible, or occasional amounts of money that are due each month?",
        "answer": "expenses",
        "distractor_1": "debt",
        "distractor_2": "finance charge",
        "distractor_3": "loans"
      },
      {
        "id": "6593",
        "question": "What is the term for money borrowed from a lending institution that must be paid back?",
        "answer": "loan",
        "distractor_1": "debt",
        "distractor_2": "finance charge",
        "distractor_3": "bank balance"
      },
      {
        "id": "6594",
        "question": "What is an agreement between you and a bank in which the bank keeps your money and pays you interest on it?",
        "answer": "savings account",
        "distractor_1": "checking account",
        "distractor_2": "stocks",
        "distractor_3": "investment account"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "210",
    "name": "Research & Design",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1682",
        "question": "What does friction cause moving objects to do?",
        "answer": "slow down",
        "distractor_1": "accelerate",
        "distractor_2": "turn right",
        "distractor_3": "turn left"
      },
      {
        "id": "1683",
        "question": "To complete a smooth paint job, what should be applied to the bare wood on your CO2 car?",
        "answer": "primer",
        "distractor_1": "gloss enamel",
        "distractor_2": "varnish",
        "distractor_3": "latex paint"
      },
      {
        "id": "1684",
        "question": "What force propels your car?",
        "answer": "thrust",
        "distractor_1": "horsepower",
        "distractor_2": "push",
        "distractor_3": "lift"
      },
      {
        "id": "1685",
        "question": "Which scientific study deals with the motion and forces associated with air and other gases, especially as they interact with solid objects?",
        "answer": "aerodynamics",
        "distractor_1": "physics",
        "distractor_2": "air speed",
        "distractor_3": "air waves"
      },
      {
        "id": "1686",
        "question": "When you paint your CO2 car, you will be changing the surface by placing a coating on it. What is this process called?",
        "answer": "finishing",
        "distractor_1": "processing",
        "distractor_2": "coloring",
        "distractor_3": "conditioning"
      },
      {
        "id": "1687",
        "question": "Which field of technology deals with ergonomics?",
        "answer": "physical needs of human beings",
        "distractor_1": "civil engineering",
        "distractor_2": "aerodynamics",
        "distractor_3": "aesthetics or styling"
      },
      {
        "id": "1688",
        "question": "What is the first model, or working version, of a design called?",
        "answer": "prototype",
        "distractor_1": "thumbnail",
        "distractor_2": "production model",
        "distractor_3": "target vehicle"
      },
      {
        "id": "1691",
        "question": "What term describes the test model of a product built before production?",
        "answer": "prototype",
        "distractor_1": "template",
        "distractor_2": "first run",
        "distractor_3": "example"
      },
      {
        "id": "1692",
        "question": "What term is defined as making large quantities of a product?",
        "answer": "mass production",
        "distractor_1": "design",
        "distractor_2": "prototype",
        "distractor_3": "scale model"
      },
      {
        "id": "1693",
        "question": "At what point during the production process does the prototype, or working model, of a product get built?",
        "answer": "before",
        "distractor_1": "during",
        "distractor_2": "after",
        "distractor_3": "instead of"
      },
      {
        "id": "1694",
        "question": "According to Newton's second law of motion, which of the following is the formula for the acceleration of a dragster?",
        "answer": "acceleration = force ÷ mass",
        "distractor_1": "acceleration = mass x force",
        "distractor_2": "acceleration = mass ÷ force",
        "distractor_3": "acceleration = force x mass"
      },
      {
        "id": "1695",
        "question": "Appearance will have no effect on what factor of your CO2 car?",
        "answer": "speed",
        "distractor_1": "weight",
        "distractor_2": "friction",
        "distractor_3": "mass"
      },
      {
        "id": "1696",
        "question": "What is made during mass production?",
        "answer": "large quantities of a product",
        "distractor_1": "small quantities of a product",
        "distractor_2": "massive products",
        "distractor_3": "products for the masses"
      },
      {
        "id": "1697",
        "question": "Two screw eyes are placed on your dragster as part of the guidance system. They should be equal distance from the ends of the dragster. If your dragster is 12' long and the screw eyes are 4' apart, how far from the end should each screw eye be placed?",
        "answer": "4 inches",
        "distractor_1": "2 inches",
        "distractor_2": "3 inches",
        "distractor_3": "5 inches"
      },
      {
        "id": "1698",
        "question": "Cars today are made in factories where the cars are brought to the worker on an assembly line, and he or she does the same job on each car. What is this manufacturing method?",
        "answer": "mass production",
        "distractor_1": "job shop",
        "distractor_2": "just in time",
        "distractor_3": "model shop"
      },
      {
        "id": "1700",
        "question": "What force acts like a brake on moving objects?",
        "answer": "friction",
        "distractor_1": "lift",
        "distractor_2": "thrust",
        "distractor_3": "load"
      },
      {
        "id": "1701",
        "question": "What is the name of the shaft that supports the weight of your car?",
        "answer": "axle",
        "distractor_1": "engine",
        "distractor_2": "cartridge",
        "distractor_3": "canister"
      },
      {
        "id": "1702",
        "question": "A CO2 cartridge produces a force much like the air shooting from a balloon. What is this force?",
        "answer": "thrust",
        "distractor_1": "push",
        "distractor_2": "horsepower",
        "distractor_3": "lift"
      },
      {
        "id": "1703",
        "question": "What occurs during the final stage of your CO2 car production?",
        "answer": "You are changing the painting surface.",
        "distractor_1": "You are finished.",
        "distractor_2": "You are declared the race winner.",
        "distractor_3": "You are sanding."
      },
      {
        "id": "1704",
        "question": "What term is defined as the shaft that supports the weight of your car?",
        "answer": "axle",
        "distractor_1": "wheel shaft",
        "distractor_2": "carrier shaft",
        "distractor_3": "drive shaft"
      },
      {
        "id": "1705",
        "question": "Auto seats are designed to provide a good driving position. What field of technology deals with the physical needs of human beings?",
        "answer": "ergonomics",
        "distractor_1": "applied physics",
        "distractor_2": "innovation",
        "distractor_3": "human engineering"
      },
      {
        "id": "1706",
        "question": "According to Newton's second law of motion, which of the following is the formula for the acceleration of a dragster?",
        "answer": "acceleration = force ÷ mass",
        "distractor_1": "acceleration = force x mass ",
        "distractor_2": "acceleration = mass x force",
        "distractor_3": "acceleration = mass ÷ force"
      },
      {
        "id": "1707",
        "question": "Which of the following is not an important factor in the speed of your CO2 car?",
        "answer": "appearance",
        "distractor_1": "weight",
        "distractor_2": "friction",
        "distractor_3": "aerodynamics"
      },
      {
        "id": "1708",
        "question": "Auto seats are designed to provide a good driving position. What field of technology deals with the physical needs of human beings?",
        "answer": "ergonomics",
        "distractor_1": "applied physics",
        "distractor_2": "innovation",
        "distractor_3": "biotech engineering"
      },
      {
        "id": "1709",
        "question": "To complete a smooth paint job, you should first apply what to the bare wood?",
        "answer": "primer",
        "distractor_1": "latex paint",
        "distractor_2": "varnish",
        "distractor_3": "gloss enamel"
      },
      {
        "id": "5466",
        "question": "Which of the following symbols represents carbon dioxide; a colorless, odorless gas that will not burn and is composed of carbon and oxygen?",
        "answer": "CO2",
        "distractor_1": "O2",
        "distractor_2": "C2",
        "distractor_3": "O2C"
      },
      {
        "id": "5467",
        "question": "Which of the following is described as the force in which air resists the forward motion of an object?",
        "answer": "drag",
        "distractor_1": "resistance",
        "distractor_2": "gravity",
        "distractor_3": "lift"
      },
      {
        "id": "5468",
        "question": "What is a repeated design, or a model for an object?",
        "answer": "pattern",
        "distractor_1": "sketch",
        "distractor_2": "prototype",
        "distractor_3": "replica"
      },
      {
        "id": "5469",
        "question": "Which of the following is a basic drawing of an object that shows little detail?",
        "answer": "sketch",
        "distractor_1": "pattern",
        "distractor_2": "doodle",
        "distractor_3": "thumbnail"
      },
      {
        "id": "5470",
        "question": "Which of the following means to design an object so that it has the least amount of air resistance?",
        "answer": "streamline",
        "distractor_1": "aerodynamic",
        "distractor_2": "finish",
        "distractor_3": "sleek"
      },
      {
        "id": "5471",
        "question": "Which of the following is described as a miniature version of an image; a kind of preview?",
        "answer": "thumbnail",
        "distractor_1": "model ",
        "distractor_2": "sketch",
        "distractor_3": "prototype"
      },
      {
        "id": "5472",
        "question": "Which term is defined as the amount by which a dimension, or value, may vary?",
        "answer": "tolerance",
        "distractor_1": "difference",
        "distractor_2": "variance",
        "distractor_3": "variant"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "211",
    "name": "Robots",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2423",
        "question": "Which term is best described as a computer-controlled machine that can be programmed to do different kinds of work?",
        "answer": "robot",
        "distractor_1": "mechanically inclined",
        "distractor_2": "remote antenna",
        "distractor_3": "automatic"
      },
      {
        "id": "2424",
        "question": "What type of sensor emits a sound and then times how long it takes for an echo to return?",
        "answer": "ultrasonic sensor",
        "distractor_1": "sound sensor",
        "distractor_2": "touch sensor",
        "distractor_3": "infrared sensor"
      },
      {
        "id": "2426",
        "question": "A robot can be programmed by simply guiding it through movements. What is this type of programming, or teaching, called?",
        "answer": "direct teaching or pendant teaching",
        "distractor_1": "indirect teaching or copy teaching",
        "distractor_2": "follow the leader",
        "distractor_3": "monkey see, monkey do"
      },
      {
        "id": "2430",
        "question": "Which action occurs when the ''if''statement in a Boolean logic if-then-else statement is determined to be false?",
        "answer": "The robot performs the ''else'' action.",
        "distractor_1": "The robot performs the ''then'' action.",
        "distractor_2": "The robot performs an emergency shutdown.",
        "distractor_3": "The robot performs a restart action."
      },
      {
        "id": "2431",
        "question": "What is a sensor?",
        "answer": "input device used to measure or detect something",
        "distractor_1": "hand of a robot",
        "distractor_2": "computer program",
        "distractor_3": "remote antenna"
      },
      {
        "id": "2432",
        "question": "Which of the following sensors measures the strength of vibrations?",
        "answer": "sound sensor",
        "distractor_1": "touch sensor",
        "distractor_2": "ultrasonic sensor",
        "distractor_3": "infrared sensor"
      },
      {
        "id": "2433",
        "question": "What term is often used to identify an industrial robot arm?",
        "answer": "manipulator",
        "distractor_1": "gripper",
        "distractor_2": "forearm",
        "distractor_3": "terminator"
      },
      {
        "id": "2435",
        "question": "Which of the following tasks can robots relieve humans from doing?",
        "answer": "completing hazardous jobs",
        "distractor_1": "thinking",
        "distractor_2": "working with other humans",
        "distractor_3": "working with high-tech computers"
      },
      {
        "id": "2436",
        "question": "Which of the listed items is an input device used to detect or measure something?",
        "answer": "sensor",
        "distractor_1": "receiver",
        "distractor_2": "emitter",
        "distractor_3": "artificial intelligence"
      },
      {
        "id": "2439",
        "question": "What is the function of a robot gripper?",
        "answer": "It grabs and holds objects.",
        "distractor_1": "A person uses it to control the robot's movements.",
        "distractor_2": "It rotates right and left.",
        "distractor_3": "It keeps the robot from slipping."
      },
      {
        "id": "2443",
        "question": "Which action occurs when the ''if'' statement in a Boolean logic if-then-else statement is determind to be true?",
        "answer": "The robot performs the ''then'' action.",
        "distractor_1": "The robot performs the ''else'' action.",
        "distractor_2": "The robot performs an emergency shutdown.",
        "distractor_3": "The robot performs a restart action."
      },
      {
        "id": "2445",
        "question": "What does the word 'robot' mean?",
        "answer": "labor or slave",
        "distractor_1": "machine",
        "distractor_2": "mechanical man",
        "distractor_3": "automatic"
      },
      {
        "id": "2449",
        "question": "What is the part of the robot's hand that touches and holds objects called?",
        "answer": "gripper",
        "distractor_1": "wrist",
        "distractor_2": "clamper",
        "distractor_3": "finger"
      },
      {
        "id": "7806",
        "question": "What type of sensor detects physical pressure?",
        "answer": "touch sensor",
        "distractor_1": "sound sensor",
        "distractor_2": "ultrasonic sensor",
        "distractor_3": "infrared sensor"
      },
      {
        "id": "6693",
        "question": "What is using computers and robots to do tasks?",
        "answer": "automation",
        "distractor_1": "programming",
        "distractor_2": "repetitive",
        "distractor_3": "teach pendant"
      },
      {
        "id": "6694",
        "question": "What is the line around which an object or figure rotates?",
        "answer": "axis",
        "distractor_1": "boundary",
        "distractor_2": "rotation",
        "distractor_3": "repetitive"
      },
      {
        "id": "6695",
        "question": "What is a system for locating any point using three perpendicular planes: x, y, and z?",
        "answer": "Cartesian coordinate system",
        "distractor_1": "Cartesian map system",
        "distractor_2": "axis ",
        "distractor_3": "automation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6696",
        "question": "What is the part of a robot that touches or secures things; for example, a gripper?",
        "answer": "end effector",
        "distractor_1": "end affector",
        "distractor_2": "teach pendant",
        "distractor_3": "extension"
      },
      {
        "id": "6697",
        "question": "What is entering a sequence of instructions into a computer so it can control a robot's movements?",
        "answer": "programming (robots)",
        "distractor_1": "programming (AI)",
        "distractor_2": "repetitive",
        "distractor_3": "teach pendant"
      },
      {
        "id": "6698",
        "question": "What is an external, often wireless, device (transmitter) used to control the actions of another device (a robot)?",
        "answer": "remote control",
        "distractor_1": "teach pendant",
        "distractor_2": "intercom",
        "distractor_3": "end effector"
      },
      {
        "id": "6699",
        "question": "What is something that is done over and over many times?",
        "answer": "repetitive",
        "distractor_1": "redundant",
        "distractor_2": "repeated",
        "distractor_3": "automation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6700",
        "question": "What is a way of teaching a robot by guiding it through movements and having the computer remember them?",
        "answer": "teach pendant",
        "distractor_1": "automation",
        "distractor_2": "education",
        "distractor_3": "programming (robots)"
      },
      {
        "id": "6701",
        "question": "What is the space in which a robot can operate?",
        "answer": "work envelope",
        "distractor_1": "axis",
        "distractor_2": "automation",
        "distractor_3": "space"
      },
      {
        "id": "7826",
        "question": "Which type of sensor measures the amount of visible electromagnetic energy striking it?",
        "answer": "light sensor",
        "distractor_1": "ultrasonic sensor",
        "distractor_2": "touch sensor",
        "distractor_3": "sound sensor"
      },
      {
        "id": "8096",
        "question": "What is one great advantage robots have over other automatic machines?",
        "answer": "They can be reprogrammed.",
        "distractor_1": "They are made of metal.",
        "distractor_2": "Thay are more modern.",
        "distractor_3": "They last a long time."
      },
      {
        "id": "8097",
        "question": "Which of the listed terms is defined as when computers and robots seem to learn from experience or think as humans?",
        "answer": "artificial intelligence",
        "distractor_1": "mathematics",
        "distractor_2": "programming",
        "distractor_3": "remote control"
      },
      {
        "id": "8098",
        "question": "If a robot is moving at a constant speed, and it takes 2 seconds for the robot to rotate 25°, how long will it take to rotate 40°?",
        "answer": "3.2 seconds",
        "distractor_1": "5.1 seconds",
        "distractor_2": "2.8 seconds",
        "distractor_3": "4 seconds"
      },
      {
        "id": "8524",
        "question": "In 2012, NASA's Curiosity rover safely landed on Mars. This robot is equipped with several instruments for studying Mars. What is the function of Curiosity's ChemCam laser instrument?",
        "answer": "to determine the chemical composition of rocks from a distance",
        "distractor_1": "to scoop up and take pictures of rock samples",
        "distractor_2": "to blast rocks out of its way",
        "distractor_3": "to beam video of chemical reactions in collected rock samples back to Earth "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "212",
    "name": "Rocketry & Space",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2718",
        "question": "A liquid-fueled rocket engine has two liquids, usually called the fuel and the oxidizer. Which two liquids are most commonly used for this propellant?",
        "answer": "liquid hydrogen and liquid oxygen",
        "distractor_1": "liquid hydrogen and liquid nitrogen",
        "distractor_2": "liquid nitrogen and liquid oxygen",
        "distractor_3": "liquid plutonium and liquid uranium"
      },
      {
        "id": "2719",
        "question": "What type of satellites do most communications companies prefer? These satellites stay in the same position above the Earth.",
        "answer": "geostationary",
        "distractor_1": "fixed aerial",
        "distractor_2": "constant point",
        "distractor_3": "static position"
      },
      {
        "id": "2721",
        "question": "What was the name of the space program that was dedicated to putting a man on the Moon?",
        "answer": "Apollo",
        "distractor_1": "Skylab",
        "distractor_2": "Mercury",
        "distractor_3": "Soyuz"
      },
      {
        "id": "2724",
        "question": "What was the first U.S. space station called?",
        "answer": "Skylab",
        "distractor_1": "Mir",
        "distractor_2": "Gemini",
        "distractor_3": "Explorer"
      },
      {
        "id": "2725",
        "question": "Man first set foot on the Moon in what year?",
        "answer": "1969",
        "distractor_1": "1957",
        "distractor_2": "1960",
        "distractor_3": "1973"
      },
      {
        "id": "2726",
        "question": "What was the name of the first space shuttle flown into space?",
        "answer": "Columbia",
        "distractor_1": "Challenger",
        "distractor_2": "Discovery",
        "distractor_3": "Explorer"
      },
      {
        "id": "2727",
        "question": "What type of fuel is used in model rocketry?",
        "answer": "solid",
        "distractor_1": "liquid",
        "distractor_2": "gas",
        "distractor_3": "plasma"
      },
      {
        "id": "2728",
        "question": "Select the statement that best describes Yuri Gagarin's accomplishment on April 12, 1961.",
        "answer": "He became the first man in space.",
        "distractor_1": "He became the first man on the Moon.",
        "distractor_2": "He invented the rocket engine.",
        "distractor_3": "He was born."
      },
      {
        "id": "2729",
        "question": "In which field was Goddard considered an American pioneer?",
        "answer": "modern rocketry",
        "distractor_1": "railroad systems",
        "distractor_2": "airplane travel",
        "distractor_3": "the Moon"
      },
      {
        "id": "2730",
        "question": "In what year did humans first set foot on the Moon?",
        "answer": "1969",
        "distractor_1": "1957",
        "distractor_2": "1960",
        "distractor_3": "1973"
      },
      {
        "id": "2731",
        "question": "The 'Columbia' was the first of what to be flown into space?",
        "answer": "space shuttle",
        "distractor_1": "Apollo rocket",
        "distractor_2": "satellite",
        "distractor_3": "monkey"
      },
      {
        "id": "2732",
        "question": "What type of fuel is used in model rocketry?",
        "answer": "solid",
        "distractor_1": "liquid",
        "distractor_2": "gas",
        "distractor_3": "carbon dioxide"
      },
      {
        "id": "2733",
        "question": "What was the motivating factor that inspired the members of the Apollo space program?",
        "answer": "dedication to putting a man on the Moon",
        "distractor_1": "dedication to putting a man in space",
        "distractor_2": "dedication to launching the first satellite",
        "distractor_3": "dedication to exploring Mars"
      },
      {
        "id": "2734",
        "question": "What does the fire-retardant wadding in a model rocket protect?",
        "answer": "parachute or streamer",
        "distractor_1": "fins",
        "distractor_2": "body tube",
        "distractor_3": "engine"
      },
      {
        "id": "2735",
        "question": "Who was the first American in space?",
        "answer": "Alan Shepard, Jr.",
        "distractor_1": "Buzz Aldrin",
        "distractor_2": "John Glenn",
        "distractor_3": "Yuri Gagarin"
      },
      {
        "id": "2736",
        "question": "According to Newton's third law of motion, for every action there is what kind of reaction?",
        "answer": "equal and opposite",
        "distractor_1": "greater and opposite",
        "distractor_2": "different",
        "distractor_3": "basic"
      },
      {
        "id": "2737",
        "question": "Why do rockets work?",
        "answer": "Newton's law",
        "distractor_1": "Galileo's law",
        "distractor_2": "Ohm's law",
        "distractor_3": "Murphy's law"
      },
      {
        "id": "2738",
        "question": "Who was the first man to set foot on the Moon?",
        "answer": "Armstrong",
        "distractor_1": "Aldrin",
        "distractor_2": "Smith",
        "distractor_3": "Crippen"
      },
      {
        "id": "2739",
        "question": "What was Alan Shepard the first person to accomplish?",
        "answer": "first American in space",
        "distractor_1": "first person to break the sound barrier",
        "distractor_2": "first person in space",
        "distractor_3": "first American to land a spacecraft on the Moon"
      },
      {
        "id": "2740",
        "question": "Why do rockets work?",
        "answer": "Newton's law",
        "distractor_1": "Galileo's law",
        "distractor_2": "Ohm's law",
        "distractor_3": "Murphy's law"
      },
      {
        "id": "2741",
        "question": "Armstrong was the first man to do what on the Moon?",
        "answer": "set foot on",
        "distractor_1": "drive on",
        "distractor_2": "return to",
        "distractor_3": "orbit"
      },
      {
        "id": "2744",
        "question": "On April 12, 1961, who became the first man in space?",
        "answer": "Yuri Gagarin",
        "distractor_1": "Buzz Aldrin",
        "distractor_2": "John Glenn",
        "distractor_3": "Alan Shepard, Jr."
      },
      {
        "id": "2745",
        "question": "Who is considered an American pioneer in modern rocketry?",
        "answer": "Goddard",
        "distractor_1": "Galileo",
        "distractor_2": "Newton",
        "distractor_3": "Gagarin"
      },
      {
        "id": "6721",
        "question": "What is National Aeronautics Space Administration; this agency is responsible for the American Space Transportation System?",
        "answer": "NASA",
        "distractor_1": "EMU",
        "distractor_2": "National Space Convention",
        "distractor_3": "National Airspace Agency"
      },
      {
        "id": "6722",
        "question": "What is a person trained in space technology?",
        "answer": "astronaut",
        "distractor_1": "architect",
        "distractor_2": "scientist",
        "distractor_3": "rocket scientist"
      },
      {
        "id": "6723",
        "question": "What is the extra propulsion power provided to a rocket or spacecraft during liftoff, ascent, or flight?",
        "answer": "boost",
        "distractor_1": "propulsion",
        "distractor_2": "propellant",
        "distractor_3": "SRBs"
      },
      {
        "id": "6724",
        "question": "What is the crew member responsible for overseeing all aspects of a mission?",
        "answer": "commander",
        "distractor_1": "captain",
        "distractor_2": "admiral",
        "distractor_3": "corporal"
      },
      {
        "id": "6725",
        "question": "What is the backward counting in hours, minutes, and seconds of the time remaining before launch?",
        "answer": "countdown",
        "distractor_1": "launch sequence",
        "distractor_2": "launch count",
        "distractor_3": "Takeoff countdown"
      },
      {
        "id": "6726",
        "question": "What is Extravehicular Mobility Unit, integrated spacesuit, and life-support system worn by crew members during activities outside the spacecraft?",
        "answer": "EMU",
        "distractor_1": "Extra Mobile Unit",
        "distractor_2": "Top secret",
        "distractor_3": "Classified information"
      },
      {
        "id": "6727",
        "question": "What contains fuel for the shuttle's main engines?",
        "answer": "external tank",
        "distractor_1": "internal tank",
        "distractor_2": "external fuel tank",
        "distractor_3": "SRBs"
      },
      {
        "id": "6728",
        "question": "What is the start of a rocket or spacecraft's flight from the launch pad; more commonly called blast off?",
        "answer": "Liftoff",
        "distractor_1": "takeoff",
        "distractor_2": "departure",
        "distractor_3": "success!"
      },
      {
        "id": "6729",
        "question": "What is a propulsion backpack device used during extravehicular activity?",
        "answer": "manned maneuvering unit",
        "distractor_1": "payload",
        "distractor_2": "propellant",
        "distractor_3": "SRBs"
      },
      {
        "id": "6730",
        "question": "What is the crew and payload transport component of the space shuttle system?",
        "answer": "orbiter",
        "distractor_1": "payload",
        "distractor_2": "satellite",
        "distractor_3": "SRBs"
      },
      {
        "id": "6731",
        "question": "What instruments, equipment, support hardware, and consumables carried in a spacecraft during a mission?",
        "answer": "payload",
        "distractor_1": "SRBs",
        "distractor_2": "Consumables",
        "distractor_3": "Necessities"
      },
      {
        "id": "6732",
        "question": "What is liquid or solid substance burned in a rocket for the purpose of providing thrust?",
        "answer": "propellant",
        "distractor_1": "gas",
        "distractor_2": "fuel",
        "distractor_3": "boost"
      },
      {
        "id": "6733",
        "question": "What is a natural or man-made body moving around a celestial body?",
        "answer": "satellite",
        "distractor_1": "orbiter",
        "distractor_2": "moon",
        "distractor_3": "manned maneuvering unit"
      },
      {
        "id": "6734",
        "question": "What provides most of the fuel needed to lift the shuttle during the first two minutes of flight?",
        "answer": "SRBs",
        "distractor_1": "Solid rockers",
        "distractor_2": "Manmade rocket boosters",
        "distractor_3": "External tanks"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "301",
    "name": "Fashion & Textiles",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2746",
        "question": "In a retail store, who is responsible for the purchases, sales, and profits of the clothing department?",
        "answer": "buyer",
        "distractor_1": "sales clerk",
        "distractor_2": "store manager",
        "distractor_3": "department manager"
      },
      {
        "id": "2747",
        "question": "What are balance, proportion, emphasis, and rhythm considered when discussing design in the fashion world?",
        "answer": "principles",
        "distractor_1": "elements",
        "distractor_2": "categories",
        "distractor_3": "segments"
      },
      {
        "id": "2748",
        "question": "Identify the term for clothing that is popular at any given time.",
        "answer": "fashion",
        "distractor_1": "garments",
        "distractor_2": "apparel",
        "distractor_3": "fabric"
      },
      {
        "id": "2749",
        "question": "Which of the following may have the textile designs woven, knitted, or printed on it?",
        "answer": "fabric",
        "distractor_1": "fiber",
        "distractor_2": "yarn",
        "distractor_3": "apparel"
      },
      {
        "id": "2751",
        "question": "What is the most common method of dyeing fabrics?",
        "answer": "piece dyeing",
        "distractor_1": "solution dyeing",
        "distractor_2": "yarn dyeing",
        "distractor_3": "fiber dyeing"
      },
      {
        "id": "2753",
        "question": "In the fashion world, what are balance, proportion, emphasis, and rhythm considered?",
        "answer": "principles",
        "distractor_1": "elements",
        "distractor_2": "categories",
        "distractor_3": "segments"
      },
      {
        "id": "2754",
        "question": "In the fashion world, what are color, shape, line, and texture considered?",
        "answer": "elements",
        "distractor_1": "principles",
        "distractor_2": "categories",
        "distractor_3": "segments"
      },
      {
        "id": "2756",
        "question": "On what might textile designs be woven, knitted, or printed?",
        "answer": "fabric",
        "distractor_1": "fiber",
        "distractor_2": "yarn",
        "distractor_3": "apparel"
      },
      {
        "id": "2757",
        "question": "Fibers are twisted or spun into yarn, then used to make fabrics. What are the three most common ways to make fabrics?",
        "answer": "weaving, knitting, bonding",
        "distractor_1": "sewing, knitting, recycling",
        "distractor_2": "quilting, sewing, weaving",
        "distractor_3": "bonding, recycling, quilting"
      },
      {
        "id": "2758",
        "question": "Which of the following words refers to men's, women's, and children's clothing?",
        "answer": "apparel",
        "distractor_1": "fabrics",
        "distractor_2": "garments",
        "distractor_3": "textiles"
      },
      {
        "id": "2759",
        "question": "Identify the term for an article of clothing.",
        "answer": "garment",
        "distractor_1": "fabric",
        "distractor_2": "textile",
        "distractor_3": "apparel"
      },
      {
        "id": "2760",
        "question": "What is the most widely used textile fiber?",
        "answer": "polyester",
        "distractor_1": "cotton",
        "distractor_2": "wool",
        "distractor_3": "silk"
      },
      {
        "id": "2761",
        "question": "Identify the term for unfinished fabrics.",
        "answer": "greige goods",
        "distractor_1": "converter goods",
        "distractor_2": "gray goods",
        "distractor_3": "fringe goods"
      },
      {
        "id": "2762",
        "question": "Which of the following is a principle of design?",
        "answer": "balance",
        "distractor_1": "color",
        "distractor_2": "line",
        "distractor_3": "form"
      },
      {
        "id": "2765",
        "question": "Identify the term for the way apparel is displayed in a store.",
        "answer": "visual merchandising",
        "distractor_1": "advertising",
        "distractor_2": "publicity",
        "distractor_3": "direct selling"
      },
      {
        "id": "2766",
        "question": "Identify the term for men's, women's, and children's clothing.",
        "answer": "apparel",
        "distractor_1": "garments",
        "distractor_2": "fabric",
        "distractor_3": "textile"
      },
      {
        "id": "2767",
        "question": "What are color, shape, line, and texture considered when discussing design in the fashion world?",
        "answer": "elements",
        "distractor_1": "principles",
        "distractor_2": "categories",
        "distractor_3": "segments"
      },
      {
        "id": "2772",
        "question": "What word means an article of clothing?",
        "answer": "garment",
        "distractor_1": "fabric",
        "distractor_2": "textile",
        "distractor_3": "apparel"
      },
      {
        "id": "2773",
        "question": "Through what process are products designed, developed, and promoted to the point of sale?",
        "answer": "merchandising",
        "distractor_1": "distributing",
        "distractor_2": "consulting",
        "distractor_3": "marketing"
      },
      {
        "id": "6392",
        "question": "What is a schedule or plan used to estimate how money should or will be used?",
        "answer": "Budget",
        "distractor_1": "Business plan",
        "distractor_2": "Balance sheet",
        "distractor_3": "Cash flow statement"
      },
      {
        "id": "6393",
        "question": "What is checking the price and quality of an item at several stores before buying?",
        "answer": "Comparison shopping",
        "distractor_1": "Sampling",
        "distractor_2": "Retail",
        "distractor_3": "Secret shopper"
      },
      {
        "id": "6394",
        "question": "What is any person who has money with which to purchase an item?",
        "answer": "Consumer",
        "distractor_1": "Producer",
        "distractor_2": "Supply",
        "distractor_3": "Demand"
      },
      {
        "id": "6395",
        "question": "What is a special method of cleaning delicate fabrics with chemicals?",
        "answer": "Dry cleaning",
        "distractor_1": "Washing",
        "distractor_2": "Steaming",
        "distractor_3": "Dry washing"
      },
      {
        "id": "6396",
        "question": "What is a required amount of something?",
        "answer": "Quota",
        "distractor_1": "Amount",
        "distractor_2": "Retail",
        "distractor_3": "Comparison shopping"
      },
      {
        "id": "6397",
        "question": "What is it when products are sold in individual-sized portions to the general public?",
        "answer": "Retail",
        "distractor_1": "Wholesale",
        "distractor_2": "Sampling",
        "distractor_3": "Discounted"
      },
      {
        "id": "6398",
        "question": "What is the price a member of the general public pays for an item?",
        "answer": "Retail price",
        "distractor_1": "Wholesale price",
        "distractor_2": "Discounted price",
        "distractor_3": "sampling price"
      },
      {
        "id": "6399",
        "question": "What is a small portion that is representative of an entire object?",
        "answer": "Sampling",
        "distractor_1": "Wholesale",
        "distractor_2": "Retail",
        "distractor_3": "Discount"
      },
      {
        "id": "6400",
        "question": "What is a name, symbol, or identifying mark that is associated with a certain product and is legally protected?",
        "answer": "Trademark",
        "distractor_1": "Copyright",
        "distractor_2": "Patent",
        "distractor_3": "Designer's logo"
      },
      {
        "id": "6401",
        "question": "What is it when products are sold to businesses of the general public in large quantities?",
        "answer": "Wholesale",
        "distractor_1": "Retail",
        "distractor_2": "Sampled",
        "distractor_3": "Discounted"
      },
      {
        "id": "6402",
        "question": "What is the price a store pays for an item that it plans to resell?",
        "answer": "Wholesale price",
        "distractor_1": "Retail price",
        "distractor_2": "Discounted price",
        "distractor_3": "Sale price"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "302",
    "name": "Audio Broadcasting",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2062",
        "question": "A transmitter is a device that does which of the following?",
        "answer": "sends radio waves",
        "distractor_1": "mixes radio waves",
        "distractor_2": "amplifies radio waves",
        "distractor_3": "controls radio waves"
      },
      {
        "id": "2063",
        "question": "What does a synthesizer use to produce sound?",
        "answer": "electronic circuits",
        "distractor_1": "strings",
        "distractor_2": "turn tables",
        "distractor_3": "a mix master"
      },
      {
        "id": "2065",
        "question": "Which of the following terms describes the basic function of a radio?",
        "answer": "receiver",
        "distractor_1": "transmitter",
        "distractor_2": "producer",
        "distractor_3": "generator"
      },
      {
        "id": "2066",
        "question": "In order for your radio to pick up radio waves, it must have what device?",
        "answer": "antenna",
        "distractor_1": "transmitter",
        "distractor_2": "microphone",
        "distractor_3": "recorder"
      },
      {
        "id": "2067",
        "question": "What is another name for a radio broadcast's plan?",
        "answer": "format",
        "distractor_1": "outline",
        "distractor_2": "script",
        "distractor_3": "sponsor"
      },
      {
        "id": "2068",
        "question": "What is another word for sound?",
        "answer": "audio",
        "distractor_1": "light",
        "distractor_2": "visual",
        "distractor_3": "motion"
      },
      {
        "id": "2069",
        "question": "Who works primarily in the studio of a radio station?",
        "answer": "on-air hosts",
        "distractor_1": "engineers",
        "distractor_2": "artists",
        "distractor_3": "writers"
      },
      {
        "id": "2070",
        "question": "A decibel is the unit of measurement for which of the following?",
        "answer": "loudness of sound",
        "distractor_1": "voltage of sound",
        "distractor_2": "frequency of sound",
        "distractor_3": "speed of sound"
      },
      {
        "id": "2082",
        "question": "What is another word for audio?",
        "answer": "sound",
        "distractor_1": "light",
        "distractor_2": "visual",
        "distractor_3": "motion"
      },
      {
        "id": "2083",
        "question": "A radio is essentially which of the following?",
        "answer": "a receiver",
        "distractor_1": "a controller",
        "distractor_2": "a mixer",
        "distractor_3": "a transmitter"
      },
      {
        "id": "2084",
        "question": "What is an instrument that uses electronic circuits to produce sound called?",
        "answer": "synthesizer",
        "distractor_1": "recorder",
        "distractor_2": "amplifier",
        "distractor_3": "mixer"
      },
      {
        "id": "2085",
        "question": "Of what is amplitude a measurement?",
        "answer": "height of a radio wave",
        "distractor_1": "frequency of a radio wave",
        "distractor_2": "speed of a radio wave",
        "distractor_3": "length of a radio wave"
      },
      {
        "id": "2086",
        "question": "What is another term for the format of a radio broadcast?",
        "answer": "plan",
        "distractor_1": "sponsor",
        "distractor_2": "script",
        "distractor_3": "outline"
      },
      {
        "id": "2087",
        "question": "The unit of measurement for sound intensity is the decibel. Each time the decibel level of a sound is increased by 1, the sound intensity becomes 10 times greater. If you increase the decibel level by 2, how many times louder is the sound?",
        "answer": "100 times louder",
        "distractor_1": "2 times louder",
        "distractor_2": "5 times louder",
        "distractor_3": "20 times louder"
      },
      {
        "id": "2088",
        "question": "What is a device that sends out radio waves?",
        "answer": "transmitter",
        "distractor_1": "controller",
        "distractor_2": "mixer",
        "distractor_3": "microphone"
      },
      {
        "id": "2089",
        "question": "What is the unit of measurement for the loudness of sound?",
        "answer": "decibel",
        "distractor_1": "voltage",
        "distractor_2": "audio",
        "distractor_3": "frequency"
      },
      {
        "id": "2072",
        "question": "Measured in hertz, what is the number of radio waves transmitted per second called?",
        "answer": "frequency",
        "distractor_1": "wavelength",
        "distractor_2": "wave speed",
        "distractor_3": "amplitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "2073",
        "question": "What is a device that changes sound into an electrical signal?",
        "answer": "microphone",
        "distractor_1": "speaker",
        "distractor_2": "amplifier",
        "distractor_3": "mixer"
      },
      {
        "id": "2074",
        "question": "Which of the following is the term for the height of a radio wave's peak?",
        "answer": "amplitude",
        "distractor_1": "frequency",
        "distractor_2": "wavelength",
        "distractor_3": "greatness"
      },
      {
        "id": "2075",
        "question": "How fast do all radio waves travel?",
        "answer": "at the speed of light",
        "distractor_1": "at the speed of sound",
        "distractor_2": "at the speed of frequency",
        "distractor_3": "at the speed of decibels"
      },
      {
        "id": "2076",
        "question": "Where do on-air radio personalities primarily work at radio stations?",
        "answer": "in the studio",
        "distractor_1": "in the shop",
        "distractor_2": "in the lab",
        "distractor_3": "in the control room"
      },
      {
        "id": "2077",
        "question": "What do radio waves do at 186,000 miles per second, or the speed of light?",
        "answer": "travel",
        "distractor_1": "vibrate",
        "distractor_2": "oscillate",
        "distractor_3": "modulate"
      },
      {
        "id": "2078",
        "question": "What does an antenna allow your radio to do?",
        "answer": "receive radio waves",
        "distractor_1": "mix radio waves",
        "distractor_2": "amplify radio waves",
        "distractor_3": "record radio waves"
      },
      {
        "id": "2079",
        "question": "How does a radio interact with radio waves?",
        "answer": "receives them",
        "distractor_1": "controls them",
        "distractor_2": "mixes them",
        "distractor_3": "transmits them"
      },
      {
        "id": "5519",
        "question": "What is information such as words or numbers that is analyzed and organized into something useful?",
        "answer": "data",
        "distractor_1": "information",
        "distractor_2": "audio",
        "distractor_3": "communication"
      },
      {
        "id": "5520",
        "question": "Choose the device that blends signals from several sources into one signal?",
        "answer": "mixer",
        "distractor_1": "microphone",
        "distractor_2": "radio",
        "distractor_3": "synthesizer"
      },
      {
        "id": "5521",
        "question": "Which of the following is a receiver of radio waves?",
        "answer": "radio",
        "distractor_1": "microphone",
        "distractor_2": "antenna",
        "distractor_3": "transmitter"
      },
      {
        "id": "5522",
        "question": "Which of the following is an electromagnetic wave in the frequency range that transmits signals for radio?",
        "answer": "radio wave",
        "distractor_1": "decibel",
        "distractor_2": "format",
        "distractor_3": "data"
      },
      {
        "id": "8198",
        "question": "The speed of sound is about 1,200 kilometers per hour, and there are 3,600 seconds in an hour. What is the speed of sound in kilometers per second?",
        "answer": "about 1/3 km/sec",
        "distractor_1": "about 3 km/sec",
        "distractor_2": "about 1.2 km/sec",
        "distractor_3": "about 20 km/sec"
      },
      {
        "id": "8199",
        "question": "A radio station has a frequency of 96,000 kilohertz. What would that frequency be in hertz?",
        "answer": "96,000,000 hertz",
        "distractor_1": "960,000 hertz",
        "distractor_2": "96 hertz",
        "distractor_3": "960 hertz"
      },
      {
        "id": "8200",
        "question": "A pistol is fired at the starting line of a 2,000-meter boat race. The speed of sound is about 330 meters/second. How long after the pistol is fired will the finish line judge hear the shot?",
        "answer": "about 6 seconds",
        "distractor_1": "about 3 seconds",
        "distractor_2": "about 4 seconds",
        "distractor_3": "about 8 seconds"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "303",
    "name": "Animals",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2006",
        "question": "Which of the following classes of vertebrates are endotherms?",
        "answer": "birds and mammals",
        "distractor_1": "reptiles and birds",
        "distractor_2": "reptiles and amphibians",
        "distractor_3": "amphibians and mammals"
      },
      {
        "id": "2033",
        "question": "Which of the following classes of vertebrates are ectotherms?",
        "answer": "fish, amphibians, and reptiles",
        "distractor_1": "fish, amphibians, and birds",
        "distractor_2": "reptiles, birds, and mammals",
        "distractor_3": "amphibians, reptiles, and birds"
      },
      {
        "id": "8226",
        "question": "An animal having radial symmetry and a tissue level of organization belongs to which phylum?",
        "answer": "Cnidaria",
        "distractor_1": "Porifera",
        "distractor_2": "Mollusca",
        "distractor_3": "Enchinodermata"
      },
      {
        "id": "8227",
        "question": "In which of the following levels of animal taxonomy are the animals most closely related to each other? ",
        "answer": "genus",
        "distractor_1": "phylum",
        "distractor_2": "class",
        "distractor_3": "family"
      },
      {
        "id": "5577",
        "question": "What is it called when there is a change in an organism that helps it better fit a particular environment.",
        "answer": "adaptation",
        "distractor_1": "chameleon",
        "distractor_2": "change",
        "distractor_3": "evolution"
      },
      {
        "id": "5578",
        "question": "What is the most specific category of organisms, members of which can mate and produce fertile offspring?",
        "answer": "species",
        "distractor_1": "vertebrate",
        "distractor_2": "Chordata",
        "distractor_3": "Arthropoda"
      },
      {
        "id": "5579",
        "question": "What is the term for an animal that cannot regulate its body temperature, but maintains the environmental temperature?",
        "answer": "ectotherm",
        "distractor_1": "endotherm",
        "distractor_2": "invertebrates",
        "distractor_3": "warm-blooded"
      },
      {
        "id": "8228",
        "question": "To be classified as a chordate, an animal must have which of the following characteristics?",
        "answer": "dorsal hollow nerve cord",
        "distractor_1": "amniotic egg",
        "distractor_2": "vertebral column",
        "distractor_3": "bilateral symmetry"
      },
      {
        "id": "5581",
        "question": "What is an animal with a backbone, or vertebral column, consisting of interconnected bones?",
        "answer": "vertebrate",
        "distractor_1": "invertebrate",
        "distractor_2": "exoskeleton",
        "distractor_3": "endoskeleton"
      },
      {
        "id": "5582",
        "question": "What is an animal that lacks a backbone, or vertebral column?",
        "answer": "invertebrate",
        "distractor_1": "vertebrate",
        "distractor_2": "exoskeleton",
        "distractor_3": "endoskeleton"
      },
      {
        "id": "5583",
        "question": "What is the organization of body structure around one or more body axes?",
        "answer": "symmetry",
        "distractor_1": "segmentation",
        "distractor_2": "cephalization",
        "distractor_3": "exoskeleton"
      },
      {
        "id": "5584",
        "question": "What is the separation of an animal body into rings in which various body parts are repeated?",
        "answer": "segmentation",
        "distractor_1": "symmetry",
        "distractor_2": "vertebrate",
        "distractor_3": "evolution"
      },
      {
        "id": "5585",
        "question": "Concentration of nervous and sensory tissue at the head end of an animal is called what?",
        "answer": "cephalization",
        "distractor_1": "natural selection",
        "distractor_2": "ganglia",
        "distractor_3": "ganglion"
      },
      {
        "id": "5586",
        "question": "What is the hard, outer body covering that protects the animal and aids in movement by attaching to muscles?",
        "answer": "exoskeleton",
        "distractor_1": "endoskeleton",
        "distractor_2": "skeleton",
        "distractor_3": "shell"
      },
      {
        "id": "5587",
        "question": "What is the internal bony skeleton covered by muscle and skin, used in support, structure, and movement?",
        "answer": "endoskeleton",
        "distractor_1": "exoskeleton",
        "distractor_2": "ligaments",
        "distractor_3": "tendons"
      },
      {
        "id": "5588",
        "question": "What is the term for an animal that is able to reproduce on land because it produces a waterproof, shelled egg containing membranes to protect and nourish the embryo?",
        "answer": "amniote",
        "distractor_1": "tortoise",
        "distractor_2": "amphibians",
        "distractor_3": "embryos"
      },
      {
        "id": "5589",
        "question": "What is the name of the phylum of animals characterized by presence of a notochord, dorsal hollow nerve cord, pharyngeal gill slits, and a tail?",
        "answer": "chordate",
        "distractor_1": "class",
        "distractor_2": "genus",
        "distractor_3": "phyla"
      },
      {
        "id": "5590",
        "question": "What is the gradual genetic change in a species or population over time?",
        "answer": "evolution",
        "distractor_1": "timeline",
        "distractor_2": "mutations",
        "distractor_3": "natural selection"
      },
      {
        "id": "5591",
        "question": "What is the process by which evolution occurs, in which environmental stress acts on genetic variability to cause genetic change over many generations?",
        "answer": "natural selection",
        "distractor_1": "genotype",
        "distractor_2": "heritable traits",
        "distractor_3": "adaptation"
      },
      {
        "id": "5592",
        "question": "What is the explanation for a natural phenomenon based on a large amount of verifiable evidence obtained from multiple sources?",
        "answer": "scientific theory",
        "distractor_1": "hypothesis",
        "distractor_2": "experiment",
        "distractor_3": "observation"
      },
      {
        "id": "5593",
        "question": "What is the term for preserved remains of ancient organisms, such as bones, shells, casts, or impressions?",
        "answer": "fossil",
        "distractor_1": "paleontology",
        "distractor_2": "sedimentary",
        "distractor_3": "mineralized"
      },
      {
        "id": "8229",
        "question": "Among vertebrates, development of the amniotic egg and internal fertilization enabled life to spread into which of the following environments?",
        "answer": "land",
        "distractor_1": "water",
        "distractor_2": "cold climates",
        "distractor_3": "hot climates"
      },
      {
        "id": "8230",
        "question": "Parental care in birds and mammals is possible because of the development of which characteristic?",
        "answer": "large brain",
        "distractor_1": "oviparous reproduction",
        "distractor_2": "endothermy",
        "distractor_3": "amniotic egg"
      },
      {
        "id": "8231",
        "question": "About what percentage of Earth's animals are vertebrates?",
        "answer": "3 percent",
        "distractor_1": "10 percent",
        "distractor_2": "50 percent",
        "distractor_3": "90 percent"
      },
      {
        "id": "8232",
        "question": "Which of the following is not always a characteristic of mammals?",
        "answer": "gives birth to live young",
        "distractor_1": "has hair or fur",
        "distractor_2": "produces milk",
        "distractor_3": "regulates its body temperature"
      },
      {
        "id": "8234",
        "question": "An organism with an exoskeleton and bilateral symmetry is a member of which phylum?",
        "answer": "Arthropoda",
        "distractor_1": "Chordata",
        "distractor_2": "Annelida",
        "distractor_3": "Mollusca"
      },
      {
        "id": "8235",
        "question": "Which phylum and class of animals contains the greatest number of species?",
        "answer": "Phylum Arthropoda, Class Insecta",
        "distractor_1": "Phylum Arthropoda, Class Crustacea",
        "distractor_2": "Phylum Chordata, Class Mammalia",
        "distractor_3": "Phylum Chordata, Class Reptilia"
      },
      {
        "id": "8251",
        "question": "About 2/3 of the known species of fish are bony fish. There are about 20,000 species of bony fish. About how many species of fish are known?",
        "answer": "30,000",
        "distractor_1": "13,333",
        "distractor_2": "40,000",
        "distractor_3": "26,667"
      },
      {
        "id": "8236",
        "question": "An animal having radial symmetry and an organ system level of organization most likely belongs to which phylum?",
        "answer": "Echinodermata",
        "distractor_1": "Porifera",
        "distractor_2": "Cnidaria",
        "distractor_3": "Nematoda"
      },
      {
        "id": "8237",
        "question": "Which of the following levels of taxonomy is the most general, inclusive category? ",
        "answer": "domain",
        "distractor_1": "phylum",
        "distractor_2": "species",
        "distractor_3": "order"
      },
      {
        "id": "8238",
        "question": "In most chordates, the notochord develops into which structure?",
        "answer": "vertebral column",
        "distractor_1": "spinal cord",
        "distractor_2": "muscle segments",
        "distractor_3": "tail"
      },
      {
        "id": "8239",
        "question": "Animals were able to leave water and live entirely on land due to which adaptation?",
        "answer": "amniotic egg",
        "distractor_1": "scales",
        "distractor_2": "vertebral column",
        "distractor_3": "external fertilization"
      },
      {
        "id": "8240",
        "question": "Development of large brains in birds and mammals was important in the development of which adaptation?",
        "answer": "long-term parental care",
        "distractor_1": "migration",
        "distractor_2": "metamorphosis",
        "distractor_3": "temperature regulation"
      },
      {
        "id": "8241",
        "question": "About what percentage of Earth's animals are invertebrates?",
        "answer": "97 percent",
        "distractor_1": "35 percent",
        "distractor_2": "56 percent",
        "distractor_3": "10 percent"
      },
      {
        "id": "8242",
        "question": "Which of the following characteristics do some mammals lack?",
        "answer": "viviparous reproduction",
        "distractor_1": "hair or fur",
        "distractor_2": "endothermy",
        "distractor_3": "milk production"
      },
      {
        "id": "8244",
        "question": "An organism with an external shell and modified bilateral symmetry belongs to which phylum?",
        "answer": "Mollusca",
        "distractor_1": "Arthropoda",
        "distractor_2": "Chordata",
        "distractor_3": "Annelida"
      },
      {
        "id": "8245",
        "question": "Which animal phylum contains the largest number of species?",
        "answer": "Arthropoda",
        "distractor_1": "Chordata",
        "distractor_2": "Mollusca",
        "distractor_3": "Echinodermata"
      },
      {
        "id": "8246",
        "question": "Which of the following types of worms feeds like a vacuum cleaner, sucking up food that has been partially digested outside its body?",
        "answer": "planarian",
        "distractor_1": "tapeworm",
        "distractor_2": "roundworm",
        "distractor_3": "segmented worm"
      },
      {
        "id": "8247",
        "question": "How do sand lizards avoid the heat of the sand during the midday in the desert?",
        "answer": "dance by lifting their legs up alternately",
        "distractor_1": "hide under rocks",
        "distractor_2": "come out only at night",
        "distractor_3": "bury themselves under the sand"
      },
      {
        "id": "8248",
        "question": "Newly hatched baby gulls crouch down when they see any bird's shadow. Older gull babies crouch only when they see hawk shadows. What type of behavior does this show?",
        "answer": "learning",
        "distractor_1": "instinct",
        "distractor_2": "conditioning",
        "distractor_3": "imprinting"
      },
      {
        "id": "8249",
        "question": "Birds use their tail feathers for all of the following functions except _______.",
        "answer": "power during flight",
        "distractor_1": "balancing when perched",
        "distractor_2": "steering during flight",
        "distractor_3": "courtship displays"
      },
      {
        "id": "8252",
        "question": "Of the approximately 4,000 species of mammals, only two are monotremes, or egg-laying mammals. What percentage of the species of mammals are monotremes?",
        "answer": "0.05 percent",
        "distractor_1": "2 percent",
        "distractor_2": "0.02 percent",
        "distractor_3": "0.5 percent"
      },
      {
        "id": "8253",
        "question": "A cheetah can sprint as fast as 70 mph. If a gazelle is 50 yards away, and the cheetah rushes toward it at approximately 60 mph (approximately 88 ft/sec), how many seconds will it take the cheetah to reach the gazelle? Hint: Distance = speed x time",
        "answer": "1.7 seconds",
        "distractor_1": "2.3 seconds",
        "distractor_2": "1.3 seconds",
        "distractor_3": "2.7 seconds"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "306",
    "name": "Computer Graph. & Anim.",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2200",
        "question": "What is an electronic device that allows computers to share information across telephone lines?",
        "answer": "modem",
        "distractor_1": "coprocessor",
        "distractor_2": "chip",
        "distractor_3": "virus"
      },
      {
        "id": "2203",
        "question": "What is used to describe the environments of electronic bulletin boards, computer networks, virtual reality worlds, and other virtual communities?",
        "answer": "cyberspace",
        "distractor_1": "cyberuniverse",
        "distractor_2": "cybernetics",
        "distractor_3": "cyberstage"
      },
      {
        "id": "2204",
        "question": "What is a type of computer-generated design where each part of the pattern has the same structure as the whole pattern?",
        "answer": "fractal",
        "distractor_1": "COBOL",
        "distractor_2": "geometric sequence",
        "distractor_3": "tessellation"
      },
      {
        "id": "2205",
        "question": "How are stop-motion special effects in animated films created?",
        "answer": "by exposing one frame at a time",
        "distractor_1": "by starting and stopping the film rapidly",
        "distractor_2": "by filming in complete darkness and viewing the negative",
        "distractor_3": "by changing the speed of the camera while filming"
      },
      {
        "id": "2206",
        "question": "What are controlled by microprocessors?",
        "answer": "electronic machines",
        "distractor_1": "macroprocessors",
        "distractor_2": "coprocessors",
        "distractor_3": "resistors"
      },
      {
        "id": "2207",
        "question": "Which of the following describes a type of computer-generated design known as a fractal?",
        "answer": "Each part of the pattern has the same structure as the whole thing.",
        "distractor_1": "Only a fraction of the whole thing is saved.",
        "distractor_2": "The whole thing is broken into pieces.",
        "distractor_3": "Each part of the pattern has a structure different from the rest."
      },
      {
        "id": "2210",
        "question": "What are the tiny picture elements called that computers manipulate to create or change images?",
        "answer": "pixels",
        "distractor_1": "periods",
        "distractor_2": "picas",
        "distractor_3": "points"
      },
      {
        "id": "2212",
        "question": "Special effects in animated films are sometimes created by exposing one frame at a time. What is this technique?",
        "answer": "stop-motion",
        "distractor_1": "motion-control",
        "distractor_2": "model-mation",
        "distractor_3": "break-motion"
      },
      {
        "id": "2213",
        "question": "How do computer animators define morphing?",
        "answer": "a special effect that transforms one image into another image",
        "distractor_1": "waffling",
        "distractor_2": "interpolation",
        "distractor_3": "a process to transfer data from a floppy disk to a computer’s hard disk"
      },
      {
        "id": "2214",
        "question": "How are pixels best described?",
        "answer": "tiny picture elements",
        "distractor_1": "periods",
        "distractor_2": "picas",
        "distractor_3": "points"
      },
      {
        "id": "2215",
        "question": "An animator creates which of the following?",
        "answer": "animated cartoons",
        "distractor_1": "newspaper comics",
        "distractor_2": "headline news",
        "distractor_3": "magazine cartoons"
      },
      {
        "id": "2219",
        "question": "Who creates animated cartoons?",
        "answer": "animator",
        "distractor_1": "journalist",
        "distractor_2": "actuary",
        "distractor_3": "technical artist"
      },
      {
        "id": "2221",
        "question": "Which of the following electronic machines can receive, process, store, and output information?",
        "answer": "computers",
        "distractor_1": "transistors",
        "distractor_2": "digitizers",
        "distractor_3": "lasers"
      },
      {
        "id": "2223",
        "question": "How is a virtual reality environment described?",
        "answer": "computer-generated, interactive, and three-dimensional",
        "distractor_1": "audio-generated, passive, and one-dimensional",
        "distractor_2": "computer-generated, interactive, and one-dimensional",
        "distractor_3": "audio-generated, passive, and three-dimensional"
      },
      {
        "id": "2226",
        "question": "What is a computer special effect that transforms one image into another image?",
        "answer": "morphing",
        "distractor_1": "waffling",
        "distractor_2": "interpolation",
        "distractor_3": "mutating"
      },
      {
        "id": "6848",
        "question": "Which term is defined as a multimedia application that uses 3-D graphics to create a realistic simulation?",
        "answer": "virtual reality",
        "distractor_1": "stop-motion",
        "distractor_2": "interpolation",
        "distractor_3": "interactive"
      },
      {
        "id": "6852",
        "question": "What is used to determine color, texture and reflection for 3-D objects?",
        "answer": "shaders",
        "distractor_1": "patterns",
        "distractor_2": "backgrounds",
        "distractor_3": "highlighting"
      },
      {
        "id": "6853",
        "question": "What is the process in which 3-D effects are applied to a 2-D object?",
        "answer": "rendering",
        "distractor_1": "resolution",
        "distractor_2": "direct manipulation",
        "distractor_3": "modifying"
      },
      {
        "id": "6854",
        "question": "What is a basic object that cannot be broken down into a more simple form?",
        "answer": "primitive",
        "distractor_1": "key frame",
        "distractor_2": "tweener",
        "distractor_3": "import"
      },
      {
        "id": "6856",
        "question": "Which of the following is determined by a computerized formula to move an object between key frames?",
        "answer": "tweener",
        "distractor_1": "direct manipulation",
        "distractor_2": "animation",
        "distractor_3": "stop-motion"
      },
      {
        "id": "6857",
        "question": "Which of the following is an electronic representation of an individual used in cyberspace?",
        "answer": "avatar",
        "distractor_1": "shader",
        "distractor_2": "tweener",
        "distractor_3": "morph"
      },
      {
        "id": "6858",
        "question": "Which of the following is used to define a specific position of an object in a animation?",
        "answer": "key frame",
        "distractor_1": "modifier",
        "distractor_2": "tweener",
        "distractor_3": "primitive"
      },
      {
        "id": "6242",
        "question": "What is the term for a situation in which you can enter a question or command and the computer gives immediate results?",
        "answer": "interactive",
        "distractor_1": "connective event",
        "distractor_2": "search engine",
        "distractor_3": "high speed"
      },
      {
        "id": "6243",
        "question": "What is a central processing unit (CPU) contained on a single chip?",
        "answer": "microprocessor",
        "distractor_1": "computer chip",
        "distractor_2": "smart chip",
        "distractor_3": "memory"
      },
      {
        "id": "6245",
        "question": "What is the term for the clarity or fineness of detail in an image on a monitor or in printed material?",
        "answer": "resolution",
        "distractor_1": "pixel",
        "distractor_2": "virtual reality",
        "distractor_3": "animation"
      },
      {
        "id": "8340",
        "question": "Computer information is in a digital format that travels at the speed of light. What is the speed of light?",
        "answer": "186,282 miles per second",
        "distractor_1": "89,234 miles per second",
        "distractor_2": "195,729 miles per second",
        "distractor_3": "54,112 miles per second"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "307",
    "name": "Ecology",
    "weight": "90",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "6884",
        "question": "A green plant belongs to which trophic, or feeding, level?",
        "answer": "Producer",
        "distractor_1": "First-level consumer",
        "distractor_2": "Top-level consumer",
        "distractor_3": "Decomposer"
      },
      {
        "id": "6904",
        "question": "What is the term for the process by which nutrients are moved continuously  through various parts of the biosphere?",
        "answer": "biogeochemical cycling",
        "distractor_1": "energy flow ",
        "distractor_2": "nutrient flow",
        "distractor_3": "succession"
      },
      {
        "id": "4465",
        "question": "In a natural population, limiting factors act by doing which of the following?",
        "answer": "decreasing the birthrate or increasing the death rate",
        "distractor_1": "decreasing the death rate or increasing the birthrate",
        "distractor_2": "decreasing both the birth and death rates",
        "distractor_3": "increasing both the birth and death rates"
      },
      {
        "id": "4466",
        "question": "As a community goes through succession, how does its structure change with time?",
        "answer": "Its food webs and interactions become more complex.",
        "distractor_1": "It keeps the same species, and their populations increase.",
        "distractor_2": "It becomes less stable and more likely to change.",
        "distractor_3": "It begins to run out of resources and species die out."
      },
      {
        "id": "4467",
        "question": "Which statement best describes the difference between the movement of energy and the movement of matter in an ecosystem?",
        "answer": "Energy flows in one direction whereas matter is recycled.",
        "distractor_1": "Matter flows in one direction whereas energy is recycled.",
        "distractor_2": "Both matter and energy flow in one direction.",
        "distractor_3": "Both matter and energy are recycled."
      },
      {
        "id": "4468",
        "question": "In a food chain, which trophic, or feeding, level supports the largest biomass of organisms?",
        "answer": "producers",
        "distractor_1": "herbivores",
        "distractor_2": "primary carnivores",
        "distractor_3": "top carnivores"
      },
      {
        "id": "4469",
        "question": "Which of the following substances participates in a gaseous cycle within the biosphere?",
        "answer": "nitrogen",
        "distractor_1": "phosphorus",
        "distractor_2": "water",
        "distractor_3": "energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "4470",
        "question": "In a natural population, which of the following could NOT act as a limiting factor to prevent uncontrolled population growth?",
        "answer": "genetic variation within the population",
        "distractor_1": "competition with other species",
        "distractor_2": "availability of food or nutrients",
        "distractor_3": "an epidemic disease"
      },
      {
        "id": "4471",
        "question": "Which of the following substances participates in a sedimentary cycle within the biosphere?",
        "answer": "phosphorus",
        "distractor_1": "nitrogen",
        "distractor_2": "water",
        "distractor_3": "energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "4472",
        "question": "Barnacles attach to whales, which carry them from place to place, enabling them to find food and colonize new habitats. This is an example of which type of symbiosis?",
        "answer": "commensalism",
        "distractor_1": "parasitism",
        "distractor_2": "competition",
        "distractor_3": "mutualism"
      },
      {
        "id": "4473",
        "question": "A population is stabilized when which of the following situations occurs?",
        "answer": "Birthrates equal death rates.",
        "distractor_1": "Birthrates exceed death rates.",
        "distractor_2": "Birthrates exceed immigration rates.",
        "distractor_3": "Death rates equal immigration rates."
      },
      {
        "id": "4476",
        "question": "Species that are well adapted to live on or near mountaintops would also be well adapted to live in which type of ecosystem or biome?",
        "answer": "tundra",
        "distractor_1": "grassland",
        "distractor_2": "temperate deciduous forest",
        "distractor_3": "coniferous forest, or taiga"
      },
      {
        "id": "4477",
        "question": "An ecosystem that has many species and a very complex web of interactions has which of the following pairs of characteristics?",
        "answer": "high biodiversity and high stability",
        "distractor_1": "high biodiversity and low stability",
        "distractor_2": "low biodiversity and low stability",
        "distractor_3": "low biodiversity and high stability"
      },
      {
        "id": "4478",
        "question": "For natural selection to occur in a population, which two factors must interact?",
        "answer": "genetic variability and selective pressure",
        "distractor_1": "biodiversity and stability",
        "distractor_2": "species richness and predation",
        "distractor_3": "evolution and extinction"
      },
      {
        "id": "4479",
        "question": "Which of the following is true of a population that has an S-shaped, or logistic, growth curve?",
        "answer": "It has reached the carrying capacity of its environment.",
        "distractor_1": "It is growing exponentially.",
        "distractor_2": "It is growing at its biotic potential.",
        "distractor_3": "Its population has exploded and it will crash."
      },
      {
        "id": "4480",
        "question": "Which of the following characteristics describes an ecosystem with high biodiversity?",
        "answer": "high stability",
        "distractor_1": "short food chains",
        "distractor_2": "few species",
        "distractor_3": "short life span"
      },
      {
        "id": "4481",
        "question": "What process is occurring when selective pressures from the environment act on the genetic variability within a population?",
        "answer": "natural selection",
        "distractor_1": "extinction",
        "distractor_2": "biodiversity",
        "distractor_3": "competition"
      },
      {
        "id": "4484",
        "question": "A population's birthrate is lower than its death rate, and its immigration and emigration rates are both zero. What is the best description of this population?",
        "answer": "declining",
        "distractor_1": "growing",
        "distractor_2": "stable",
        "distractor_3": "variable"
      },
      {
        "id": "4485",
        "question": "In a food chain, which trophic, or feeding, level supports the smallest biomass of organisms?",
        "answer": "top carnivores",
        "distractor_1": "producers",
        "distractor_2": "herbivores",
        "distractor_3": "primary carnivores"
      },
      {
        "id": "4486",
        "question": "'With every energy transformation, some energy is degraded to heat and the system becomes more disordered.' This is a statement of which law or principle?",
        "answer": "second law of thermodynamics",
        "distractor_1": "principle of energy conservation",
        "distractor_2": "principle of trophic levels",
        "distractor_3": "first law of thermodynamics"
      },
      {
        "id": "4489",
        "question": "According to the second law of thermodynamics, what happens to energy as it moves through a food web?",
        "answer": "It moves in one direction; some is lost as heat at each level.",
        "distractor_1": "It is all lost to the environment as heat.",
        "distractor_2": "It is all retained and continually recycled.",
        "distractor_3": "Some is retained and recycled; some is lost as heat."
      },
      {
        "id": "4490",
        "question": "Which of the following is true of a population that has a J-shaped, or exponential, growth curve?",
        "answer": "Its population is exploding, or growing without limits.",
        "distractor_1": "It is being affected by limiting factors.",
        "distractor_2": "It is growing below its biotic potential.",
        "distractor_3": "It has reached the carrying capacity of its environment."
      },
      {
        "id": "4491",
        "question": "Oxpeckers, a type of bird, feed on ticks that live on the back of the black rhinoceros. This is an example of which type of symbiosis?",
        "answer": "mutualism",
        "distractor_1": "parasitism",
        "distractor_2": "commensalism",
        "distractor_3": "competition"
      },
      {
        "id": "4492",
        "question": "Which of the following examples represents a community currently undergoing primary succession?",
        "answer": "a mountaintop where a volcano has recently erupted",
        "distractor_1": "a climax oak-hickory forest",
        "distractor_2": "a coral reef that has existed for several thousand years",
        "distractor_3": "a wheat field that has been plowed and not replanted"
      },
      {
        "id": "6295",
        "question": "What is the term for the variety of types of living organisms on Earth?",
        "answer": "Biodiversity",
        "distractor_1": "Community",
        "distractor_2": "Population",
        "distractor_3": "Ecosystem"
      },
      {
        "id": "6296",
        "question": "What is the layer of Earth where all living things reside?",
        "answer": "Biosphere",
        "distractor_1": "Troposphere",
        "distractor_2": "Ecosystem",
        "distractor_3": "Niche"
      },
      {
        "id": "6297",
        "question": "What term describes an orderly change of a community's structure from simple to complex over time?",
        "answer": "Succession",
        "distractor_1": "Population",
        "distractor_2": "Competition",
        "distractor_3": "Niche"
      },
      {
        "id": "6298",
        "question": "What is a group of individuals of one species living together in a defined area?",
        "answer": "Population",
        "distractor_1": "Community",
        "distractor_2": "Ecosystem",
        "distractor_3": "Habitat"
      },
      {
        "id": "6299",
        "question": "What are all the populations within a defined area, living and interacting with each other?",
        "answer": "Community",
        "distractor_1": "Ecosystem",
        "distractor_2": "Niche",
        "distractor_3": "Habitat"
      },
      {
        "id": "6300",
        "question": "What is a complete disappearance of a species from Earth?",
        "answer": "Extinction",
        "distractor_1": "Evolution",
        "distractor_2": "Symbiosis",
        "distractor_3": "Competition"
      },
      {
        "id": "6301",
        "question": "What is a community of organisms, its nonliving environment, and all interactions of both?",
        "answer": "Ecosystem",
        "distractor_1": "Habitat",
        "distractor_2": "Niche",
        "distractor_3": "Community"
      },
      {
        "id": "6302",
        "question": "What is an organism's location within a community?",
        "answer": "Habitat",
        "distractor_1": "Community",
        "distractor_2": "Ecosystem",
        "distractor_3": "Niche"
      },
      {
        "id": "6303",
        "question": "What is an organism's function within a community?",
        "answer": "Niche",
        "distractor_1": "Competition",
        "distractor_2": "Habitat",
        "distractor_3": "Community"
      },
      {
        "id": "6304",
        "question": "What kind of animal obtains energy by eating both plants and animals?",
        "answer": "Omnivore",
        "distractor_1": "Herbivore",
        "distractor_2": "Carnivore",
        "distractor_3": "Autotroph"
      },
      {
        "id": "6305",
        "question": "What is the term for a producer organism, such as a green plant, that makes its own food?",
        "answer": "Autotroph",
        "distractor_1": "Heterotroph",
        "distractor_2": "Carnivore",
        "distractor_3": "Omnivore"
      },
      {
        "id": "6306",
        "question": "What is the term for a consumer organism, such as an animal, that cannot make its own food?",
        "answer": "Heterotroph",
        "distractor_1": "Autotroph",
        "distractor_2": "Producer",
        "distractor_3": "Biome"
      },
      {
        "id": "6307",
        "question": "What is the term for a genetic change through time in a population or species?",
        "answer": "Evolution",
        "distractor_1": "Succession",
        "distractor_2": "Population",
        "distractor_3": "Biodiversity"
      },
      {
        "id": "6308",
        "question": "What process in which two or more species use the same resource causes some harm to both?",
        "answer": "Competition",
        "distractor_1": "Mutualism",
        "distractor_2": "Succession",
        "distractor_3": "Evolution"
      },
      {
        "id": "6309",
        "question": "What is any extremely close relationship between members of two different species?",
        "answer": "Symbiosis",
        "distractor_1": "Mutualism",
        "distractor_2": "Commensalism",
        "distractor_3": "Competition"
      },
      {
        "id": "6310",
        "question": "What kind of animal obtains its energy by eating only plants?",
        "answer": "Herbivore",
        "distractor_1": "Omnivore",
        "distractor_2": "Carnivore",
        "distractor_3": "Producer"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "308",
    "name": "Families",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2984",
        "question": "Which term describes two or more people who share goals and values, have long-term commitments to one another, and are related to each other?",
        "answer": "family",
        "distractor_1": "generation",
        "distractor_2": "coworkers",
        "distractor_3": "schoolmates"
      },
      {
        "id": "2985",
        "question": "Which of the following is a diagram that shows a family's ancestry?",
        "answer": "family tree",
        "distractor_1": "family life cycle",
        "distractor_2": "generation gap",
        "distractor_3": "pedigree profile"
      },
      {
        "id": "2986",
        "question": "Each family member has roles to play. There are three ways you receive your family roles. They may be assigned to you, you may choose them, or which of the following?",
        "answer": "inherit them",
        "distractor_1": "buy them",
        "distractor_2": "get them from socialization",
        "distractor_3": "get them from peer pressure"
      },
      {
        "id": "2988",
        "question": "What is one important way to keep relationships with parents from becoming strained during your teenage years?",
        "answer": "communicate with them",
        "distractor_1": "get a job",
        "distractor_2": "avoid them",
        "distractor_3": "live with a friend"
      },
      {
        "id": "2990",
        "question": "Which term describes the bearing of children in order to extend the family?",
        "answer": "procreation",
        "distractor_1": "communication",
        "distractor_2": "socialization",
        "distractor_3": "generation"
      },
      {
        "id": "2991",
        "question": "As young teenagers, you are in what stage of the family life cycle?",
        "answer": "developing",
        "distractor_1": "beginning",
        "distractor_2": "expanding",
        "distractor_3": "launching"
      },
      {
        "id": "2995",
        "question": "Some families have higher divorce rates than others. Families in which the spouses have a low level of education or no religious ties are two examples. Which of the following is another example of a group with a high divorce rate?",
        "answer": "married teenagers",
        "distractor_1": "baby boomers",
        "distractor_2": "college graduates",
        "distractor_3": "farmers"
      },
      {
        "id": "2996",
        "question": "Life expectancy for the average American increased by about 10% between 1950 and 1985. Assume that the rate of increase remains 10% between 1990 and 2025. If the life expectancy for the average American was 75 in 1990, what would it be in 2025?",
        "answer": "82.5 years",
        "distractor_1": "78 years",
        "distractor_2": "85 years",
        "distractor_3": "87.5 years"
      },
      {
        "id": "2997",
        "question": "One role of families is to teach children about the rules and customs of the society in which they live. Which term best describes this task?",
        "answer": "socialization",
        "distractor_1": "procreation",
        "distractor_2": "indoctrination",
        "distractor_3": "adaptation"
      },
      {
        "id": "2998",
        "question": "What type of family is formed when a single parent remarries?",
        "answer": "blended",
        "distractor_1": "extended",
        "distractor_2": "one-parent",
        "distractor_3": "nuclear"
      },
      {
        "id": "3000",
        "question": "Which term describes the competition between brothers and sisters?",
        "answer": "sibling rivalry",
        "distractor_1": "child development",
        "distractor_2": "the competitive edge",
        "distractor_3": "the child challenge"
      },
      {
        "id": "3002",
        "question": "Which stage in the family life cycle begins when the first child starts school?",
        "answer": "developing",
        "distractor_1": "expanding",
        "distractor_2": "launching",
        "distractor_3": "aging"
      },
      {
        "id": "3003",
        "question": "What type of family consists of a father, mother, and children?",
        "answer": "nuclear",
        "distractor_1": "extended",
        "distractor_2": "single-parent",
        "distractor_3": "blended"
      },
      {
        "id": "3008",
        "question": "If a family spends an average of $1,650 per year on food for a child, how much will be spent on food for that child from birth to age 18?",
        "answer": "$29,700",
        "distractor_1": "$22,300",
        "distractor_2": "$49,410",
        "distractor_3": "$13,200"
      },
      {
        "id": "3009",
        "question": "There are three ways to receive the roles you play in your family. You may choose them yourself, have them assigned to you, or which of the following?",
        "answer": "inherit them",
        "distractor_1": "get them from peer pressure",
        "distractor_2": "get them from socialization",
        "distractor_3": "buy them"
      },
      {
        "id": "3010",
        "question": "When a single parent marries, what type of family is formed?",
        "answer": "blended",
        "distractor_1": "nuclear",
        "distractor_2": "single-parent",
        "distractor_3": "extended"
      },
      {
        "id": "3011",
        "question": "When a couple marries, what type of family is formed?",
        "answer": "nuclear",
        "distractor_1": "blended",
        "distractor_2": "adopted",
        "distractor_3": "extended"
      },
      {
        "id": "6377",
        "question": "What are behaviors, beliefs, and traditions that are passed from one generation to the next?",
        "answer": "cultural heritage",
        "distractor_1": "inherited heritage",
        "distractor_2": "social heritage",
        "distractor_3": "generational heritage"
      },
      {
        "id": "6378",
        "question": "What is a family that includes parents, children, and other relatives such as grandparents, aunts, uncles, and cousins, all of whom sometimes live under the same roof?",
        "answer": "extended family",
        "distractor_1": "blended family",
        "distractor_2": "nuclear family",
        "distractor_3": "big family"
      },
      {
        "id": "6379",
        "question": "What is a group of people who grow up during the same time period?",
        "answer": "generation",
        "distractor_1": "cultural heritage",
        "distractor_2": "social heritage",
        "distractor_3": "unique heritage"
      },
      {
        "id": "6380",
        "question": "What are the things a person must have to be healthy, including food, water, clothing, shelter, and sleep?",
        "answer": "physical needs",
        "distractor_1": "emotional needs",
        "distractor_2": "social needs",
        "distractor_3": "psychological needs"
      },
      {
        "id": "6381",
        "question": "What is one's duty to account for actions of self and others?",
        "answer": "responsibility",
        "distractor_1": "physical needs",
        "distractor_2": "cultural heritage",
        "distractor_3": "generation"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "309",
    "name": "Flight Technology",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2634",
        "question": "Which of the following best describes the action of the elevator on the tail of an airplane?",
        "answer": "movable horizontal",
        "distractor_1": "movable vertical",
        "distractor_2": "stationary vertical",
        "distractor_3": "stationary horizontal"
      },
      {
        "id": "2635",
        "question": "An airplane accelerates or increases in speed when this force is greater than drag.",
        "answer": "thrust",
        "distractor_1": "weight",
        "distractor_2": "lift",
        "distractor_3": "gravity"
      },
      {
        "id": "2636",
        "question": "What is the main structure or body of an aircraft called?",
        "answer": "fuselage",
        "distractor_1": "aileron",
        "distractor_2": "cargo bay",
        "distractor_3": "empennage"
      },
      {
        "id": "2637",
        "question": "What is the force that enables airplanes to overcome gravity?",
        "answer": "lift",
        "distractor_1": "thrust",
        "distractor_2": "weight",
        "distractor_3": "drag"
      },
      {
        "id": "2639",
        "question": "For an airplane to achieve lift, what must the air pressure on the top surface of the wing be in relationship to the bottom surface of the wing?",
        "answer": "less than",
        "distractor_1": "equal",
        "distractor_2": "twice as much",
        "distractor_3": "greater than"
      },
      {
        "id": "2641",
        "question": "Who was the first man to break the sound barrier?",
        "answer": "Chuck Yeager",
        "distractor_1": "Sir George Cayley",
        "distractor_2": "John Glenn",
        "distractor_3": "Charles Lindbergh"
      },
      {
        "id": "2642",
        "question": "Four types of air navigation are used by pilots. They are pilotage, dead reckoning, celestial navigation, and radio navigation. Which one uses calculations of speed and time?",
        "answer": "dead reckoning",
        "distractor_1": "pilotage",
        "distractor_2": "celestial navigation",
        "distractor_3": "radio navigation"
      },
      {
        "id": "2644",
        "question": "Identify the term for a movable horizontal piece on the tail of an airplane.",
        "answer": "elevator",
        "distractor_1": "aileron",
        "distractor_2": "rudder",
        "distractor_3": "fuselage"
      },
      {
        "id": "2645",
        "question": "Several factors affect lift. Name the one factor having the greatest effect on the magnitude of lift.",
        "answer": "area",
        "distractor_1": "wing thickness",
        "distractor_2": "altitude",
        "distractor_3": "aileron"
      },
      {
        "id": "2646",
        "question": "According to Bernoulli's principle, if the speed of air moving over a wing increases, what happens to the internal pressure of that same air?",
        "answer": "decreases",
        "distractor_1": "stays the same",
        "distractor_2": "increases",
        "distractor_3": "quadruples"
      },
      {
        "id": "2648",
        "question": "What force is created when an object moves through a fluid like an aircraft moves through air?",
        "answer": "drag",
        "distractor_1": "acceleration",
        "distractor_2": "thrust",
        "distractor_3": "weight"
      },
      {
        "id": "2649",
        "question": "The wing of an airplane is also known as which one of the following terms?",
        "answer": "airfoil",
        "distractor_1": "aileron",
        "distractor_2": "elevator",
        "distractor_3": "stabilizer"
      },
      {
        "id": "2650",
        "question": "Which of the listed factors has the greatest effect on the magnitude of lift?",
        "answer": "area",
        "distractor_1": "wing thickness",
        "distractor_2": "altitude",
        "distractor_3": "aileron"
      },
      {
        "id": "2651",
        "question": "Which principle states that “as the velocity of a fluid increases, its internal pressure decreases?'",
        "answer": "Bernoulli's principle",
        "distractor_1": "Newton's principle",
        "distractor_2": "aerodynamic principle",
        "distractor_3": "relational fluids principle"
      },
      {
        "id": "2655",
        "question": "What are the movable portions, or control surfaces, on wings called?",
        "answer": "ailerons",
        "distractor_1": "rudders",
        "distractor_2": "elevators",
        "distractor_3": "lifts"
      },
      {
        "id": "2657",
        "question": "Because there is an equal and opposite reaction for every action, name the force that opposes thrust.",
        "answer": "drag",
        "distractor_1": "speed",
        "distractor_2": "lift",
        "distractor_3": "weight"
      },
      {
        "id": "2658",
        "question": "There are four forces that act upon a plane in flight. Identify the force that enables airplanes to overcome gravity.",
        "answer": "lift",
        "distractor_1": "drag",
        "distractor_2": "thrust",
        "distractor_3": "weight"
      },
      {
        "id": "2659",
        "question": "According to Newton's third law, for every action there is an equal and opposite reaction. Therefore, what is the force that opposes lift?",
        "answer": "weight",
        "distractor_1": "thrust",
        "distractor_2": "drag",
        "distractor_3": "speed"
      },
      {
        "id": "2661",
        "question": "An airplane accelerates or increases in speed when what force is greater than drag?",
        "answer": "thrust",
        "distractor_1": "gravity",
        "distractor_2": "weight",
        "distractor_3": "lift"
      },
      {
        "id": "6403",
        "question": "What is a height measurement from sea level on the Earth’s surface?",
        "answer": "Altitude",
        "distractor_1": "Latitude",
        "distractor_2": "Elevation",
        "distractor_3": "Distance"
      },
      {
        "id": "6404",
        "question": "What is an angular direction, used in navigation, from one point to another?",
        "answer": "Bearing",
        "distractor_1": "Drag",
        "distractor_2": "Equilibrium",
        "distractor_3": "Wind shear"
      },
      {
        "id": "6405",
        "question": "What is a state of balance or equality?",
        "answer": "Equilibrium",
        "distractor_1": "Heading",
        "distractor_2": "Bearing",
        "distractor_3": "Drag"
      },
      {
        "id": "6406",
        "question": "What is the direction in which an airplane is moving?",
        "answer": "Heading",
        "distractor_1": "Backing",
        "distractor_2": "Bearing",
        "distractor_3": "Drag"
      },
      {
        "id": "6407",
        "question": "What is an angular measurement of distance north or south of the equator?",
        "answer": "Latitude",
        "distractor_1": "Longitude",
        "distractor_2": "Heading ",
        "distractor_3": "Backing"
      },
      {
        "id": "6408",
        "question": "What is an angular measurement of distance east or west of an imaginary line that runs from the North Pole to the South Pole through Greenwich, England?",
        "answer": "Longitude",
        "distractor_1": "Latitude",
        "distractor_2": "Lift",
        "distractor_3": "Wind shear"
      },
      {
        "id": "6409",
        "question": "What is the speed of an airplane that is equal to the speed of sound?",
        "answer": "Mach 1",
        "distractor_1": "Mach 2",
        "distractor_2": "Speed of sound",
        "distractor_3": "Speed of light"
      },
      {
        "id": "6410",
        "question": "What is the speed of an airplane that is equal to twice the speed of sound?",
        "answer": "Mach 2",
        "distractor_1": "Mach 1",
        "distractor_2": "Speed of light",
        "distractor_3": "Speed of sound"
      },
      {
        "id": "6411",
        "question": "What is a movable, or controllable, surface on an airplane’s tail that causes the plane to turn?",
        "answer": "Rudder",
        "distractor_1": "Header",
        "distractor_2": "Lifter",
        "distractor_3": "Airfoil"
      },
      {
        "id": "6412",
        "question": "What is a very quick change in wind speed or direction?",
        "answer": "Wind shear",
        "distractor_1": "Wind current",
        "distractor_2": "Lift",
        "distractor_3": "Airfoil"
      },
      {
        "id": "8338",
        "question": "What term is used to describe the difference between the chord line of an airfoil and the relative wind?",
        "answer": "angle of attack",
        "distractor_1": "camber",
        "distractor_2": "elevator",
        "distractor_3": "aileron"
      },
      {
        "id": "8339",
        "question": "The angle of attack is the difference between which two lines?",
        "answer": "chord line of the airfoil and the relative wind",
        "distractor_1": "centerlines of the elevator and the stabilizer",
        "distractor_2": "centerlines of the aileron and rudder",
        "distractor_3": "centerlines of the fuselage and the stabilizer"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "310",
    "name": "Graphic Communications",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "3035",
        "question": "When does making a freehand sketch of an object occur during the design process?",
        "answer": "before making an instrument drawing",
        "distractor_1": "at the same time as making an instrument drawing",
        "distractor_2": "after making an instrument drawing",
        "distractor_3": "instead of making an instrument drawing"
      },
      {
        "id": "3036",
        "question": "A draftsperson uses a triangle to make what kinds of lines and angles?",
        "answer": "vertical",
        "distractor_1": "horizontal",
        "distractor_2": "thin",
        "distractor_3": "thick"
      },
      {
        "id": "3037",
        "question": "What is a plotter?",
        "answer": "device that produces high quality drawings from a CAD system",
        "distractor_1": "person who surveys land",
        "distractor_2": "big piece of paper that keeps your desk from getting marked up",
        "distractor_3": "photocopy machine"
      },
      {
        "id": "3039",
        "question": "Which piece of drafting equipment consists of the blade and the head?",
        "answer": "T square",
        "distractor_1": "knife",
        "distractor_2": "edge",
        "distractor_3": "arm"
      },
      {
        "id": "3040",
        "question": "Which drawing provides the most realistic picture of objects?",
        "answer": "pictorial",
        "distractor_1": "realistic",
        "distractor_2": "orthographic projection",
        "distractor_3": "auxiliary"
      },
      {
        "id": "3041",
        "question": "What is the language of industry called?",
        "answer": "drafting",
        "distractor_1": "Spanish",
        "distractor_2": "English",
        "distractor_3": "sketching"
      },
      {
        "id": "3043",
        "question": "Which of the lines displayed is an example of a hidden line?",
        "answer": "- - - - - -",
        "distractor_1": "_______",
        "distractor_2": "____ _ ____",
        "distractor_3": "========="
      },
      {
        "id": "3046",
        "question": "What is the sum of the three angles inside any triangle?",
        "answer": "180°",
        "distractor_1": "90°",
        "distractor_2": "240°",
        "distractor_3": "360°"
      },
      {
        "id": "3047",
        "question": "What is the first step in making an instrument drawing?",
        "answer": "freehand sketch",
        "distractor_1": "blueprint",
        "distractor_2": "negative",
        "distractor_3": "bar graph"
      },
      {
        "id": "3048",
        "question": "What term is defined as the equipment that produces your drawing when using a computer-aided drafting system?",
        "answer": "plotter",
        "distractor_1": "Image Writer II",
        "distractor_2": "drafting machine",
        "distractor_3": "micro"
      },
      {
        "id": "3049",
        "question": "What are object lines used to show?",
        "answer": "the outline of an object",
        "distractor_1": "hidden details of an object",
        "distractor_2": "the dimensions of an object",
        "distractor_3": "where an object should be"
      },
      {
        "id": "3050",
        "question": "What is drafting?",
        "answer": "communicating an idea by sketching or drawing",
        "distractor_1": "creating a prototype",
        "distractor_2": "using grids to represent numbers",
        "distractor_3": "how computers communicate with machines"
      },
      {
        "id": "3052",
        "question": "How many sides does a cube have?",
        "answer": "6",
        "distractor_1": "3",
        "distractor_2": "4",
        "distractor_3": "8"
      },
      {
        "id": "3053",
        "question": "What are the most common views on a multiview drawing?",
        "answer": "front, top, right side",
        "distractor_1": "front, top, left side",
        "distractor_2": "front, bottom, top",
        "distractor_3": "rear, bottom, top"
      },
      {
        "id": "3054",
        "question": "A T square consists of which two parts?",
        "answer": "head and blade",
        "distractor_1": "head and knife",
        "distractor_2": "edge and blade",
        "distractor_3": "arm and head"
      },
      {
        "id": "3055",
        "question": "What is another term for drafting?",
        "answer": "the language of industry",
        "distractor_1": "a computer language",
        "distractor_2": "a sign language",
        "distractor_3": "the blueprint language"
      },
      {
        "id": "3057",
        "question": "What are the most common views on a multiview drawing?",
        "answer": "front, top, right side",
        "distractor_1": "front, bottom, top",
        "distractor_2": "front, top, left side",
        "distractor_3": "rear, bottom, top"
      },
      {
        "id": "3058",
        "question": "What term is defined as lines used to show the outline of an object?",
        "answer": "object lines",
        "distractor_1": "hidden lines",
        "distractor_2": "border lines",
        "distractor_3": "outlines"
      },
      {
        "id": "3060",
        "question": "What term is defined as a tool that is used in drafting to make vertical lines and angles?",
        "answer": "triangle",
        "distractor_1": "ruler",
        "distractor_2": "angler",
        "distractor_3": "square"
      },
      {
        "id": "3062",
        "question": "What term is defined as drawing an idea on paper in the form of a picture (graphic)?",
        "answer": "drafting",
        "distractor_1": "floor plan",
        "distractor_2": "detailing",
        "distractor_3": "blueprint"
      },
      {
        "id": "6451",
        "question": "What type of drawing of an object shows multiview drawings?",
        "answer": "isometric drawing",
        "distractor_1": "oblique drawing",
        "distractor_2": "myriad drawing",
        "distractor_3": "crystallographic drawing"
      },
      {
        "id": "6452",
        "question": "Which of these is multiview drawing, usually containing the top, front, and right-side views?",
        "answer": "orthographic projection",
        "distractor_1": "oblique drawing",
        "distractor_2": "myriad drawing",
        "distractor_3": "multitudinous drawing"
      },
      {
        "id": "6453",
        "question": "What type of lines never intersect?",
        "answer": "parallel",
        "distractor_1": "perpendicular",
        "distractor_2": "vertical",
        "distractor_3": "horizontal"
      },
      {
        "id": "6454",
        "question": "What type of lines intersect at right, or 90-degree, angles?",
        "answer": "perpendicular",
        "distractor_1": "parallel",
        "distractor_2": "horizontal",
        "distractor_3": "vertical"
      },
      {
        "id": "6455",
        "question": "What is a polygon of eight angles and eight sides?",
        "answer": "octagon",
        "distractor_1": "oxagon",
        "distractor_2": "hexagon",
        "distractor_3": "trapezoid"
      },
      {
        "id": "6456",
        "question": "What triangle has three sides  of equal length and angles?",
        "answer": "equilateral ",
        "distractor_1": "isosceles ",
        "distractor_2": "scalene ",
        "distractor_3": "right "
      },
      {
        "id": "6457",
        "question": "What is the distance of a straight line from any point on a circle to the center of the circle?",
        "answer": "radius",
        "distractor_1": "ratio",
        "distractor_2": "diameter",
        "distractor_3": "dimension"
      },
      {
        "id": "6458",
        "question": "What type of lines run up and down?",
        "answer": "vertical",
        "distractor_1": "horizontal",
        "distractor_2": "parallel",
        "distractor_3": "perpendicular"
      },
      {
        "id": "6446",
        "question": "What is the figure formed by two lines coming together at a point?",
        "answer": "angle",
        "distractor_1": "corner",
        "distractor_2": "dimension",
        "distractor_3": "perpendicular lines"
      },
      {
        "id": "6447",
        "question": "What type of pictorial drawing is characterized by a vertical axis and a horizontal axis for the two dimensions of the front face?",
        "answer": "oblique drawing",
        "distractor_1": "isometric drawing",
        "distractor_2": "orthographic drawing",
        "distractor_3": "axis drawing"
      },
      {
        "id": "6448",
        "question": "What is the length of a straight line that passes through the center of a circle and touches two points on the circle?",
        "answer": "diameter",
        "distractor_1": "radius",
        "distractor_2": "dimension",
        "distractor_3": "measurement"
      },
      {
        "id": "6449",
        "question": "What term is used to describe the size of a geometrical feature of an object?",
        "answer": "dimension",
        "distractor_1": "diameter",
        "distractor_2": "radius",
        "distractor_3": "angle"
      },
      {
        "id": "6450",
        "question": "What type of lines run from side to side?",
        "answer": "horizontal",
        "distractor_1": "perpendicular",
        "distractor_2": "parallel",
        "distractor_3": "vertical"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "304",
    "name": "Immune System",
    "weight": "90",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1452",
        "question": "What is an injection or pill that helps the body fight future disease by stimulating production of antibodies?",
        "answer": "vaccine",
        "distractor_1": "antibiotic",
        "distractor_2": "toxin",
        "distractor_3": "allergen"
      },
      {
        "id": "1455",
        "question": "A typical bacterium is about one micrometer (1 µ) or one one-thousandth of a millimeter (.001 mm) long. If a bacterium is magnified by 400X, how large (in mm) will it appear under the microscope?",
        "answer": "0.4 mm",
        "distractor_1": "4 mm",
        "distractor_2": "40 mm",
        "distractor_3": "400 mm"
      },
      {
        "id": "1456",
        "question": "What is the major function of the lymph nodes?",
        "answer": "to filter and destroy pathogens",
        "distractor_1": "to secrete antibodies",
        "distractor_2": "to produce stem cells",
        "distractor_3": "to produce T cells"
      },
      {
        "id": "1458",
        "question": "When an antibiotic is unable to cure a bacterial infection that it could cure in the past, this condition is called what?",
        "answer": "antibiotic resistance",
        "distractor_1": "antibiotic immunity",
        "distractor_2": "autoimmune disease",
        "distractor_3": "communicable disease"
      },
      {
        "id": "1459",
        "question": "Which of the following are clumps of tissue containing white blood cells that filter and destroy pathogens?",
        "answer": "lymph nodes",
        "distractor_1": "leukocytes",
        "distractor_2": "thymus cells",
        "distractor_3": "stem cells"
      },
      {
        "id": "1460",
        "question": "Lyme disease is spread by the tiny deer tick. What kind of microorganism causes the disease?",
        "answer": "bacterium",
        "distractor_1": "virus",
        "distractor_2": "protozoan",
        "distractor_3": "fungus"
      },
      {
        "id": "1461",
        "question": "Before birth, antibodies from the mother pass into the baby, protecting the baby for the first few months of life. What is this type of immunity called?",
        "answer": "passive immunity",
        "distractor_1": "active immunity",
        "distractor_2": "acquired immunity",
        "distractor_3": "maternal immunity"
      },
      {
        "id": "1463",
        "question": "Tears, saliva, and stomach acid are included in which of the body's systems of defense?",
        "answer": "nonspecific immunity",
        "distractor_1": "specific immunity",
        "distractor_2": "acquired immunity",
        "distractor_3": "active immunity"
      },
      {
        "id": "1465",
        "question": "HIV attacks the body's immune system by destroying what kind of cells?",
        "answer": "helper T cells",
        "distractor_1": "neutrophils",
        "distractor_2": "B cells",
        "distractor_3": "killer T cells"
      },
      {
        "id": "1466",
        "question": "Who was the scientist who developed the process for determining the causative agent of a disease?",
        "answer": "Robert Koch",
        "distractor_1": "Louis Pasteur",
        "distractor_2": "Edward Jenner",
        "distractor_3": "Albert Sabin"
      },
      {
        "id": "1467",
        "question": "What type of disease can be spread from person to person?",
        "answer": "communicable",
        "distractor_1": "autoimmune",
        "distractor_2": "deficiency",
        "distractor_3": "genetic"
      },
      {
        "id": "1471",
        "question": "The body is able to resist a specific disease by producing which of the following?",
        "answer": "antibodies",
        "distractor_1": "tears and saliva",
        "distractor_2": "macrophages",
        "distractor_3": "antigens"
      },
      {
        "id": "1472",
        "question": "Heat, redness, swelling, and pain are the four indicators of which process?",
        "answer": "the inflammation response",
        "distractor_1": "phagocytosis",
        "distractor_2": "a viral infection",
        "distractor_3": "a specific immune response"
      },
      {
        "id": "1473",
        "question": "In the Irish potato famine of 1845-1846, the potato crop was destroyed by which kind of microorganism?",
        "answer": "fungus-like protist",
        "distractor_1": "bacterium",
        "distractor_2": "virus",
        "distractor_3": "fungus"
      },
      {
        "id": "1474",
        "question": "What is the special class of proteins to which antibodies belong?",
        "answer": "immunoglobulins",
        "distractor_1": "antibiotics",
        "distractor_2": "enzymes",
        "distractor_3": "cytokines"
      },
      {
        "id": "8138",
        "question": "A bacterium has a generation time of 20 minutes. That is, it reproduces and the number of bacteria doubles every 20 minutes. If you start with one bacterium, how many bacteria will be present in a colony after 5 hours?",
        "answer": "32,768",
        "distractor_1": "1,024",
        "distractor_2": "16,384",
        "distractor_3": "8,192"
      },
      {
        "id": "8139",
        "question": "Which of the following types of pathogens are too small to be seen with a typical light microscope?",
        "answer": "viruses",
        "distractor_1": "fungi",
        "distractor_2": "bacteria",
        "distractor_3": "protozoans"
      },
      {
        "id": "8140",
        "question": "What type of disease is caused by an organism that enters the body and reproduces?",
        "answer": "infectious",
        "distractor_1": "genetic",
        "distractor_2": "autoimmune",
        "distractor_3": "deficiency"
      },
      {
        "id": "6641",
        "question": "In what type of disease does the immune system malfunction and fail to protect the person from infections?",
        "answer": "immunodeficiency disease",
        "distractor_1": "immunodefiant disease",
        "distractor_2": "immunosuppressant disease",
        "distractor_3": "immunity disease"
      },
      {
        "id": "6642",
        "question": "What substance kills bacteria or inhibits their growth?",
        "answer": "antibiotic",
        "distractor_1": "antigen",
        "distractor_2": "vaccine",
        "distractor_3": "bacterial suppressant"
      },
      {
        "id": "6643",
        "question": "What is a condition caused by an organism entering the body and reproducing?",
        "answer": "infection",
        "distractor_1": "infestation",
        "distractor_2": "epidemic",
        "distractor_3": "pandemic"
      },
      {
        "id": "6644",
        "question": "What is the ability to resist infectious disease?",
        "answer": "immunity",
        "distractor_1": "vaccine",
        "distractor_2": "antibody",
        "distractor_3": "immunoresistance"
      },
      {
        "id": "6645",
        "question": "What substance or particle causes an immune response?",
        "answer": "antigen",
        "distractor_1": "antibody",
        "distractor_2": "antibiotic",
        "distractor_3": "immune system"
      },
      {
        "id": "6646",
        "question": "What protein binds to a specific antigen and helps destroy it?",
        "answer": "antibody",
        "distractor_1": "antigen",
        "distractor_2": "antibiotic",
        "distractor_3": "T cell"
      },
      {
        "id": "6647",
        "question": "What term describes the spread of an infectious disease over a large geographical area, such as a state or country?",
        "answer": "epidemic",
        "distractor_1": "pandemic",
        "distractor_2": "communicable",
        "distractor_3": "community infection"
      },
      {
        "id": "6648",
        "question": "What is a disease-causing organism or agent, such as a bacterium or virus?",
        "answer": "pathogen",
        "distractor_1": "infection",
        "distractor_2": "leukocyte",
        "distractor_3": "parasite"
      },
      {
        "id": "6649",
        "question": "What is a hypersensitive immune response to a typically harmless environmental agent?",
        "answer": "allergy",
        "distractor_1": "immunodeficiency",
        "distractor_2": "infection",
        "distractor_3": "epidemic"
      },
      {
        "id": "6650",
        "question": "What is a general term for white blood cells, the cells that are responsible for immunity?",
        "answer": "leukocyte",
        "distractor_1": "B cell",
        "distractor_2": "T cell",
        "distractor_3": "antibody"
      },
      {
        "id": "6651",
        "question": "What term describes the spread of an infectious disease around the world?",
        "answer": "pandemic",
        "distractor_1": "epidemic",
        "distractor_2": "pathogen",
        "distractor_3": "communicable disease"
      },
      {
        "id": "6652",
        "question": "What type of leukocyte produces antibodies?",
        "answer": "B cell",
        "distractor_1": "antigen",
        "distractor_2": "T cell",
        "distractor_3": "prokocyte"
      },
      {
        "id": "6653",
        "question": "What type of leukocyte matures into several cell types with important immune functions?",
        "answer": "T cell",
        "distractor_1": "B cell",
        "distractor_2": "antibody",
        "distractor_3": "antigen"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "311",
    "name": "Plants & Pollination",
    "weight": "90",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "4275",
        "question": "There are about 285,000 species of flowering plants. This represents about 66 percent of all species of plants. About how many species of plants exist?",
        "answer": "432,000",
        "distractor_1": "185,000",
        "distractor_2": "356,000",
        "distractor_3": "512,000"
      },
      {
        "id": "4276",
        "question": "Which group of characteristics describes the angiosperm group of plants?",
        "answer": "seed-bearing, vascular, flowering",
        "distractor_1": "seed-bearing, vascular, cone-bearing",
        "distractor_2": "seedless, non-vascular, flowering",
        "distractor_3": "seedless, vascular, cone-bearing"
      },
      {
        "id": "4277",
        "question": "Which group of animals pollinates the largest percentage of plants on Earth?",
        "answer": "bees",
        "distractor_1": "butterflies",
        "distractor_2": "birds",
        "distractor_3": "bats"
      },
      {
        "id": "4278",
        "question": "Over 80 percent of our food crops rely on pollination by which method?",
        "answer": "animals",
        "distractor_1": "wind",
        "distractor_2": "water",
        "distractor_3": "self-pollination"
      },
      {
        "id": "4279",
        "question": "What is the name of the group within the plant kingdom that is composed of flowering plants?",
        "answer": "angiosperms",
        "distractor_1": "gymnosperms",
        "distractor_2": "seedless vascular plants",
        "distractor_3": "fungi"
      },
      {
        "id": "4280",
        "question": "What are the two products of  photosynthesis?",
        "answer": "glucose and oxygen",
        "distractor_1": "carbon dioxide and water",
        "distractor_2": "starch and water",
        "distractor_3": "oxygen and carbon dioxide"
      },
      {
        "id": "4290",
        "question": "Scientists estimate that there are 80,000 kinds of edible plants on the Earth. Today, only about 150 are widely raised by people. What percentage of all edible plants are raised by people?",
        "answer": "0.1875%",
        "distractor_1": "1.875%",
        "distractor_2": "18.75%",
        "distractor_3": " 5.33%"
      },
      {
        "id": "4291",
        "question": "In what part of the plant leaf does most photosynthesis occur?",
        "answer": "palisade parenchyma",
        "distractor_1": "epidermis",
        "distractor_2": "air spaces",
        "distractor_3": "spongy parenchyma"
      },
      {
        "id": "4292",
        "question": "On a hot, sunny day, what is the likely condition of most stomata on a leaf?",
        "answer": "closed, to prevent water loss by evaporation",
        "distractor_1": "open, to take in as much carbon dioxide as possible",
        "distractor_2": "open, to take in as much sunlight as possible",
        "distractor_3": "closed, to prevent the plant from getting too hot"
      },
      {
        "id": "4293",
        "question": "Which process occurs immediately after the pollen grain reaches the anther and grows a pollen tube?",
        "answer": "fertilization",
        "distractor_1": "transpiration",
        "distractor_2": "germination",
        "distractor_3": "respiration"
      },
      {
        "id": "4294",
        "question": "During photosynthesis, plants produce glucose, or simple sugar. Within which cell structure does photosynthesis occur?",
        "answer": "chloroplasts",
        "distractor_1": "xylem",
        "distractor_2": "phloem",
        "distractor_3": "stomata"
      },
      {
        "id": "4295",
        "question": "In what part of the plant does most photosynthesis occur?",
        "answer": "leaf",
        "distractor_1": "flower",
        "distractor_2": "tuber",
        "distractor_3": "fruit"
      },
      {
        "id": "4296",
        "question": "Which term describes the transfer of a pollen grain from the anther of one flower to the stigma of another?",
        "answer": "pollination",
        "distractor_1": "transpiration",
        "distractor_2": "fertilization",
        "distractor_3": "respiration"
      },
      {
        "id": "4297",
        "question": "Egg and sperm cells are formed during which stage of a plant's life cycle?",
        "answer": "gametophyte",
        "distractor_1": "sporophyte",
        "distractor_2": "zygophyte",
        "distractor_3": "epiphyte"
      },
      {
        "id": "4298",
        "question": "Why are root hairs important to a plant?",
        "answer": "They absorb water and dissolved minerals.",
        "distractor_1": "They are the major areas of plant growth.",
        "distractor_2": "They prevent water loss from the plant.",
        "distractor_3": "They are storage areas for excess plant sugars."
      },
      {
        "id": "4299",
        "question": "What two plant cell structures are most responsible for plant structure and support?",
        "answer": "cell wall and central vacuole",
        "distractor_1": "cell membrane and nucleus",
        "distractor_2": "nucleus and chloroplast",
        "distractor_3": "cell wall and cell membrane"
      },
      {
        "id": "4300",
        "question": "Which structures of a plant absorb water and dissolved minerals?",
        "answer": "root hairs",
        "distractor_1": "stomata",
        "distractor_2": "stamens",
        "distractor_3": "carpels"
      },
      {
        "id": "4301",
        "question": "Plants produced by which form of reproduction are genetically different from the parent generation?",
        "answer": "cross-pollination",
        "distractor_1": "runners",
        "distractor_2": "cuttings",
        "distractor_3": "self-pollination"
      },
      {
        "id": "4302",
        "question": "About 90 percent of the water a plant receives is lost through transpiration. If a plant receives 10 ounces of water, how many ounces does it lose through transpiration?",
        "answer": " 9 ounces ",
        "distractor_1": "11 ounces",
        "distractor_2": " 0.9 ounces",
        "distractor_3": "1.1 ounces"
      },
      {
        "id": "8103",
        "question": "The wild grasses known as 'emmer' and 'spelt' are probably ancestors of what important food crop grown today?",
        "answer": "wheat",
        "distractor_1": "corn",
        "distractor_2": "soybeans",
        "distractor_3": "rye"
      },
      {
        "id": "4281",
        "question": "During the process of transpiration, which cell structure closes to help the plant retain water?",
        "answer": "stomata",
        "distractor_1": "chloroplasts",
        "distractor_2": "phloem",
        "distractor_3": "xylem"
      },
      {
        "id": "4282",
        "question": "Before photosynthesis can occur, a plant must have energy from sunlight and which two substances?",
        "answer": "carbon dioxide and water",
        "distractor_1": "oxygen and water",
        "distractor_2": "glucose and oxygen",
        "distractor_3": "starch and carbon dioxide"
      },
      {
        "id": "4283",
        "question": "What is the major advantage of cross-pollination over self-pollination?",
        "answer": "Cross-pollination leads to variation in offspring.",
        "distractor_1": "Cross-pollination is more likely to occur.",
        "distractor_2": "Cross-pollination is more efficient.",
        "distractor_3": "Only cross-pollination can be done by animals."
      },
      {
        "id": "4284",
        "question": "When a haploid egg and a haploid sperm cell combine in the plant ovary, they form which of the following?",
        "answer": "a diploid zygote",
        "distractor_1": "a haploid zygote",
        "distractor_2": "a monocot",
        "distractor_3": "a dicot"
      },
      {
        "id": "4285",
        "question": "What are two cell structures found in plant cells but not in animal cells?",
        "answer": "cell wall and central vacuole",
        "distractor_1": "cell wall and cell membrane",
        "distractor_2": "cell membrane and nucleus",
        "distractor_3": "nucleus and chloroplast"
      },
      {
        "id": "4286",
        "question": "Which type of plant cells open and close the stomata to adjust the flow of air and water into and out of the plant?",
        "answer": "guard cells",
        "distractor_1": "chloroplasts",
        "distractor_2": "xylem cells",
        "distractor_3": "phloem cells"
      },
      {
        "id": "4287",
        "question": "Which two types of plant cells are haploid, or contain only one set of chromosomes?",
        "answer": "egg and sperm",
        "distractor_1": "monocot and dicot",
        "distractor_2": "stamen and carpel",
        "distractor_3": "zygote and pollen grain"
      },
      {
        "id": "6570",
        "question": "What is the name of a male reproductive structure composed of anther and filament?",
        "answer": "Stamen",
        "distractor_1": "Dicot",
        "distractor_2": "stoma",
        "distractor_3": "Phloem"
      },
      {
        "id": "6571",
        "question": "What is green plant pigment that captures energy from sunlight?",
        "answer": "Chlorophyll",
        "distractor_1": "Dicot",
        "distractor_2": "Monocot",
        "distractor_3": "Photosynthesis"
      },
      {
        "id": "6573",
        "question": "What is a type of plant having two cotyledons, or seed leaves?",
        "answer": "Dicot",
        "distractor_1": "Monocot",
        "distractor_2": "Carpel",
        "distractor_3": "Tropism"
      },
      {
        "id": "6574",
        "question": "What is a process by which a seed begins to grow?",
        "answer": "Germination",
        "distractor_1": "Photosynthesis",
        "distractor_2": "Transpiration",
        "distractor_3": "Tropism"
      },
      {
        "id": "6575",
        "question": "What is a structure formed from ovary that encloses one or more seeds?",
        "answer": "Fruit",
        "distractor_1": "Nuts",
        "distractor_2": "Stoma",
        "distractor_3": "Xylem"
      },
      {
        "id": "6576",
        "question": "What is a type of plant having one cotyledon, or seed leaf?",
        "answer": "Monocot",
        "distractor_1": "Dicot",
        "distractor_2": "Stoma",
        "distractor_3": "Carpel"
      },
      {
        "id": "6578",
        "question": "What is a female reproductive structure that produces egg cells?",
        "answer": "Ovary",
        "distractor_1": "Testes",
        "distractor_2": "Uterus",
        "distractor_3": "Stoma"
      },
      {
        "id": "6579",
        "question": "What is a chemical process by which plants make food using carbon dioxide, water and energy from sunlight?",
        "answer": "Photosynthesis",
        "distractor_1": "Germination",
        "distractor_2": "Pollination",
        "distractor_3": "Transpiration"
      },
      {
        "id": "6581",
        "question": "What is the female reproductive organ composed of ovary, style, and stigma?",
        "answer": "Carpel",
        "distractor_1": "Stoma",
        "distractor_2": "Xylem",
        "distractor_3": "Phloem"
      },
      {
        "id": "6582",
        "question": "What is the tiny opening on the leaf epidermis that enables gases and water to move into and out of the plant?",
        "answer": "Stoma",
        "distractor_1": "Dicot",
        "distractor_2": "Stamen",
        "distractor_3": "Carpel"
      },
      {
        "id": "6584",
        "question": "What is the process by which plants release water into the air?",
        "answer": "Transpiration",
        "distractor_1": "Germination",
        "distractor_2": "Pollination",
        "distractor_3": "Photosynthesis"
      },
      {
        "id": "6585",
        "question": "What is a plant response to a stimulus, in which plant grows toward or away from the stimulus?",
        "answer": "Tropism",
        "distractor_1": "Carpel",
        "distractor_2": "Fruit",
        "distractor_3": "Germination"
      },
      {
        "id": "6587",
        "question": "What is the tube-like tissue that supports the plant and transports water and dissolved minerals up the plant stem?",
        "answer": "Xylem",
        "distractor_1": "Phloem",
        "distractor_2": "Carpel",
        "distractor_3": "Stoma"
      },
      {
        "id": "6588",
        "question": "What is the thin tube-like tissue that transports sugars produced in the leaves down to all plant cells?",
        "answer": "Phloem",
        "distractor_1": "Xylem",
        "distractor_2": "Ovary",
        "distractor_3": "Monocot"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "312",
    "name": "Breakfast Nutrition",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2118",
        "question": "Natural, whole-grain cereals are a good source of what?",
        "answer": "fiber",
        "distractor_1": "fat",
        "distractor_2": "sodium",
        "distractor_3": "cholesterol"
      },
      {
        "id": "2119",
        "question": "What causes processed foods to lose some of their nutritional value?",
        "answer": "freezing, canning, or packaging",
        "distractor_1": "cooking in oil",
        "distractor_2": "using fresh items",
        "distractor_3": "mixing with other foods"
      },
      {
        "id": "2139",
        "question": "What fraction of a teaspoon is equal to one pinch?",
        "answer": "1/16 teaspoon",
        "distractor_1": "1/8 teaspoon",
        "distractor_2": "1/4 teaspoon",
        "distractor_3": "1/2 teaspoon"
      },
      {
        "id": "2140",
        "question": "How do you poach an egg?",
        "answer": "Cook it in boiling water.",
        "distractor_1": "Cook it in fat.",
        "distractor_2": "Cook it with dry heat.",
        "distractor_3": "Cook it over a gas flame."
      },
      {
        "id": "2143",
        "question": "What causes processed foods to lose some of their nutritional value?",
        "answer": "They are frozen, canned, or packaged.",
        "distractor_1": "They are cooked in oil.",
        "distractor_2": "They are prepared fresh.",
        "distractor_3": "They are mixed with other foods."
      },
      {
        "id": "2120",
        "question": "What gives a person most of his or her energy?",
        "answer": "carbohydrates",
        "distractor_1": "fats",
        "distractor_2": "sugars",
        "distractor_3": "proteins"
      },
      {
        "id": "2121",
        "question": "About how many different nutrients are in one glass of milk?",
        "answer": "100",
        "distractor_1": "25",
        "distractor_2": "200",
        "distractor_3": "10"
      },
      {
        "id": "2122",
        "question": "What part of a person's daily nutritional needs should be supplied by breakfast?",
        "answer": "one-fourth",
        "distractor_1": "one-third",
        "distractor_2": "one-half",
        "distractor_3": "one-eighth"
      },
      {
        "id": "2126",
        "question": "What does it mean when a breakfast cereal has been fortified?",
        "answer": "It has added nutrients.",
        "distractor_1": "It becomes tougher to chew.",
        "distractor_2": "It is sugar coated.",
        "distractor_3": "It stays crispier longer."
      },
      {
        "id": "2127",
        "question": "Your only measuring tool is a tablespoon, and a recipe calls for one-fourth cup of an ingredient. How many tablespoons of the ingredient would you need?",
        "answer": "4",
        "distractor_1": "6",
        "distractor_2": "8",
        "distractor_3": "10"
      },
      {
        "id": "2128",
        "question": "How many ounces equal 3/4 cup of juice? (8 ounces = 1 cup)",
        "answer": "6",
        "distractor_1": "4",
        "distractor_2": "10",
        "distractor_3": "12"
      },
      {
        "id": "2129",
        "question": "Fat-soluble vitamins dissolve in fat rather than water. Without some fat, the body could not use these vitamins. What are the fat-soluble vitamins?",
        "answer": "A, D, E, and K",
        "distractor_1": "A, B, C, and E",
        "distractor_2": "B, C, D, and K",
        "distractor_3": "A, B, C, and K"
      },
      {
        "id": "2131",
        "question": "From what does a person get most of his or her energy?",
        "answer": "carbohydrates",
        "distractor_1": "protein",
        "distractor_2": "fat",
        "distractor_3": "sugar"
      },
      {
        "id": "2132",
        "question": "A fast-food breakfast made up of a biscuit, sausage, and an egg supplies a whole day's amount of what?",
        "answer": "fat and cholesterol",
        "distractor_1": "protein and fiber",
        "distractor_2": "sugar and carbohydrates",
        "distractor_3": "vitamins and minerals"
      },
      {
        "id": "2135",
        "question": "Which of the following foods is low in cholesterol?",
        "answer": "fruits and vegetables",
        "distractor_1": "eggs and cheese",
        "distractor_2": "liver and onions",
        "distractor_3": "shrimp"
      },
      {
        "id": "2137",
        "question": "If the following breakfasts contain 8, 14, 20, and 33 grams of fat, which do you think contains the least fat?",
        "answer": "frosted flakes, whole milk, one banana",
        "distractor_1": "one glazed donut",
        "distractor_2": "two eggs, two slices of bacon",
        "distractor_3": "one biscuit, one egg, one sausage"
      },
      {
        "id": "5544",
        "question": "This term is defined as a carbohydrate that cannot be digested by humans but is necessary to cause the muscles of the digestive system to contract.",
        "answer": "fiber",
        "distractor_1": "starch",
        "distractor_2": "grain",
        "distractor_3": "protein"
      },
      {
        "id": "5545",
        "question": "This term is defined as the process of adding nutrients to food.",
        "answer": "fortified",
        "distractor_1": "ionized",
        "distractor_2": "beautified",
        "distractor_3": "pasteurized"
      },
      {
        "id": "5546",
        "question": "This term is defined as a method of cooking food by lowering it into a pot of boiling water.",
        "answer": "poach",
        "distractor_1": "boil",
        "distractor_2": "steam",
        "distractor_3": "fry"
      },
      {
        "id": "5547",
        "question": "This term is defined as a nutrient containing amino acids; found primarily in meat and nut products and helps the body's muscles strengthen.",
        "answer": "protein",
        "distractor_1": "carbohydrate",
        "distractor_2": "fat",
        "distractor_3": "vitamin"
      },
      {
        "id": "5548",
        "question": "This term is defined as a naturally occurring compound that is necessary for the body to function.",
        "answer": "vitamin",
        "distractor_1": "calorie",
        "distractor_2": "protein",
        "distractor_3": "fat"
      },
      {
        "id": "5549",
        "question": "This term is defined as foods that contain the entire grain kernel.",
        "answer": "whole grain",
        "distractor_1": "synthetic",
        "distractor_2": "micronutrient",
        "distractor_3": "KFC"
      },
      {
        "id": "5550",
        "question": "This term is defined as the measurement of the amount of energy given to the body in the food that is eaten.",
        "answer": "calorie",
        "distractor_1": "speed",
        "distractor_2": "cholesterol",
        "distractor_3": "Recommended Dietary Allowance"
      },
      {
        "id": "8329",
        "question": "This term is defined as any of the inorganic elements that are essential to the functioning of the human body; obtained from food; needed to build strong bones and soft tissue; and needed to regulate body processes.",
        "answer": "minerals",
        "distractor_1": "vitamins",
        "distractor_2": "proteins",
        "distractor_3": "calories"
      },
      {
        "id": "8330",
        "question": "This term is defined as any of a variety of aromatic vegetable substances, such as ginger, cinnamon, or nutmeg, that is used as flavourings.",
        "answer": "spice",
        "distractor_1": "extra",
        "distractor_2": "sugar",
        "distractor_3": "gusto"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "313",
    "name": "Heart Fitness",
    "weight": "75",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "4167",
        "question": "What is the best definition of heart fitness?",
        "answer": "Heart rapidly adjusts to daily changes.",
        "distractor_1": "Heart rate never varies from normal range.",
        "distractor_2": "Heart has minimal scar tissue after a heart attack.",
        "distractor_3": "Heart remains functional without daily exercise."
      },
      {
        "id": "4168",
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT an aerobic exercise that would strengthen your heart?",
        "answer": "stretching",
        "distractor_1": "jogging",
        "distractor_2": "swimming",
        "distractor_3": "bicycling"
      },
      {
        "id": "4169",
        "question": "Linda checks her heart rate and counts 18 beats in 15 seconds. What is Linda's heart rate?",
        "answer": "72 beats per minute",
        "distractor_1": "270 beats per minute",
        "distractor_2": "36 beats per minute",
        "distractor_3": "120 beats per minute"
      },
      {
        "id": "4170",
        "question": "What is the process by which materials are exchanged between the blood and body cells?",
        "answer": "diffusion",
        "distractor_1": "osmosis",
        "distractor_2": "circulation",
        "distractor_3": "cellular transfer"
      },
      {
        "id": "4171",
        "question": "As a healthy adult male, about 10 to 15 percent of Jim's body weight should be fat. If Jim weighs 185 pounds, how many pounds of his body weight should be fat?",
        "answer": "18.50 to 27.75 pounds",
        "distractor_1": "27.90 to 28.30 pounds",
        "distractor_2": "28.00 to 36.85 pounds",
        "distractor_3": "37.50 to 44.80 pounds"
      },
      {
        "id": "4172",
        "question": "Which three lifestyle changes would best help a person maintain cardiovascular fitness?",
        "answer": "increase exercise, decrease dietary fat, stop smoking",
        "distractor_1": "increase exercise, decrease dietary carbohydrates, stop smoking",
        "distractor_2": "decrease exercise, decrease dietary fat, stop drinking alcohol",
        "distractor_3": "decrease exercise, decrease dietary carbohydrates, stop smoking"
      },
      {
        "id": "4173",
        "question": "How does your cardiovascular system respond to an aerobic exercise program?",
        "answer": "Heart strength increases and resting pulse rate decreases.",
        "distractor_1": "Heart strength decreases and resting pulse rate increases.",
        "distractor_2": "Heart becomes more efficient and more compact in size.",
        "distractor_3": "Heart begins to tire more easily, increasing recovery time."
      },
      {
        "id": "4174",
        "question": "Combined with increased physical activity, which of the following factors would best help you control body weight?",
        "answer": "decrease total Calories",
        "distractor_1": "keep total Calories the same",
        "distractor_2": "limit only daily carbohydrate levels",
        "distractor_3": "limit only daily fat levels"
      },
      {
        "id": "4175",
        "question": "What is the condition in which fatty deposits called plaque accumulate on artery walls, decreasing their diameter and raising blood pressure?",
        "answer": "atherosclerosis",
        "distractor_1": "arteriosclerosis",
        "distractor_2": "high blood cholesterol",
        "distractor_3": "hardening of the arteries"
      },
      {
        "id": "4176",
        "question": "When smoking is combined with another cardiovascular risk factor, how does this affect heart attack risk?",
        "answer": "greatly increases the risk",
        "distractor_1": "slightly increases the risk",
        "distractor_2": "has little or no effect on the risk",
        "distractor_3": "slightly decreases the risk"
      },
      {
        "id": "4177",
        "question": "Which structures prevent backflow of blood in areas where blood pressure is near zero?",
        "answer": "valves",
        "distractor_1": "atria",
        "distractor_2": "veins",
        "distractor_3": "capillaries"
      },
      {
        "id": "4178",
        "question": "In the systemic circulation, what is the correct order of structures through which blood travels?",
        "answer": "left ventricle to aorta to small arteries to body capillaries",
        "distractor_1": "left ventricle to small arteries to aorta to body capillaries",
        "distractor_2": "right ventricle to vena cava to body capillaries to aorta",
        "distractor_3": "right ventricle to aorta to small arteries to body capillaries"
      },
      {
        "id": "4179",
        "question": "Which of the following ranges of blood pressure is considered normal?",
        "answer": "90-119 systolic; 60-79 diastolic",
        "distractor_1": "89 or less systolic; 59 or less diastolic",
        "distractor_2": "120-139 systolic; 80-89 diastolic",
        "distractor_3": "140 or more systolic; 90 or more diastolic"
      },
      {
        "id": "4180",
        "question": "Which blood vessel carries oxygen-rich blood from the left ventricle to the body?",
        "answer": "aorta",
        "distractor_1": "atrium",
        "distractor_2": "carotid",
        "distractor_3": "vena cava"
      },
      {
        "id": "4181",
        "question": "How many more times per day does a person's heart beat if his or her resting heart rate is 75, compared to a person whose resting heart rate is 60?",
        "answer": "21,600 more times per day",
        "distractor_1": "216,000 more times per day",
        "distractor_2": "15,000 more times per day",
        "distractor_3": "12,500 more times per day"
      },
      {
        "id": "4182",
        "question": "In the pulmonary circulation, what is the correct order of structures through which blood travels?",
        "answer": "right ventricle to pulmonary arteries to lungs to left atrium",
        "distractor_1": "right ventricle to vena cava to lungs to left atrium",
        "distractor_2": "left ventricle to pulmonary arteries to lungs to right atrium",
        "distractor_3": "left ventricle to vena cava to lungs to right atrium"
      },
      {
        "id": "4183",
        "question": "What is the name of the structure that initiates, or starts, the heartbeat?",
        "answer": "pacemaker",
        "distractor_1": "atrium",
        "distractor_2": "septum",
        "distractor_3": "vena cava"
      },
      {
        "id": "4184",
        "question": "What term describes the pattern of blood flow from the right side of the heart through the lungs and from the left side through the body?",
        "answer": "double circulation",
        "distractor_1": "pulmonary circulation",
        "distractor_2": "systemic circulation",
        "distractor_3": "cardiovascular circulation"
      },
      {
        "id": "4185",
        "question": "What is the result of a coronary artery blockage caused by plaque, a blood clot, or a calcium deposit?",
        "answer": "heart attack",
        "distractor_1": "atherosclerosis",
        "distractor_2": "arteriosclerosis",
        "distractor_3": "stroke"
      },
      {
        "id": "4187",
        "question": "An adult human heart pumps about 130 milliliters of blood per beat. At 72 beats per minute, about how many liters of blood will the heart pump in one hour? (Hint: 1,000 milliliters = 1 liter)",
        "answer": "about 560 liters",
        "distractor_1": "about 450 liters",
        "distractor_2": "about 960 liters",
        "distractor_3": "about 720 liters"
      },
      {
        "id": "4188",
        "question": "What is the function of the heart's pacemaker?",
        "answer": "to start and regulate the heartbeat",
        "distractor_1": "to keep track of how many times the heart beats",
        "distractor_2": "to prevent backflow of blood in the heart",
        "distractor_3": "to start and stop the heart as needed"
      },
      {
        "id": "4189",
        "question": "In veins where blood pressure is zero, what structures help blood return to the heart?",
        "answer": "body muscles and valves",
        "distractor_1": "heart and valves",
        "distractor_2": "heart and capillaries",
        "distractor_3": "body muscles and heart"
      },
      {
        "id": "4190",
        "question": "Why is the heart's double circulation important?",
        "answer": "It increases the efficiency of oxygen delivery to cells.",
        "distractor_1": "It slows blood flow, giving cells more time to obtain nutrients.",
        "distractor_2": "It decreases the amount of blood needed by body cells.",
        "distractor_3": "It mixes oxygen-rich blood with oxygen-poor blood."
      },
      {
        "id": "4191",
        "question": "Which of the following blood pressure ranges is the range for pre-hypertension?",
        "answer": "120-139 systolic; 80-89 diastolic",
        "distractor_1": "89 or less systolic; 59 or less diastolic",
        "distractor_2": "90-119 systolic; 60-79 diastolic",
        "distractor_3": "140 or more systolic; 90 or more diastolic"
      },
      {
        "id": "4192",
        "question": "Which of the following is a normal proportion of nutrients in a healthy diet?",
        "answer": "15% protein, 25% fat, 60% carbohydrate",
        "distractor_1": "60% protein, 25% fat, 15% carbohydrate",
        "distractor_2": "15% protein, 60% fat, 25% carbohydrate",
        "distractor_3": "25% protein, 15% fat, 60% carbohydrate"
      },
      {
        "id": "4193",
        "question": "How does smoking affect cardiovascular health?",
        "answer": "It greatly increases most cardiovascular risk factors.",
        "distractor_1": "It doesn't; it affects only the respiratory system.",
        "distractor_2": "It slightly increases the progression of atherosclerosis.",
        "distractor_3": "It slightly increases blood pressure."
      },
      {
        "id": "4194",
        "question": "What is the iron-containing protein found in red blood cells that picks up and releases oxygen in the body cells?",
        "answer": "hemoglobin",
        "distractor_1": " antibody",
        "distractor_2": "lymph",
        "distractor_3": "fibrin"
      },
      {
        "id": "8190",
        "question": "In what year did the first human heart transplant occur?",
        "answer": "1967",
        "distractor_1": "1901",
        "distractor_2": "1944",
        "distractor_3": "1992"
      },
      {
        "id": "6467",
        "question": "What type of vessel carries blood away from the heart?",
        "answer": "artery",
        "distractor_1": "vein",
        "distractor_2": "ventricle",
        "distractor_3": "capillary"
      },
      {
        "id": "6468",
        "question": "What type of vessel carries blood toward the heart?",
        "answer": "vein",
        "distractor_1": "capillary",
        "distractor_2": "artery",
        "distractor_3": "atrium"
      },
      {
        "id": "6469",
        "question": "What is the upper chamber of heart that receives blood?",
        "answer": "atrium",
        "distractor_1": "ventricle",
        "distractor_2": "vena cava",
        "distractor_3": "aorta"
      },
      {
        "id": "6470",
        "question": "What is the force exerted by ventricles as they contract and push blood into arteries?",
        "answer": "blood pressure",
        "distractor_1": "systolic pressure",
        "distractor_2": "hypertension",
        "distractor_3": "atherosclerosis"
      },
      {
        "id": "6471",
        "question": "What term describes the number of times heart beats per minute?",
        "answer": "heart rate",
        "distractor_1": "cardiac cycle",
        "distractor_2": "blood pressure",
        "distractor_3": "hypertension"
      },
      {
        "id": "6472",
        "question": "What is the rhythmic pattern of contraction and relaxation during each heartbeat?",
        "answer": "cardiac cycle",
        "distractor_1": "heart rate",
        "distractor_2": "blood pressure",
        "distractor_3": "heart rhythm"
      },
      {
        "id": "6473",
        "question": "What measures electrical activity in heart muscle?",
        "answer": "electrocardiogram",
        "distractor_1": "pacemaker",
        "distractor_2": "vena cava",
        "distractor_3": "diastole monitor"
      },
      {
        "id": "6474",
        "question": "What is the term for blood pressure as ventricles contract?",
        "answer": "systole",
        "distractor_1": "diastole",
        "distractor_2": "blood pressure",
        "distractor_3": "atherosclerosis"
      },
      {
        "id": "6475",
        "question": "What is the term for blood pressure as ventricles relax?",
        "answer": "diastole",
        "distractor_1": "systole",
        "distractor_2": "hypertension",
        "distractor_3": "blood pressure"
      },
      {
        "id": "6476",
        "question": "What is consistently high blood pressure and a symptom of cardiovascular disease?",
        "answer": "hypertension",
        "distractor_1": "atherosclerosis",
        "distractor_2": "arteriosclerosis",
        "distractor_3": "aneurysm"
      },
      {
        "id": "6477",
        "question": "What is cholesterol, fats, and debris that stick to and narrow the artery walls?",
        "answer": "plaque",
        "distractor_1": "adipose film",
        "distractor_2": "waxy build-up",
        "distractor_3": "vena cava"
      },
      {
        "id": "6478",
        "question": "What is the lower chamber of heart that pumps blood out?",
        "answer": "ventricle",
        "distractor_1": "atrium",
        "distractor_2": "vena cava",
        "distractor_3": "capillary"
      },
      {
        "id": "6479",
        "question": "What is the region of right atrium where heartbeat is initiated?",
        "answer": "pacemaker",
        "distractor_1": "ventricle",
        "distractor_2": "atrium",
        "distractor_3": "vena cava"
      },
      {
        "id": "6480",
        "question": "What is the condition in which artery walls are thickened and narrowed by plaque?",
        "answer": "atherosclerosis",
        "distractor_1": "arteriosclerosis",
        "distractor_2": "hypertension",
        "distractor_3": "aneurysm"
      },
      {
        "id": "6481",
        "question": "What is body's largest vein?",
        "answer": "vena cava",
        "distractor_1": "aorta",
        "distractor_2": "pericardium",
        "distractor_3": "hepatic vein"
      },
      {
        "id": "6482",
        "question": "What is a tiny blood vessel through which substances are exchanged with body cells?",
        "answer": "capillary",
        "distractor_1": "pores",
        "distractor_2": "permeable cell wall",
        "distractor_3": "cell terminals"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "314",
    "name": "Interior Design",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "3063",
        "question": "What type of color scheme is created by using different values and intensities of one color?",
        "answer": "monochromatic",
        "distractor_1": "analogous",
        "distractor_2": "triadic",
        "distractor_3": "complementary"
      },
      {
        "id": "3064",
        "question": "Your room has a low ceiling and you want it to appear higher. What type of lines should be on the wallpaper?",
        "answer": "vertical",
        "distractor_1": "diagonal",
        "distractor_2": "horizontal",
        "distractor_3": "curved"
      },
      {
        "id": "3065",
        "question": "What should you use if you were redecorating a small room and wanted to make it seem wider?",
        "answer": "light colors and horizontal lines",
        "distractor_1": "dark colors and horizontal lines",
        "distractor_2": "dark colors and vertical lines",
        "distractor_3": "light colors and vertical lines"
      },
      {
        "id": "3066",
        "question": "A floor plan is drawn on a quarter-inch scale (1/4 inch = 1 foot). How long would a 6-foot bed would be drawn?",
        "answer": "1 1/2 inches",
        "distractor_1": "1 1/4 inches",
        "distractor_2": "6 inches",
        "distractor_3": "2 inches"
      },
      {
        "id": "3068",
        "question": "A painter charges $15 labor for each gallon of paint he uses on the interior of a house. If the area of the walls are 2,300 square feet and one gallon covers 400 square feet, how much is the painter’s labor charge? (Hint: Find gallons of paint used.)",
        "answer": "$90.00",
        "distractor_1": "$108.00",
        "distractor_2": "$84.00",
        "distractor_3": "$96.00"
      },
      {
        "id": "3069",
        "question": "What is the term for a color scheme created by using colors that are direct contrasts?",
        "answer": "complementary",
        "distractor_1": "triadic",
        "distractor_2": "analogous",
        "distractor_3": "monochromatic"
      },
      {
        "id": "3070",
        "question": "Resilient floor coverings include which of the following?",
        "answer": "cork, vinyl, no-wax flooring",
        "distractor_1": "carpet, cork, wood",
        "distractor_2": "cork, wood, tile",
        "distractor_3": "carpet, cork, cement"
      },
      {
        "id": "3072",
        "question": "Which is the least expensive and easiest wall covering to change?",
        "answer": "paint",
        "distractor_1": "paneling",
        "distractor_2": "tile",
        "distractor_3": "wallpaper"
      },
      {
        "id": "3073",
        "question": "What type of lighting is bounced off walls or ceilings?",
        "answer": "indirect",
        "distractor_1": "artificial",
        "distractor_2": "direct",
        "distractor_3": "natural"
      },
      {
        "id": "3075",
        "question": "A feeling of steadiness and being orderly is produced by balance. Identify the word used when one side of the wall matches the other or the walls are symmetrical.",
        "answer": "formal ",
        "distractor_1": "informal ",
        "distractor_2": "unity",
        "distractor_3": "rhythm"
      },
      {
        "id": "3076",
        "question": "What kind of color scheme is produced by combining hues (colors) that are next to each other on the color wheel?",
        "answer": "analogous",
        "distractor_1": "monochromatic",
        "distractor_2": "complementary",
        "distractor_3": "accented-neutral"
      },
      {
        "id": "3077",
        "question": "Balance produces a feeling of steadiness and order. What term is used for balance occurring when one side of a wall matches the other?",
        "answer": "formal",
        "distractor_1": "rhythm",
        "distractor_2": "informal",
        "distractor_3": "unity"
      },
      {
        "id": "3078",
        "question": "You are redecorating a small room and want to make it seem wider. What colors and lines should you use?",
        "answer": "light colors and horizontal lines",
        "distractor_1": "dark colors and horizontal lines",
        "distractor_2": "dark colors and vertical lines",
        "distractor_3": "light colors and vertical lines"
      },
      {
        "id": "3081",
        "question": "What type of color scheme is created by using colors that are in direct contrast?",
        "answer": "complementary",
        "distractor_1": "triadic",
        "distractor_2": "analogous",
        "distractor_3": "monochromatic"
      },
      {
        "id": "3083",
        "question": "Where on the list should you place the most expensive items when making a budget for a remodeling project?",
        "answer": "at the top",
        "distractor_1": "in the middle",
        "distractor_2": "at the bottom",
        "distractor_3": "anywhere"
      },
      {
        "id": "3084",
        "question": "Identify what you feel when you touch an object.",
        "answer": "texture",
        "distractor_1": "intensity",
        "distractor_2": "color",
        "distractor_3": "shape"
      },
      {
        "id": "3087",
        "question": "Identify the term for how people move around in the room.",
        "answer": "traffic patterns",
        "distractor_1": "people patterns",
        "distractor_2": "traffic paths",
        "distractor_3": "people paths"
      },
      {
        "id": "6617",
        "question": "What is a mark or object that adds emphasis or distinction to another object?",
        "answer": "Accent",
        "distractor_1": "Harmony",
        "distractor_2": "Shade",
        "distractor_3": "Intensity"
      },
      {
        "id": "6618",
        "question": "What is the effect caused by a collection of objects that creates a visual appearance pleasing to the eye?",
        "answer": "Harmony",
        "distractor_1": "Balance",
        "distractor_2": "Shade",
        "distractor_3": "Proportion"
      },
      {
        "id": "6619",
        "question": "What are lines or patterns that run from side to side?",
        "answer": "Horizontal lines",
        "distractor_1": "Vertical lines ",
        "distractor_2": "Monochromatic lines",
        "distractor_3": "traffic patterns"
      },
      {
        "id": "6620",
        "question": "What is positioning objects in an asymmetrical design to create balance?",
        "answer": "Informal balance",
        "distractor_1": "Formal balance",
        "distractor_2": "Traffic patterns",
        "distractor_3": "Proportion"
      },
      {
        "id": "6621",
        "question": "What is the brightness or dullness of a color that determines the strength of the color?",
        "answer": "Intensity",
        "distractor_1": "Harmony",
        "distractor_2": "Proportion",
        "distractor_3": "Shade"
      },
      {
        "id": "6622",
        "question": "What is the relationship of the size of an object to another object or group of objects?",
        "answer": "Proportion",
        "distractor_1": "Harmony",
        "distractor_2": "Balance",
        "distractor_3": "Intensity"
      },
      {
        "id": "6623",
        "question": "What is the darkness of a color changed by adding black to the color?",
        "answer": "Shade",
        "distractor_1": "Intensity",
        "distractor_2": "Harmony",
        "distractor_3": "Accent"
      },
      {
        "id": "6624",
        "question": "What is the path that people use in a home to get from one room to another?",
        "answer": "Traffic pattern",
        "distractor_1": "Horizontal lines",
        "distractor_2": "Vertical lines",
        "distractor_3": "Monochromatic lines"
      },
      {
        "id": "8178",
        "question": "What are the elements of design used in interior design?",
        "answer": "color, line, texture, and form",
        "distractor_1": "balance, rhythm, texture, and form",
        "distractor_2": "proportion, form, line, and color",
        "distractor_3": "proportion, rhythm, balance, and emphasis"
      },
      {
        "id": "8179",
        "question": "If one gallon of paint will cover 400 square feet, how many gallons will have to be purchased to paint a house with 1,750 suare feet of wall space?",
        "answer": "5 gallons",
        "distractor_1": "3 gallons",
        "distractor_2": "4 gallons",
        "distractor_3": "6 gallons"
      },
      {
        "id": "8180",
        "question": "Identify an advantage of incandescent bulbs over fluorescent bulbs.",
        "answer": "incandescent bulbs are cheaper",
        "distractor_1": "incandescent bulbs last longer",
        "distractor_2": "fluorescent bulbs are oddly shaped",
        "distractor_3": "fluorescent bulbs can be rounded"
      },
      {
        "id": "8181",
        "question": "Identify the principles of design in interior design.",
        "answer": "proportion, rhythm, balance, and emphasis",
        "distractor_1": "balance, rhythm, texture, and form",
        "distractor_2": "color, line, texture, and form",
        "distractor_3": "proportion, form, line, and color"
      },
      {
        "id": "8182",
        "question": "What do you feel when you touch an object?",
        "answer": "texture",
        "distractor_1": "shape",
        "distractor_2": "color",
        "distractor_3": "intensity"
      },
      {
        "id": "8183",
        "question": "What kind of color scheme is produced by combining hues of the same color?",
        "answer": "monochromatic",
        "distractor_1": "analogous",
        "distractor_2": "complementary",
        "distractor_3": "neutral"
      },
      {
        "id": "8184",
        "question": "What type of lines is drawn in an up and down direction?",
        "answer": "vertical lines",
        "distractor_1": "horizontal lines",
        "distractor_2": "perpendicular lines",
        "distractor_3": "parallel lines"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "315",
    "name": "Clothing Care",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1628",
        "question": "What is the correct term for the process of removing wrinkles from clothes using a steam iron and a lifting motion rather than a rubbing motion?",
        "answer": "pressing",
        "distractor_1": "ironing",
        "distractor_2": "steaming",
        "distractor_3": "setting"
      },
      {
        "id": "1629",
        "question": "Which of the following cleaning agents should be used to wash clothes if the water is hard?",
        "answer": "water softener",
        "distractor_1": "soap",
        "distractor_2": "detergent",
        "distractor_3": "bleach"
      },
      {
        "id": "1630",
        "question": "Which of the following is the best time to treat a stain?",
        "answer": "immediately after it occurs",
        "distractor_1": "between washing and drying",
        "distractor_2": "after laundering garment",
        "distractor_3": "after ironing"
      },
      {
        "id": "1634",
        "question": "Proper water temperatures are important when washing clothes. A permanent-press shirt will have fewer wrinkles if it is washed and rinsed in which of the following water temperatures?",
        "answer": "warm wash, cold rinse",
        "distractor_1": "hot wash, cold rinse",
        "distractor_2": "cold wash, cold rinse",
        "distractor_3": "hot wash, hot rinse"
      },
      {
        "id": "1636",
        "question": "When washing clothes in hard water, what in the water mixes with soap causing clothes to appear dull?",
        "answer": "minerals",
        "distractor_1": "petroleum",
        "distractor_2": "ice",
        "distractor_3": "bacteria"
      },
      {
        "id": "1637",
        "question": "What types of stains are removed by solvents?",
        "answer": "oil-based",
        "distractor_1": "water-based",
        "distractor_2": "organic",
        "distractor_3": "juice"
      },
      {
        "id": "1638",
        "question": "What should be used to remove a blood stain?",
        "answer": "cold water",
        "distractor_1": "vinegar",
        "distractor_2": "milk",
        "distractor_3": "baking soda"
      },
      {
        "id": "1646",
        "question": "How does oxygen bleach compare to chlorine bleach?",
        "answer": "Oxygen bleach is milder than chlorine bleach.",
        "distractor_1": "Oxygen bleach is stronger than chlorine bleach.",
        "distractor_2": "Oxygen bleach is harder on clothes than chlorine bleach.",
        "distractor_3": "Oxygen bleach is a better stain remover than chlorine bleach."
      },
      {
        "id": "1650",
        "question": "Which of the following statements describes how oxygen bleach compares to chlorine bleach?",
        "answer": "it is milder",
        "distractor_1": "it is stronger",
        "distractor_2": "it is harder on clothes",
        "distractor_3": "it is a better stain remover"
      },
      {
        "id": "6208",
        "question": "What is able to soak up liquid?",
        "answer": "Absorbent",
        "distractor_1": "Detergent",
        "distractor_2": "Antistatic",
        "distractor_3": "Yarn"
      },
      {
        "id": "6209",
        "question": "What is a compound used on fabric to reduce static electricity?",
        "answer": "Antistatic",
        "distractor_1": "Absorbent",
        "distractor_2": "Detergent",
        "distractor_3": "Yarn"
      },
      {
        "id": "6210",
        "question": "What is the process of removing the color from fabric using chemicals?",
        "answer": "Bleaching",
        "distractor_1": "Antistatic",
        "distractor_2": "Durable finish",
        "distractor_3": "Permanent press"
      },
      {
        "id": "6211",
        "question": "What is if a label does not advise against a cleaner, type of cleaning, or type of maintenance, then it is probably OK to use it or do it?",
        "answer": "Care labeling rule",
        "distractor_1": "Crease resistance rule",
        "distractor_2": "Durable finish rule",
        "distractor_3": "Permanent pressing rules"
      },
      {
        "id": "6212",
        "question": "What is a fabric that has had chemicals added to it to help resist wrinkles?",
        "answer": "Crease resistant",
        "distractor_1": "Antistatic",
        "distractor_2": "Permanent Press",
        "distractor_3": "Absorbent"
      },
      {
        "id": "6213",
        "question": "What is a treatment used on fabric that extends the finish over several washings?",
        "answer": "Durable finish",
        "distractor_1": "Permanent press",
        "distractor_2": "Crease resistant",
        "distractor_3": "Antistatic"
      },
      {
        "id": "6214",
        "question": "What is a treatment given to fabric that lasts the life of the fabric and helps keep its shape while resisting wrinkles?",
        "answer": "Permanent press",
        "distractor_1": "Crease resistant",
        "distractor_2": "Care labeling rule",
        "distractor_3": "Antistatic"
      },
      {
        "id": "6215",
        "question": "What is fibers put together in a continuous strand?",
        "answer": "Yarn",
        "distractor_1": "Absorbent",
        "distractor_2": "Durable finish",
        "distractor_3": " Permanent press"
      },
      {
        "id": "8210",
        "question": "Suppose you have a 2.5-cubic-foot capacity washing machine. How much water would this machine hold? (Hint: One cubic foot is approximately 7.5 gallons.)",
        "answer": "about 18.75 gallons",
        "distractor_1": "about 3 gallons",
        "distractor_2": "about 10 gallons",
        "distractor_3": "about 26.25 gallons"
      },
      {
        "id": "8211",
        "question": "Which of the following is a chemical compound used to clean fabric?",
        "answer": "detergent",
        "distractor_1": "bleach",
        "distractor_2": "soap",
        "distractor_3": "minerals"
      },
      {
        "id": "8212",
        "question": "Using which of the following while ironing helps protect garments and prevents shine from forming on fabrics?",
        "answer": "a pressing cloth",
        "distractor_1": "bleach",
        "distractor_2": "fabric softener",
        "distractor_3": "starch"
      },
      {
        "id": "8201",
        "question": "How should you start the thread when sewing a button onto a garment?",
        "answer": "on the inside of the garment",
        "distractor_1": "by tying it to the button",
        "distractor_2": "under the button",
        "distractor_3": "on the outside of the garment"
      },
      {
        "id": "8204",
        "question": "A garment's care label contains which of the following pieces of information?",
        "answer": "drying temperature",
        "distractor_1": "color (dye)",
        "distractor_2": "age",
        "distractor_3": "drying time"
      },
      {
        "id": "8205",
        "question": "There are two types of stains, water-based and oil-based. Which of the following stains is oil-based?",
        "answer": "cosmetics",
        "distractor_1": "coffee",
        "distractor_2": "tea",
        "distractor_3": "fruit juice"
      },
      {
        "id": "8207",
        "question": "What should be done to repair a snag?",
        "answer": "Pull the snag to the inside of the garment, then stretch the surrounding fabric. ",
        "distractor_1": "Cut the loop of thread and tie it on the inside of the garment.",
        "distractor_2": "Gently stretch the material around the snag without touching the loop.",
        "distractor_3": "Cut the loop, and then pull on the thread to remove it."
      },
      {
        "id": "8208",
        "question": "For each cubic-foot capacity of a washing machine, 1/4 cup of detergent is used. How much detergent is used in a machine with a 3.5 cubic-foot capacity?",
        "answer": "7/8 cup",
        "distractor_1": "1/2 cup",
        "distractor_2": "1 1/4 cups",
        "distractor_3": "3/4 cup"
      },
      {
        "id": "8209",
        "question": "What is the quickest way to dry clothes?",
        "answer": "tumble drying",
        "distractor_1": "line drying",
        "distractor_2": "flat drying",
        "distractor_3": "dry cleaning"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "316",
    "name": "Entrepreneurship: Child Care",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2934",
        "question": "Which of these activities can you do after the children have gone to sleep?",
        "answer": "read, watch TV, or listen to music",
        "distractor_1": "go to sleep",
        "distractor_2": "play with the computer",
        "distractor_3": "check out the neighborhood"
      },
      {
        "id": "2936",
        "question": "Which of these qualities would be most important to parents when choosing a babysitter?",
        "answer": "responsible",
        "distractor_1": "fun for their children",
        "distractor_2": "polite",
        "distractor_3": "clean and neat"
      },
      {
        "id": "5491",
        "question": "What is known as the stage of life between childhood and adulthood when many physical and emotional changes take place?",
        "answer": "adolescence",
        "distractor_1": "maturity",
        "distractor_2": "toddler",
        "distractor_3": "infant"
      },
      {
        "id": "2937",
        "question": "What practical method of advertising would be the best to let people know that you want babysitting jobs?",
        "answer": "give business cards to friends and neighbors",
        "distractor_1": "place a large ad in the local newspaper",
        "distractor_2": "radio",
        "distractor_3": "television"
      },
      {
        "id": "2938",
        "question": "For each babysitting customer, what should you maintain and keep in your portfolio?",
        "answer": "information checklist",
        "distractor_1": "Social Security number",
        "distractor_2": "list of video games",
        "distractor_3": "pay scale"
      },
      {
        "id": "2939",
        "question": "What is a babysitter's most important task?",
        "answer": "keep the children safe",
        "distractor_1": "arrive on time",
        "distractor_2": "agree on the pay before starting",
        "distractor_3": "make no long-distance calls"
      },
      {
        "id": "2942",
        "question": "A child admires you enough to imitate your behavior. What have you become to that child?",
        "answer": "a role model",
        "distractor_1": "a parent figure",
        "distractor_2": "a hero",
        "distractor_3": "a peer"
      },
      {
        "id": "2943",
        "question": "At about what age is a child called a toddler?",
        "answer": "1 to 3 years",
        "distractor_1": "6 months to 1 year",
        "distractor_2": "3 to 5 years",
        "distractor_3": "under 1 year"
      },
      {
        "id": "2944",
        "question": "The parents of the children you will babysit tell you that they expect to be gone for six hours. If you are to be at their house by 7:30 p.m., at what time do they expect to return?",
        "answer": "1:30 a.m.",
        "distractor_1": "11:30 p.m.",
        "distractor_2": "12:30 a.m.",
        "distractor_3": "12:30 p.m."
      },
      {
        "id": "2945",
        "question": "What is the key to being successful in any business?",
        "answer": "keeping the customer satisfied",
        "distractor_1": "making lots of money",
        "distractor_2": "working short hours",
        "distractor_3": "not paying taxes"
      },
      {
        "id": "2947",
        "question": "What should a good business card contain?",
        "answer": "your phone number",
        "distractor_1": "your age",
        "distractor_2": "your GPA in school",
        "distractor_3": "your Social Security number"
      },
      {
        "id": "2948",
        "question": "If a fire starts in the house where you are babysitting, what should you do first?",
        "answer": "get the children out of the house",
        "distractor_1": "call 911",
        "distractor_2": "find the fire extinguisher",
        "distractor_3": "call home for instructions"
      },
      {
        "id": "2950",
        "question": "While babysitting, which of these should you be expected to do?",
        "answer": "answer the phone",
        "distractor_1": "prepare a meal",
        "distractor_2": "clean the house",
        "distractor_3": "do the laundry"
      },
      {
        "id": "2951",
        "question": "How many hours of sleep do toddlers generally need each night?",
        "answer": "10-12",
        "distractor_1": "8-10",
        "distractor_2": "6-8",
        "distractor_3": "13-15"
      },
      {
        "id": "2952",
        "question": "A child you are babysitting needs to take medicine every four hours. If you arrive at 9:30 a.m. and are told that the child's last dose was an hour ago, what time should you give the next dose?",
        "answer": "12:30 p.m.",
        "distractor_1": "1:30 p.m.",
        "distractor_2": "3:30 p.m.",
        "distractor_3": "2:30 p.m."
      },
      {
        "id": "2954",
        "question": "If the toddler you are babysitting begins to choke, what should you do first?",
        "answer": "use the Heimlich maneuver",
        "distractor_1": "give mouth-to-mouth resuscitation",
        "distractor_2": "get a neighbor",
        "distractor_3": "call 911"
      },
      {
        "id": "2955",
        "question": "Most of all, parents want what characteristic in a babysitter?",
        "answer": "someone who is responsible",
        "distractor_1": "someone who is clean and neat",
        "distractor_2": "someone who is fun for their children",
        "distractor_3": "someone who is polite"
      },
      {
        "id": "5492",
        "question": "What is the term that refers to not meeting the physical and emotional needs of a child?",
        "answer": "child neglect",
        "distractor_1": "childproofing",
        "distractor_2": "discipline",
        "distractor_3": "privilege"
      },
      {
        "id": "5493",
        "question": "What is known as the process of removing possible dangers from an area to keep a child safe?",
        "answer": "childproofing",
        "distractor_1": "role modeling",
        "distractor_2": "discipline",
        "distractor_3": "neglect"
      },
      {
        "id": "5494",
        "question": "What is the task of teaching children the difference between acceptable behaviors and unacceptable behaviors and what is right or wrong through setting limitations and guidelines?",
        "answer": "discipline",
        "distractor_1": "behavior modification",
        "distractor_2": "privilege",
        "distractor_3": "role modeling"
      },
      {
        "id": "5495",
        "question": "What term is defined by the procedure used to dislodge an object that is causing a person to choke?",
        "answer": "Heimlich maneuver",
        "distractor_1": "CPR",
        "distractor_2": "life-saving measures",
        "distractor_3": "chest compressions"
      },
      {
        "id": "5496",
        "question": "What is known as the first stage of life, when a child is 0-12 months old?",
        "answer": "infant",
        "distractor_1": "toddler",
        "distractor_2": "adult",
        "distractor_3": "adolescence"
      },
      {
        "id": "5497",
        "question": "Which term is defined as the period when a person begins accepting the responsibility of decisions and actions in his or her life?",
        "answer": "maturity",
        "distractor_1": "adulthood",
        "distractor_2": "adolescence",
        "distractor_3": "teens"
      },
      {
        "id": "5498",
        "question": "What is the process of taking food into the body and how the body makes use of that food?",
        "answer": "nutrition",
        "distractor_1": "privilege",
        "distractor_2": "ingesting",
        "distractor_3": "digesting"
      },
      {
        "id": "5499",
        "question": "What is the third stage of life, when a child is 3-5 years old?",
        "answer": "preschooler",
        "distractor_1": "toddler",
        "distractor_2": "adolescent",
        "distractor_3": "teenager"
      },
      {
        "id": "5500",
        "question": "What is an individual whose behavior is imitated by others?",
        "answer": "role model",
        "distractor_1": "a star",
        "distractor_2": "parent",
        "distractor_3": "sibling"
      },
      {
        "id": "5501",
        "question": "Which term refers to a series of actions that is repeated on a regular basis?",
        "answer": "routine",
        "distractor_1": "habit",
        "distractor_2": "superstition",
        "distractor_3": "everyday occurrence"
      },
      {
        "id": "5502",
        "question": "What is the second stage of life, when a child is 1-3 years old?",
        "answer": "toddler",
        "distractor_1": "infant",
        "distractor_2": "adult",
        "distractor_3": "teen"
      },
      {
        "id": "5503",
        "question": "What is defined as a right or benefit that is given to a select few?",
        "answer": "privilege",
        "distractor_1": "gift",
        "distractor_2": "favor",
        "distractor_3": "allowance"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "317",
    "name": "Baking & Measurement",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8261",
        "question": "Carbohydrates are the body's most important source of this.",
        "answer": "energy",
        "distractor_1": "protein",
        "distractor_2": "nutrients",
        "distractor_3": "fiber"
      },
      {
        "id": "8262",
        "question": "What term is defined as the measurement of the amount of energy given to the body in the food we eat?",
        "answer": "calories",
        "distractor_1": "fat",
        "distractor_2": "grams",
        "distractor_3": "saturated fat"
      },
      {
        "id": "2397",
        "question": "What is one advantage of convection cooking over microwave cooking?",
        "answer": "sealing in flavor",
        "distractor_1": "cooking foods from the inside out",
        "distractor_2": "cooking faster",
        "distractor_3": "cooking more cheaply"
      },
      {
        "id": "2399",
        "question": "One-eighth cup is equal to how many tablespoons?",
        "answer": "2",
        "distractor_1": "5",
        "distractor_2": "3",
        "distractor_3": "4"
      },
      {
        "id": "5481",
        "question": "This person specializes in nutrition and helping people to eat healthy foods.",
        "answer": "dietitian",
        "distractor_1": "magician",
        "distractor_2": "barber",
        "distractor_3": "chef"
      },
      {
        "id": "2401",
        "question": "A healthy diet contains which of the following? ",
        "answer": "a wide variety of foods",
        "distractor_1": "only fresh foods",
        "distractor_2": "no fats",
        "distractor_3": "no fiber"
      },
      {
        "id": "2403",
        "question": "What are the main body-building nutrients?",
        "answer": "proteins",
        "distractor_1": "minerals",
        "distractor_2": "vitamins",
        "distractor_3": "carbohydrates"
      },
      {
        "id": "2404",
        "question": "If a recipe calls for one cup of sugar, what is the correct way to measure the sugar?",
        "answer": "loose and level with the top of the cup",
        "distractor_1": "loose and heaped over the top of the cup",
        "distractor_2": "packed tightly and level with the top of the cup",
        "distractor_3": "loose and slightly rounded over the top of the cup"
      },
      {
        "id": "2406",
        "question": "How do convection ovens cook food?",
        "answer": "by circulating hot air",
        "distractor_1": "by steaming",
        "distractor_2": "by open-flame grilling",
        "distractor_3": "by emitting microwaves"
      },
      {
        "id": "2409",
        "question": "A one-ounce bag of potato chips contains 10 grams of fat. Each gram of fat contains about 9 calories. How many calories of fat are in the bag of potato chips?",
        "answer": "90",
        "distractor_1": "95",
        "distractor_2": "45",
        "distractor_3": "900"
      },
      {
        "id": "2410",
        "question": "Which of the following aids in digestion by helping the body get rid of waste?",
        "answer": "fiber",
        "distractor_1": "minerals",
        "distractor_2": "vitamins",
        "distractor_3": "protein"
      },
      {
        "id": "2411",
        "question": "Why should recycled paper products not be used in the microwave?",
        "answer": "They might contain metal.",
        "distractor_1": "They might contain chemicals.",
        "distractor_2": "They might contain ink.",
        "distractor_3": "They deflect microwaves."
      },
      {
        "id": "2414",
        "question": "What is the term for sickness caused by eating contaminated food?",
        "answer": "food-borne illness",
        "distractor_1": "malaria",
        "distractor_2": "influenza",
        "distractor_3": "diabetes"
      },
      {
        "id": "2422",
        "question": "Foods contain many things that make your body work, grow, and repair itself. What is the term for these things?",
        "answer": "nutrients",
        "distractor_1": "energy",
        "distractor_2": "preservatives",
        "distractor_3": "additives"
      },
      {
        "id": "5487",
        "question": "This term refers to a process in which dairy products are heated to a certain temperature to kill harmful bacteria.",
        "answer": "pasteurization",
        "distractor_1": "osteoporosis",
        "distractor_2": "supplementation",
        "distractor_3": "fortification"
      },
      {
        "id": "5489",
        "question": "This term is defined as when a food is cooked too long or at too high a temperature, often turning the food a different color.",
        "answer": "scorching",
        "distractor_1": "roasting",
        "distractor_2": "frying",
        "distractor_3": "grilling"
      },
      {
        "id": "5490",
        "question": "This term is defined as a method of cooking food at a very gentle boil.",
        "answer": "simmer",
        "distractor_1": "sauté",
        "distractor_2": "broil",
        "distractor_3": "deep fry"
      },
      {
        "id": "8322",
        "question": "This term is defined as a calories with little or no nutritional value.",
        "answer": "empty calories",
        "distractor_1": "fat",
        "distractor_2": "sweets",
        "distractor_3": "unhealthy"
      },
      {
        "id": "8320",
        "question": "What is the body's most important source of energy? ",
        "answer": "carbohydrates",
        "distractor_1": "protein",
        "distractor_2": "sweets",
        "distractor_3": "exercise"
      },
      {
        "id": "8321",
        "question": "Which of the following nutrients is essential in order for your body to grow? ",
        "answer": "proteins",
        "distractor_1": "vitamins",
        "distractor_2": "minerals",
        "distractor_3": "water"
      },
      {
        "id": "8323",
        "question": "Which material should not be used when cooking in the convection oven?",
        "answer": "paper products",
        "distractor_1": "metal",
        "distractor_2": "CorningWare",
        "distractor_3": "ceramic cookware"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "318",
    "name": "Genetics",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2450",
        "question": "What is the term for the expression of an organism's genetic code?",
        "answer": "phenotype",
        "distractor_1": "genotype",
        "distractor_2": "chromosome",
        "distractor_3": "carbohydrate"
      },
      {
        "id": "2451",
        "question": "If 3/8 of the population have at least one gene for green eyes and 3/8 of those have two genes for green eyes, what fraction of the population has two genes for green eyes?",
        "answer": "9/64",
        "distractor_1": "3/4",
        "distractor_2": "3/8",
        "distractor_3": "9/8"
      },
      {
        "id": "2453",
        "question": "What is the scientific term that describes the genetic code for an organism?",
        "answer": "genotype",
        "distractor_1": "homozygous",
        "distractor_2": "heterozygous",
        "distractor_3": "chromosome"
      },
      {
        "id": "2454",
        "question": "What are different genes for the same trait?",
        "answer": "alleles",
        "distractor_1": "family tree",
        "distractor_2": "Punnett square",
        "distractor_3": "isotopes"
      },
      {
        "id": "2455",
        "question": "Segments of DNA molecules within a cell are responsible for both the sameness of a species and differences among individuals. What are these segments called?",
        "answer": "genes",
        "distractor_1": "traits",
        "distractor_2": "nuclei",
        "distractor_3": "mitochondria"
      },
      {
        "id": "2456",
        "question": "What is the term for different genes for the same trait?",
        "answer": "alleles",
        "distractor_1": "genes",
        "distractor_2": "genomes",
        "distractor_3": "chromosomes"
      },
      {
        "id": "2457",
        "question": "Which of these is a graphic organizer used to determine potential traits in offspring?",
        "answer": "Punnett square",
        "distractor_1": "pedigree",
        "distractor_2": "gene pool",
        "distractor_3": "random selection"
      },
      {
        "id": "2458",
        "question": "Which of these are segments of DNA?",
        "answer": "genes",
        "distractor_1": "atoms",
        "distractor_2": "molecules",
        "distractor_3": "modules"
      },
      {
        "id": "2459",
        "question": "What is the term for genetic traits that are expressed?",
        "answer": "dominant",
        "distractor_1": "recessive",
        "distractor_2": "masked",
        "distractor_3": "loud"
      },
      {
        "id": "2460",
        "question": "What is the scientific term used to describe an organism that has two different alleles for a specific trait? (for example: Tt)",
        "answer": "heterozygous",
        "distractor_1": "recessive",
        "distractor_2": "homozygous",
        "distractor_3": "chromosome"
      },
      {
        "id": "2463",
        "question": "What type of gene is expressed by an organism?",
        "answer": "dominant",
        "distractor_1": "recessive",
        "distractor_2": "mutant",
        "distractor_3": "replication"
      },
      {
        "id": "2464",
        "question": "What is the expression of an organism's genetic code?",
        "answer": "phenotype",
        "distractor_1": "biology",
        "distractor_2": "genotype",
        "distractor_3": "cell division"
      },
      {
        "id": "2465",
        "question": "What are traits that are carried on the sex chromosomes called?",
        "answer": "sex-linked traits",
        "distractor_1": "biology",
        "distractor_2": "autosomes",
        "distractor_3": "mutations"
      },
      {
        "id": "2467",
        "question": "Where are chromosomes located in every cell of higher organisms?",
        "answer": "nucleus",
        "distractor_1": "lysosomes",
        "distractor_2": "cytoplasm",
        "distractor_3": "ribosomes"
      },
      {
        "id": "2468",
        "question": "What molecules make up chromosomes?",
        "answer": "DNA",
        "distractor_1": "genes",
        "distractor_2": "jeans",
        "distractor_3": "plasmids"
      },
      {
        "id": "2469",
        "question": "Genotype is a scientific term. What does it describe about an organism?",
        "answer": "genetic code",
        "distractor_1": "mutation",
        "distractor_2": "nucleus",
        "distractor_3": "chromosomes"
      },
      {
        "id": "2473",
        "question": "What structure in each cell of higher organisms contains the chromosomes?",
        "answer": "nucleus",
        "distractor_1": "ribosomes",
        "distractor_2": "lysosomes",
        "distractor_3": "mitochondria"
      },
      {
        "id": "2474",
        "question": "Who was credited with developing the branch of biology now called genetics?",
        "answer": "Gregor Mendel",
        "distractor_1": "Charles Darwin",
        "distractor_2": "Sebastian Cabot",
        "distractor_3": "Dominick Dapuchi"
      },
      {
        "id": "2475",
        "question": "What is used to determine the possible gene combinations that an offspring might inherit from its parents?",
        "answer": "Punnett square",
        "distractor_1": "family tree",
        "distractor_2": "pedigree",
        "distractor_3": "genetic chart"
      },
      {
        "id": "2476",
        "question": "What is the term for traits that are carried on the sex chromosomes?",
        "answer": "sex-linked traits",
        "distractor_1": "gender genes",
        "distractor_2": "male and female",
        "distractor_3": "autosomes"
      },
      {
        "id": "2477",
        "question": "Chromosomes are structures inside the nucleus of a cell. They are made up of what large molecule?",
        "answer": "DNA",
        "distractor_1": "AZT",
        "distractor_2": "ATP",
        "distractor_3": "TRM"
      },
      {
        "id": "6435",
        "question": "What are the structures in the nucleus that contains DNA?",
        "answer": "chromosome",
        "distractor_1": "genes",
        "distractor_2": "alleles",
        "distractor_3": "traits"
      },
      {
        "id": "6436",
        "question": "What is the scientific term used to describe an organism that has an identical set of genes for a specific trait?",
        "answer": "homozygous",
        "distractor_1": "heterozygous",
        "distractor_2": "phenotype",
        "distractor_3": "genotype"
      },
      {
        "id": "6437",
        "question": "What type of gene is a gene that is present, but is not expressed by the organism?",
        "answer": "recessive",
        "distractor_1": "genotype",
        "distractor_2": "phenotype",
        "distractor_3": "dominant"
      },
      {
        "id": "6438",
        "question": "What is the term for a distinguishing feature, such as eye color, height, skin color, and hair color?",
        "answer": "trait",
        "distractor_1": "genes",
        "distractor_2": "DNA",
        "distractor_3": "dominant gene"
      },
      {
        "id": "8653",
        "question": "How many different traits are being examined at the same time when performing a dihybrid cross?",
        "answer": "2",
        "distractor_1": "12",
        "distractor_2": "20",
        "distractor_3": "22"
      },
      {
        "id": "8654",
        "question": "When performing a Punnett square on sex determination in offspring, there is a fifty percent chance of an offspring being male and a fifty percent chance of an offspring being female. If a couple have three female children and are expecting a fourth ",
        "answer": "50%",
        "distractor_1": "100%",
        "distractor_2": "25%",
        "distractor_3": "12.5%"
      },
      {
        "id": "8655",
        "question": "What is the name of the structure that binds two sister chromatids together at the beginning of mitosis?",
        "answer": "centromere",
        "distractor_1": "centriole",
        "distractor_2": "nuclear membrane",
        "distractor_3": "cytoplasm"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "319",
    "name": "Fitness & Health",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1925",
        "question": "Why does your heart beat faster when you exercise?",
        "answer": "muscles need more oxygen",
        "distractor_1": "muscles need less oxygen",
        "distractor_2": "muscles need more carbon dioxide",
        "distractor_3": "muscles need higher blood pressure"
      },
      {
        "id": "1926",
        "question": "When exercising, one person's target heart rate (aerobic capacity) varies from another person's because of what factor?",
        "answer": "age",
        "distractor_1": "blood pressure",
        "distractor_2": "weight",
        "distractor_3": "body fat"
      },
      {
        "id": "1928",
        "question": "Name the substance that makes your skin look oily and waterproofs it. If your body produces too much of this substance, acne can occur.",
        "answer": "sebum",
        "distractor_1": "fat",
        "distractor_2": "sweat",
        "distractor_3": "epidermis"
      },
      {
        "id": "1932",
        "question": "This type of exercise is a good form of exercise and should raise your pulse and breathing rates to their target numbers. You should do this type of exercise at least three times a week. What type of exercise is it?",
        "answer": "aerobics",
        "distractor_1": "body building",
        "distractor_2": "isometrics",
        "distractor_3": "strengthening"
      },
      {
        "id": "1934",
        "question": "Your skin consists of two main layers: the outer layer and  the inner layer. Select the answer that gives their scientific names in the same order.",
        "answer": "epidermis, dermis",
        "distractor_1": "fatty tissue, sebaceous glands",
        "distractor_2": "dermis, epidermis",
        "distractor_3": "complexion, melanin"
      },
      {
        "id": "1938",
        "question": "Most people's hair grows about half an inch per month. At that rate, how often would you need to have your hair cut if you did not want to have the length vary by more than 1-1/2 inches?",
        "answer": "4 times per year",
        "distractor_1": "monthly",
        "distractor_2": "6 times per year",
        "distractor_3": "semi-annually"
      },
      {
        "id": "1940",
        "question": "What term is best defined as being able to bend, twist, and stretch easily?",
        "answer": "suppleness",
        "distractor_1": "stamina",
        "distractor_2": "strength",
        "distractor_3": "posture"
      },
      {
        "id": "1942",
        "question": "Which of the following terms best describes a person who looks nice, dresses neatly, has good posture, and is clean?",
        "answer": "well-groomed",
        "distractor_1": "healthy",
        "distractor_2": "fit",
        "distractor_3": "fashionable"
      },
      {
        "id": "1943",
        "question": "What is one of the most important needs of your body? It will make your body more efficient, stronger, and healthier.",
        "answer": "exercise",
        "distractor_1": "calories",
        "distractor_2": "suppleness",
        "distractor_3": "good posture"
      },
      {
        "id": "1944",
        "question": "Which of the following is the invisible film of bacteria that forms on your teeth?",
        "answer": "plaque",
        "distractor_1": "decay",
        "distractor_2": "tartar",
        "distractor_3": "fluoride"
      },
      {
        "id": "1945",
        "question": "Which of the following terms means that you can do more exercise with less effort?",
        "answer": "stamina",
        "distractor_1": "suppleness",
        "distractor_2": "strength",
        "distractor_3": "energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "1946",
        "question": "Dentists advise you to brush your teeth at least twice a day. What type of toothbrush do dentists suggest to use?",
        "answer": "soft",
        "distractor_1": "electric",
        "distractor_2": "hard",
        "distractor_3": "large"
      },
      {
        "id": "1948",
        "question": "If your pulse is 12 beats every 10 seconds, what would your heart rate per minute be?",
        "answer": "72",
        "distractor_1": "120",
        "distractor_2": "84",
        "distractor_3": "60"
      },
      {
        "id": "1949",
        "question": "How much sleep do most teens need each night to look and feel their best?",
        "answer": "8 to 10 hours",
        "distractor_1": "10 to 12 hours",
        "distractor_2": "6 to 8 hours",
        "distractor_3": "4 to 6 hours"
      },
      {
        "id": "6109",
        "question": "What is the ability of muscles to function without oxygen?",
        "answer": "Anaerobic respiration",
        "distractor_1": "Aerobic respiration",
        "distractor_2": "Exercise",
        "distractor_3": "Stamina"
      },
      {
        "id": "6110",
        "question": "What is an overproduction of perspiration or abnormal sebaceous gland activity?",
        "answer": "Hyperhidrosis",
        "distractor_1": "Halitosis",
        "distractor_2": "Epidermis",
        "distractor_3": "Anaerobic respiration"
      },
      {
        "id": "6111",
        "question": "What is measurement of the amount of energy given to the body in the food we eat?",
        "answer": "Calorie",
        "distractor_1": "Fat",
        "distractor_2": "Grams",
        "distractor_3": "Saturated fat"
      },
      {
        "id": "6112",
        "question": "What is a doctor who specializes in skin diseases and disorders, such as acne?",
        "answer": "Dermatologist",
        "distractor_1": "Hyperhidrosis",
        "distractor_2": "Bacteriologist",
        "distractor_3": "Pharmacist"
      },
      {
        "id": "6113",
        "question": "What is the protective top layer of the skin?",
        "answer": "Epidermis",
        "distractor_1": "Halitosis",
        "distractor_2": "Skinadermis",
        "distractor_3": "Cuticle"
      },
      {
        "id": "6114",
        "question": "What is oily or greasy matter making up the bulk of adipose tissue?",
        "answer": "Fat",
        "distractor_1": "Halitosis",
        "distractor_2": "Tartar",
        "distractor_3": "Epidermis"
      },
      {
        "id": "6115",
        "question": "What is the amount of physical activity a person's body can do; it is increased by regular exercise and proper nutrition?",
        "answer": "Fitness",
        "distractor_1": "Anaerobic respiration",
        "distractor_2": "Aerobic respiration",
        "distractor_3": "Exertion"
      },
      {
        "id": "6116",
        "question": "What is a condition in which bacteria from tooth decay or smoking cause a bad odor in the mouth?",
        "answer": "Halitosis",
        "distractor_1": "Hyperhidrosis",
        "distractor_2": "Fatigue",
        "distractor_3": "Tartar"
      },
      {
        "id": "6117",
        "question": "What is the look and shape of a body?",
        "answer": "Physique",
        "distractor_1": "Body shape",
        "distractor_2": "Body type",
        "distractor_3": "Fitness"
      },
      {
        "id": "6118",
        "question": "What is a deposit build-up of small pieces of food and plaque on the teeth that causes decay?",
        "answer": "Tartar",
        "distractor_1": "Plaque",
        "distractor_2": "Gingivitis",
        "distractor_3": "Cavity"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "320",
    "name": "Weights & Measures",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "5345",
        "question": "What is the abbreviation for pound?",
        "answer": "lb",
        "distractor_1": "'",
        "distractor_2": "P",
        "distractor_3": "'"
      },
      {
        "id": "5283",
        "question": "How many milliliters are in one liter?",
        "answer": "1,000",
        "distractor_1": "100",
        "distractor_2": "10,000",
        "distractor_3": "10"
      },
      {
        "id": "5284",
        "question": "Four cubic centimeters of tree sap are put into a beaker that weighs 14 grams. The weight on a scale is 32 grams. What is the weight of one cubic centimeter of tree sap?",
        "answer": "4.5 grams",
        "distractor_1": "4.8 grams",
        "distractor_2": "8 grams",
        "distractor_3": "18 grams"
      },
      {
        "id": "5285",
        "question": "If the thermometer outside reads 10º Celsius, what should you wear?",
        "answer": "lightweight coat",
        "distractor_1": "heavy coat, gloves, and a hat",
        "distractor_2": "shorts and sandals",
        "distractor_3": "swimming suit"
      },
      {
        "id": "5286",
        "question": "What are the units for measuring capacity in the Customary System?",
        "answer": "fluid ounce, cup, pint, quart, gallon",
        "distractor_1": "ounce, pound, ton",
        "distractor_2": "milliliter, liter, kiloliter",
        "distractor_3": "inch, foot, mile"
      },
      {
        "id": "5287",
        "question": "Find the volume of a rectangular aquarium that is 3 feet long, 1.5 feet wide, and 2.5 feet deep.",
        "answer": "11.25 cubic feet",
        "distractor_1": "7 cubic feet",
        "distractor_2": "4.5 cubic feet",
        "distractor_3": "9 cubic feet"
      },
      {
        "id": "5288",
        "question": "What is the term defined by the amount of space that an object occupies?",
        "answer": "volume",
        "distractor_1": "weight",
        "distractor_2": "density",
        "distractor_3": "specific gravity"
      },
      {
        "id": "5289",
        "question": "What is the primary International System unit used to measure liquid capacity?",
        "answer": "liter",
        "distractor_1": "meter",
        "distractor_2": "ounce",
        "distractor_3": "gram"
      },
      {
        "id": "5290",
        "question": "The temperature outside reads 0º Celsius. If you placed a pan of water outside, what would you expect to happen?",
        "answer": "The water will freeze.",
        "distractor_1": "The water will be warm.",
        "distractor_2": "The water will boil.",
        "distractor_3": "The water will be cool."
      },
      {
        "id": "5291",
        "question": "What are the units for measuring capacity in the Customary System?",
        "answer": "fluid ounce, cup, pint, quart, gallon",
        "distractor_1": "ounce, pound, ton",
        "distractor_2": "milliliter, liter, kiloliter",
        "distractor_3": "inch, foot, mile"
      },
      {
        "id": "5292",
        "question": "How many millimeters are in one meter?",
        "answer": "1,000",
        "distractor_1": "10,000",
        "distractor_2": "100",
        "distractor_3": "10"
      },
      {
        "id": "5293",
        "question": "How many quarts are in one gallon?",
        "answer": "4",
        "distractor_1": "2",
        "distractor_2": "6",
        "distractor_3": "8"
      },
      {
        "id": "5294",
        "question": "Which unit of measurement is NOT in the International System of Units?",
        "answer": "inch",
        "distractor_1": "gram",
        "distractor_2": "meter",
        "distractor_3": "liter"
      },
      {
        "id": "5295",
        "question": "Which unit of measurement is NOT in the International System of Units?",
        "answer": "quart",
        "distractor_1": "liter",
        "distractor_2": "meter",
        "distractor_3": "gram"
      },
      {
        "id": "5296",
        "question": "How many quarts are in one gallon?",
        "answer": "4",
        "distractor_1": "8",
        "distractor_2": "6",
        "distractor_3": "2"
      },
      {
        "id": "5297",
        "question": "How many meters are in one kilometer?",
        "answer": "1,000",
        "distractor_1": "10",
        "distractor_2": "100",
        "distractor_3": "10,000"
      },
      {
        "id": "5298",
        "question": "What does the prefix 'centi' mean?",
        "answer": "0.01",
        "distractor_1": "100",
        "distractor_2": "10",
        "distractor_3": "0.001"
      },
      {
        "id": "5299",
        "question": "If you set a pan of water outside and the thermometer outside reads 0º Celsius, what can you expect to happen?",
        "answer": "The water will freeze.",
        "distractor_1": "The water will boil.",
        "distractor_2": "The water will be warm.",
        "distractor_3": "The water will be cool."
      },
      {
        "id": "5300",
        "question": "One additional unit of measurement is the long ton. How many pounds are in the long ton?",
        "answer": "2,240 pounds",
        "distractor_1": "2,000 pounds",
        "distractor_2": "2,200 pounds",
        "distractor_3": "2,400 pounds"
      },
      {
        "id": "5301",
        "question": "To determine the volume of a rock, Sue placed it in a graduated cylinder that contained 50 milliliters of water. After the rock was placed in the cylinder, the water level read 73 milliliters. What was the volume of the rock?",
        "answer": "23 milliliters",
        "distractor_1": "123 milliliters",
        "distractor_2": "50 milliliters",
        "distractor_3": "72 milliliters"
      },
      {
        "id": "5302",
        "question": "What are the three primary units of measurement in the International System of Units?",
        "answer": "liter, meter, gram",
        "distractor_1": "ounce, kilogram, pound",
        "distractor_2": "liter, quart, inch",
        "distractor_3": "pound, liter, gram"
      },
      {
        "id": "5303",
        "question": "Which formula would be used to calculate the area of a piece of land on which elk travel that is 2 kilometers wide and 8 kilometers long?",
        "answer": "A = L  •. W",
        "distractor_1": "V = pi  •. r²",
        "distractor_2": "L  •. W  •. H",
        "distractor_3": "A + B = C"
      },
      {
        "id": "5304",
        "question": "Which represents the prefixes in order from least to greatest?",
        "answer": "milli, centi, deci, deka, hecto, kilo",
        "distractor_1": "kilo, hecto, deka, deci, centi, milli",
        "distractor_2": "milli, centi, deka, hecto, deci, kilo",
        "distractor_3": "kilo, milli, hecto, centi, deka, deci"
      },
      {
        "id": "5306",
        "question": "If the thermometer outside reads 30º Celsius, how should you dress?",
        "answer": "shorts and sandals",
        "distractor_1": "heavy coat, gloves, and a hat",
        "distractor_2": "lightweight coat",
        "distractor_3": "sweatshirt and jeans"
      },
      {
        "id": "5307",
        "question": "The water in Joe's home contains 152 mg/l of calcium carbonate. Joe uses 76 liters of water when showering. How much calcium carbonate passes through during each shower?",
        "answer": "11.552 grams",
        "distractor_1": "228 grams",
        "distractor_2": "1.1552 grams",
        "distractor_3": "2 grams"
      },
      {
        "id": "5308",
        "question": "What is a benchmark measurement for one kilogram?",
        "answer": "mass of a small textbook",
        "distractor_1": "length of a loaf of bread",
        "distractor_2": "mass of a paper clip",
        "distractor_3": "weight of a slice of bread"
      },
      {
        "id": "5310",
        "question": "Which represents the prefixes in order from least to greatest?",
        "answer": "milli, centi, deci, deka, hecto, kilo",
        "distractor_1": "kilo, milli, hecto, centi, deka, deci",
        "distractor_2": "kilo, hecto, deka, deci, centi, milli",
        "distractor_3": "milli, centi, deka, hecto, deci, kilo"
      },
      {
        "id": "6019",
        "question": "What is a system of measurement used in the U.S?  This system includes units for measuring length, capacity, and weight.",
        "answer": "Customary System",
        "distractor_1": "Metric System",
        "distractor_2": "English Metrics",
        "distractor_3": "Inches and feet"
      },
      {
        "id": "6020",
        "question": "What is the basic unit of length in the metric system?",
        "answer": "Meter",
        "distractor_1": "Inch",
        "distractor_2": "Centimeter",
        "distractor_3": "Foot"
      },
      {
        "id": "6021",
        "question": "What is an ancient unit of linear measurement originally equal to the distance from the tip of the middle finger to the elbow?",
        "answer": "Cubit",
        "distractor_1": "Cubed centimeter",
        "distractor_2": "Inch",
        "distractor_3": "millimeter"
      },
      {
        "id": "6023",
        "question": "What is the line segment where two faces of a solid figure meet?",
        "answer": "Edge",
        "distractor_1": "Corner",
        "distractor_2": "Intersection",
        "distractor_3": "Perpendicular"
      },
      {
        "id": "6024",
        "question": "What is a comparison of two numbers using division?",
        "answer": "Ratio",
        "distractor_1": "Denominator",
        "distractor_2": "Inequality",
        "distractor_3": "Cubit"
      },
      {
        "id": "6026",
        "question": "What method solves a problem by analyzing the units?",
        "answer": "Dimensional analysis",
        "distractor_1": "Parallel analysis",
        "distractor_2": "Dimensional integrating",
        "distractor_3": "Analog dimensions "
      },
      {
        "id": "6029",
        "question": "What is a standard system of measurement based on the metric system?",
        "answer": "International System of Units",
        "distractor_1": "English National System of Units",
        "distractor_2": "United Kingdom System of Measurement",
        "distractor_3": "National System of Measurement"
      },
      {
        "id": "6030",
        "question": "What is the amount of matter in an object?",
        "answer": "Mass",
        "distractor_1": "Weight",
        "distractor_2": "Force",
        "distractor_3": "Volume"
      },
      {
        "id": "6031",
        "question": "What is the maximum amount that can be contained by an object?",
        "answer": "Capacity",
        "distractor_1": "Volume",
        "distractor_2": "Mass",
        "distractor_3": "Weight"
      },
      {
        "id": "6032",
        "question": "What is the basic unit of mass or weight in the metric system?",
        "answer": "Gram",
        "distractor_1": "Ounce",
        "distractor_2": "Pound",
        "distractor_3": "Centimeter"
      },
      {
        "id": "6034",
        "question": "What is a plane figure that serves as one side of a solid figure?",
        "answer": "Faces",
        "distractor_1": "Interface",
        "distractor_2": "Dimension",
        "distractor_3": "Flat"
      },
      {
        "id": "6035",
        "question": "What is the point at which two line segments, lines, or rays meet to form an angle?",
        "answer": "Vertex",
        "distractor_1": "Vortex",
        "distractor_2": "Vertox",
        "distractor_3": "Vertigo"
      },
      {
        "id": "6037",
        "question": "What is information, especially numerical information, organized for analysis?",
        "answer": "Data",
        "distractor_1": "Scientific research",
        "distractor_2": "example",
        "distractor_3": "hypothesis"
      },
      {
        "id": "6057",
        "question": "What is a s a single mark used to indicate congruent line segments. Segments that have the same number of hatch marks are congruent?",
        "answer": "Single Hatch Mark",
        "distractor_1": "Unit marks",
        "distractor_2": "Value marks",
        "distractor_3": "Tally mark"
      },
      {
        "id": "6058",
        "question": "What is a double mark used to indicate congruent line segments. Segments that have the same number of hatch marks are congruent?",
        "answer": "Double Hatch Mark",
        "distractor_1": "Unit marks",
        "distractor_2": "Value marks",
        "distractor_3": "Tally mark"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "322",
    "name": "Snack Nutrition",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8326",
        "question": "What are the main body-building nutrients?",
        "answer": "proteins",
        "distractor_1": "minerals",
        "distractor_2": "vitamins",
        "distractor_3": "carbohydrates"
      },
      {
        "id": "2526",
        "question": "Which of the following snacks have the lowest fat content?",
        "answer": "100 jelly beans",
        "distractor_1": "20 potato chips",
        "distractor_2": "10 chocolate kisses",
        "distractor_3": "2 peanut butter cups"
      },
      {
        "id": "2527",
        "question": "A material found in the skins of potatoes, apples, grapes, and grains aids digestion and is thought to prevent some kinds of cancer. What is this material?",
        "answer": "fiber",
        "distractor_1": "vitamins",
        "distractor_2": "protein",
        "distractor_3": "sugar"
      },
      {
        "id": "2528",
        "question": "Cholesterol intake should be limited in a diet. Why?",
        "answer": "It has been linked to heart disease.",
        "distractor_1": "It causes cancer.",
        "distractor_2": "It contains a lot of calories.",
        "distractor_3": "It is a mood-altering drug."
      },
      {
        "id": "2529",
        "question": "What are the three types of carbohydrates?",
        "answer": "sugar, starch, and fiber",
        "distractor_1": "sugar, protein, and fiber",
        "distractor_2": "sugar, protein, and fat",
        "distractor_3": "vitamins, minerals, and starch"
      },
      {
        "id": "2533",
        "question": "Some types of fat in foods can lead to a waxy buildup in the arteries that makes it difficult for blood to pass through. In what age group does this process begin?",
        "answer": "childhood",
        "distractor_1": "teenagers",
        "distractor_2": "young adults",
        "distractor_3": "older adults"
      },
      {
        "id": "2536",
        "question": "Most vending machine snacks and fast food snacks are bad for you. Why?",
        "answer": "they are high in fat",
        "distractor_1": "they are high in protein",
        "distractor_2": "they are high in fiber",
        "distractor_3": "they are high in nutrients"
      },
      {
        "id": "2537",
        "question": "Depending on their age, activity level, and body efficiency, people require different amounts of calories. How many calories does the average middle school student require to meet his or her daily needs?",
        "answer": "2,000-3,000 calories",
        "distractor_1": "1,200-1,500 calories",
        "distractor_2": "1,500-2,000 calories",
        "distractor_3": "3,000-4,000 calories"
      },
      {
        "id": "2538",
        "question": "What type of vitamins are thiamine, niacin, and riboflavin?",
        "answer": "B vitamins",
        "distractor_1": "A vitamins",
        "distractor_2": "C vitamins",
        "distractor_3": "D vitamins"
      },
      {
        "id": "2539",
        "question": "Which of the following are foods high in sugar and empty calories?",
        "answer": "junk foods",
        "distractor_1": "growth foods",
        "distractor_2": "body-building foods",
        "distractor_3": "repair foods"
      },
      {
        "id": "2541",
        "question": "What fraction of the average teenager’s diet consists of snacks?",
        "answer": "1/4",
        "distractor_1": "1/10",
        "distractor_2": "1/2",
        "distractor_3": "1/3"
      },
      {
        "id": "8189",
        "question": "What are chemical substances in food that are used by your body to keep it going?",
        "answer": "nutrients",
        "distractor_1": "vitamins",
        "distractor_2": " additives",
        "distractor_3": "calories"
      },
      {
        "id": "2543",
        "question": "Which of the following can be associated with the large amounts of sodium that are found in many snack foods including crackers, chips, and nuts?",
        "answer": "high blood pressure",
        "distractor_1": "slow metabolism",
        "distractor_2": "good eyesight",
        "distractor_3": "healthy hair"
      },
      {
        "id": "2547",
        "question": "Which group of people need the most calories and nutrients?",
        "answer": "teenagers",
        "distractor_1": "preteens",
        "distractor_2": "young adults",
        "distractor_3": "older adults"
      },
      {
        "id": "2548",
        "question": "How many teaspoons equal one tablespoon when measuring ingredients?",
        "answer": "3",
        "distractor_1": "4",
        "distractor_2": "2",
        "distractor_3": "5"
      },
      {
        "id": "2550",
        "question": "Suppose a recipe will make four dozen cookies. How many cookies will the recipe make?",
        "answer": "48",
        "distractor_1": "16",
        "distractor_2": "36",
        "distractor_3": "24"
      },
      {
        "id": "5551",
        "question": "This term is defined as the measurement of the amount of energy given to the body in the food we eat.",
        "answer": "calorie",
        "distractor_1": "etiquette",
        "distractor_2": "fat",
        "distractor_3": "obesity"
      },
      {
        "id": "8327",
        "question": "This term is defined as the process by which the body takes in and uses food substances.",
        "answer": "nutrition",
        "distractor_1": "absorption",
        "distractor_2": "digestion",
        "distractor_3": "conversion"
      },
      {
        "id": "5552",
        "question": "This term is defined as a nutrient compound found in foods that gives the body essential energy.",
        "answer": "carbohydrate",
        "distractor_1": "protein",
        "distractor_2": "fat",
        "distractor_3": "mineral"
      },
      {
        "id": "5553",
        "question": "This term is defined as a bowl with many small holes used to drain liquid from foods.",
        "answer": "colander",
        "distractor_1": "casserole",
        "distractor_2": "cavity",
        "distractor_3": "cellulose"
      },
      {
        "id": "5554",
        "question": "This term is defined as a condition in the body when it is lacking fluids; also, a process in which foods are dried by removing the liquid from them.",
        "answer": "dehydration",
        "distractor_1": "inhalation",
        "distractor_2": "immunization",
        "distractor_3": "pasteurization"
      },
      {
        "id": "5556",
        "question": "This term is defined as a compound found in foods, such as butter, that is essential to the body.",
        "answer": "fat",
        "distractor_1": "calorie",
        "distractor_2": "vitamin",
        "distractor_3": "protein"
      },
      {
        "id": "5559",
        "question": "This term is defined as a disorder in which a person has excessive body fat.",
        "answer": "obesity",
        "distractor_1": "intolerance",
        "distractor_2": "deficiency",
        "distractor_3": "hyperthyroidism"
      },
      {
        "id": "5560",
        "question": "This term is defined as a carbohydrate for the body usually found in plants, especially wheat and rice.",
        "answer": "starch",
        "distractor_1": "fat",
        "distractor_2": "protein",
        "distractor_3": "mineral"
      },
      {
        "id": "8328",
        "question": "What particle is made up of two or more atoms held together by forces between the atoms?",
        "answer": "molecule",
        "distractor_1": "atom",
        "distractor_2": "nucleus",
        "distractor_3": "electron"
      },
      {
        "id": "8331",
        "question": "Members of which age group need the most calories and nutrients?",
        "answer": "teenagers",
        "distractor_1": "preteens",
        "distractor_2": "young adults",
        "distractor_3": "older adults"
      },
      {
        "id": "8332",
        "question": "Teenagers love to snack. Snacks account for what fraction of the average teenager's diet?",
        "answer": "one-fourth",
        "distractor_1": "one-tenth",
        "distractor_2": "one-third",
        "distractor_3": "one-half "
      },
      {
        "id": "8333",
        "question": "People require different amounts of calories depending on their age, activity level, and body efficiency. How many calories does the average middle school student need each day?",
        "answer": "2,000-3,000",
        "distractor_1": "1,200-1,500",
        "distractor_2": "1,500-2,000",
        "distractor_3": "3,000-4,000"
      },
      {
        "id": "8334",
        "question": "When measuring ingredients, how many teaspoons equal one tablespoon?",
        "answer": "three",
        "distractor_1": "four",
        "distractor_2": "two",
        "distractor_3": "five"
      },
      {
        "id": "8335",
        "question": "The skins on potatoes, apples, grapes, and grains contain a material that aids digestion and is thought to prevent some kinds of cancer. What is it?",
        "answer": "fiber",
        "distractor_1": "sugar",
        "distractor_2": "vitamins",
        "distractor_3": "protein"
      },
      {
        "id": "8336",
        "question": "Many snack foods, including crackers, chips, and nuts, contain high amounts of sodium. Salt is associated with which of the following?",
        "answer": "high blood pressure",
        "distractor_1": "good eyesight",
        "distractor_2": "slow metabolism",
        "distractor_3": "healthy hair "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "323",
    "name": "Life Skills",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "3116",
        "question": "What term is defined as the body's response to events or changes in one's life?",
        "answer": "stress",
        "distractor_1": "conflict",
        "distractor_2": "physical fitness",
        "distractor_3": "body language"
      },
      {
        "id": "3117",
        "question": "If one of your friends shows signs of serious depression, how can you help him or her?",
        "answer": "tell a responsible adult",
        "distractor_1": "throw a party",
        "distractor_2": "offer antidepressants",
        "distractor_3": "avoid him or her (don't bother him or her)"
      },
      {
        "id": "3118",
        "question": "Developing your talents, abilities, and sense of humor and looking for positive relationships are ways to improve what aspect of your character?",
        "answer": "self-concept",
        "distractor_1": "behavior",
        "distractor_2": "personality",
        "distractor_3": "attitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "3119",
        "question": "By what are you influenced if you are pushed by your friends into doing something you don't really want to do?",
        "answer": "peer pressure",
        "distractor_1": "a gang",
        "distractor_2": "group action",
        "distractor_3": "affirmative action"
      },
      {
        "id": "3121",
        "question": "What is the most common illegal drug used by teenagers?",
        "answer": "alcohol",
        "distractor_1": "cocaine",
        "distractor_2": "marijuana",
        "distractor_3": "steroids"
      },
      {
        "id": "3122",
        "question": "What term is defined as sense of worth, or how a person feels about himself or herself?",
        "answer": "self-esteem",
        "distractor_1": "attitude",
        "distractor_2": "personality profile",
        "distractor_3": "self-actualization"
      },
      {
        "id": "3123",
        "question": "When people maintain positive relationships with others, they have fewer what?",
        "answer": "physical illnesses",
        "distractor_1": "careers",
        "distractor_2": "children",
        "distractor_3": "friends"
      },
      {
        "id": "3124",
        "question": "Warning signs such as withdrawal, lack of interest, personality changes, moody behavior, neglect of personal appearance, and the giving away of cherished possessions are indicators of what condition?",
        "answer": "suicide",
        "distractor_1": "depression",
        "distractor_2": "alcoholism",
        "distractor_3": "stress"
      },
      {
        "id": "3125",
        "question": "What are two major factors that influence one's personality?",
        "answer": "heredity and environment",
        "distractor_1": "age and wealth",
        "distractor_2": "culture and nationality",
        "distractor_3": "size and IQ"
      },
      {
        "id": "3126",
        "question": "What term is defined as ideas, objects, and beliefs that are important to an individual?",
        "answer": "values",
        "distractor_1": "standards",
        "distractor_2": "ethics",
        "distractor_3": "goals"
      },
      {
        "id": "3129",
        "question": "There are many ways to manage stress. What are two personal habits that you should examine when feeling stressed?",
        "answer": "eating and sleeping",
        "distractor_1": "exercise and work",
        "distractor_2": "time management and study",
        "distractor_3": "posture and hygiene"
      },
      {
        "id": "3132",
        "question": "To help you manage stress, you should examine these two personal habits.",
        "answer": "eating, sleeping",
        "distractor_1": "posture, hygiene",
        "distractor_2": "exercise, work",
        "distractor_3": "time management, study"
      },
      {
        "id": "3133",
        "question": "What commonly used defense mechanism is defined as the transfer of negative feelings about one situation to another person?",
        "answer": "displacement",
        "distractor_1": "projection",
        "distractor_2": "rationalization",
        "distractor_3": "compensation"
      },
      {
        "id": "3135",
        "question": "What term is defined as forming an interconnected group whose members work together to help one another?",
        "answer": "networking",
        "distractor_1": "therapy",
        "distractor_2": "help group",
        "distractor_3": "work group"
      },
      {
        "id": "8191",
        "question": "Smoking is linked to about 360,000 deaths per year in the United States. In the past 15 years, approximately how many deaths in the United States resulted from smoking?",
        "answer": "5.4 million",
        "distractor_1": "4.2 million",
        "distractor_2": "6.4 million",
        "distractor_3": "4.8 million"
      },
      {
        "id": "8192",
        "question": "In 1980, 72% of high school seniors drank alcohol the month prior to a National Institute survey. In 1990, the number fell to 57%. At this rate, how many seniors will drink alcohol in the year 2010?",
        "answer": "27%",
        "distractor_1": "42%",
        "distractor_2": "32%",
        "distractor_3": "15%"
      },
      {
        "id": "5390",
        "question": "Which of the following is the overwhelming negative and sad feelings about oneself and/or life? ",
        "answer": "depression",
        "distractor_1": "self-concept",
        "distractor_2": "self-esteem",
        "distractor_3": "personality"
      },
      {
        "id": "5391",
        "question": "What is the set of traits that are consistent with a person's behavior? ",
        "answer": "personality",
        "distractor_1": "attitude",
        "distractor_2": "values",
        "distractor_3": "behavior"
      },
      {
        "id": "5392",
        "question": "What term means a body's response to physical or mental tension?",
        "answer": "stress",
        "distractor_1": "peer pressure",
        "distractor_2": "depression",
        "distractor_3": "attitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "5393",
        "question": "What are the principles and beliefs that a person feels that impact their behavior and decisions? ",
        "answer": "values",
        "distractor_1": "morals",
        "distractor_2": "responsibilities",
        "distractor_3": "personality"
      },
      {
        "id": "5394",
        "question": "What is one's feelings toward a person or thing, usually learned from one's environment? ",
        "answer": "attitude",
        "distractor_1": "stress",
        "distractor_2": "ethics",
        "distractor_3": "anger"
      },
      {
        "id": "5396",
        "question": "What does it mean to be accountable for one's actions?",
        "answer": "responsible",
        "distractor_1": "irresponsible",
        "distractor_2": "unhappy",
        "distractor_3": "depressed"
      },
      {
        "id": "8193",
        "question": "There are about 110,000 deaths yearly due to lung cancer. About 4,000 of these deaths were people who didn't smoke, but who inhaled second-hand smoke. What percentage of the lung-cancer deaths were due to second-hand smoke?",
        "answer": "3.6%",
        "distractor_1": "4%",
        "distractor_2": "4.4%",
        "distractor_3": "3.2%"
      },
      {
        "id": "8194",
        "question": "The National Crime survey estimates that 6.7 percent of teenagers have been victims of violent crime, compared to 2.6 percent of people over age 19. Based on these statistics, which of the following statements is true?",
        "answer": "Teens are about 2.5 times more likely to be victims.",
        "distractor_1": "Most teenagers have already been victims.",
        "distractor_2": "Most violent crimes are committed against people over 19.",
        "distractor_3": "Most violent crimes are committed against people under 19."
      },
      {
        "id": "8214",
        "question": "What term is defined as the mental picture you have of yourself?",
        "answer": "self-concept",
        "distractor_1": "mood",
        "distractor_2": "self-esteem",
        "distractor_3": "perception"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "324",
    "name": "Body Systems",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "3989",
        "question": "What is the importance of valves in the heart and veins of the circulatory system?",
        "answer": "to prevent backflow of blood",
        "distractor_1": "to speed the rate of blood flow",
        "distractor_2": "to increase efficiency of oxygen exchange with body tissues",
        "distractor_3": "to ensure that nutrients and oxygen flow in different directions"
      },
      {
        "id": "4521",
        "question": "Of the following body systems that excrete waste products, which system also helps to regulate body temperature?",
        "answer": "integumentary",
        "distractor_1": "digestive",
        "distractor_2": "urinary",
        "distractor_3": "respiratory"
      },
      {
        "id": "4522",
        "question": "Which body system returns body fluids from the tissues to the bloodstream?",
        "answer": "lymphatic",
        "distractor_1": "respiratory",
        "distractor_2": "urinary",
        "distractor_3": "integumentary"
      },
      {
        "id": "4523",
        "question": "Which function does the nervous system have that the endocrine system lacks?",
        "answer": "rapid response to body changes",
        "distractor_1": "communication and control",
        "distractor_2": "response to internal body conditions",
        "distractor_3": "hormone production"
      },
      {
        "id": "3990",
        "question": "Of the following body systems that excrete waste products, which system filters the blood to remove metabolic wastes?",
        "answer": "urinary",
        "distractor_1": "digestive",
        "distractor_2": "respiratory",
        "distractor_3": "integumentary"
      },
      {
        "id": "3991",
        "question": "Which body system is lined with mucous membranes and cilia that trap and prevent disease organisms from entering the body?",
        "answer": "respiratory",
        "distractor_1": "circulatory",
        "distractor_2": "lymphatic",
        "distractor_3": "integumentary"
      },
      {
        "id": "3993",
        "question": "Compare the direction in which oxygen and carbon dioxide move during gas exchange in the alveoli.",
        "answer": "Only oxygen moves from alveoli into capillaries.",
        "distractor_1": "Only oxygen moves from capillaries into alveoli.",
        "distractor_2": "Both move from alveoli into capillaries.",
        "distractor_3": "Both move from capillaries into alveoli."
      },
      {
        "id": "3995",
        "question": "Which digestive process occurs between the villi of the small intestine and the intestinal capillaries?",
        "answer": "absorption",
        "distractor_1": "digestion",
        "distractor_2": "elimination",
        "distractor_3": "peristalsis"
      },
      {
        "id": "3996",
        "question": "Which two systems serve as the body's communication and control systems?",
        "answer": "nervous and endocrine",
        "distractor_1": "nervous and circulatory",
        "distractor_2": "endocrine and lymphatic",
        "distractor_3": "circulatory and lymphatic"
      },
      {
        "id": "3998",
        "question": "What is removed from the body as oxygen is drawn into the lungs through the respiratory system? ",
        "answer": "carbon dioxide",
        "distractor_1": "excess white blood cells",
        "distractor_2": "platelets",
        "distractor_3": "sulfuric acid"
      },
      {
        "id": "3999",
        "question": "In the circulatory system, these blood vessels carry oxygen-rich blood away from the heart.",
        "answer": "arteries",
        "distractor_1": "capillaries",
        "distractor_2": "veins",
        "distractor_3": "platelets"
      },
      {
        "id": "4000",
        "question": "Which two structures work together to absorb nutrients in the digestive tract?",
        "answer": "villi of small intestine and intestinal capillaries",
        "distractor_1": "mucous cells of stomach and stomach capillaries",
        "distractor_2": "villi of small intestine and liver tissue",
        "distractor_3": "liver tissue and liver capillaries"
      },
      {
        "id": "4001",
        "question": "Which organs or tissues serve as the body's first line of defense against invading disease organisms?",
        "answer": "skin and mucous membranes",
        "distractor_1": "lungs and spleen",
        "distractor_2": "lymph nodes",
        "distractor_3": "white blood cells"
      },
      {
        "id": "4002",
        "question": "In what structure of the respiratory system does gas exchange occur?",
        "answer": "alveolus",
        "distractor_1": "bronchiole",
        "distractor_2": "trachea",
        "distractor_3": "diaphragm"
      },
      {
        "id": "4003",
        "question": "What term describes all body systems working together to maintain a stable and healthy internal environment?",
        "answer": "homeostasis",
        "distractor_1": "metabolism",
        "distractor_2": "cellular respiration",
        "distractor_3": "physiology"
      },
      {
        "id": "4005",
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a type of muscle tissue?",
        "answer": "compact",
        "distractor_1": "cardiac",
        "distractor_2": "skeletal",
        "distractor_3": "smooth"
      },
      {
        "id": "4007",
        "question": "Blood cell production and calcium storage are important functions of which body system?",
        "answer": "skeletal",
        "distractor_1": "muscular",
        "distractor_2": "lymphatic",
        "distractor_3": "circulatory"
      },
      {
        "id": "4008",
        "question": "Skeletal, or voluntary, muscle tissue is found in which region of the body?",
        "answer": "arms and legs",
        "distractor_1": "heart",
        "distractor_2": "torso",
        "distractor_3": "digestive tract"
      },
      {
        "id": "4009",
        "question": "Which system, working with the circulatory system, stores and releases white blood cells to fight disease?",
        "answer": "lymphatic",
        "distractor_1": "respiratory",
        "distractor_2": "urinary",
        "distractor_3": "integumentary"
      },
      {
        "id": "4011",
        "question": "When does the digestive process begin?",
        "answer": "as soon as you take a bite of food",
        "distractor_1": "approximately 30 minutes after eating",
        "distractor_2": "as soon as food enters the stomach",
        "distractor_3": "in the small intestine"
      },
      {
        "id": "4013",
        "question": "In double circulation, the right and left sides of the heart pump blood to different body regions. Why is this important?",
        "answer": "It increases efficiency of oxygen exchange with tissues.",
        "distractor_1": "It speeds the rate of blood flow.",
        "distractor_2": "It prevents back-flow of blood.",
        "distractor_3": "It pumps nutrients and oxygen in different directions."
      },
      {
        "id": "4014",
        "question": "In addition to structure and support, the skeletal system carries out which two functions?",
        "answer": "calcium storage; blood cell production",
        "distractor_1": "toxic product storage; disease prevention",
        "distractor_2": "nerve impulse transmission; hormone production",
        "distractor_3": "oxygen uptake; carbon dioxide removal"
      },
      {
        "id": "4015",
        "question": "Which body movement is controlled by the actions of smooth muscle tissue?",
        "answer": "peristalsis",
        "distractor_1": "heartbeat",
        "distractor_2": "walking",
        "distractor_3": "flexing the biceps"
      },
      {
        "id": "4016",
        "question": "Homeostasis, or maintenance of a stable internal environment, is the function of which system or systems?",
        "answer": "all body systems working together",
        "distractor_1": "nervous system only",
        "distractor_2": "nervous and endocrine systems",
        "distractor_3": "endocrine and excretory systems"
      },
      {
        "id": "6159",
        "question": "What is the name of the blood vessel that carries blood toward the heart?",
        "answer": "vein",
        "distractor_1": "artery",
        "distractor_2": "cerebellum",
        "distractor_3": "synovial membrane"
      },
      {
        "id": "6160",
        "question": "What is the structure forming skin and containing oil glands, sweat glands, and hair follicles?",
        "answer": "cutaneous membrane",
        "distractor_1": "cerebellum",
        "distractor_2": "liver",
        "distractor_3": "ligament"
      },
      {
        "id": "6161",
        "question": "What is known as the structure lining a joint cavity and secreting a lubricating fluid?",
        "answer": "synovial membrane",
        "distractor_1": "cutaneous membrane",
        "distractor_2": "cartilage",
        "distractor_3": "muscle"
      },
      {
        "id": "6162",
        "question": "What is the largest portion of brain, including areas for learning, thought, and memory?",
        "answer": "cerebrum",
        "distractor_1": "cerebellum",
        "distractor_2": "temporal lobe",
        "distractor_3": "skull"
      },
      {
        "id": "6163",
        "question": "What is known as the portion of brain that initiates and helps control movement, balance, and coordination?",
        "answer": "cerebellum",
        "distractor_1": "cerebrum",
        "distractor_2": "cutaneous membrane",
        "distractor_3": "synovial membrane"
      },
      {
        "id": "6164",
        "question": "What endocrine gland of the female reproductive system that produces estrogen?",
        "answer": "ovary",
        "distractor_1": "pancreas",
        "distractor_2": "uterus",
        "distractor_3": "liver"
      },
      {
        "id": "6165",
        "question": "What endocrine gland of the male reproductive system that produces testosterone?",
        "answer": "testis",
        "distractor_1": "ovary",
        "distractor_2": "pancreas",
        "distractor_3": "liver"
      },
      {
        "id": "6166",
        "question": "Identify the substance inside long bones, in which blood cells are produced?",
        "answer": "marrow",
        "distractor_1": "cartilage",
        "distractor_2": "muscle",
        "distractor_3": "fluid"
      },
      {
        "id": "6167",
        "question": "Which organ produces both digestive enzymes and the hormone insulin?",
        "answer": "pancreas",
        "distractor_1": "liver",
        "distractor_2": "stomach",
        "distractor_3": "intestine"
      },
      {
        "id": "6168",
        "question": "Identify the vessel associated with veins that moves fluid from tissues into bloodstream?",
        "answer": "lymph vessel",
        "distractor_1": "blood vessel",
        "distractor_2": "vein",
        "distractor_3": "artery"
      },
      {
        "id": "6169",
        "question": "Which organ produces bile and digestive enzymes?",
        "answer": "liver",
        "distractor_1": "stomach",
        "distractor_2": "pancreas",
        "distractor_3": "kidney"
      },
      {
        "id": "6170",
        "question": "What is known as a series of chemical reactions that uses oxygen to break down sugars and release energy?",
        "answer": "cellular respiration",
        "distractor_1": "breathing",
        "distractor_2": "perspiration",
        "distractor_3": "radiation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6171",
        "question": "Which of the following is a connective tissue that binds bones together?",
        "answer": "ligament",
        "distractor_1": "cartilage",
        "distractor_2": "muscle",
        "distractor_3": "tendon"
      },
      {
        "id": "6172",
        "question": "Which of the following is one of a set of bones in the backbone, which protects the spinal cord?",
        "answer": "vertebra",
        "distractor_1": "spinal column",
        "distractor_2": "discs",
        "distractor_3": "spinal bones"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "325",
    "name": "Basic Sewing",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1711",
        "question": "How can threads be secured at the beginning and end of a seam?",
        "answer": "by backstitching",
        "distractor_1": "by directional stitching",
        "distractor_2": "by stay-stitching",
        "distractor_3": "by darts"
      },
      {
        "id": "1712",
        "question": "Identify the term for the looseness or tightness of stitches.",
        "answer": "tension",
        "distractor_1": "drag",
        "distractor_2": "bias",
        "distractor_3": "balance"
      },
      {
        "id": "1716",
        "question": "What are fabrics that combine natural fibers and manufactured fibers?",
        "answer": "blends",
        "distractor_1": "combos",
        "distractor_2": "mixes",
        "distractor_3": "duo fibers"
      },
      {
        "id": "1717",
        "question": "What is the part of the sewing machine that holds the fabric against the feed dog?",
        "answer": "presser foot",
        "distractor_1": "feed foot",
        "distractor_2": "pressure foot",
        "distractor_3": "pusher foot"
      },
      {
        "id": "1720",
        "question": "How wide is a standard seam allowance?",
        "answer": "5/8 inch",
        "distractor_1": "1/2 inch",
        "distractor_2": "3 millimeters",
        "distractor_3": "3 centimeters"
      },
      {
        "id": "1722",
        "question": "What is the term for stitching that joins two pieces of fabric?",
        "answer": "seam",
        "distractor_1": "dart",
        "distractor_2": "facing",
        "distractor_3": "baste"
      },
      {
        "id": "1723",
        "question": "What determines the speed of the sewing machine?",
        "answer": "foot control unit",
        "distractor_1": "handwheel",
        "distractor_2": "speed dial",
        "distractor_3": "hand control unit"
      },
      {
        "id": "1725",
        "question": "The terms conventional, separating, two-way, trouser, and decorative refer to different types of what?",
        "answer": "zippers",
        "distractor_1": "stitches",
        "distractor_2": "buttons",
        "distractor_3": "fabrics"
      },
      {
        "id": "6876",
        "question": "This term is defined as a layer of padding used between two pieces of fabric to add fullness and warmth.",
        "answer": "batting",
        "distractor_1": "grain",
        "distractor_2": "interface",
        "distractor_3": "selvage"
      },
      {
        "id": "6877",
        "question": "This term is defined as a spool-like object used to hold thread while sewing.",
        "answer": "bobbin",
        "distractor_1": "gauge",
        "distractor_2": "guide",
        "distractor_3": "handwheel"
      },
      {
        "id": "1729",
        "question": "What is a pencil-shaped object with a small blade on one end used to remove stitches?",
        "answer": "seam ripper",
        "distractor_1": "thread cutter",
        "distractor_2": "stitch remover",
        "distractor_3": "thread clipper"
      },
      {
        "id": "1731",
        "question": "How can you secure stitches at the end of a seam?",
        "answer": "backstitch",
        "distractor_1": "tie a knot",
        "distractor_2": "leave extra thread",
        "distractor_3": "zigzag stitch"
      },
      {
        "id": "1733",
        "question": "Identify the term for one letter or a group of letters that makes up a design.",
        "answer": "monogram",
        "distractor_1": "panagram",
        "distractor_2": "telegram",
        "distractor_3": "hologram"
      },
      {
        "id": "1734",
        "question": "To what do conventional, separating, two-way, trouser, and decorative refer?",
        "answer": "types of zippers",
        "distractor_1": "types of buttons",
        "distractor_2": "types of fabrics",
        "distractor_3": "types of stitches"
      },
      {
        "id": "1735",
        "question": "Identify the term for items such as thread, buttons, zippers, elastic, and interfacing that become part of a garment.",
        "answer": "notions",
        "distractor_1": "accessories",
        "distractor_2": "tools",
        "distractor_3": "trims"
      },
      {
        "id": "1736",
        "question": "Identify an example of a fiber that comes from a plant.",
        "answer": "flax",
        "distractor_1": "nylon",
        "distractor_2": "rayon",
        "distractor_3": "silk"
      },
      {
        "id": "6878",
        "question": "This term is defined as a method of sewing a tapered stitch on a garment that allows the garment to better fit the shape of the body.",
        "answer": "dart",
        "distractor_1": "bat",
        "distractor_2": "hand",
        "distractor_3": "back"
      },
      {
        "id": "6879",
        "question": "This term is defined as the part of the sewing machine that moves fabric toward the back of the machine under the presser foot.",
        "answer": "feed dog",
        "distractor_1": "sewing gauge",
        "distractor_2": "foot control",
        "distractor_3": "handwheel"
      },
      {
        "id": "6880",
        "question": "This term is defined as the round knob on the end of a sewing machine that advances the feed dog and causes the needle to move when turned.",
        "answer": "handwheel",
        "distractor_1": "feed dog",
        "distractor_2": "foot control",
        "distractor_3": "sewing gauge"
      },
      {
        "id": "6881",
        "question": "This term is defined as a fabric used to back another fabric and provide support and shape.",
        "answer": "interfacing",
        "distractor_1": "batting",
        "distractor_2": "quilting",
        "distractor_3": "lifting"
      },
      {
        "id": "6882",
        "question": "This term is defined as a six-inch ruler with a movable indicator that is used to transfer measurements in sewing.",
        "answer": "sewing gauge",
        "distractor_1": "thread guide",
        "distractor_2": "feed dog",
        "distractor_3": "handwheel"
      },
      {
        "id": "6883",
        "question": "This term is defined as a metal catch on a sewing machine that holds the thread and makes sure that it follows the correct path to the needle.",
        "answer": "thread guide",
        "distractor_1": "feed dog",
        "distractor_2": "sewing gauge",
        "distractor_3": "handwheel"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "327",
    "name": "Sewing & Design",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "5524",
        "question": "This term is defined as using design to create a sense of equality.",
        "answer": "balance",
        "distractor_1": "equal rights",
        "distractor_2": "evenism",
        "distractor_3": "proportion"
      },
      {
        "id": "5525",
        "question": "This term is defined as a diagonal line intersecting both grain lines.",
        "answer": "bias",
        "distractor_1": "mias",
        "distractor_2": "dias",
        "distractor_3": "chaise"
      },
      {
        "id": "5526",
        "question": "This term is defined as a method of permanently attaching two fabrics, usually done with chemicals.",
        "answer": "bonding",
        "distractor_1": "basting",
        "distractor_2": "stitching",
        "distractor_3": "ironing"
      },
      {
        "id": "5527",
        "question": "This term is defined as a selling agreement between two people in which Person A agrees to sell a product for Person B in return for a percentage of the profit.",
        "answer": "consignment",
        "distractor_1": "assignment",
        "distractor_2": "allowance",
        "distractor_3": "contractual"
      },
      {
        "id": "5528",
        "question": "This term is defined as pulling fabric together to add fullness.",
        "answer": "gathering",
        "distractor_1": "rendering",
        "distractor_2": "bonding",
        "distractor_3": "forming"
      },
      {
        "id": "5529",
        "question": "This term is defined as a type of fabric whose length-wise and cross-wise threads are at right angles from each other.",
        "answer": "on-grain",
        "distractor_1": "bias",
        "distractor_2": "gathering",
        "distractor_3": "Georgette"
      },
      {
        "id": "5530",
        "question": "This term is defined as a fabric weave used to make satin, because the weave of this fabric is shiny and soft.",
        "answer": "satin weave",
        "distractor_1": "Grosgrain",
        "distractor_2": "heading",
        "distractor_3": "Viscose"
      },
      {
        "id": "5532",
        "question": "This term is defined as an outline of an object.",
        "answer": "silhouette",
        "distractor_1": "draft",
        "distractor_2": "front band",
        "distractor_3": "grain line"
      },
      {
        "id": "5533",
        "question": "This term is defined as the look and feel of a fabric determined by how the threads and yarn are woven.",
        "answer": "texture",
        "distractor_1": "grain",
        "distractor_2": "bias",
        "distractor_3": "stitch"
      },
      {
        "id": "1743",
        "question": "You are buying material for a 24-inch by 24-inch square pillow. The material you want is 36 inches wide and sells for $6.95 per square yard. How much will the material for the pillow cost?",
        "answer": "$9.27",
        "distractor_1": "$10.43",
        "distractor_2": "$8.69",
        "distractor_3": "$12.74"
      },
      {
        "id": "1745",
        "question": "What is the best way to prepare the end of a piece of thread for threading a needle?",
        "answer": "cut it at an angle",
        "distractor_1": "bite it in two",
        "distractor_2": "break it in two",
        "distractor_3": "use a seam ripper"
      },
      {
        "id": "1746",
        "question": "What is the strongest of all the hand-sewn stitches?",
        "answer": "backstitch",
        "distractor_1": "running stitch",
        "distractor_2": "slipstitch",
        "distractor_3": "basting stitch"
      },
      {
        "id": "1747",
        "question": "What kind of stitch would you use to sew a pocket on a pair of jeans?",
        "answer": "topstitch",
        "distractor_1": "cross-stitch",
        "distractor_2": "basting stitch",
        "distractor_3": "overcast stitch"
      },
      {
        "id": "1748",
        "question": "What is the term for the sewing tool with an adjustable marker used for measuring short lengths?",
        "answer": "seam gauge",
        "distractor_1": "skirt marker",
        "distractor_2": "hem gauge",
        "distractor_3": "sewing caliper"
      },
      {
        "id": "1749",
        "question": "What could be used to push the needle through the fabric to keep from hurting your fingers when hand sewing?",
        "answer": "a thimble",
        "distractor_1": "the countertop",
        "distractor_2": "your fingernail",
        "distractor_3": "a rubber eraser"
      },
      {
        "id": "1751",
        "question": "Which of the following is a temporary stitch used to mark or hold layers of fabric together?",
        "answer": "basting stitch",
        "distractor_1": "straight stitch",
        "distractor_2": "backstitch",
        "distractor_3": "zigzag stitch"
      },
      {
        "id": "1754",
        "question": "What two types of yarn are found in woven fabrics?",
        "answer": "warp, filling",
        "distractor_1": "grain, off-grain",
        "distractor_2": "grain, filling",
        "distractor_3": "vertical, horizontal"
      },
      {
        "id": "1755",
        "question": "What is the term for stitching together two pieces of fabric and placing a soft material or stuffing between them?",
        "answer": "quilting",
        "distractor_1": "patchwork",
        "distractor_2": "appliqué",
        "distractor_3": "beadwork"
      },
      {
        "id": "1757",
        "question": "Fabric is made from natural and manufactured fibers. Which fiber is natural?",
        "answer": "cotton",
        "distractor_1": "rayon",
        "distractor_2": "nylon",
        "distractor_3": "polyester"
      },
      {
        "id": "1759",
        "question": "Where should you keep pins and needles to avoid accidents?",
        "answer": "pincushion",
        "distractor_1": "thimble",
        "distractor_2": "bobbin",
        "distractor_3": "needle threader"
      },
      {
        "id": "1761",
        "question": "Which type of thread is a good all-purpose thread used for sewing on most fabrics?",
        "answer": "polyester/cotton",
        "distractor_1": "mercerized cotton",
        "distractor_2": "silk",
        "distractor_3": "heavy-duty"
      },
      {
        "id": "1763",
        "question": "Which fabric is the lightest and will even float in water?",
        "answer": "olefin",
        "distractor_1": "cotton",
        "distractor_2": "acetate",
        "distractor_3": "polyester"
      },
      {
        "id": "1764",
        "question": "What element of design refers to the shape of an object?",
        "answer": "form",
        "distractor_1": "texture",
        "distractor_2": "harmony",
        "distractor_3": "balance"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "328",
    "name": "Cell Structure",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "3961",
        "question": "What is the name of the passive process by which water moves into and out of cells?",
        "answer": "osmosis",
        "distractor_1": "diffusion",
        "distractor_2": "transport",
        "distractor_3": "dialysis"
      },
      {
        "id": "3962",
        "question": "Which of the following structures is found ONLY in plant cells?",
        "answer": "cell wall",
        "distractor_1": "nucleus",
        "distractor_2": "cytoplasm",
        "distractor_3": "cell membrane"
      },
      {
        "id": "3963",
        "question": "Bacteria have recently been divided into two groups: Archaebacteria and Eubacteria. These two groups are considered to belong to which level of classification?",
        "answer": "kingdom",
        "distractor_1": "phylum",
        "distractor_2": "genus",
        "distractor_3": "species"
      },
      {
        "id": "3964",
        "question": "Which of the following organelles is the cell's powerhouse, the site of cellular respiration and  ATP formation?",
        "answer": "mitochondrion",
        "distractor_1": "nucleus",
        "distractor_2": "Golgi body",
        "distractor_3": "ribosome"
      },
      {
        "id": "3965",
        "question": "Which two features of plant cells help to support and maintain the plant's structure?",
        "answer": "cell wall and central vacuole",
        "distractor_1": "cell wall and chloroplast",
        "distractor_2": "cell membrane and central vacuole",
        "distractor_3": "cell membrane and chloroplast"
      },
      {
        "id": "3966",
        "question": "Which organelle provides sites for synthesis of molecules and forms channels for movement of materials through cells?",
        "answer": "endoplasmic reticulum",
        "distractor_1": "ribosome",
        "distractor_2": "mitochondrion",
        "distractor_3": "Golgi body"
      },
      {
        "id": "3967",
        "question": "What is the general term for specialized structures found in the cytoplasm of eukaryotic cells?",
        "answer": "organelles",
        "distractor_1": "organs",
        "distractor_2": "tissues",
        "distractor_3": "Golgi bodies"
      },
      {
        "id": "3968",
        "question": "What is the process by which exact copies of DNA are made in the cell nucleus?",
        "answer": "replication",
        "distractor_1": "duplication",
        "distractor_2": "respiration",
        "distractor_3": "meiosis"
      },
      {
        "id": "3969",
        "question": "What is the major purpose of cell division by mitosis?",
        "answer": "to form exact cell copies for growth and repair",
        "distractor_1": "to form gametes, or sex cells",
        "distractor_2": "to produce variation in offspring",
        "distractor_3": "to remove damaged chromosomes"
      },
      {
        "id": "3971",
        "question": "The typical cell is composed of 70% water, 15% protein, and 1% carbohydrate. Fat, DNA, and other cell materials account for what percentage of the cell's composition?",
        "answer": "14%",
        "distractor_1": "75%",
        "distractor_2": "86%",
        "distractor_3": "10%"
      },
      {
        "id": "3972",
        "question": "What is the process of cell division in which one mother cell divides to form two identical daughter cells?",
        "answer": "mitosis",
        "distractor_1": "meiosis",
        "distractor_2": "osmosis",
        "distractor_3": "duplication"
      },
      {
        "id": "3981",
        "question": "Which organelle contains chemicals that break down food particles and worn-out cell parts?",
        "answer": "lysosome",
        "distractor_1": "ribosome",
        "distractor_2": "vacuole",
        "distractor_3": "mitochondrion"
      },
      {
        "id": "3983",
        "question": " What is the process of sexual reproduction in bacteria called?",
        "answer": "conjugation",
        "distractor_1": "meiosis",
        "distractor_2": "binary fission",
        "distractor_3": "cytokinesis"
      },
      {
        "id": "3985",
        "question": "Which structure encloses the cytoplasm of a cell and separates it from the outside world?",
        "answer": "cell membrane",
        "distractor_1": "endoplasmic reticulum",
        "distractor_2": "nuclear membrane",
        "distractor_3": "cell organelle"
      },
      {
        "id": "3986",
        "question": "Why are cell membranes called semipermeable?",
        "answer": "Only specific substances  pass through them.",
        "distractor_1": "They are easily damaged.",
        "distractor_2": "They have short life spans.",
        "distractor_3": "Only eukaryotic cells have them."
      },
      {
        "id": "3987",
        "question": "The green pigment used in photosynthesis is stored in which part of the plant cell?",
        "answer": "chloroplast",
        "distractor_1": "Golgi bodies",
        "distractor_2": "nucleus",
        "distractor_3": "central vacuole"
      },
      {
        "id": "3988",
        "question": "How does osmosis differ from diffusion?",
        "answer": "Osmosis refers specifically to diffusion of water molecules.",
        "distractor_1": "Osmosis occurs in living organisms; diffusion occurs only in nonliving systems.",
        "distractor_2": "Osmosis requires energy; diffusion does not.",
        "distractor_3": "Osmosis occurs through a semipermeable membrane; diffusion does not."
      },
      {
        "id": "7909",
        "question": "Which cell organelle is the site of protein synthesis?",
        "answer": "ribosome",
        "distractor_1": "lysosome",
        "distractor_2": "nucleus",
        "distractor_3": "mitochondrion"
      },
      {
        "id": "3973",
        "question": "Which of the following statements is a correct principle of the cell theory?",
        "answer": "New cells form only from preexisting cells.",
        "distractor_1": "Most organisms are multicellular.",
        "distractor_2": "All cells must have nuclei to reproduce.",
        "distractor_3": "Only animals have cells."
      },
      {
        "id": "3974",
        "question": "Which organelle contains the DNA, or genetic material, and serves as the cell's 'control center'?",
        "answer": "nucleus",
        "distractor_1": "mitochondrion",
        "distractor_2": "ribosome",
        "distractor_3": "endoplasmic reticulum"
      },
      {
        "id": "3975",
        "question": "Genes on DNA contain information for making proteins. Where in the cell are these proteins made?",
        "answer": "ribosomes",
        "distractor_1": "mitochondria",
        "distractor_2": "smooth ER",
        "distractor_3": "nucleus"
      },
      {
        "id": "3976",
        "question": "What is the smallest unit of matter having all characteristics of life?",
        "answer": "cell",
        "distractor_1": "atom",
        "distractor_2": "molecule",
        "distractor_3": "organelle"
      },
      {
        "id": "3977",
        "question": "What type of membrane allows some molecules to pass through it and prevents others?",
        "answer": "semipermeable",
        "distractor_1": "transparent",
        "distractor_2": "translucent",
        "distractor_3": "diffusible"
      },
      {
        "id": "3978",
        "question": "What is the protective layer that surrounds and encloses ALL cells?",
        "answer": "cell membrane",
        "distractor_1": "cell cytoplasm",
        "distractor_2": "cell wall",
        "distractor_3": "nuclear membrane"
      },
      {
        "id": "3979",
        "question": "Which structure in eukaryotic cells contains the hereditary instructions?",
        "answer": "nucleus",
        "distractor_1": "mitochondrion",
        "distractor_2": "endoplasmic reticulum",
        "distractor_3": "ribosome"
      },
      {
        "id": "3980",
        "question": "Which two scientists performed experiments showing that life comes only from preexisting life?",
        "answer": "Redi and Pasteur",
        "distractor_1": "Schleiden and Schwann",
        "distractor_2": "Hooke and van Leeuwenhoek",
        "distractor_3": "Watson and Crick"
      },
      {
        "id": "6186",
        "question": "What is an organism having eukaryotic, or true, cells with nuclei and organelles?",
        "answer": "eukaryote",
        "distractor_1": "prokaryote",
        "distractor_2": "zygote",
        "distractor_3": "virus"
      },
      {
        "id": "6187",
        "question": "What energy-containing molecule is produced during cellular respiration?",
        "answer": "ATP",
        "distractor_1": "protein",
        "distractor_2": "carbohydrate",
        "distractor_3": "oxygen"
      },
      {
        "id": "6188",
        "question": "What form of cell division results in production of gametes with one-half the original chromosome number?",
        "answer": "meiosis",
        "distractor_1": "mitosis",
        "distractor_2": "diffusion",
        "distractor_3": "osmosis"
      },
      {
        "id": "6189",
        "question": "What is a factor or condition that changes during a scientific experiment?",
        "answer": "variable",
        "distractor_1": "control",
        "distractor_2": "hypothesis",
        "distractor_3": "result"
      },
      {
        "id": "6190",
        "question": "What is a factor or condition against which results of a scientific experiment are compared?",
        "answer": "control",
        "distractor_1": "variable",
        "distractor_2": "conclusion",
        "distractor_3": "hypothesis"
      },
      {
        "id": "6191",
        "question": "What is the name of a group of cells specialized for a particular function?",
        "answer": "tissue",
        "distractor_1": "endoplasmic reticulum",
        "distractor_2": "molecule",
        "distractor_3": "organ"
      },
      {
        "id": "6192",
        "question": "What is a passive movement of molecules from a region of high concentration to a region of lower concentration?",
        "answer": "diffusion",
        "distractor_1": "active transport",
        "distractor_2": "meiosis",
        "distractor_3": "mitosis"
      },
      {
        "id": "7908",
        "question": "Which organelle contains chlorophyll and is the site of photosynthesis in the plant cell?",
        "answer": "chloroplast",
        "distractor_1": "ribosome",
        "distractor_2": "central vacuole",
        "distractor_3": "lysosome"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "329",
    "name": "Environmental Issues",
    "weight": "85",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "4766",
        "question": "How should a substance with a pH of 3.5 be classified?",
        "answer": "an acid",
        "distractor_1": "a base",
        "distractor_2": "an ion",
        "distractor_3": "a neutral substance"
      },
      {
        "id": "4767",
        "question": "Which of the following methods of solid waste handling is considered a disposal method?",
        "answer": "incineration",
        "distractor_1": "composting",
        "distractor_2": "source reduction",
        "distractor_3": "recycling"
      },
      {
        "id": "4768",
        "question": "What is the current state of human population growth on planet Earth?",
        "answer": "The population is growing exponentially.",
        "distractor_1": "The population is stabilized.",
        "distractor_2": "The population is declining slightly.",
        "distractor_3": "The population is declining rapidly."
      },
      {
        "id": "4769",
        "question": "Growth of which factor has contributed most to the demand for natural resources?",
        "answer": "human population",
        "distractor_1": "pollution levels",
        "distractor_2": "interest in environmental sciences",
        "distractor_3": "interest in recycled goods"
      },
      {
        "id": "4770",
        "question": "Acid precipitation results when which two substances in the atmosphere combine with air pollutants from fossil fuel combustion?",
        "answer": "oxygen and water",
        "distractor_1": "carbon dioxide and smog",
        "distractor_2": "sulfur and nitrogen",
        "distractor_3": "oxygen and greenhouse gases"
      },
      {
        "id": "4771",
        "question": "Why are renewable resources such as fisheries and soil sometimes considered nonrenewable, in practical terms?",
        "answer": "They can be depleted by overharvesting or are replaced slowly.",
        "distractor_1": "They cannot be recycled or composted.",
        "distractor_2": "They are available in very small quantities.",
        "distractor_3": "They are too difficult to extract from the environment."
      },
      {
        "id": "4772",
        "question": "Global warming is enhancing Earth's greenhouse effect, causing what change in Earth's average temperature?",
        "answer": "increasing it above the average of 59ºF",
        "distractor_1": "increasing it above the average of -18ºC",
        "distractor_2": "decreasing it below the average of 59ºF",
        "distractor_3": "decreasing it below the average of -18ºC"
      },
      {
        "id": "4773",
        "question": "A population that has reached its carrying capacity can be represented by which type of graph?",
        "answer": "logistic, or S-curve",
        "distractor_1": "exponential, or J-curve",
        "distractor_2": "linear, or  straight-line curve",
        "distractor_3": "linear curve at first, followed by exponential curve"
      },
      {
        "id": "4774",
        "question": "A tanker accident causing a major oil spill is an example of which type of pollution?",
        "answer": "point source pollution",
        "distractor_1": "nonpoint source pollution",
        "distractor_2": "global pollution",
        "distractor_3": "thermal pollution"
      },
      {
        "id": "4775",
        "question": "Which atmospheric condition is responsible for maintaining Earth's temperature at a level that enables life to exist?",
        "answer": "greenhouse effect",
        "distractor_1": "global warming",
        "distractor_2": "presence of oxygen",
        "distractor_3": "presence of nitrogen"
      },
      {
        "id": "4776",
        "question": "How should a substance with an excess of hydrogen ions be classified?",
        "answer": "acid, with a pH less than 7.0",
        "distractor_1": "acid, with a pH greater than 7.0",
        "distractor_2": "base, with a pH greater than 7.0",
        "distractor_3": "base, with a pH less than 7.0"
      },
      {
        "id": "4777",
        "question": "Which method of waste handling conserves the most resources while minimizing pollution and energy use?",
        "answer": "source reduction",
        "distractor_1": "landfills",
        "distractor_2": "recycling",
        "distractor_3": "composting"
      },
      {
        "id": "4778",
        "question": "Petroleum, coal, and natural gas are examples of which type of resource?",
        "answer": "nonrenewable",
        "distractor_1": "perpetual",
        "distractor_2": "renewable",
        "distractor_3": "sustainable"
      },
      {
        "id": "4779",
        "question": "Why are renewable and perpetual resources sometimes lumped together?",
        "answer": "Normally, both types of resources will always be available.",
        "distractor_1": "The two words refer to the same resources.",
        "distractor_2": "Both types of resources consist of living organisms.",
        "distractor_3": "Normally, both types of resources can be reused or recycled."
      },
      {
        "id": "4780",
        "question": "Which atmospheric gas is a component of smog near ground level, but in the upper atmosphere protects us from the Sun's ultraviolet rays?",
        "answer": "ozone",
        "distractor_1": "oxygen",
        "distractor_2": "nitrogen dioxide",
        "distractor_3": "carbon dioxide"
      },
      {
        "id": "4781",
        "question": "Which of the following situations is an example of point source pollution?",
        "answer": "toxic chemicals entering a river from an industrial pipe",
        "distractor_1": "fertilizers running off agricultural land",
        "distractor_2": "sediment from eroding construction sites",
        "distractor_3": "salt runoff from irrigated fields"
      },
      {
        "id": "4782",
        "question": "Which of the following atmospheric gases is a naturally occurring greenhouse gas?",
        "answer": "carbon dioxide",
        "distractor_1": "oxygen",
        "distractor_2": "nitrogen",
        "distractor_3": "CFCs"
      },
      {
        "id": "4783",
        "question": "Which substance or substances released during fossil fuel combustion are most responsible for the production of acid precipitation?",
        "answer": "nitrogen and sulfur",
        "distractor_1": "oxygen and ozone",
        "distractor_2": "carbon dioxide",
        "distractor_3": "carbon monoxide"
      },
      {
        "id": "4784",
        "question": "What percentage of Earth's atmosphere consists of greenhouse gases, which trap and reradiate heat?",
        "answer": "less than 1 percent",
        "distractor_1": "about 70 percent",
        "distractor_2": "about 50 percent",
        "distractor_3": "about 20 percent"
      },
      {
        "id": "4785",
        "question": "What factor is the major cause of the current increase in organism extinctions?",
        "answer": "habitat destruction",
        "distractor_1": "introduction of exotic species",
        "distractor_2": "competition with existing species",
        "distractor_3": "pollution"
      },
      {
        "id": "4786",
        "question": "What factor makes it impossible to recycle petroleum, coal, and natural gas?",
        "answer": "They are burned as fuel and consumed.",
        "distractor_1": "They were formed long ago and more cannot be made.",
        "distractor_2": "They are nonliving and cannot be reproduced.",
        "distractor_3": "They cannot be broken down by microorganisms."
      },
      {
        "id": "6364",
        "question": "What is rain, snow, or sleet having a pH of 5.0 or less?",
        "answer": "Acid precipitation",
        "distractor_1": "Nonacidic precipitation",
        "distractor_2": "Ph balanced rain",
        "distractor_3": "Normal rain"
      },
      {
        "id": "6365",
        "question": "What is any environmental factor used by organisms to survive or carry out daily activities?",
        "answer": "Resource",
        "distractor_1": "Renewable",
        "distractor_2": "Nonrenewable",
        "distractor_3": "Biotic potential"
      },
      {
        "id": "6366",
        "question": "What is the ability of a resource or product to be made, used, and disposed of over and over?",
        "answer": "Sustainability",
        "distractor_1": "Bioremediation",
        "distractor_2": "Pollution",
        "distractor_3": "Recycling"
      },
      {
        "id": "6367",
        "question": "What is the use of microorganisms to assist in cleaning contaminated areas by breaking down pollutants?",
        "answer": "Bioremediation",
        "distractor_1": "Recycling",
        "distractor_2": "Exponential growth",
        "distractor_3": "Logistic growth"
      },
      {
        "id": "6368",
        "question": "What is an area of land set aside and managed for disposal of solid waste by burial?",
        "answer": "Landfill",
        "distractor_1": "Pollution",
        "distractor_2": "Wastestream",
        "distractor_3": "Bioremediation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6369",
        "question": "What is an increase in Earth's average temperature due to trapping of excess greenhouse gases in the atmosphere?",
        "answer": "Global warming",
        "distractor_1": "Greenhouse effect",
        "distractor_2": "Incineration",
        "distractor_3": "Source reduction"
      },
      {
        "id": "6370",
        "question": "What is contamination of the environment with harmful or unnatural substances or with an excess of natural substances?",
        "answer": "Pollution",
        "distractor_1": "Bioremediation",
        "distractor_2": "Wastestream",
        "distractor_3": "Landfill"
      },
      {
        "id": "6371",
        "question": "What is collecting, processing, and reusing of wastes to make new products?",
        "answer": "Recycling",
        "distractor_1": "Landfill",
        "distractor_2": "Sustainability",
        "distractor_3": "Source reduction"
      },
      {
        "id": "6372",
        "question": "What is the maximum rate at which a population can grow under ideal circumstances, including sufficient resources?",
        "answer": "Biotic potential",
        "distractor_1": "Carrying capacity",
        "distractor_2": "Logistic growth",
        "distractor_3": "Sustainability"
      },
      {
        "id": "6373",
        "question": "What is the maximum population size an environment can support, given the resources available?",
        "answer": "Carrying capacity",
        "distractor_1": "Logistic growth",
        "distractor_2": "exponential growth",
        "distractor_3": "Bioremediation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6374",
        "question": "What is unlimited growth, occurring when a population grows at its biotic potential?",
        "answer": "Exponential growth",
        "distractor_1": "Logistic growth",
        "distractor_2": "Biotic potential",
        "distractor_3": "Source increase"
      },
      {
        "id": "6375",
        "question": "What is regulated growth, occurring when a population levels off at its carrying capacity due to limitation by resources, predation, or other factors?",
        "answer": "Logistic growth",
        "distractor_1": "Exponential growth",
        "distractor_2": "Biotic potential",
        "distractor_3": "Bioremediation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6376",
        "question": "What is continuous flow of solid waste into the country's waste management system?",
        "answer": "Wastestrream",
        "distractor_1": "Pollution",
        "distractor_2": "Landfill",
        "distractor_3": "Recycling"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "330",
    "name": "Microwave Ckg. & Nutr.",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "5534",
        "question": "This term is defined as electromagnetic waves, shorter than visible light but longer than radio waves, that provide the energy for microwave ovens.",
        "answer": "microwaves",
        "distractor_1": "sound waves",
        "distractor_2": "tidal waves",
        "distractor_3": "gamma rays"
      },
      {
        "id": "5535",
        "question": "This term is defined as a reflection of microwaves between a metal container and the microwave walls, resulting in sparks and possibly fire.",
        "answer": "arcing",
        "distractor_1": "panic",
        "distractor_2": "electricity",
        "distractor_3": "wattage"
      },
      {
        "id": "5536",
        "question": "This term is defined as substances required by the body, including carbohydrates, proteins, lipids, vitamins, and minerals.",
        "answer": "nutrients",
        "distractor_1": "energy",
        "distractor_2": "calories",
        "distractor_3": "Recommended Daily Allowance"
      },
      {
        "id": "5537",
        "question": "This term is defined as a short time period after removal of food from the microwave, during which it finishes cooking.",
        "answer": "standing time",
        "distractor_1": "walking time",
        "distractor_2": "overtime",
        "distractor_3": "lunch time"
      },
      {
        "id": "5538",
        "question": "This term is defined as a food dish with a variety of ingredients baked in an oven or microwave.",
        "answer": "casserole",
        "distractor_1": "specialty",
        "distractor_2": "Salmonella",
        "distractor_3": "carbohydrate"
      },
      {
        "id": "5539",
        "question": "In 2011 the USDA released this diagram, which defines required food groups and amounts needed.",
        "answer": "MyPlate",
        "distractor_1": "Recommended Daily Allowance",
        "distractor_2": "Food Pyramid",
        "distractor_3": "FDA"
      },
      {
        "id": "5540",
        "question": "This term is defined as a measure of the energy contained in foods or burned during exercise.",
        "answer": "calorie",
        "distractor_1": "nutrient",
        "distractor_2": "repetition",
        "distractor_3": "conversion"
      },
      {
        "id": "2857",
        "question": "What happens to foods that are cooked quickly, as they are in a microwave oven?",
        "answer": "They lose fewer nutrients.",
        "distractor_1": "They taste saltier.",
        "distractor_2": "They lose more nutrients.",
        "distractor_3": "They don't cook on the inside."
      },
      {
        "id": "2861",
        "question": "Which of the following can be placed in the microwave and cooked on high for five minutes to remove odors from the microwave?",
        "answer": "a mixture of water and lemon juice",
        "distractor_1": "oven cleaner",
        "distractor_2": "baking powder",
        "distractor_3": "vinegar, mineral water, and salt"
      },
      {
        "id": "2862",
        "question": "Which of these is caused as microwaves enter the food, thereby producing the heat that cooks the food?",
        "answer": "friction",
        "distractor_1": "micro energy",
        "distractor_2": "an electric charge",
        "distractor_3": "a magnetic charge"
      },
      {
        "id": "2863",
        "question": "Which of the following characteristics of food will affect whether its internal heat will continue the cooking process after it is removed from the microwave oven?",
        "answer": "amount and composition",
        "distractor_1": "cooking time",
        "distractor_2": "color and temperature",
        "distractor_3": "quality"
      },
      {
        "id": "5541",
        "question": "This term is defined as the process by which the body takes in and uses food substances.",
        "answer": "nutrition",
        "distractor_1": "absorption",
        "distractor_2": "digestion",
        "distractor_3": "conversion"
      },
      {
        "id": "5542",
        "question": "This term is defined as the taking in of electromagnetic waves by a substance, as when a food absorbs microwaves and becomes cooked.",
        "answer": "absorption",
        "distractor_1": "radiation",
        "distractor_2": "electromagnetism",
        "distractor_3": "broiling"
      },
      {
        "id": "5543",
        "question": "This term is defined as the bending or turning away of electromagnetic waves by a substance, as when food wrapped in aluminum reflects microwaves and does not cook.",
        "answer": "reflection",
        "distractor_1": "arcing",
        "distractor_2": "snubbing",
        "distractor_3": "simmering"
      },
      {
        "id": "2864",
        "question": "To see if a dish is microwave safe, place it in the microwave. Place a cup of cold water next to it. Run the microwave on high for one minute. If the dish is microwave safe, what will happen to the dish?",
        "answer": "It stays cool.",
        "distractor_1": "It won't break.",
        "distractor_2": "It gets hot.",
        "distractor_3": "It doesn't spark."
      },
      {
        "id": "2865",
        "question": "In case of a fire in a microwave oven, what should you do?",
        "answer": "Unplug the oven and keep the door closed.",
        "distractor_1": "Press Stop and get help.",
        "distractor_2": "Open the door and use a fire extinguisher.",
        "distractor_3": "Open the door and douse with water."
      },
      {
        "id": "2866",
        "question": "When measuring liquids, which of the following is equal to one ounce?",
        "answer": "two tablespoons",
        "distractor_1": "one cup",
        "distractor_2": "one teaspoon",
        "distractor_3": "two teaspoons"
      },
      {
        "id": "2867",
        "question": "Which of the following are paper products that can be used safely in a microwave oven?",
        "answer": "plain paper towels",
        "distractor_1": "recycled paper",
        "distractor_2": "egg cartons",
        "distractor_3": "brown paper sacks"
      },
      {
        "id": "2868",
        "question": "In comparison with cooking foods with few fats and sugars, how do foods with more fats and sugars cook in a microwave?",
        "answer": "faster and hotter",
        "distractor_1": "slower",
        "distractor_2": "more evenly",
        "distractor_3": "dryer and tougher"
      },
      {
        "id": "2872",
        "question": "What happens to the microwaves as a result of placing metal objects in a microwave oven?",
        "answer": "They are reflected.",
        "distractor_1": "They are enhanced.",
        "distractor_2": "They are absorbed.",
        "distractor_3": "They are generated."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "140",
    "name": "CNC Manufacturing",
    "weight": "75",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8265",
        "question": "Raw materials are either renewable or exhaustible. Renewable means there is limitless supply if managed properly. Exhaustible means that when we use all of the material available, there will be no more. Which of these materials is/are exhausible?",
        "answer": "coal",
        "distractor_1": "oxygen",
        "distractor_2": "trees",
        "distractor_3": "leather"
      },
      {
        "id": "1161",
        "question": "Which of the following occurs when humans take a material and change it to make it more useful?",
        "answer": "manufacturing",
        "distractor_1": "construction",
        "distractor_2": "fabrication",
        "distractor_3": "modification"
      },
      {
        "id": "1162",
        "question": "Raw materials are either renewable or exhaustible. Renewable means there is limitless supply if managed properly. Exhaustible means that when we use all of the material available, there will be no more. Which of these materials is/are renewable?",
        "answer": "trees",
        "distractor_1": "oil",
        "distractor_2": "coal",
        "distractor_3": "metal ores"
      },
      {
        "id": "1163",
        "question": "What is one advantage that digital automation, or manufacturing, has over mechanical automation?",
        "answer": "It is reprogrammable.",
        "distractor_1": "It is larger.",
        "distractor_2": "It is more durable.",
        "distractor_3": "It is stronger."
      },
      {
        "id": "1164",
        "question": "In the world of manufacturing, what does the acronym CNC stand for?",
        "answer": "computer numerical control",
        "distractor_1": "computer network center",
        "distractor_2": "cash-n-carry",
        "distractor_3": "cost-n-customer"
      },
      {
        "id": "1165",
        "question": "This method is defined as locating addresses or locations identified by X, Y, and Z values.",
        "answer": "Cartesian coordinate system",
        "distractor_1": "binary system",
        "distractor_2": "XYZ system",
        "distractor_3": "computer numerical control"
      },
      {
        "id": "1166",
        "question": "When using this system, all the steps required to produce a product are computer controlled.",
        "answer": "Computer-Integrated Manufacturing (CIM)",
        "distractor_1": "Computer-Aided Drafting (CAD)",
        "distractor_2": "Computer-Aided Machining (CAM)",
        "distractor_3": "Computer Numerical Control (CNC)"
      },
      {
        "id": "1167",
        "question": "During this time period, beginning in the late 1700s and going into the 1900s, machines began replacing skilled labor.",
        "answer": "Industrial Revolution",
        "distractor_1": "Age of Discovery",
        "distractor_2": "Robot Revolution",
        "distractor_3": "Automation Age"
      },
      {
        "id": "1168",
        "question": "Which of the following is used to turn raw materials into useful products?",
        "answer": "primary and secondary processes",
        "distractor_1": "manufacturing",
        "distractor_2": "computers",
        "distractor_3": "electronics"
      },
      {
        "id": "1169",
        "question": "Which of the following terms is defined as natural resources found in or on the Earth and oceans?",
        "answer": "raw materials",
        "distractor_1": "engineering materials",
        "distractor_2": "standard stock",
        "distractor_3": "primary materials"
      },
      {
        "id": "1170",
        "question": "Which axis on a milling machine travels in a vertical direction?",
        "answer": "z",
        "distractor_1": "x",
        "distractor_2": "y",
        "distractor_3": "Cartesian"
      },
      {
        "id": "6859",
        "question": "Which process is defined as the changing of materials to make them more useful?",
        "answer": "manufacturing",
        "distractor_1": "production",
        "distractor_2": "construction",
        "distractor_3": "engineering"
      },
      {
        "id": "6860",
        "question": "You have been asked to provide 18 pieces of plywood that measure 16 inches by 32 inches each. How many sheets of plywood will you need? A sheet of plywood measures 4 feet by 8 feet.",
        "answer": "2",
        "distractor_1": "3",
        "distractor_2": "4",
        "distractor_3": "5"
      },
      {
        "id": "6861",
        "question": "Industiral goods are changed into finished goods by secondary processes. Which of the following is an example of a secondary process?",
        "answer": "conditioning",
        "distractor_1": "drilling",
        "distractor_2": "mechanical",
        "distractor_3": "industrial"
      },
      {
        "id": "6862",
        "question": "This process is defined as changing of raw materials, such as plants, animals, and minerals, into engineering materials or standard stock.",
        "answer": "primary processing",
        "distractor_1": "secondary processing",
        "distractor_2": "manufacturing",
        "distractor_3": "conditioning"
      },
      {
        "id": "6863",
        "question": "This program links all departments of a manufacturing facility together.",
        "answer": "computer-integrated manufacturing",
        "distractor_1": "computers in manufacturing",
        "distractor_2": "computer intellegence monitoring",
        "distractor_3": "continous integrated manufacturing"
      },
      {
        "id": "6864",
        "question": "Identify the continous system that uses computers to operate machines and material handling devices. This system allows companies to produce small quantities of products and maintain high quality and low cost. ",
        "answer": "flexible manufacturing",
        "distractor_1": "custom manufacturing",
        "distractor_2": "intermittent manufacturing",
        "distractor_3": "continous manufacturing"
      },
      {
        "id": "6216",
        "question": "What is sometimes called computer-aided machining, this is the use of computers to monitor and control machines and manufacturing support activities?",
        "answer": "Computer-aided manufacturing (CAM)",
        "distractor_1": "Computer-integrated manufacturing (CIM)",
        "distractor_2": "Computer numerical control (CNC)",
        "distractor_3": "Computer-aided drafting (CAD)"
      },
      {
        "id": "6217",
        "question": "What is a software program that connects all departments of a manufacturing facility?",
        "answer": "Computer-integrated manufacturing (CIM)",
        "distractor_1": "Computer-aided manufacturing (CAM)",
        "distractor_2": "Computer numerical control (CNC)",
        "distractor_3": "Computer-aided drafting (CAD)"
      },
      {
        "id": "6218",
        "question": "What is controlling a machine with a computer?",
        "answer": "Computer-numerical control (CNC)",
        "distractor_1": "Computer-aided drafting (CAD)",
        "distractor_2": "Computer-aided manufacturing (CAM)",
        "distractor_3": "Cartesian coordinate system"
      },
      {
        "id": "6219",
        "question": "What is a way of communicating addresses or positions to machines involving three perpendicular axes, labeled x, y, and z, with assigned values.?",
        "answer": "Cartesian coordinate system",
        "distractor_1": "Computer numerical control (CNC)",
        "distractor_2": "Automation",
        "distractor_3": "Industry"
      },
      {
        "id": "6220",
        "question": "What are the methods of converting raw materials into standard stock or engineering materials; they are thermal, chemical, and mechanical?",
        "answer": "Primary processes",
        "distractor_1": "Secondary processes",
        "distractor_2": "Automation",
        "distractor_3": "Industry"
      },
      {
        "id": "6221",
        "question": "What are the methods of converting standard stock materials into useful products; they are separating, conditioning, assembling, casting, forming and molding, and finishing?",
        "answer": "Secondary processes",
        "distractor_1": "Primary processes",
        "distractor_2": "Engineering materials",
        "distractor_3": "Automation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6222",
        "question": "What are sometimes called standard stock items, materials that have been changed from raw materials into shapes and conditions that can be used to make products?",
        "answer": "Engineering materials",
        "distractor_1": "Raw materials",
        "distractor_2": "Industry",
        "distractor_3": "Automation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6223",
        "question": "What are objects that have length, width, and depth?",
        "answer": "3 - D (three-dimensional)",
        "distractor_1": "Flat",
        "distractor_2": "2 - D (two-dimensional)",
        "distractor_3": "Round"
      },
      {
        "id": "6224",
        "question": "What is a period of time from the late 1700s to the mid-1900s in which machines were built to relieve humans from making things manually?",
        "answer": "Industrial Revolution",
        "distractor_1": "Revolution of Industry",
        "distractor_2": "Automation",
        "distractor_3": "The Depression"
      },
      {
        "id": "6225",
        "question": "What is controlling a machine with mechanical or electronic devices rather than a person?",
        "answer": "Automation",
        "distractor_1": "Computer Numerical Control (CNC)",
        "distractor_2": "Primary processes",
        "distractor_3": "Secondary Processes"
      },
      {
        "id": "6226",
        "question": "What is a series of companies that make similar products, for example, the automotive industry?",
        "answer": "Industry",
        "distractor_1": "Industrial Revolution",
        "distractor_2": "Automation",
        "distractor_3": "Safety"
      },
      {
        "id": "6227",
        "question": "What is not putting any object, including fingers, close to the cutter in the machine and wearing safety glasses when the machine is running?",
        "answer": "Safety",
        "distractor_1": "Automation",
        "distractor_2": "Industry",
        "distractor_3": "Primary Processes"
      },
      {
        "id": "6228",
        "question": "What is the use of a computer to do drafting and design functions?",
        "answer": "Computer-aided drafting (CAD)",
        "distractor_1": "Computer numerical control (CNC)",
        "distractor_2": "Computer-aided manufacturing (CAM)",
        "distractor_3": "Computer-integrated manufacturing (CIM)"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "128",
    "name": "Engines",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1236",
        "question": "Most engines convert a repetitive up-and-down, or reciprocal, motion of what engine part into rotational motion?",
        "answer": "piston",
        "distractor_1": "valve",
        "distractor_2": "camshaft",
        "distractor_3": "crankshaft"
      },
      {
        "id": "1237",
        "question": "What is the position of the intake valve and the exhaust valve during the compression stroke?",
        "answer": "closed, closed",
        "distractor_1": "open, closed",
        "distractor_2": "closed, open",
        "distractor_3": "open, open"
      },
      {
        "id": "1238",
        "question": "Name the system that works in conjunction with the fuel system to maintain constant engine speed for maximum performance.",
        "answer": "governor",
        "distractor_1": "ignition",
        "distractor_2": "compression",
        "distractor_3": "lubrication"
      },
      {
        "id": "1239",
        "question": "Name the system that is mostly affected by the governor system.",
        "answer": "fuel",
        "distractor_1": "ignition",
        "distractor_2": "compression",
        "distractor_3": "lubrication"
      },
      {
        "id": "1241",
        "question": "Name the engine part that provides both the space and strength needed to house the internal and external engine components.",
        "answer": "block",
        "distractor_1": "head",
        "distractor_2": "cylinder",
        "distractor_3": "valve cover"
      },
      {
        "id": "1242",
        "question": "Choose the proper order of steps to complete one engine cycle in a four-stroke engine.",
        "answer": "intake, compression, power, and exhaust",
        "distractor_1": "intake, power, compression, and exhaust",
        "distractor_2": "exhaust, intake, power, and compression",
        "distractor_3": "power, compression, intake, and exhaust"
      },
      {
        "id": "1243",
        "question": "In which of these four tool groups is a torque wrench classified?",
        "answer": "specialty tool",
        "distractor_1": "measuring tool",
        "distractor_2": "fastening tool",
        "distractor_3": "striking/driving tool"
      },
      {
        "id": "1244",
        "question": "Under what tool classification does a torque wrench fall?",
        "answer": "specialty tool",
        "distractor_1": "striking/driving tool",
        "distractor_2": "fastening tool",
        "distractor_3": "measuring tool"
      },
      {
        "id": "1245",
        "question": "List in order the steps of combustion in a four-stroke engine.",
        "answer": "intake, compression, power, and exhaust",
        "distractor_1": "power, compression, intake, and exhaust",
        "distractor_2": "intake, power, compression, and exhaust",
        "distractor_3": "exhaust, intake, power, and compression"
      },
      {
        "id": "1246",
        "question": "The design and operation of transportation systems are often influenced by what factor?",
        "answer": "governmental regulations",
        "distractor_1": "humidity",
        "distractor_2": "motion pictures",
        "distractor_3": "potential energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "1248",
        "question": "Choose the factor that often influences the design and operation of transportation systems.",
        "answer": "governmental regulations",
        "distractor_1": "motion pictures",
        "distractor_2": "potential energy",
        "distractor_3": "humidity"
      },
      {
        "id": "1249",
        "question": "What engine part do the cam lobes move, changing rotary motion into linear motion?",
        "answer": "valve tappets",
        "distractor_1": "push rods",
        "distractor_2": "rocker arms",
        "distractor_3": "valve caps"
      },
      {
        "id": "1250",
        "question": "What engine component moves the valve tappets, changing rotary motion into linear motion?",
        "answer": "cam lobes",
        "distractor_1": "push rods",
        "distractor_2": "rocker arms",
        "distractor_3": "valve caps"
      },
      {
        "id": "1251",
        "question": "What tool is used to measure valve clearance?",
        "answer": "feeler gauge",
        "distractor_1": "dial caliper",
        "distractor_2": "ruler",
        "distractor_3": "combination wrench"
      },
      {
        "id": "1252",
        "question": "Where would a feeler gauge be used?",
        "answer": "valve clearance",
        "distractor_1": "cylinder bore",
        "distractor_2": "stroke",
        "distractor_3": "area of the combustion chamber"
      },
      {
        "id": "1253",
        "question": "What part on a gasoline powered internal combustion engine ignites the fuel?",
        "answer": "spark plug",
        "distractor_1": "carburetor",
        "distractor_2": "intake valve",
        "distractor_3": "fuel injector"
      },
      {
        "id": "1254",
        "question": "Choose the engine part that converts linear motion to rotational motion inside a reciprocating internal combustion engine.",
        "answer": "crankshaft",
        "distractor_1": "camshaft",
        "distractor_2": "valve",
        "distractor_3": "piston"
      },
      {
        "id": "1255",
        "question": "Identify the only moving parts of the ignition system.",
        "answer": "magnets",
        "distractor_1": "pistons",
        "distractor_2": "valves",
        "distractor_3": "tappets"
      },
      {
        "id": "8218",
        "question": "What type of engine converts thermal energy from the combustion of a fuel inside the engine to mechanical energy?",
        "answer": "internal combustion",
        "distractor_1": "external combustion",
        "distractor_2": "reciprocating",
        "distractor_3": "steam"
      },
      {
        "id": "8219",
        "question": "About how much pressure is exerted on a piston with an area of 5.67 square inches when acted on with an explosive force of 2,000 pounds?",
        "answer": "353 psi",
        "distractor_1": "630 psi",
        "distractor_2": "744 psi",
        "distractor_3": "1,488 psi"
      },
      {
        "id": "6351",
        "question": "What is the number of times the piston moves up or down before creating power?",
        "answer": "Stroke",
        "distractor_1": "Power",
        "distractor_2": "Torque",
        "distractor_3": "Energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "6352",
        "question": "What is a turning or twisting force?",
        "answer": "Torque",
        "distractor_1": "Stroke",
        "distractor_2": "Energy",
        "distractor_3": "Power"
      },
      {
        "id": "6353",
        "question": "What is the ability to do work?",
        "answer": "Energy",
        "distractor_1": "Torque",
        "distractor_2": "Power",
        "distractor_3": "Stroke"
      },
      {
        "id": "6354",
        "question": "What is an up-and-down or back-and-forth motion?",
        "answer": "Reciprocal",
        "distractor_1": "Stroke",
        "distractor_2": "Torque",
        "distractor_3": "Energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "6355",
        "question": "What is the part that is responsible for converting the reciprocating linear motion of the piston into rotational motion?",
        "answer": "Crankshaft",
        "distractor_1": "Camshaft",
        "distractor_2": "Intake valve",
        "distractor_3": "Flywheel"
      },
      {
        "id": "6356",
        "question": "What is the part that is responsible for driving the entire valve train and regulating the flow of gases into and out of the combustion chamber?",
        "answer": "Camshaft",
        "distractor_1": "Crankshaft",
        "distractor_2": "Exhaust valve",
        "distractor_3": "Crankcase"
      },
      {
        "id": "6357",
        "question": "What is a valve opened and closed at the precise time by the valve-train system to allow an air-fuel mixture to enter the combustion chamber?",
        "answer": "Intake valve",
        "distractor_1": "Exhaust valve",
        "distractor_2": "Flywheel",
        "distractor_3": "Push rod"
      },
      {
        "id": "6358",
        "question": "What is a valve opened and closed at the precise time by the valve-train system to allow exhaust gases to exit the combustion chamber?",
        "answer": "Exhaust valve",
        "distractor_1": "Intake valve",
        "distractor_2": "Rocker arm",
        "distractor_3": "Crankshaft"
      },
      {
        "id": "6359",
        "question": "What is an engine component that belongs to the cooling and ignition systems?",
        "answer": "Flywheel",
        "distractor_1": "Exhaust valve",
        "distractor_2": "Intake valve",
        "distractor_3": "Rocker arm"
      },
      {
        "id": "6360",
        "question": "What is a chemical reaction that requires oxygen, fire, and fuel?",
        "answer": "Combustion",
        "distractor_1": "Fumes",
        "distractor_2": "Exhaust",
        "distractor_3": "Exhaust valve"
      },
      {
        "id": "6361",
        "question": "What is the part of the engine block that houses the crankshaft and serves as an oil reservoir in horizontal-shaft engines?",
        "answer": "Crankcase",
        "distractor_1": "Crankshaft",
        "distractor_2": "Camshaft",
        "distractor_3": "Flywheel"
      },
      {
        "id": "6362",
        "question": "What is rests on a valve tappet and moves as the valve tappet moves?",
        "answer": "Push rod",
        "distractor_1": "Rocker arm",
        "distractor_2": "Crank case",
        "distractor_3": "Camshaft"
      },
      {
        "id": "6363",
        "question": "What are pivots with the movement of the push rod?",
        "answer": "Rocker arm",
        "distractor_1": "Push rode",
        "distractor_2": "Crankshaft",
        "distractor_3": "Crankcase"
      },
      {
        "id": "8220",
        "question": "What is another name for the linear distance a piston travels inside a cylinder?",
        "answer": "stroke",
        "distractor_1": "throw",
        "distractor_2": "work",
        "distractor_3": "pitch"
      },
      {
        "id": "8221",
        "question": "If a force of 60 pounds is applied to a ratchet handle that is 6 inches (.5 foot) long, how much torque will be transferred to the ratchet's drive?",
        "answer": "30 ft lbs",
        "distractor_1": "15 ft lbs",
        "distractor_2": "60 ft lbs",
        "distractor_3": "120 ft lbs"
      },
      {
        "id": "8222",
        "question": "What is the main structure of an engine?",
        "answer": "block",
        "distractor_1": "head",
        "distractor_2": "combustion chamber",
        "distractor_3": "piston"
      },
      {
        "id": "8223",
        "question": "What's the approximate displacement of the single-cylinder engine with a cylinder bore of 3.25 inches and stroke of 3.9 inches?",
        "answer": "32 cubic inches",
        "distractor_1": "27 cubic inches",
        "distractor_2": "39 cubic inches",
        "distractor_3": "323,536 cubic inches"
      },
      {
        "id": "8224",
        "question": "Select the engine part that acts as a pivoting device for opening and closing overhead valves.",
        "answer": "rocker arm",
        "distractor_1": "push rod",
        "distractor_2": "tappet",
        "distractor_3": "valve guide"
      },
      {
        "id": "8225",
        "question": "What is the horsepower rating of an engine that produces 363,000 foot-pounds of work in two minutes?",
        "answer": "5.5 hp",
        "distractor_1": "2.25 hp",
        "distractor_2": "11 hp",
        "distractor_3": "16.5 hp"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "137",
    "name": "Climate & Biomes",
    "weight": "95",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "5313",
        "question": "Which of the following biomes has no reptiles or amphibians?",
        "answer": "tundra",
        "distractor_1": "desert",
        "distractor_2": "taiga",
        "distractor_3": "savanna"
      },
      {
        "id": "5314",
        "question": "Which of the following is the largest terrestrial biome?",
        "answer": "taiga",
        "distractor_1": "tundra",
        "distractor_2": "grassland",
        "distractor_3": "temperate forest"
      },
      {
        "id": "5315",
        "question": "In the last 50 years, which of the following changes has occurred as a result of global warming?",
        "answer": "significant melting of permafrost and glaciers",
        "distractor_1": "average global temperature increase of 3 percent",
        "distractor_2": "average global precipitation increase of 3 percent",
        "distractor_3": "submerging of several Pacific islands"
      },
      {
        "id": "1292",
        "question": "Which of the following greenhouse gases comes only from human sources?",
        "answer": "CFCs",
        "distractor_1": "carbon dioxide",
        "distractor_2": "methane",
        "distractor_3": "nitrous oxide"
      },
      {
        "id": "1293",
        "question": "Which of the following types of biomes has an average temperature of 80 degrees Fahrenheit and average annual precipitation between 60 and 160 inches?",
        "answer": "tropical rainforest",
        "distractor_1": "boreal forest or taiga",
        "distractor_2": "temperate deciduous forest",
        "distractor_3": "tundra"
      },
      {
        "id": "1294",
        "question": "Chlorofluorocarbons, or CFCs, are different from other greenhouse gases for which of the following reasons?",
        "answer": "They come only from human sources.",
        "distractor_1": "They break down the most rapidly.",
        "distractor_2": "They are the most abundant.",
        "distractor_3": "They are increasing, while other gases are decreasing."
      },
      {
        "id": "1295",
        "question": "Changes in atmospheric carbon dioxide that have occurred in the past 50 years are most strongly correlated with increases in which of the following factors?",
        "answer": "burning of fossil fuels",
        "distractor_1": "photosynthesis",
        "distractor_2": "respiration",
        "distractor_3": "increased volcanic activity"
      },
      {
        "id": "1296",
        "question": "Ice cores from Greenland and Antarctica provide information on ancient climates that is based on which of the following types of data?",
        "answer": "atmospheric carbon dioxide trapped in the ice",
        "distractor_1": "types of pollen grains",
        "distractor_2": "thickness of the rings of ice",
        "distractor_3": "imbedded fossils of large animals"
      },
      {
        "id": "1297",
        "question": "In the last 150 years, an increase in what factor has caused most of the increase in atmospheric carbon dioxide?",
        "answer": "burning of fossil fuels",
        "distractor_1": "volcanic activity",
        "distractor_2": "photosynthesis",
        "distractor_3": "respiration"
      },
      {
        "id": "1298",
        "question": "Which of the following locations on Earth would have the highest albedo?",
        "answer": "a white ice- and snow-covered polar area",
        "distractor_1": "a large expanse of plowed fields",
        "distractor_2": "a dark-green forested area",
        "distractor_3": "a light-green grassland"
      },
      {
        "id": "1299",
        "question": "If predictions come true for increased temperature and weather extremes over Earth in the next few decades, which of the following human diseases will likely NOT increase?",
        "answer": "flu",
        "distractor_1": "malaria",
        "distractor_2": "allergies",
        "distractor_3": "cholera"
      },
      {
        "id": "1300",
        "question": "An increase in Earth’s average temperature is associated with an increase in the concentration of which of the following gases?",
        "answer": "carbon dioxide",
        "distractor_1": "oxygen",
        "distractor_2": "nitrogen",
        "distractor_3": "ozone"
      },
      {
        "id": "1301",
        "question": "What is the result of changes in the tilt of Earth’s axis that cause variations in insolation?",
        "answer": "climatic cycles lasting thousands of years",
        "distractor_1": "short-term occurrences of extreme weather patterns",
        "distractor_2": "a steady rise in Earth’s temperature",
        "distractor_3": "climatic cycles lasting hundreds of years"
      },
      {
        "id": "1279",
        "question": "What is the driving force that controls Earth's climate?",
        "answer": "radiant energy from the Sun",
        "distractor_1": "the Coriolis force",
        "distractor_2": "convection currents in the atmosphere",
        "distractor_3": "convection currents in the ocean"
      },
      {
        "id": "1280",
        "question": "As the concentration of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere increases, what happens to Earth’s average temperature?",
        "answer": "It increases.",
        "distractor_1": "It decreases.",
        "distractor_2": "It stays the same.",
        "distractor_3": "It varies randomly."
      },
      {
        "id": "1282",
        "question": "When an ice core is analyzed, which two pieces of information from each sample are used to determine changes in atmospheric temperature over time?",
        "answer": "age and carbon dioxide concentration",
        "distractor_1": "age and oxygen concentration",
        "distractor_2": "carbon dioxide concentration and types of pollen grains",
        "distractor_3": "oxygen concentration and concentration of dust and sea salt"
      },
      {
        "id": "1283",
        "question": "A tree-ring analysis shows a time period when the rings were much wider than at any other time. What kind of climate was present during this time period?",
        "answer": "cool and wet",
        "distractor_1": "hot and dry",
        "distractor_2": "hot and wet",
        "distractor_3": "cool and dry"
      },
      {
        "id": "1284",
        "question": "Which of the following surfaces would have the lowest albedo?",
        "answer": "ocean",
        "distractor_1": "iceberg",
        "distractor_2": "sandy desert",
        "distractor_3": "sunny area with high, white clouds"
      },
      {
        "id": "1285",
        "question": "Which of the following descriptions best fits a tropical rainforest?",
        "answer": "hot and wet, with little temperature variation throughout the year",
        "distractor_1": "hot and dry, with large day-night temperature fluctuations",
        "distractor_2": "moderate temperature and precipitation, with distinct summers and winters",
        "distractor_3": "short, moist summers and long, cold dry winters"
      },
      {
        "id": "1286",
        "question": "Analysis of tree rings provides the best information about which of the following aspects of climate?",
        "answer": "rainfall",
        "distractor_1": "temperature",
        "distractor_2": "wind speed and direction",
        "distractor_3": "carbon dioxide concentration"
      },
      {
        "id": "1287",
        "question": "Why is the greenhouse effect important to life on Earth?",
        "answer": "It balances radiation entering and leaving the atmosphere, maintaining Earth’s temperature so that it can support life.",
        "distractor_1": "It is causing Earth to overheat, and therefore poses a threat to many forms of life.",
        "distractor_2": "It prevents heat loss from the atmosphere due to convection, thereby keeping solar radiation near Earth’s surface.",
        "distractor_3": "It ensures that the amount of radiation leaving Earth is greater than the amount entering, so that Earth does not overheat."
      },
      {
        "id": "1288",
        "question": "Long-term climatic changes, lasting thousands of years, are caused by which of the following factors?",
        "answer": "changes in the tilt of Earth’s axis",
        "distractor_1": "changes in Earth’s vegetation patterns",
        "distractor_2": "increases in rates of atmospheric convection cycles",
        "distractor_3": "increases in greenhouse gases due to human activities"
      },
      {
        "id": "1290",
        "question": "What factor initiates and controls the convection currents of Earth’s general circulation?",
        "answer": "Radiant energy from the Sun",
        "distractor_1": "Coriolis force",
        "distractor_2": "Atmospheric concentration of carbon dioxide",
        "distractor_3": "Surface convection currents in the ocean"
      },
      {
        "id": "1291",
        "question": "The greenhouse effect works primarily by which of the following processes?",
        "answer": "absorbing and reradiating heat between the atmosphere and surface",
        "distractor_1": "trapping the Sun’s radiation so that none of it can escape",
        "distractor_2": "preventing atmospheric convection currents from circulating",
        "distractor_3": "preventing radiation from reaching Earth"
      },
      {
        "id": "6193",
        "question": "What is a measure of expected weather in a region, based on average weather statistics?",
        "answer": "Climate",
        "distractor_1": "Biome",
        "distractor_2": "Biosphere",
        "distractor_3": "Dendrochronology"
      },
      {
        "id": "6194",
        "question": "What is a global biological community, characterized by its climate and vegetation?",
        "answer": "Biome",
        "distractor_1": "Biosphere",
        "distractor_2": "Albedo",
        "distractor_3": "Model"
      },
      {
        "id": "6195",
        "question": "What is the layer of Earth in which all living organisms reside?",
        "answer": "Biosphere",
        "distractor_1": "Atmosphere",
        "distractor_2": "Troposphere",
        "distractor_3": "Convection"
      },
      {
        "id": "6196",
        "question": "What is the process of moving heat around Earth by means of circular currents of air or water?",
        "answer": "Convection",
        "distractor_1": "Evaporation",
        "distractor_2": "Albedo",
        "distractor_3": "Greenhouse Affect"
      },
      {
        "id": "6197",
        "question": "What is reconstruction of ancient climates by measurement and analysis of tree rings?",
        "answer": "Dendrochronology",
        "distractor_1": "Optometry",
        "distractor_2": "Meteorology",
        "distractor_3": "Scientific Theory"
      },
      {
        "id": "6198",
        "question": "What is the process by which the atmosphere traps and reradiates heat, keeping Earth's temperature warm enough to support life?",
        "answer": "Greenhouse effect",
        "distractor_1": "Global warming",
        "distractor_2": "Climograph",
        "distractor_3": "Scientific Theory"
      },
      {
        "id": "6199",
        "question": "What is an increase in the average temperature of Earth?",
        "answer": "Global warming",
        "distractor_1": "Albedo",
        "distractor_2": "Temperate",
        "distractor_3": "Convection"
      },
      {
        "id": "6200",
        "question": "What is a percentage of electromagnetic radiation that is reflected by a surface?",
        "answer": "Albedo",
        "distractor_1": "Biosphere",
        "distractor_2": "Convection",
        "distractor_3": "Polar"
      },
      {
        "id": "6201",
        "question": "What is the pattern of annual temperature and precipitation that characterizes a biome or region?",
        "answer": "Climograph",
        "distractor_1": "Scientific Theory",
        "distractor_2": "Seismology",
        "distractor_3": "Greenhouse effect"
      },
      {
        "id": "6202",
        "question": "What is a pattern or simplified representation used to help visualize or understand a system?",
        "answer": "Model",
        "distractor_1": "Evidence",
        "distractor_2": "Climograph",
        "distractor_3": "Biome"
      },
      {
        "id": "6203",
        "question": "What is a type of climate characterized by moderate temperatures and rainfall and distinct seasons?",
        "answer": "Temperate",
        "distractor_1": "Polar",
        "distractor_2": "Biome",
        "distractor_3": "Biosphere"
      },
      {
        "id": "6204",
        "question": "What is an opinion or judgment based on the most complete, unbiased information available?",
        "answer": "Informed opinion",
        "distractor_1": "Scientific theory",
        "distractor_2": "Hypothesis",
        "distractor_3": "Evidence"
      },
      {
        "id": "6205",
        "question": "What is a type of climate characterized by very low temperatures and rainfall and soil with a permafrost layer?",
        "answer": "Polar",
        "distractor_1": "Temperate",
        "distractor_2": "Biosphere",
        "distractor_3": "Biome"
      },
      {
        "id": "6206",
        "question": "What are observations and measurements that furnish proof or support for a hypothesis or theory?",
        "answer": "Evidence",
        "distractor_1": "Informed opinion",
        "distractor_2": "Scientific Theory",
        "distractor_3": "Hypothesis"
      },
      {
        "id": "6207",
        "question": "What is a framework that explains all data collected and validates all predictions about a scientific phenomenon?",
        "answer": "Scientific Theory",
        "distractor_1": "Hypothesis",
        "distractor_2": "Evidence",
        "distractor_3": "Informed opinion"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "124",
    "name": "Oceanography",
    "weight": "97",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8680",
        "question": "Which of the following is defined as tiny floating organisms found in the ocean?",
        "answer": "plankton",
        "distractor_1": "hydrothermal vent",
        "distractor_2": "jellyfish",
        "distractor_3": "wetland"
      },
      {
        "id": "1302",
        "question": "What is a wetland?",
        "answer": "a community of rooted plants often found near an estuary",
        "distractor_1": "a region of tiny, floating organisms in the open ocean",
        "distractor_2": "another name for an estuary",
        "distractor_3": "a forest whose roots are always underwater"
      },
      {
        "id": "1303",
        "question": "As we travel downward through the ocean, what happens to the water pressure?",
        "answer": "It increases at a constant rate.",
        "distractor_1": "It decreases at a constant rate.",
        "distractor_2": "It remains the same all the way to the bottom.",
        "distractor_3": "It remains the same to 1,000 feet, then it increases rapidly to a maximum."
      },
      {
        "id": "1304",
        "question": "What is the term for an ocean community where fresh and saltwater mix?",
        "answer": "estuary",
        "distractor_1": "pelagic zone",
        "distractor_2": "thermocline",
        "distractor_3": "benthopelagic zone"
      },
      {
        "id": "1305",
        "question": "What is the term for a community of rooted plants, such as salt-marsh grasses and mangroves, that is found near an estuary?",
        "answer": "wetland",
        "distractor_1": "swamp",
        "distractor_2": "coral reef",
        "distractor_3": "phytoplankton"
      },
      {
        "id": "1307",
        "question": "Which of the following types of ocean pollution causes the most seabird deaths?",
        "answer": "oil spills",
        "distractor_1": "sewage",
        "distractor_2": "plastic waste",
        "distractor_3": "pesticides and fertilizers"
      },
      {
        "id": "1308",
        "question": "Which of the following characteristics is most true of estuaries?",
        "answer": "They are areas where fresh and salt water mix.",
        "distractor_1": "They are found only in tropical areas.",
        "distractor_2": "They are the ocean's least productive communities.",
        "distractor_3": "They contain most of Earth's salt water."
      },
      {
        "id": "1309",
        "question": "The climate along the East Coast of the United States is warmer than would be expected. Which of the following factors is responsible for this?",
        "answer": "the Gulf Stream",
        "distractor_1": "the tides",
        "distractor_2": "the Coriolis force",
        "distractor_3": "the presence of estuaries"
      },
      {
        "id": "1310",
        "question": "Which of the following types of animal builds large structures in the ocean by secreting calcium carbonate?",
        "answer": "coral",
        "distractor_1": "jellyfish",
        "distractor_2": "oyster",
        "distractor_3": "crab"
      },
      {
        "id": "1311",
        "question": "What percentage of evaporated water returns to Earth as precipitation?",
        "answer": "90 percent",
        "distractor_1": "10 percent",
        "distractor_2": "20 percent",
        "distractor_3": "80 percent"
      },
      {
        "id": "1312",
        "question": "What factor must be measured to determine the speed of ocean waves?",
        "answer": "wave frequency",
        "distractor_1": "wavelength",
        "distractor_2": "wave height",
        "distractor_3": "wave crest"
      },
      {
        "id": "1313",
        "question": "Where would the salinity of ocean water be least?",
        "answer": "in the ocean near a river outflow",
        "distractor_1": "in the open ocean, far from any coast",
        "distractor_2": "in the ocean near a desert coast",
        "distractor_3": "at the poles, where there are many icebergs"
      },
      {
        "id": "1314",
        "question": "Which of the following processes is caused by the Moon's gravity pulling on the oceans?",
        "answer": "tides",
        "distractor_1": "waves",
        "distractor_2": "currents",
        "distractor_3": "seasons"
      },
      {
        "id": "1315",
        "question": "Which of the following is the best definition of plankton?",
        "answer": "tiny floating organisms found in the ocean",
        "distractor_1": "swimming animals",
        "distractor_2": "animals found in the twilight zone",
        "distractor_3": "largest type of algae in the world"
      },
      {
        "id": "1316",
        "question": "Where would the salinity of ocean water be greatest?",
        "answer": "in a tropical ocean, far from any coast",
        "distractor_1": "in an estuary",
        "distractor_2": "in the ocean near a river outflow",
        "distractor_3": "at the poles, where there are many icebergs"
      },
      {
        "id": "1317",
        "question": "What is the major cause of tides?",
        "answer": "the Moon's gravity pulling on the oceans",
        "distractor_1": "seasonal climatic changes",
        "distractor_2": "the movement of ocean currents",
        "distractor_3": "random water movements due to storms"
      },
      {
        "id": "1319",
        "question": "Which of the following ocean communities has the greatest biodiversity?",
        "answer": "coral reefs",
        "distractor_1": "kelp forests",
        "distractor_2": "estuaries",
        "distractor_3": "hydrothermal vents"
      },
      {
        "id": "1320",
        "question": "Oceans and other saltwater bodies make up what percentage of all the water on Earth?",
        "answer": "97 percent",
        "distractor_1": "29 percent",
        "distractor_2": "40 percent",
        "distractor_3": "71 percent"
      },
      {
        "id": "1321",
        "question": "The amount of biodiversity in coral reefs is most similar to the amount of biodiversity in which other ecosystem?",
        "answer": "tropical rain forest",
        "distractor_1": "kelp forest",
        "distractor_2": "desert",
        "distractor_3": "hydrothermal vent"
      },
      {
        "id": "1322",
        "question": "As we travel downward through the ocean, which of the following factors increases?",
        "answer": "pressure",
        "distractor_1": "temperature",
        "distractor_2": "light",
        "distractor_3": "wave action"
      },
      {
        "id": "1323",
        "question": "The greatest percentage of water on Earth exists in which of the following forms?",
        "answer": "ocean water",
        "distractor_1": "ice caps and icebergs",
        "distractor_2": "freshwater",
        "distractor_3": "brackish water"
      },
      {
        "id": "6894",
        "question": "Who was the first person to describe the principle of buoyant force, which explains why certain objects rise or float in water?",
        "answer": "Archimedes",
        "distractor_1": "Aristotle",
        "distractor_2": "Bernoulli",
        "distractor_3": "Linnaeus"
      },
      {
        "id": "6895",
        "question": "In which habitat would green anemones and hermit crabs most likely be found?",
        "answer": "tide pools",
        "distractor_1": "kelp forests",
        "distractor_2": "coral reefs",
        "distractor_3": "the twilight zone"
      },
      {
        "id": "6896",
        "question": "The Bermuda Triangle, famous for mysterious disappearances of ships and planes, is located in which ocean?",
        "answer": "Atlantic",
        "distractor_1": "Arctic",
        "distractor_2": "Indian",
        "distractor_3": "Pacific"
      },
      {
        "id": "8679",
        "question": "What percentage of water is retained in the atmosphere?",
        "answer": "10 percent",
        "distractor_1": "90 percent",
        "distractor_2": "20 percent",
        "distractor_3": "80 percent"
      },
      {
        "id": "6595",
        "question": "What is a mass of water that moves like a river through the ocean?",
        "answer": "current",
        "distractor_1": "tide ",
        "distractor_2": "wave",
        "distractor_3": "hydrothermal vent"
      },
      {
        "id": "6596",
        "question": "What are microscopic floating plants that carry out much of the photosynthesis in the ocean?",
        "answer": "phytoplankton",
        "distractor_1": "coral",
        "distractor_2": "estuary",
        "distractor_3": "shrimp"
      },
      {
        "id": "6597",
        "question": "What is a disturbance produced when energy flows through a medium, such as air or water?",
        "answer": "wave",
        "distractor_1": "current",
        "distractor_2": "tide",
        "distractor_3": "absolute pressure"
      },
      {
        "id": "6598",
        "question": "What is a measurement of the saltiness of a water sample?",
        "answer": "salinity",
        "distractor_1": "conductivity",
        "distractor_2": "density",
        "distractor_3": "buoyancy"
      },
      {
        "id": "6599",
        "question": "What is a measurement of the amount of electrical current a water sample can carry?",
        "answer": "conductivity",
        "distractor_1": "salinity",
        "distractor_2": "density",
        "distractor_3": "absolute pressure"
      },
      {
        "id": "6600",
        "question": "What is the flat part of the ocean floor, which averages several miles in depth?",
        "answer": "abyssal plain",
        "distractor_1": "thermocline",
        "distractor_2": "photic zone",
        "distractor_3": "hydrothermal vent"
      },
      {
        "id": "6601",
        "question": "What is the part of the ocean's water column where temperature changes most rapidly?",
        "answer": "thermocline",
        "distractor_1": "photic zone",
        "distractor_2": "twilight zone",
        "distractor_3": "abyssal plain"
      },
      {
        "id": "6602",
        "question": "What is the top layer of the ocean where sunlight penetrates and most life is found?",
        "answer": "photic zone",
        "distractor_1": "hydrothermal vent",
        "distractor_2": "abyssal plain",
        "distractor_3": "twilight zone"
      },
      {
        "id": "6603",
        "question": "What is a crack in the ocean floor that attracts organisms because of its warmth and nutrients?",
        "answer": "hydrothermal vent",
        "distractor_1": "trench",
        "distractor_2": "abyssal plain",
        "distractor_3": "guyot"
      },
      {
        "id": "6604",
        "question": "What is a measure of the variety of types of organisms in an ecosystem?",
        "answer": "biodiversity",
        "distractor_1": "density",
        "distractor_2": "variation",
        "distractor_3": "conductivity"
      },
      {
        "id": "6605",
        "question": "What term describes sound navigation and ranging, which is used to determine depth and locate underwater objects?",
        "answer": "sonar",
        "distractor_1": "sodar",
        "distractor_2": "radar",
        "distractor_3": "sound propagation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6606",
        "question": "What characteristic of an object is measured as mass per unit of volume (for example, grams per milliliter)?",
        "answer": "density",
        "distractor_1": "mass",
        "distractor_2": "velocity",
        "distractor_3": "weight"
      },
      {
        "id": "6607",
        "question": "What is an underwater pressure reading that includes atmospheric pressure at sea level?",
        "answer": "absolute pressure",
        "distractor_1": "partial pressure",
        "distractor_2": "sea-level pressure",
        "distractor_3": "density"
      },
      {
        "id": "6608",
        "question": "What is the ability of an object to float in a liquid?",
        "answer": "buoyancy",
        "distractor_1": "density",
        "distractor_2": "salinity",
        "distractor_3": "conductivity"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "136",
    "name": "Research & Presentation",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1348",
        "question": "When trying to decide if a Web site will be a valuable resource to use for researching a topic, which of the following criteria should you consider?",
        "answer": "Does the Web site list the name and credentials of its creator?",
        "distractor_1": "Does the Web site have a guest book?",
        "distractor_2": "Does the Web site have several graphics and animations?",
        "distractor_3": "Does the Web site have several advertising banners?"
      },
      {
        "id": "1349",
        "question": "What is the name of the reading technique in which you quickly read through text looking for main ideas and keywords?",
        "answer": "skimming technique",
        "distractor_1": "framework technique",
        "distractor_2": "comprehensive technique",
        "distractor_3": "fluency technique"
      },
      {
        "id": "1350",
        "question": "What is a visual representation of ideas that helps to identify important facts and sort information called?",
        "answer": "a graphic organizer",
        "distractor_1": "a bibliography",
        "distractor_2": "an index",
        "distractor_3": "a citation"
      },
      {
        "id": "1351",
        "question": "To expand your research and make it more successful, you should make a list of what before beginning to research?",
        "answer": "related topics and keywords",
        "distractor_1": "keywords and antonyms",
        "distractor_2": "antonyms and related topics",
        "distractor_3": "synonyms and antonyms"
      },
      {
        "id": "1352",
        "question": "If you use another person's words or ideas in your work without giving him or her credit, what have you done?",
        "answer": "plagiarized the author's words",
        "distractor_1": "scanned the author's words",
        "distractor_2": "skimmed the author's words",
        "distractor_3": "paraphrased the author's words"
      },
      {
        "id": "1353",
        "question": "What is the term for using your own words to rewrite the information from a source?",
        "answer": "paraphrasing",
        "distractor_1": "skimming",
        "distractor_2": "quoting",
        "distractor_3": "plagiarizing"
      },
      {
        "id": "1354",
        "question": "When taking notes, how should you indicate that you have written a sentence exactly as it appears in the source?",
        "answer": "put quotation marks around it",
        "distractor_1": "put it in brackets",
        "distractor_2": "underline it",
        "distractor_3": "highlight it"
      },
      {
        "id": "1355",
        "question": "What is the effect that is added between slides in a 'PowerPoint' presentation called?",
        "answer": "a transition",
        "distractor_1": "an embedded element",
        "distractor_2": "an animation",
        "distractor_3": "an import"
      },
      {
        "id": "1356",
        "question": "Which of the following lists pieces of information used in the most common documentation styles?",
        "answer": "author, title, and year the book was published",
        "distractor_1": "author, call number, and year the book was published",
        "distractor_2": "publisher, title, and call number",
        "distractor_3": "library where the book is located, author, and title"
      },
      {
        "id": "1357",
        "question": "If you quickly read through a text to identify the main ideas and look for keywords, you are using what reading technique?",
        "answer": "skimming technique",
        "distractor_1": "comprehensive technique",
        "distractor_2": "fluency technique",
        "distractor_3": "framework technique"
      },
      {
        "id": "1358",
        "question": "Using your own words to rewrite the information from a source is called what?",
        "answer": "paraphrasing",
        "distractor_1": "plagiarizing",
        "distractor_2": "quoting",
        "distractor_3": "skimming"
      },
      {
        "id": "1360",
        "question": "A word made from the first letters of other words is referred to as what?",
        "answer": "acronym",
        "distractor_1": "antonym",
        "distractor_2": "synonym",
        "distractor_3": "initialization"
      },
      {
        "id": "1361",
        "question": "To create a visual representation of ideas to identify important facts and sort information, you should use what?",
        "answer": "a graphic organizer",
        "distractor_1": "a bibliography",
        "distractor_2": "a citation",
        "distractor_3": "an index"
      },
      {
        "id": "1362",
        "question": "What is the term for using another person's words in your writing without giving him or her the credit for the work?",
        "answer": "plagiarism",
        "distractor_1": "paraphrasing",
        "distractor_2": "scanning",
        "distractor_3": "skimming"
      },
      {
        "id": "1364",
        "question": "Each volume of an encyclopedia set contains approximately 2,031 articles. About how many articles would be contained in 32 volumes?",
        "answer": "65,000",
        "distractor_1": "6,400",
        "distractor_2": "64,000",
        "distractor_3": "67,000"
      },
      {
        "id": "1365",
        "question": "One book has 26 pages on your topic. A second book has 17 pages. It takes you 3 minutes per page to skim the first book. The second book requires 2 minutes per page. How long will it take you to skim all the selected pages in both books?",
        "answer": "about 2 hours",
        "distractor_1": "about 1 hour",
        "distractor_2": "about 1-1/2 hours",
        "distractor_3": "about 3 hours"
      },
      {
        "id": "1366",
        "question": "Which of the following parts of a book would be the most helpful if you wanted to locate the exact page that discusses a particular piece of information?",
        "answer": "index",
        "distractor_1": "glossary",
        "distractor_2": "abstract",
        "distractor_3": "title page"
      },
      {
        "id": "1367",
        "question": "You should do which of the following while delivering a presentation to make it more effective?",
        "answer": "make eye contact with different people in your audience",
        "distractor_1": "lean on a piece of furniture to appear relaxed during the presentation",
        "distractor_2": "constantly look at your slides to make sure you don't forget anything",
        "distractor_3": "speak quickly to make sure you get all of your points into the presentation"
      },
      {
        "id": "1368",
        "question": "The most common documentation styles include which of the following pieces of information?",
        "answer": "author, title, and year the book was published",
        "distractor_1": "publisher, title, and call number",
        "distractor_2": "library where the book is located, author, and title",
        "distractor_3": "author, call number, and year the book was published"
      },
      {
        "id": "1369",
        "question": "Which of the following criteria is useful in determining if a Web site is a valuable resource for researching a topic?",
        "answer": "Does the Web site list the name and credentials of its creator?",
        "distractor_1": "Does the Web site have several advertising banners?",
        "distractor_2": "Does the Web site have several graphics and animations?",
        "distractor_3": "Does the Web site have a guest book?"
      },
      {
        "id": "1370",
        "question": "A video clip was recorded with the dimensions of 640 x 480 pixels. If the dimensions of the original clip are reduced by one-fourth, what will the new dimensions be?",
        "answer": "480 x 360",
        "distractor_1": "160 x 120",
        "distractor_2": "180 x 120",
        "distractor_3": "200 x 400"
      },
      {
        "id": "1371",
        "question": "Doing which of the following while delivering a presentation will make it more effective?",
        "answer": "making eye contact with different people in your audience",
        "distractor_1": "constantly looking at your slides to make sure you don't forget anything",
        "distractor_2": "leaning on a piece of furniture to appear relaxed during the presentation",
        "distractor_3": "speaking quickly to make sure you get all of your points into the presentation"
      },
      {
        "id": "1372",
        "question": "What is a word made from the first letters of other words?",
        "answer": "acronym",
        "distractor_1": "synonym",
        "distractor_2": "antonym",
        "distractor_3": "initialization"
      },
      {
        "id": "1373",
        "question": "What is the part of a book that lists the exact page on which a piece of information can be found?",
        "answer": "index",
        "distractor_1": "title page",
        "distractor_2": "abstract",
        "distractor_3": "glossary"
      },
      {
        "id": "5380",
        "question": "Which of the following is a listing at the beginning of a book detailing the organization of the chapters, giving the page numbers for each? ",
        "answer": "table of contents",
        "distractor_1": "bibliography",
        "distractor_2": "index",
        "distractor_3": "chapters"
      },
      {
        "id": "5382",
        "question": "What is the term for the list of sources used in research? ",
        "answer": "bibliography",
        "distractor_1": "index",
        "distractor_2": "table of contents",
        "distractor_3": "dictionary"
      },
      {
        "id": "5384",
        "question": "What is the term for words or expressions that have the same or nearly the same meaning? ",
        "answer": "synonym",
        "distractor_1": "acronym",
        "distractor_2": "antonym",
        "distractor_3": "keyword"
      },
      {
        "id": "5385",
        "question": "What is an important word used in a title or paragraph that is easily identifed and often appears in boldface or italics? ",
        "answer": "keyword",
        "distractor_1": "title",
        "distractor_2": "chapter",
        "distractor_3": "acronym"
      },
      {
        "id": "5387",
        "question": "Which of the following refers to reading the text fairly quickly in order to understand the topic and the main points? ",
        "answer": "skimming",
        "distractor_1": "speed reading",
        "distractor_2": "paraphrasing",
        "distractor_3": "plagiarizing"
      },
      {
        "id": "5388",
        "question": "What does it mean to seek and collect information about a particular topic?",
        "answer": "research",
        "distractor_1": "skimming",
        "distractor_2": "publishing",
        "distractor_3": "plagiarizing"
      },
      {
        "id": "8195",
        "question": "Original words of a writer, such as a novel, poem, play, autobiography, and speech are considered which type of source?",
        "answer": "primary",
        "distractor_1": "verbatim",
        "distractor_2": "literal",
        "distractor_3": "secondary"
      },
      {
        "id": "8196",
        "question": "What is the keyboard shortcut for adding a new slide to your <i>PowerPoint</i> presentation?",
        "answer": "Ctrl+M",
        "distractor_1": "Ctrl+P",
        "distractor_2": "Ctrl+N",
        "distractor_3": "Ctrl+S"
      },
      {
        "id": "8197",
        "question": "Suppose you are creating a 20-slide presentation for your topic. If you want 15% of your slides to have graphics, on how many slides will you need to insert a graphic?",
        "answer": "3",
        "distractor_1": "4",
        "distractor_2": "5",
        "distractor_3": "6"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "127",
    "name": "Astronomy",
    "weight": "90",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1327",
        "question": "Which of these types of cycles is caused by Earth's rotation on its axis?",
        "answer": "day-and-night cycles",
        "distractor_1": "seasonal cycles",
        "distractor_2": "tidal cycles",
        "distractor_3": "eclipse cycles"
      },
      {
        "id": "1328",
        "question": "So far, life has been found on which planet or planets in the solar system?",
        "answer": "only on Earth",
        "distractor_1": "on Earth and Mars",
        "distractor_2": "on all the inner planets",
        "distractor_3": "on all planets in the solar system"
      },
      {
        "id": "1336",
        "question": "What two factors determine the amount of gravitational force exerted by one celestial object on another celestial object?",
        "answer": "mass and distance",
        "distractor_1": "volume and shape",
        "distractor_2": "composition and atmosphere",
        "distractor_3": "rotation and revolution"
      },
      {
        "id": "1338",
        "question": "What term is used to describe the Moon's 'seas,' which are really darkened plains of hardened lava?",
        "answer": "mares or maria",
        "distractor_1": "craters",
        "distractor_2": "rays",
        "distractor_3": "rills or rilles"
      },
      {
        "id": "1339",
        "question": "The Very Large Array in New Mexico and the Arecibo dish in Puerto Rico are examples of which kinds of telescopes?",
        "answer": "radio telescopes",
        "distractor_1": "optical telescopes",
        "distractor_2": "infrared telescopes",
        "distractor_3": "Gamma ray telescopes"
      },
      {
        "id": "1340",
        "question": "Suppose a celestial body, such as a planet or star, has a large mass and is close to another celestial body. What type of force does it exert on the other body?",
        "answer": "gravitational",
        "distractor_1": "rotational",
        "distractor_2": "electromagnetic",
        "distractor_3": "elliptical"
      },
      {
        "id": "1341",
        "question": "Space-based telescopes obtain better images of stars and galaxies than do Earth-based telescopes. What factor relating to space-based telescopes makes this possible?",
        "answer": "They have no interference from gas, clouds, and dust in Earth's atmosphere.",
        "distractor_1": "They are the only telescopes that collect visible light rays and radio waves.",
        "distractor_2": "They have much higher magnifications than Earth-based telescopes.",
        "distractor_3": "They are significantly closer to the stars and galaxies they are observing."
      },
      {
        "id": "5311",
        "question": "What is the term for the geometric figure that best describes the path of planets orbiting the Sun?",
        "answer": "ellipse",
        "distractor_1": "eclipse",
        "distractor_2": "circle",
        "distractor_3": "focus"
      },
      {
        "id": "5312",
        "question": "Which of the following shows distances between planets by making a path in which each centimeter of the path represents a million miles in the solar system?",
        "answer": "scale model",
        "distractor_1": "map",
        "distractor_2": "diorama",
        "distractor_3": "representation"
      },
      {
        "id": "1343",
        "question": "What causes day-and-night cycles on Earth?",
        "answer": "Earth's rotation on its axis",
        "distractor_1": "the tilt of Earth's axis",
        "distractor_2": "the phases of the Moon",
        "distractor_3": "Earth's distance from the Sun"
      },
      {
        "id": "1344",
        "question": "Earth is the only planet that is known to have which of the following characteristics?",
        "answer": "life",
        "distractor_1": "an atmosphere",
        "distractor_2": "a rocky composition",
        "distractor_3": "craters"
      },
      {
        "id": "1345",
        "question": "Which type of telescope produces very clear images because it  receives no interference from gas, clouds, and dust in Earth's atmosphere?",
        "answer": "a space-based telescope",
        "distractor_1": "an optical telescope",
        "distractor_2": "a radio telescope",
        "distractor_3": "an Earth-based telescope"
      },
      {
        "id": "1347",
        "question": "Which of the following planets is NOT a gas giant?",
        "answer": "Mars",
        "distractor_1": "Jupiter",
        "distractor_2": "Saturn",
        "distractor_3": "Neptune"
      },
      {
        "id": "6907",
        "question": "A number expressed as a base and a power of 10 is using which type of format?",
        "answer": "scientific notation",
        "distractor_1": "standard notation",
        "distractor_2": "astronomical units",
        "distractor_3": "scaled units"
      },
      {
        "id": "6908",
        "question": "What causes seasons on Earth?",
        "answer": "the tilt of Earth's axis",
        "distractor_1": "Earth's distance from the Sun",
        "distractor_2": "Earth's rotation on its axis",
        "distractor_3": "Earth's revolution around the Sun"
      },
      {
        "id": "1324",
        "question": "Which of the following planets is considered a gas giant?",
        "answer": "Saturn",
        "distractor_1": "Mars",
        "distractor_2": "Venus",
        "distractor_3": "Earth"
      },
      {
        "id": "6909",
        "question": "Which of the following solar system distances is expressed using correct scientific notation?",
        "answer": "9.3 • 10^7 mi",
        "distractor_1": "1 AU",
        "distractor_2": "93,000,000 mi",
        "distractor_3": "93 • 10^6 mi"
      },
      {
        "id": "5107",
        "question": "What is the movement of Earth or another planet around its axis called?",
        "answer": "rotation",
        "distractor_1": "revolution",
        "distractor_2": "orbit",
        "distractor_3": "eclipse"
      },
      {
        "id": "5108",
        "question": "What is the movement of a planet around the Sun or a moon around its planet?",
        "answer": "revolution",
        "distractor_1": "acceleration",
        "distractor_2": "rotation",
        "distractor_3": "velocity"
      },
      {
        "id": "5109",
        "question": "What is a force that any two bodies exert on each other?",
        "answer": "gravity",
        "distractor_1": "velocity",
        "distractor_2": "acceleration ",
        "distractor_3": "rotation"
      },
      {
        "id": "5110",
        "question": "What is the name of the circular or elliptical path described by a body as it revolves around another body?",
        "answer": "orbit",
        "distractor_1": "eclipse",
        "distractor_2": "ellipse",
        "distractor_3": "sphere"
      },
      {
        "id": "5111",
        "question": "What is a small, solid space object that has passed through the atmosphere and landed on Earth?",
        "answer": "meteorite",
        "distractor_1": "meteor",
        "distractor_2": "meteoroid",
        "distractor_3": "comet"
      },
      {
        "id": "5112",
        "question": "What is the name of any of the numerous chunks of space rock that orbit between Mars and Jupiter?",
        "answer": "asteroid",
        "distractor_1": "meteoroid",
        "distractor_2": "planetoid",
        "distractor_3": "cometoid"
      },
      {
        "id": "5113",
        "question": "What is an orbiting ball of ice and dust that forms a tail as it passes near the Sun?",
        "answer": "comet",
        "distractor_1": "meteor",
        "distractor_2": "moon",
        "distractor_3": "inner planet"
      },
      {
        "id": "5114",
        "question": "What is an optical telescope that uses lenses to focus light?",
        "answer": "refractor",
        "distractor_1": "reflector",
        "distractor_2": "binocular telescope",
        "distractor_3": "gamma ray telescope"
      },
      {
        "id": "5115",
        "question": "What is an optical telescope that uses mirrors to focus light?",
        "answer": "reflector",
        "distractor_1": "refractor",
        "distractor_2": "monocular telescope",
        "distractor_3": "gyroscope"
      },
      {
        "id": "5116",
        "question": "What is the distance around the outside of a circle called?",
        "answer": "circumference",
        "distractor_1": "radius",
        "distractor_2": "diameter",
        "distractor_3": "orbit"
      },
      {
        "id": "5117",
        "question": "What is one-half of a sphere called?",
        "answer": "hemisphere",
        "distractor_1": "semisphere",
        "distractor_2": "spheroid",
        "distractor_3": "semicircle"
      },
      {
        "id": "5118",
        "question": "What is a year containing one extra day, February 29, which occurs every fourth year?",
        "answer": "leap year",
        "distractor_1": "election year",
        "distractor_2": "moon year",
        "distractor_3": "magic year"
      },
      {
        "id": "5119",
        "question": "What is a model that is smaller or larger than an actual object or system, but is proportional in size or distance?",
        "answer": "scale model",
        "distractor_1": "proportional model",
        "distractor_2": "comparison model",
        "distractor_3": "accurate model"
      },
      {
        "id": "5120",
        "question": "What is a method of writing very large or small numbers as a product of two factors, a base number and a power of ten?",
        "answer": "scientific notation",
        "distractor_1": "standard notation",
        "distractor_2": "factor notation",
        "distractor_3": "power notation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6910",
        "question": "When Earth's poles are oriented vertically and the Sun at noon shines directly on the equator, what day of the year is it?",
        "answer": "March 21 or September 23",
        "distractor_1": "June 21 or December 21",
        "distractor_2": "March 21 or June 21",
        "distractor_3": "September 23 or December 21"
      },
      {
        "id": "6911",
        "question": "How do you determine which of two orbits is the most elliptical?",
        "answer": "Its foci are farther apart.",
        "distractor_1": "Its foci are closer together.",
        "distractor_2": "It is longer. ",
        "distractor_3": "It is shorter."
      },
      {
        "id": "6912",
        "question": "To determine the force exerted on an object, one must know or be able to measure which two quantities?",
        "answer": "the object's mass and acceleration",
        "distractor_1": "the object's mass and velocity",
        "distractor_2": "the object's velocity and distance traveled",
        "distractor_3": "the object's mass and the size of its orbit"
      },
      {
        "id": "6913",
        "question": "Which of the following is true of a scale model of planet distance in the solar system?",
        "answer": "Planet distances are accurate relative to each other but on a smaller scale.",
        "distractor_1": "Its planets exactly represent those in the system.",
        "distractor_2": "Its planets are accurate in size but not in distance.",
        "distractor_3": "Planet sizes and distances are both accurate relative to each other."
      },
      {
        "id": "6914",
        "question": "The equation force equals mass times accelerations, or F = ma, is an expression of which physical law?",
        "answer": "Newton's second law of motion",
        "distractor_1": "Kepler's first law of planetary motion",
        "distractor_2": "Kepler's third law of planetary motion",
        "distractor_3": "Newton's law of gravity"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "131",
    "name": "Reactions",
    "weight": "80",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1376",
        "question": "Which type of reaction always releases heat into the environment?",
        "answer": "exothermic",
        "distractor_1": "endothermic",
        "distractor_2": "endogenous",
        "distractor_3": "spontaneous"
      },
      {
        "id": "1377",
        "question": "If you increase the temperature at which a chemical reaction occurs, what will happen to the rate of the reaction?",
        "answer": "It will increase.",
        "distractor_1": "It will decrease.",
        "distractor_2": "It will remain the same.",
        "distractor_3": "It will change randomly, depending on the reactants."
      },
      {
        "id": "1378",
        "question": "Glass was first manufactured in Egypt about 3,000 B.C. What were the components of this glass?",
        "answer": "sand, soda, and lime",
        "distractor_1": "sand, iron, and carbon",
        "distractor_2": "clay, oil, and plastic",
        "distractor_3": "clay, carbon, and copper"
      },
      {
        "id": "1379",
        "question": "What type of reaction occurs when one substance donates electrons and another substance accepts those electrons?",
        "answer": "oxidation-reduction",
        "distractor_1": "gas-forming",
        "distractor_2": "neutralization",
        "distractor_3": "precipitation"
      },
      {
        "id": "1380",
        "question": "How can an exothermic reaction be identified?",
        "answer": "by the increased temperature of the surrounding environment",
        "distractor_1": "by the decreased temperature of the surrounding environment",
        "distractor_2": "by the fact that it occurs spontaneously",
        "distractor_3": "by the fact that it requires a catalyst"
      },
      {
        "id": "1381",
        "question": "An equation is balanced when what factors are the same?",
        "answer": "number of atoms of each element on each side",
        "distractor_1": "number of molecules of each substance on each side",
        "distractor_2": "number of reactants as it has products",
        "distractor_3": "types of molecules on each side"
      },
      {
        "id": "1382",
        "question": "Which of the following is a chemical process, but not a chemical reaction?",
        "answer": "dissolving salt in water",
        "distractor_1": "burning a candle",
        "distractor_2": "combining vinegar and baking soda",
        "distractor_3": "rusting metal"
      },
      {
        "id": "1383",
        "question": "The Tyndall effect is used to distinguish between which two types of substances?",
        "answer": "solutions and nonsolutions",
        "distractor_1": "acids and bases",
        "distractor_2": "precipitates and nonprecipitates",
        "distractor_3": "exothermic and endothermic reactions"
      },
      {
        "id": "1384",
        "question": "What is the type of chemical reaction in which the products can react to form the reactants again?",
        "answer": "reversible",
        "distractor_1": "exothermic",
        "distractor_2": "displacement",
        "distractor_3": "decomposition"
      },
      {
        "id": "1385",
        "question": "How does decreasing the concentration of the reactants affect the rate of a chemical reaction?",
        "answer": "It decreases the rate.",
        "distractor_1": "It increases the rate.",
        "distractor_2": "It increases, then decreases the rate.",
        "distractor_3": "It does not affect the rate."
      },
      {
        "id": "1386",
        "question": "Temperature, catalysts, and the concentration of reactants all change what characteristic of a chemical reaction?",
        "answer": "rate",
        "distractor_1": "type",
        "distractor_2": "products",
        "distractor_3": "direction"
      },
      {
        "id": "1387",
        "question": "What is a mixture containing two or more substances that have dissolved into one another?",
        "answer": "solution",
        "distractor_1": "colloid",
        "distractor_2": "suspension",
        "distractor_3": "nonsolution"
      },
      {
        "id": "1388",
        "question": "All chemical reactions have which of these characteristics?",
        "answer": "They convert reactants into products.",
        "distractor_1": "They absorb heat from the environment.",
        "distractor_2": "They have equal numbers of reactants and products.",
        "distractor_3": "They convert products into reactants."
      },
      {
        "id": "1389",
        "question": "The rate of a chemical reaction is affected by the temperature of the reaction, the presence of a catalyst, and what third factor?",
        "answer": "concentration of the reactants",
        "distractor_1": "presence of an acid",
        "distractor_2": "presence of a substance that will precipitate",
        "distractor_3": "amount of energy needed to start the reaction"
      },
      {
        "id": "1390",
        "question": "If doubling the concentration of a reactant makes the reaction rate three times faster, what will be the effect of quadrupling the concentration?",
        "answer": "The rate will be 9 times faster.",
        "distractor_1": "The rate will be 4 times faster.",
        "distractor_2": "The rate will be 6 times faster.",
        "distractor_3": "The rate will be 12 times faster."
      },
      {
        "id": "1391",
        "question": "The rates of many chemical reactions double for each 10ºC increase in temperature. If the temperature of a reaction were increased by 40ºC, how many times faster would the rate be?",
        "answer": "16",
        "distractor_1": "4",
        "distractor_2": "8",
        "distractor_3": "32"
      },
      {
        "id": "1392",
        "question": "What is the best method for distinguishing between a solution and a nonsolution?",
        "answer": "Determine if they can scatter light.",
        "distractor_1": "Compare their temperatures.",
        "distractor_2": "Test their pH values with litmus paper.",
        "distractor_3": "Determine if they form a precipitate when mixed together."
      },
      {
        "id": "1393",
        "question": "A chemical reaction is always characterized by the ability to do which of the following?",
        "answer": "convert reactants into products",
        "distractor_1": "absorb heat from the environment",
        "distractor_2": "produce a color change",
        "distractor_3": "convert products into reactants"
      },
      {
        "id": "1394",
        "question": "What does the electrolysis of water produce?",
        "answer": "the gases hydrogen and oxygen",
        "distractor_1": "an acid and a base",
        "distractor_2": "a precipitate and a soluble compound",
        "distractor_3": "heated water"
      },
      {
        "id": "1395",
        "question": "The electrolysis of water into its component parts is a chemical reaction of which of the following types?",
        "answer": "gas forming",
        "distractor_1": "neutralization",
        "distractor_2": "precipitation",
        "distractor_3": "combustion"
      },
      {
        "id": "1396",
        "question": "On the periodic table, which of the following groups of elements is inert, that is, nonreactive and able to form very few new compounds?",
        "answer": "noble gases",
        "distractor_1": "alkali metals",
        "distractor_2": "transition metals",
        "distractor_3": "nonmetals"
      },
      {
        "id": "1397",
        "question": "When pollutants called CFCs destroy ozone in the upper atmosphere, what factor increases at ground level?",
        "answer": "ultraviolet radiation",
        "distractor_1": "smog",
        "distractor_2": "ozone",
        "distractor_3": "chlorine"
      },
      {
        "id": "1398",
        "question": "Dissolving sugar in water is a process instead of a reaction, because a certain factor is NOT formed during the process. What is this factor?",
        "answer": "products",
        "distractor_1": "solution",
        "distractor_2": "ions",
        "distractor_3": "reactants"
      },
      {
        "id": "1399",
        "question": "What does a homogeneous mixture, or solution, contain?",
        "answer": "substances that have dissolved into one another",
        "distractor_1": "only one type of substance",
        "distractor_2": "particles that stay suspended after the mixture is shaken",
        "distractor_3": "substances with large, visible particles"
      },
      {
        "id": "1374",
        "question": "What type of reaction occurs when an acid and a base react to form a salt and water?",
        "answer": "neutralization",
        "distractor_1": "precipitation",
        "distractor_2": "gas-forming",
        "distractor_3": "oxidation-reduction"
      },
      {
        "id": "1375",
        "question": "What description is given to a chemical equation that has the same number of atoms of each type of molecule on each of the two sides?",
        "answer": "balanced",
        "distractor_1": "stable",
        "distractor_2": "equalized",
        "distractor_3": "endothermic"
      },
      {
        "id": "6685",
        "question": "What is a homogeneous mixture, formed when two or more substances dissolve into one another?",
        "answer": "solution",
        "distractor_1": "nonsolution",
        "distractor_2": "compound",
        "distractor_3": "matter"
      },
      {
        "id": "6686",
        "question": "What is a heterogeneous mixture, formed of two or more substances that can be separated after being mixed together?",
        "answer": "nonsolution",
        "distractor_1": "solution",
        "distractor_2": "compound",
        "distractor_3": "catalyst"
      },
      {
        "id": "6687",
        "question": "What is an insoluble solid formed when two ionic compounds dissolve and their ions recombine?",
        "answer": "precipitate",
        "distractor_1": "compound",
        "distractor_2": "base",
        "distractor_3": "combustion"
      },
      {
        "id": "6688",
        "question": "What is a substance that donates hydrogen ions during a chemical reaction, tastes sour, and turns blue litmus paper red?",
        "answer": "acid",
        "distractor_1": "base",
        "distractor_2": "compound",
        "distractor_3": "element"
      },
      {
        "id": "6689",
        "question": "What is a substance that donates hydroxide ions during a chemical reaction, tastes bitter, and turns red litmus paper blue?",
        "answer": "base",
        "distractor_1": "acid",
        "distractor_2": "compound",
        "distractor_3": "element"
      },
      {
        "id": "6690",
        "question": "What is one of the substances formed during a neutralization reaction, when an acid and a base combine?",
        "answer": "salt",
        "distractor_1": "base",
        "distractor_2": "ph",
        "distractor_3": "ions"
      },
      {
        "id": "6691",
        "question": "What is an exothermic chemical reaction that requires the presence of heat, oxygen, and fuel?",
        "answer": "combustion",
        "distractor_1": "nonsolution",
        "distractor_2": "precipitate",
        "distractor_3": "base"
      },
      {
        "id": "6692",
        "question": "What is a substance that speeds up a chemical reaction without being changed in the reaction?",
        "answer": "catalyst",
        "distractor_1": "combustion",
        "distractor_2": "nonsolution",
        "distractor_3": "element"
      },
      {
        "id": "6677",
        "question": "What is the smallest unit of an element; has all the characteristics of that element?",
        "answer": "atom",
        "distractor_1": "molecule",
        "distractor_2": "particle",
        "distractor_3": "ion"
      },
      {
        "id": "6678",
        "question": "What is a combination of atoms that forms the smallest unit of a compound and has all the characteristics of that compound?",
        "answer": "molecule",
        "distractor_1": "atom",
        "distractor_2": "particle ",
        "distractor_3": "ion"
      },
      {
        "id": "6679",
        "question": "What is a list of all elements in order of atomic number, rearranged in rows and columns based on their physical and chemical properties?",
        "answer": "periodic table",
        "distractor_1": "mineral table",
        "distractor_2": "periodic and mineral table",
        "distractor_3": "catalyst"
      },
      {
        "id": "6680",
        "question": "What is an electrically charged particle formed when a compound dissolves in water?",
        "answer": "ion",
        "distractor_1": "article",
        "distractor_2": "atom",
        "distractor_3": "molecule"
      },
      {
        "id": "6681",
        "question": "What is anything that has mass and takes up space?",
        "answer": "matter",
        "distractor_1": "mass",
        "distractor_2": "weight",
        "distractor_3": "atom"
      },
      {
        "id": "6682",
        "question": "What is a process during which chemical bonds in one or more substances are broken and new bonds are formed to make one or more new substances?",
        "answer": "chemical reaction",
        "distractor_1": "catalyst",
        "distractor_2": "combustion",
        "distractor_3": "nonsolution"
      },
      {
        "id": "6683",
        "question": "What is a substance that cannot be decomposed into a simpler substance by any chemical reaction?",
        "answer": "element",
        "distractor_1": "molecule",
        "distractor_2": "atom",
        "distractor_3": "particle"
      },
      {
        "id": "6684",
        "question": "What is a pure substance composed of two or more chemically combined elements?",
        "answer": "compound",
        "distractor_1": "element",
        "distractor_2": "solution",
        "distractor_3": "nonsolution"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "126",
    "name": "Material Science",
    "weight": "80",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1400",
        "question": "What type of electrons are found in the outermost shell of an atom?",
        "answer": "valence",
        "distractor_1": "potential",
        "distractor_2": "active",
        "distractor_3": "empty"
      },
      {
        "id": "1401",
        "question": "What type of substance is formed when elements are chemically combined?",
        "answer": "compound",
        "distractor_1": "mixture",
        "distractor_2": "ion",
        "distractor_3": "solution"
      },
      {
        "id": "1402",
        "question": "There are 112 known elements. Of those, only 17 are nonmetals. What percent of the known elements are nonmetals?",
        "answer": "15.2 percent",
        "distractor_1": "17 percent",
        "distractor_2": "83 percent",
        "distractor_3": "84.8 percent"
      },
      {
        "id": "1403",
        "question": "What is a substance that contains only one type of atom?",
        "answer": "element",
        "distractor_1": "atom",
        "distractor_2": "molecule",
        "distractor_3": "ion"
      },
      {
        "id": "1404",
        "question": "Valence electrons are found in which shell or shells of an atom?",
        "answer": "outermost shell",
        "distractor_1": "innermost shell",
        "distractor_2": "middle shells",
        "distractor_3": "scattered throughout any shells"
      },
      {
        "id": "1405",
        "question": "The atomic number of silver is 47. The most common silver isotope has an atomic mass of 108. How many neutrons are in silver 108?",
        "answer": "61",
        "distractor_1": "47",
        "distractor_2": "108",
        "distractor_3": "155"
      },
      {
        "id": "1406",
        "question": "Isotopes of an element have different numbers of what component?",
        "answer": "neutrons",
        "distractor_1": "protons",
        "distractor_2": "electrons",
        "distractor_3": "ions"
      },
      {
        "id": "1407",
        "question": "Nonmetals are primarily found in what area of the periodic table?",
        "answer": "right",
        "distractor_1": "left",
        "distractor_2": "top",
        "distractor_3": "bottom"
      },
      {
        "id": "1408",
        "question": "What is the name for a bond that involves the sharing of electrons?",
        "answer": "covalent",
        "distractor_1": "ionic",
        "distractor_2": "atomic",
        "distractor_3": "electronic"
      },
      {
        "id": "1409",
        "question": "In which state of matter are the atoms or molecules normally far apart from each other?",
        "answer": "gas",
        "distractor_1": "liquid",
        "distractor_2": "solid",
        "distractor_3": "metal"
      },
      {
        "id": "1410",
        "question": "What is the heaviest element found in nature?",
        "answer": "uranium",
        "distractor_1": "lead",
        "distractor_2": "radium",
        "distractor_3": "nobelium"
      },
      {
        "id": "1411",
        "question": "In a chemical reaction, how does the mass of the chemicals present before the reaction compare to the mass after the reaction?",
        "answer": "It is equal.",
        "distractor_1": "It is greater.",
        "distractor_2": "It is less.",
        "distractor_3": "It is not related."
      },
      {
        "id": "1412",
        "question": "What is the relationship between the atoms or molecules that make up a gas?",
        "answer": "They are far apart from each other.",
        "distractor_1": "They are bonded to each other.",
        "distractor_2": "They are touching each other.",
        "distractor_3": "They are repelled by each other."
      },
      {
        "id": "1413",
        "question": "What is the law relating the temperature and volume of a gas?",
        "answer": "Charles'",
        "distractor_1": "Avogadro's",
        "distractor_2": "Boyle's",
        "distractor_3": "Dalton's"
      },
      {
        "id": "1414",
        "question": "What is the smallest unit of a compound that retains the properties of the compound?",
        "answer": "molecule",
        "distractor_1": "element",
        "distractor_2": "atom",
        "distractor_3": "ion"
      },
      {
        "id": "1416",
        "question": "When an atom loses or gains electrons and becomes electrically charged, which of the following is formed?",
        "answer": "ion",
        "distractor_1": "compound",
        "distractor_2": "mixture",
        "distractor_3": "solution"
      },
      {
        "id": "1418",
        "question": "Where is most of the mass of an atom concentrated?",
        "answer": "in the nucleus",
        "distractor_1": "in the electron shells",
        "distractor_2": "in the spaces between electron shells",
        "distractor_3": "in the protons of the nucleus"
      },
      {
        "id": "1419",
        "question": "Charles' law shows the relationship between which two properties of a gas?",
        "answer": "temperature and volume",
        "distractor_1": "mass and volume",
        "distractor_2": "mass and energy",
        "distractor_3": "temperature and mass"
      },
      {
        "id": "1420",
        "question": "The periodic table of elements is arranged according to what property of the elements?",
        "answer": "atomic number",
        "distractor_1": "valence",
        "distractor_2": "atomic mass",
        "distractor_3": "melting point"
      },
      {
        "id": "1421",
        "question": "What comprises most of the volume of an atom?",
        "answer": "empty space",
        "distractor_1": "protons",
        "distractor_2": "neutrons",
        "distractor_3": "electrons"
      },
      {
        "id": "1422",
        "question": "Most of the elements in the periodic table are what type of element?",
        "answer": "metals",
        "distractor_1": "liquids",
        "distractor_2": "halogens",
        "distractor_3": "nonmetals"
      },
      {
        "id": "1423",
        "question": "The atomic mass of sodium is 23. The atomic mass of fluorine is 19. What is the molecular weight of NaF (sodium fluoride)?",
        "answer": "42",
        "distractor_1": "19",
        "distractor_2": "21",
        "distractor_3": "23"
      },
      {
        "id": "1424",
        "question": "Nuclear fission is a splitting reaction that  releases huge amounts of energy, including radiation. What is split during nuclear fission?",
        "answer": "the nuclei of atoms",
        "distractor_1": "electrons",
        "distractor_2": "molecules",
        "distractor_3": "the orbitals of atoms"
      },
      {
        "id": "5473",
        "question": "What occurs when two atoms share electrons?",
        "answer": "covalent bond",
        "distractor_1": "chemical bond",
        "distractor_2": "ionic bond",
        "distractor_3": "bond"
      },
      {
        "id": "5474",
        "question": "What is defined as a single unit of an element or the smallest unit into which matter can be divided without the release of electrically charged particles?",
        "answer": "atom",
        "distractor_1": "proton",
        "distractor_2": "neutron",
        "distractor_3": "electron"
      },
      {
        "id": "5475",
        "question": "What occurs when a loosely bound electron from one atom transfers to a deeper shell in another atom?",
        "answer": "ionic bond",
        "distractor_1": "covalent bond",
        "distractor_2": "chemical bond",
        "distractor_3": "bond"
      },
      {
        "id": "5476",
        "question": "What is defined as a subatomic particle with no electrical charge?",
        "answer": "neutron",
        "distractor_1": "electron",
        "distractor_2": "atom",
        "distractor_3": "isotope"
      },
      {
        "id": "5477",
        "question": "What is a negatively charged subatomic particle?",
        "answer": "electron",
        "distractor_1": "neutron",
        "distractor_2": "proton",
        "distractor_3": "ion"
      },
      {
        "id": "5478",
        "question": "Which of the following is a positively charged subatomic particle?",
        "answer": "proton",
        "distractor_1": "electron",
        "distractor_2": "ion",
        "distractor_3": "atom"
      },
      {
        "id": "5479",
        "question": "What is defined as being different form of an element?",
        "answer": "isotope",
        "distractor_1": "ion",
        "distractor_2": "compound",
        "distractor_3": "electron"
      },
      {
        "id": "5480",
        "question": "Which of the following is defined as an atom that has lost or gained electrons and is electrically charged?",
        "answer": "ion",
        "distractor_1": "electron",
        "distractor_2": "element",
        "distractor_3": "proton"
      },
      {
        "id": "5523",
        "question": "What is an aspect of an element whose value can be measured?",
        "answer": "property",
        "distractor_1": "element",
        "distractor_2": "atom",
        "distractor_3": "isotope"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "132",
    "name": "Heat & Energy",
    "weight": "80",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1427",
        "question": "Which of these substances is NOT a good heat insulator?",
        "answer": "aluminum",
        "distractor_1": "wool",
        "distractor_2": "air",
        "distractor_3": "straw"
      },
      {
        "id": "1428",
        "question": "When any substance is heated, what happens to the atoms in that substance?",
        "answer": "they speed up",
        "distractor_1": "they slow down",
        "distractor_2": "they stop moving",
        "distractor_3": "they are not affected"
      },
      {
        "id": "1429",
        "question": "A complete combustion reaction produces heat and light energy. What two compounds are also products of this reaction?",
        "answer": "carbon dioxide and water",
        "distractor_1": "carbon dioxide and oxygen",
        "distractor_2": "methane and oxygen",
        "distractor_3": "methane and water"
      },
      {
        "id": "1430",
        "question": "What type of engine converts thermal energy to mechanical energy?",
        "answer": "heat engine",
        "distractor_1": "steam engine",
        "distractor_2": "internal combustion engine",
        "distractor_3": "external combustion engine"
      },
      {
        "id": "1431",
        "question": "Which of the following situations is not an example of the release of stored chemical energy?",
        "answer": "a nuclear reactor producing heat toturn water to steam",
        "distractor_1": "cells breaking down sugar",
        "distractor_2": "the production of electric current bya car battery",
        "distractor_3": "the burning of natural gas by a heatunit in a home"
      },
      {
        "id": "1432",
        "question": "Self-feeding organisms, such as green plants, make their own food by storing the Sun's energy during photosynthesis. What scientific term is used to describe these organisms?",
        "answer": "autotrophic",
        "distractor_1": "heterotrophic",
        "distractor_2": "omnivorous",
        "distractor_3": "energetic"
      },
      {
        "id": "1433",
        "question": "What happens during an exothermic reaction?",
        "answer": "The reaction releases energy into the environment.",
        "distractor_1": "The reaction stores energy from the environment.",
        "distractor_2": "The reaction exchanges energy with the environment.",
        "distractor_3": "The reaction creates new energy from the environment."
      },
      {
        "id": "1434",
        "question": "Hydrocarbon molecules, formed from hydrogen and carbon, make up which of the following substances?",
        "answer": "fossil fuels",
        "distractor_1": "nuclear fuels",
        "distractor_2": "electricity",
        "distractor_3": "food"
      },
      {
        "id": "1435",
        "question": "What does the chemical formula of a molecule represent?",
        "answer": "the number and types of atoms in the molecule",
        "distractor_1": "the arrangement of atoms in the molecule",
        "distractor_2": "the three-dimensional shape of the molecule",
        "distractor_3": "the reactions the molecule undergoes"
      },
      {
        "id": "1436",
        "question": "When energy is transferred from a power plant to electric lines to your home, heat is lost with each transfer. This is an illustration of what concept?",
        "answer": "the second law of thermodynamics",
        "distractor_1": "the first law of thermodynamics",
        "distractor_2": "heat expansion",
        "distractor_3": "potential energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "1437",
        "question": "All fossil fuels are composed of which two elements?",
        "answer": "carbon and hydrogen",
        "distractor_1": "carbon and oxygen",
        "distractor_2": "hydrogen and oxygen",
        "distractor_3": "oxygen and sulfur"
      },
      {
        "id": "1438",
        "question": "Which of these substances would be the best heat conductor?",
        "answer": "copper",
        "distractor_1": "air",
        "distractor_2": "straw",
        "distractor_3": "wool"
      },
      {
        "id": "1439",
        "question": "Heat travels in three ways, conduction, convection, and which of the following?",
        "answer": "radiation",
        "distractor_1": "joules",
        "distractor_2": "velocity",
        "distractor_3": "contraction"
      },
      {
        "id": "1440",
        "question": "Carbon dioxide and water represent what part of a complete combustion reaction?",
        "answer": "products",
        "distractor_1": "reactants",
        "distractor_2": "catalysts",
        "distractor_3": "activation energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "1441",
        "question": "Which type of chemical reaction releases energy into the environment?",
        "answer": "exothermic",
        "distractor_1": "thermodynamic",
        "distractor_2": "endothermic",
        "distractor_3": "calorimetric"
      },
      {
        "id": "1442",
        "question": "What type of heat transfer occurs when you place your hand in warm water and the heat is transferred to your hand?",
        "answer": "conduction",
        "distractor_1": "radiation",
        "distractor_2": "convection",
        "distractor_3": "expansion"
      },
      {
        "id": "1443",
        "question": "What is another phrase for the energy of movement?",
        "answer": "kinetic energy",
        "distractor_1": "thermal energy",
        "distractor_2": "potential energy",
        "distractor_3": "nuclear energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "1444",
        "question": "What apparatus is used to measure the total amount of heat energy contained in a substance, such as food?",
        "answer": "bomb calorimeter",
        "distractor_1": "heat exchanger",
        "distractor_2": "Bunsen burner",
        "distractor_3": "fusion reactor"
      },
      {
        "id": "1445",
        "question": "Which of the following is the best statement of the second law of thermodynamics?",
        "answer": "No energy transformation is 100 percent efficient.",
        "distractor_1": "Energy can neither be created nor destroyed.",
        "distractor_2": "The total amount of energy in a system remains constant.",
        "distractor_3": "The most efficient form of energy is heat energy."
      },
      {
        "id": "1446",
        "question": "Which of the following explains the increasing rate of movement of gas molecules as the gas is heated?",
        "answer": "kinetic molecular theory",
        "distractor_1": "first law of thermodynamics",
        "distractor_2": "second law of thermodynamics",
        "distractor_3": "heat expansion theory"
      },
      {
        "id": "1447",
        "question": "Why are carbon atoms said to form the backbone of all 'molecules of life'?",
        "answer": "They are able to bond with each other, forming long chains.",
        "distractor_1": "They are the largest atoms.",
        "distractor_2": "They are the atoms with the most electrons.",
        "distractor_3": "They are the only atoms that can form covalent bonds."
      },
      {
        "id": "1448",
        "question": "Which type of formula represents the arrangement of atoms in a molecule as a two-dimensional stick figure?",
        "answer": "structural",
        "distractor_1": "chemical",
        "distractor_2": "atomic",
        "distractor_3": "bonding"
      },
      {
        "id": "1449",
        "question": "A Big-Bite hamburger contains 570 kilocalories (Calories). How many calories does it contain?",
        "answer": "570,000 cal",
        "distractor_1": "0.57 cal",
        "distractor_2": "57 cal",
        "distractor_3": "5,700 cal"
      },
      {
        "id": "1450",
        "question": "Which of the following types of atoms forms the 'backbone' of an organic molecule by bonding to itself?",
        "answer": "carbon",
        "distractor_1": "hydrogen",
        "distractor_2": "oxygen",
        "distractor_3": "calcium"
      },
      {
        "id": "1451",
        "question": "Which of the following objects is showing kinetic energy?",
        "answer": "water in the middle of a waterfall",
        "distractor_1": "a rock at the top of a hill",
        "distractor_2": "a runner poised at the starting line",
        "distractor_3": "water at the top of a waterfall"
      },
      {
        "id": "5504",
        "question": "What term is defined as the total energy resulting from the random motion of molecules in a substance?",
        "answer": "heat",
        "distractor_1": "specific heat",
        "distractor_2": "radiation",
        "distractor_3": "convection"
      },
      {
        "id": "5505",
        "question": "What is known as the measure of the average amount of heat resulting from the random motion of molecules?",
        "answer": "temperature",
        "distractor_1": "heat",
        "distractor_2": "fuel",
        "distractor_3": "energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "5506",
        "question": "Which term is defined as the ability to do work?",
        "answer": "energy",
        "distractor_1": "fuel",
        "distractor_2": "conductor",
        "distractor_3": "combustion"
      },
      {
        "id": "5507",
        "question": "What can be defined as any chemical that can be burned to release stored energy and produce power?",
        "answer": "fuel",
        "distractor_1": "hydrocarbon",
        "distractor_2": "heat",
        "distractor_3": "energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "5508",
        "question": "Which of the following is a type of fuel molecule composed only of hydrogen and carbon?",
        "answer": "hydrocarbon",
        "distractor_1": "calorie",
        "distractor_2": "carbon",
        "distractor_3": "oxygen"
      },
      {
        "id": "5509",
        "question": "What is the amount of heat energy required to raise the temperature of one gram of pure water by one degree Celsius?",
        "answer": "calorie",
        "distractor_1": "kilogram",
        "distractor_2": "joule",
        "distractor_3": "kilowatt"
      },
      {
        "id": "5510",
        "question": "What is defined as the amount of heat energy required to raise the temperature of one gram of any substance by one degree Celsius?",
        "answer": "specific heat",
        "distractor_1": "latent heat",
        "distractor_2": "calorie",
        "distractor_3": "energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "5511",
        "question": "What is defined as the amount of heat that can be stored or released by a substance during a phase change?",
        "answer": "latent heat",
        "distractor_1": "specific heat",
        "distractor_2": "energy",
        "distractor_3": "calorie"
      },
      {
        "id": "5512",
        "question": "What is a substance that slows or restricts the passage of heat?",
        "answer": "insulator",
        "distractor_1": "conductor",
        "distractor_2": "radiator",
        "distractor_3": "hydrocarbon"
      },
      {
        "id": "5513",
        "question": "What is a substance that transfers heat very efficiently through its particles by direct contact?",
        "answer": "conductor",
        "distractor_1": "radiator",
        "distractor_2": "insulator",
        "distractor_3": "hydrocarbon"
      },
      {
        "id": "5514",
        "question": "What is known as the transfer of heat energy through air or space, without the need for matter?",
        "answer": "radiation",
        "distractor_1": "convection",
        "distractor_2": "combustion",
        "distractor_3": "specific heat"
      },
      {
        "id": "5515",
        "question": "What term is defined as a form of heat transfer by means of circular currents that are driven by temperature differences in the system?",
        "answer": "convection",
        "distractor_1": "radiation",
        "distractor_2": "latent heat",
        "distractor_3": "specific heat"
      },
      {
        "id": "5516",
        "question": "Which of the following is a chemical reaction that requires oxygen, fire, and fuel?",
        "answer": "combustion",
        "distractor_1": "convection",
        "distractor_2": "melting",
        "distractor_3": "boiling"
      },
      {
        "id": "5517",
        "question": "What is the temperature at which a substance changes from a solid to a liquid?",
        "answer": "melting point",
        "distractor_1": "boiling point",
        "distractor_2": "freezing",
        "distractor_3": "40 degrees"
      },
      {
        "id": "5518",
        "question": "What is the temperature at which a substance changes from a liquid to a gas?",
        "answer": "boiling point",
        "distractor_1": "melting point",
        "distractor_2": "freezing",
        "distractor_3": "50 degrees"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "321",
    "name": "Microbiology",
    "weight": "85",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8143",
        "question": "Suppose a paramecium is 0.3 mm long. If the paramecium is magnified 75 times, how large would it appear?",
        "answer": "2.25 cm",
        "distractor_1": "22.5 cm",
        "distractor_2": "25 cm",
        "distractor_3": "2.5 cm"
      },
      {
        "id": "8144",
        "question": "The number of bacteria in a culture doubles every 30 minutes. A culture covers an area 2 mm by 2mm. How long will it take to cover an 8 mm by 8 mm area?",
        "answer": "2 hours",
        "distractor_1": "1-1/2 hours",
        "distractor_2": "2-1/2 hours",
        "distractor_3": "4 hours"
      },
      {
        "id": "8145",
        "question": "What is the name of living plant or animal that parasite lives and feeds on or in?",
        "answer": "Host",
        "distractor_1": "Bacteria",
        "distractor_2": "Animal",
        "distractor_3": "Parental"
      },
      {
        "id": "4401",
        "question": "What is the term for the short hairlike structures that extend from the cells of certain protists?",
        "answer": "cilia",
        "distractor_1": "hyphae",
        "distractor_2": "spirillum",
        "distractor_3": "nodules"
      },
      {
        "id": "4402",
        "question": "Of the four forms of motility listed, which one does a Euglena use?",
        "answer": "flagellum",
        "distractor_1": "cilia",
        "distractor_2": "pseudopod",
        "distractor_3": "gliding"
      },
      {
        "id": "4403",
        "question": "What term is defined as a group of bacteria that started with one bacterium?",
        "answer": "colony",
        "distractor_1": "bunch",
        "distractor_2": "cluster",
        "distractor_3": "plague"
      },
      {
        "id": "4404",
        "question": "Which of the following organisms is a producer?",
        "answer": "cactus",
        "distractor_1": "worm",
        "distractor_2": "diatom",
        "distractor_3": "fungus"
      },
      {
        "id": "4405",
        "question": "What type of protozoan moves by pseudopodia?",
        "answer": "amoeba",
        "distractor_1": "paramecium",
        "distractor_2": "euglena",
        "distractor_3": "diatom"
      },
      {
        "id": "4406",
        "question": "Choose the general classification for any organism that produces or makes its own food.",
        "answer": "producer",
        "distractor_1": "consumer",
        "distractor_2": "creator",
        "distractor_3": "animal"
      },
      {
        "id": "4407",
        "question": "Some bacteria can reproduce every 20 minutes. At this rate, how long would it take for a single bacteria to generate more than 100 offspring?",
        "answer": "between 2 and 2-1/2 hours",
        "distractor_1": "between 1 and 1-1/2 hours",
        "distractor_2": "between 1-1/2 and 2 hours",
        "distractor_3": "between 2-1/2 and 3 hours"
      },
      {
        "id": "4408",
        "question": "What is an organism that lives in or on another organism and harms it called?",
        "answer": "parasite",
        "distractor_1": "host",
        "distractor_2": "mutation",
        "distractor_3": "flagellum"
      },
      {
        "id": "4410",
        "question": "The deadly disease, malaria, is carried by a protist found in the gut of what organism?",
        "answer": "mosquito",
        "distractor_1": "termite",
        "distractor_2": "horsefly",
        "distractor_3": "flea"
      },
      {
        "id": "4411",
        "question": "What is binomial nomenclature?",
        "answer": "a two-part naming system used by scientists",
        "distractor_1": "a three-step program to develop a new species",
        "distractor_2": "a two-part elimination system for molds",
        "distractor_3": "a three-step process for classifying protozoa"
      },
      {
        "id": "4412",
        "question": "Two or more organisms that coexist together and are of different species have what kind of relationship?",
        "answer": "symbiotic",
        "distractor_1": "prenatal",
        "distractor_2": "parental",
        "distractor_3": "working"
      },
      {
        "id": "4413",
        "question": "Which kingdom has organisms with the simplest cell structure?",
        "answer": "moneran",
        "distractor_1": "animal",
        "distractor_2": "plant",
        "distractor_3": "fungi"
      },
      {
        "id": "4414",
        "question": "Name the large group of animallike, single-celled organisms.",
        "answer": "protozoans",
        "distractor_1": "protists",
        "distractor_2": "monerans",
        "distractor_3": "bacteria"
      },
      {
        "id": "4415",
        "question": "Which of the following is a single-celled organism that can have either plant or animal characteristics?",
        "answer": "protist",
        "distractor_1": "virus",
        "distractor_2": "bacterium",
        "distractor_3": "parasite"
      },
      {
        "id": "4416",
        "question": "Ten million salmonella bacteria can fit into a 3 mm by 3 mm square. How many salmonella can fit into a 6 mm by 6 mm square?",
        "answer": "40 million",
        "distractor_1": "20 million",
        "distractor_2": "30 million",
        "distractor_3": "36 million"
      },
      {
        "id": "4417",
        "question": "What type of organism does NOT have its genetic material enclosed inside a nucleus?",
        "answer": "prokaryote",
        "distractor_1": "eukaryote",
        "distractor_2": "monocot",
        "distractor_3": "dicot"
      },
      {
        "id": "4418",
        "question": "Which of the following statements best defines symbiosis?",
        "answer": "two organisms of different species that coexist",
        "distractor_1": "two organisms of the same species that coexist",
        "distractor_2": "two organisms that exist in the same community, but do not interact",
        "distractor_3": "two organisms of different species that feed upon one another"
      },
      {
        "id": "4419",
        "question": "Which group of organisms are prokaryotes?",
        "answer": "monerans",
        "distractor_1": "animals",
        "distractor_2": "protists",
        "distractor_3": "fungi"
      },
      {
        "id": "4420",
        "question": "What is the basic structure of the flagella that some protists use for movement?",
        "answer": "long and whip-like",
        "distractor_1": "tiny and hair-like",
        "distractor_2": "extensions of  cytoplasm",
        "distractor_3": "hard and jointed"
      },
      {
        "id": "4421",
        "question": "What are protozoa?",
        "answer": "single-celled organisms with animallike characteristics",
        "distractor_1": "multicelled organisms with flagella",
        "distractor_2": "multicelled organisms with chlorophyll",
        "distractor_3": "single-celled organisms without a nucleus"
      },
      {
        "id": "4422",
        "question": "An organism is multicellular and eukaryotic, and feeds by secreting digestive juices outside its body. It belongs to which kingdom?",
        "answer": "Fungi",
        "distractor_1": "Monera",
        "distractor_2": "Protists",
        "distractor_3": "Plantae"
      },
      {
        "id": "4423",
        "question": "What deadly disease is carried by a protist that lives inside a mosquito?",
        "answer": "malaria",
        "distractor_1": "polio",
        "distractor_2": "diphtheria",
        "distractor_3": "rabies"
      },
      {
        "id": "4424",
        "question": "What are the tiny hair-like structures called that paramecia use for movement?",
        "answer": "cilia",
        "distractor_1": "pseudopods",
        "distractor_2": "flagella",
        "distractor_3": "wings"
      },
      {
        "id": "4425",
        "question": "What is the term that defines the science of classifying organisms?",
        "answer": "taxonomy",
        "distractor_1": "amalgamy",
        "distractor_2": "microscopy",
        "distractor_3": "biology"
      },
      {
        "id": "4399",
        "question": "What is the naming system scientists use to classify organisms?",
        "answer": "binomial nomenclature",
        "distractor_1": "binomial coefficient",
        "distractor_2": "binomial distribution",
        "distractor_3": "binomial theorem"
      },
      {
        "id": "6609",
        "question": "What is any large group of single-celled organisms that have no organized nucleus?",
        "answer": "bacteria",
        "distractor_1": "algae",
        "distractor_2": "virus",
        "distractor_3": "protists"
      },
      {
        "id": "6610",
        "question": "What is a whip-like tail on bacteria and some protists that helps them move through a moist environment?",
        "answer": "flagella",
        "distractor_1": "protist",
        "distractor_2": "pseudopods",
        "distractor_3": "algae"
      },
      {
        "id": "6611",
        "question": "What is a footlike cytoplasmic extension used by some organisms to move and trap food?",
        "answer": "Pseudopods",
        "distractor_1": "Protozoan",
        "distractor_2": "Nucleus",
        "distractor_3": "Flagella"
      },
      {
        "id": "6612",
        "question": "What is a microscopic particle made of either DNA or RNA core and covered with a protein coat; it infects host cells in order to reproduce?",
        "answer": "Virus",
        "distractor_1": "Bacteria",
        "distractor_2": "Parasite",
        "distractor_3": "Protist"
      },
      {
        "id": "6613",
        "question": "What is a chiefly aquatic, eukaryotic, photosynthetic organisms, ranging in size from single-celled forms to the giant kelp?",
        "answer": "Algae",
        "distractor_1": "Bacteria",
        "distractor_2": "Host",
        "distractor_3": "Protozoan"
      },
      {
        "id": "6614",
        "question": "What is a sometimes fatal disease of the nervous system acquired from spoiled foods?",
        "answer": "Botulism",
        "distractor_1": "Algae",
        "distractor_2": "Parasite",
        "distractor_3": "Virus"
      },
      {
        "id": "6615",
        "question": "What is the term for an organism that receives nutrition from a living animal or plant?",
        "answer": "parasite",
        "distractor_1": "virus",
        "distractor_2": "bacterium",
        "distractor_3": "alga"
      },
      {
        "id": "6616",
        "question": "What is a specialized, usually spherical mass of protoplasm encased in a double membrane, and found in most living eukaryotic cells, directing their growth, metabolism, and reproduction, and functioning in the transmission of genic characters?",
        "answer": "Nucleus",
        "distractor_1": "Protist",
        "distractor_2": "Cilia",
        "distractor_3": "Flagella"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "138",
    "name": "Organism Reproduction",
    "weight": "92",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8185",
        "question": "Some bacteria can reproduce every 20 minutes. At this rate, how long would it take for a single bacteria to generate more than 100 offspring?",
        "answer": "between 2 and 2-1/2 hours",
        "distractor_1": "between 1 and 1-1/2 hours",
        "distractor_2": "between 1-1/2 and 2 hours",
        "distractor_3": "between 2-1/2 and 3 hours"
      },
      {
        "id": "8186",
        "question": "The number of bacteria in a culture doubles every 30 minutes. A culture covers an area 2 mm by 2 mm. How long will it take to cover an 8 mm by 8 mm area?",
        "answer": "2 hours",
        "distractor_1": "1-1/2 hours",
        "distractor_2": "2-1/2 hours",
        "distractor_3": "4 hours"
      },
      {
        "id": "8187",
        "question": "Cells reproduce through mitosis, a process in which the cell divides into two new cells. Suppose a cell and its offspring divide every hour. If this cell is placed alone in a dish, how many cells should be in the dish after five hours?",
        "answer": "32",
        "distractor_1": "10",
        "distractor_2": "16",
        "distractor_3": "24"
      },
      {
        "id": "8188",
        "question": "Humans have 46 chromosomes, or 23 pairs of chromosomes. For any chromosomes, the probability that two siblings will have a match is 0.5. What is the probability that the siblings will have a match in a given chromosome pair?",
        "answer": "0.25",
        "distractor_1": "0.5",
        "distractor_2": "0.75",
        "distractor_3": "1"
      },
      {
        "id": "1524",
        "question": "During cell division, what does the parent cell make an exact copy of so that the daughter cells will be identical to the parent?",
        "answer": "DNA",
        "distractor_1": "cytoplasm",
        "distractor_2": "ribosomes",
        "distractor_3": "cell wall"
      },
      {
        "id": "1525",
        "question": "During which reproductive method is a new organism formed from one parent cell?",
        "answer": "asexual reproduction",
        "distractor_1": "sexual reproduction",
        "distractor_2": "fertilization",
        "distractor_3": "meiosis"
      },
      {
        "id": "1527",
        "question": "Inside of what does an embryo develop?",
        "answer": "uterus",
        "distractor_1": "cell",
        "distractor_2": "nucleus",
        "distractor_3": "DNA"
      },
      {
        "id": "1528",
        "question": "Select the process of cell division in which one cell divides into two cells.",
        "answer": "mitosis",
        "distractor_1": "photosynthesis",
        "distractor_2": "meiosis",
        "distractor_3": "diffusion"
      },
      {
        "id": "1529",
        "question": "Select the process that occurs when part of a yeast cell wall swells and is eventually pinched off from the parent as a separate yeast cell.",
        "answer": "budding",
        "distractor_1": "splitting",
        "distractor_2": "fertilization",
        "distractor_3": "meiosis"
      },
      {
        "id": "1530",
        "question": "Select the term best described as the breeding of plants or animals with desirable traits in order to produce more offspring with those traits.",
        "answer": "selective breeding",
        "distractor_1": "cloning",
        "distractor_2": "genetic engineering",
        "distractor_3": "biotechnology"
      },
      {
        "id": "1531",
        "question": "Select the term that is defined as the joining of a sperm and an egg.",
        "answer": "fertilization",
        "distractor_1": "cell division",
        "distractor_2": "variation",
        "distractor_3": "reproduction"
      },
      {
        "id": "1534",
        "question": "What is another name for the fertilized egg that results from sexual reproduction?",
        "answer": "zygote",
        "distractor_1": "sperm",
        "distractor_2": "gamete",
        "distractor_3": "splice"
      },
      {
        "id": "1536",
        "question": "What is the outcome of cell division by mitosis?",
        "answer": "a group of cells with exact copies of DNA",
        "distractor_1": "a group of cells with variation",
        "distractor_2": "half the number of cells",
        "distractor_3": "the presence of reproductive cells"
      },
      {
        "id": "1537",
        "question": "What is the process by which living things produce more organisms like themselves?",
        "answer": "reproduction",
        "distractor_1": "variation",
        "distractor_2": "cell division",
        "distractor_3": "colonization"
      },
      {
        "id": "1538",
        "question": "What term is defined as a change in the DNA structure of a cell in which the instructions for making a particular protein are affected?",
        "answer": "mutation",
        "distractor_1": "clone",
        "distractor_2": "radiation",
        "distractor_3": "variation"
      },
      {
        "id": "1540",
        "question": "What term is defined as a group of bacteria that started with one bacterium?",
        "answer": "colony",
        "distractor_1": "plague",
        "distractor_2": "bunch",
        "distractor_3": "cluster"
      },
      {
        "id": "1541",
        "question": "When a cell's genetic code is exposed to this, mutations may occur.",
        "answer": "radiation",
        "distractor_1": "lasers",
        "distractor_2": "vibrations",
        "distractor_3": "S waves"
      },
      {
        "id": "1542",
        "question": "Where do the seeds of a conifer develop?",
        "answer": "in a female cone",
        "distractor_1": "in a male cone",
        "distractor_2": "in pollen",
        "distractor_3": "in water"
      },
      {
        "id": "1543",
        "question": "Where is a multicellular organism's DNA located?",
        "answer": "in the nucleus",
        "distractor_1": "in the cell membrane",
        "distractor_2": "in the cytoplasm",
        "distractor_3": "in the haploid cells"
      },
      {
        "id": "1544",
        "question": "Which of the reproductive methods listed limit the variation of genetic material in an organism?",
        "answer": "asexual reproduction",
        "distractor_1": "sexual reproduction",
        "distractor_2": "conjugation",
        "distractor_3": "meiosis"
      },
      {
        "id": "1545",
        "question": "Which process of cell division creates cells for growth and repair?",
        "answer": "mitosis",
        "distractor_1": "splitting",
        "distractor_2": "budding",
        "distractor_3": "fertilization"
      },
      {
        "id": "6537",
        "question": "What cell contains two copies of each type of chromosome in its nucleus?",
        "answer": "diploid cell",
        "distractor_1": "haploid cell",
        "distractor_2": "erythrocyte cell",
        "distractor_3": "osteoclast cell"
      },
      {
        "id": "6538",
        "question": "What type of cells contain only one copy of a chromosome set?",
        "answer": "haploid cells",
        "distractor_1": "diploid cells",
        "distractor_2": "hepatocyte cell",
        "distractor_3": "myoblast cell"
      },
      {
        "id": "6540",
        "question": "What cell division occurs in sex cells during gamete formation?",
        "answer": "meiosis",
        "distractor_1": "mitosis",
        "distractor_2": "regeneration",
        "distractor_3": "binary fission"
      },
      {
        "id": "6543",
        "question": "What is the term for a living thing?",
        "answer": "organism",
        "distractor_1": "gamete",
        "distractor_2": "eukaryote",
        "distractor_3": "prokaryote"
      },
      {
        "id": "6546",
        "question": "What reproductive process involving two parents who combine their genetic material to produce a new organism?",
        "answer": "sexual reproduction",
        "distractor_1": "asexual reproduction",
        "distractor_2": "binary fission",
        "distractor_3": "regeneration"
      },
      {
        "id": "6548",
        "question": "What kind of asexual reproduction that takes place when one cell divides to form two identical cells?",
        "answer": "binary fission",
        "distractor_1": "regeneration",
        "distractor_2": "mitosis",
        "distractor_3": "meiosis"
      },
      {
        "id": "6550",
        "question": "What is the term for the ability of an organism to regrow body parts?",
        "answer": "regeneration",
        "distractor_1": "binary fission",
        "distractor_2": "mitosis",
        "distractor_3": "asexual reproduction"
      },
      {
        "id": "6552",
        "question": "What are the female sex cells?",
        "answer": "egg cells",
        "distractor_1": "sperm cells",
        "distractor_2": "eukaryotes",
        "distractor_3": "prokaryotes"
      },
      {
        "id": "6554",
        "question": "What are the male sex cells?",
        "answer": "sperm cells",
        "distractor_1": "egg cells",
        "distractor_2": "diploid cells",
        "distractor_3": "haploid cells"
      },
      {
        "id": "6555",
        "question": "What is the term for a specialized sex cell such as an egg or a sperm?",
        "answer": "gamete",
        "distractor_1": "eukaryote",
        "distractor_2": "prokaryote",
        "distractor_3": "zygote"
      },
      {
        "id": "6557",
        "question": "What structure carries information controlling inherited characteristics, such as eye color and blood type?",
        "answer": "chromosome",
        "distractor_1": "DNA",
        "distractor_2": "gene",
        "distractor_3": "trait cell"
      },
      {
        "id": "6559",
        "question": "What organism cells contain a nucleus?",
        "answer": "eukaryote",
        "distractor_1": "prokaryote",
        "distractor_2": "diploid cells",
        "distractor_3": "haploid cells"
      },
      {
        "id": "6560",
        "question": "Which organism cells' genetic material is not contained?",
        "answer": "prokaryote",
        "distractor_1": "eukaryote",
        "distractor_2": "zygote",
        "distractor_3": "haploid cells"
      },
      {
        "id": "6563",
        "question": "What are single-celled organisms whose DNA is not enclosed in a cell nucleus and are classified as prokaryotes?",
        "answer": "bacteria",
        "distractor_1": "eukaryote",
        "distractor_2": "diploid cells",
        "distractor_3": "haploid cells"
      },
      {
        "id": "8215",
        "question": "What is the joining of a sperm cell and an egg cell called?",
        "answer": "fertilization",
        "distractor_1": "cell division",
        "distractor_2": "variation",
        "distractor_3": "selective breeding"
      },
      {
        "id": "8216",
        "question": "What term is defined as a fertilized egg that forms when two sets of genes combine?",
        "answer": "zygote",
        "distractor_1": "gamete",
        "distractor_2": "haploid",
        "distractor_3": "sperm"
      },
      {
        "id": "8217",
        "question": "Which reproductive process forms a new organism from one parent cell?",
        "answer": "asexual reproduction",
        "distractor_1": "sexual reproduction",
        "distractor_2": "fertilization",
        "distractor_3": "meiosis"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "133",
    "name": "Rocket Science",
    "weight": "75",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1549",
        "question": "What term is used to describe the center of all drag forces acting upon the rocket?",
        "answer": "pressure",
        "distractor_1": "gravity",
        "distractor_2": "stability",
        "distractor_3": "resistance"
      },
      {
        "id": "1551",
        "question": "An object's momentum is dependent on what two quantities?",
        "answer": "mass and velocity",
        "distractor_1": "weight and speed",
        "distractor_2": "acceleration and force",
        "distractor_3": "distance and time"
      },
      {
        "id": "1552",
        "question": "Wernher von Braun was a leading rocket scientist for the German-armed V-2 rocket. What was the actual name of the V-2 rocket?",
        "answer": "Vengeance Weapon 2",
        "distractor_1": "Victory 2",
        "distractor_2": "Velocity Rocket 2",
        "distractor_3": "Buzz-Bomb"
      },
      {
        "id": "1553",
        "question": "Which of the following terms describes the highest point a rocket reaches during flight?",
        "answer": "apogee",
        "distractor_1": "peak",
        "distractor_2": "inertia",
        "distractor_3": "elongate"
      },
      {
        "id": "1554",
        "question": "The 'things' such as instruments or people that are necessary to the mission of the rocket flight is also referred to as which of the following terms?",
        "answer": "payload",
        "distractor_1": "mission cargo",
        "distractor_2": "gear",
        "distractor_3": "vitals"
      },
      {
        "id": "1555",
        "question": "What term describes the amount of energy a moving object has?",
        "answer": "momentum",
        "distractor_1": "weight",
        "distractor_2": "inertia",
        "distractor_3": "gravity"
      },
      {
        "id": "1556",
        "question": "What is the term used to describe the highest altitude a rocket reaches during flight?",
        "answer": "apogee",
        "distractor_1": "peak",
        "distractor_2": "elongate",
        "distractor_3": "inertia"
      },
      {
        "id": "1557",
        "question": "When a rocket flies in a straight and predictable path, it is said to have what type of stability?",
        "answer": "positive",
        "distractor_1": "negative",
        "distractor_2": "neutral",
        "distractor_3": "accurate"
      },
      {
        "id": "1558",
        "question": "Which of the following scientists is credited with successfully developing and launching the first liquid-fueled rocket?",
        "answer": "Dr. Robert Goddard",
        "distractor_1": "Sir Isaac Newton",
        "distractor_2": "Wernher von Braun",
        "distractor_3": "Johann Schmidlap"
      },
      {
        "id": "1559",
        "question": "Identify the layer that is the airflow directly next to the rocket skin.",
        "answer": "boundary",
        "distractor_1": "initial",
        "distractor_2": "secondary",
        "distractor_3": "apex"
      },
      {
        "id": "1560",
        "question": "What is the center point on the rocket where all mass appears to be concentrated?",
        "answer": "gravity",
        "distractor_1": "pressure",
        "distractor_2": "inertia",
        "distractor_3": "weight"
      },
      {
        "id": "1561",
        "question": "During rocket flight, what is the main function of the rocket fin?",
        "answer": "directional stability",
        "distractor_1": "static mobility",
        "distractor_2": "friction",
        "distractor_3": "aerodynamic airflow"
      },
      {
        "id": "1562",
        "question": "Which one of Newton's scientific laws of motion states 'every action has an equal and opposite reaction?'",
        "answer": "third",
        "distractor_1": "first",
        "distractor_2": "second",
        "distractor_3": "fourth"
      },
      {
        "id": "1563",
        "question": "What type of rocket is used to send satellites or other spacecraft into space?",
        "answer": "launch vehicle",
        "distractor_1": "missile",
        "distractor_2": "carrier rocket",
        "distractor_3": "sounding rocket"
      },
      {
        "id": "1564",
        "question": "Which law or principle best describes the following statement? 'Force equals mass times acceleration.'",
        "answer": "Newton's second law of motion",
        "distractor_1": "The Rocket Principle",
        "distractor_2": "Newton's First Law of Motion",
        "distractor_3": "Newton's Third Law of Motion"
      },
      {
        "id": "1565",
        "question": "Which law or principle best describes the following statement? 'Force equals mass times acceleration.'",
        "answer": "Newton's second law of motion",
        "distractor_1": "The Rocket Principle",
        "distractor_2": "Newton's First Law of Motion",
        "distractor_3": "Newton's Third Law of Motion"
      },
      {
        "id": "1566",
        "question": "Which scientific law or principle best describes the following statement? 'Every action has an equal and opposite reaction.'",
        "answer": "Newton's third law of motion",
        "distractor_1": "The Rocket Principle",
        "distractor_2": "Newton's First Law of Motion",
        "distractor_3": "Newton's Second Law of Motion"
      },
      {
        "id": "1567",
        "question": "What is the main purpose of a rocket fin when the rocket is in flight?",
        "answer": "directional stability",
        "distractor_1": "static mobility",
        "distractor_2": "aerodynamic airflow",
        "distractor_3": "friction"
      },
      {
        "id": "1568",
        "question": "The amount of energy a moving object has is referred to as what type of energy?",
        "answer": "momentum",
        "distractor_1": "weight",
        "distractor_2": "inertia",
        "distractor_3": "ballast"
      },
      {
        "id": "1569",
        "question": "The first manned lunar landing mission, Apollo 11, launched on July 16, 1969. In what ocean did the command module splash down?",
        "answer": "Pacific",
        "distractor_1": "Atlantic",
        "distractor_2": "Indian",
        "distractor_3": "Arctic"
      },
      {
        "id": "1570",
        "question": "What is the device used to stabilize rockets and airplanes? When linked with a steering system, it can help rockets fly straight and on course.",
        "answer": "gyroscope",
        "distractor_1": "turbine",
        "distractor_2": "stabilizer",
        "distractor_3": "oscillator"
      },
      {
        "id": "1550",
        "question": "What term is used to describe the center point on the rocket where all mass appears to be concentrated?",
        "answer": "gravity",
        "distractor_1": "pressure",
        "distractor_2": "stability",
        "distractor_3": "weight"
      },
      {
        "id": "1571",
        "question": "A sleek, aerodynamically designed rocket reduces the amount of drag to a minimum and produces what type of airflow?",
        "answer": "laminar",
        "distractor_1": "turbulent",
        "distractor_2": "ballistic",
        "distractor_3": "friction-free"
      },
      {
        "id": "1572",
        "question": "Which type of stability produces a straight and predictable rocket flight?",
        "answer": "positive",
        "distractor_1": "neutral",
        "distractor_2": "negative",
        "distractor_3": "dynamic"
      },
      {
        "id": "6702",
        "question": "What acts between the object and the fluid and slows the motion of the object",
        "answer": "drag",
        "distractor_1": "mass",
        "distractor_2": "gravity",
        "distractor_3": "weight"
      },
      {
        "id": "6703",
        "question": "What is the amount of matter in an object?",
        "answer": "mass",
        "distractor_1": "matter",
        "distractor_2": "weight",
        "distractor_3": "velocity"
      },
      {
        "id": "6704",
        "question": "What is the rate of change of position along a straight line with respect to time?",
        "answer": "velocity",
        "distractor_1": "matter",
        "distractor_2": "torque",
        "distractor_3": "speed"
      },
      {
        "id": "6705",
        "question": "What is a self-propelled device that carries its own fuel?",
        "answer": "rocket",
        "distractor_1": "missile",
        "distractor_2": "thruster",
        "distractor_3": "projectile"
      },
      {
        "id": "6706",
        "question": "What law states that objects at rest will stay at rest and objects in motion will stay in motion in a straight line unless acted upon by an unbalanced force?",
        "answer": "Newton's first law of motion",
        "distractor_1": "Newton's second law of motion",
        "distractor_2": "Newton's third law of motion",
        "distractor_3": "Newton's fourth law of motion"
      },
      {
        "id": "6707",
        "question": "What occurs when the amount of thrust is greater than the weight of the rocket?",
        "answer": "liftoff",
        "distractor_1": "thrust",
        "distractor_2": "take off",
        "distractor_3": "drag"
      },
      {
        "id": "6708",
        "question": "What is a measurement of how much gravity is exerted on an object?",
        "answer": "weight",
        "distractor_1": "mass ",
        "distractor_2": "matter",
        "distractor_3": "velocity"
      },
      {
        "id": "6709",
        "question": "What is a force exerted upon or against an object to move it in a specific direction?",
        "answer": "thrust",
        "distractor_1": "liftoff",
        "distractor_2": "drag",
        "distractor_3": "ballast"
      },
      {
        "id": "6710",
        "question": "What is uneven airflow around the rocket skin; increases the amount of drag?",
        "answer": "turbulent",
        "distractor_1": "thrust",
        "distractor_2": "drag",
        "distractor_3": "propellant"
      },
      {
        "id": "6711",
        "question": "What is used during wartime and almost always carry explosive devices that cause damage to the target upon impact?",
        "answer": "missiles",
        "distractor_1": "sounding rockets",
        "distractor_2": "projectile",
        "distractor_3": "rocket"
      },
      {
        "id": "6712",
        "question": "What is used to carry scientific instruments into the atmosphere?",
        "answer": "sounding rockets",
        "distractor_1": "missiles",
        "distractor_2": "projectiles ",
        "distractor_3": "rockets"
      },
      {
        "id": "6713",
        "question": "What is small rockets used to change the speed and direction of a larger rocket traveling in space?",
        "answer": "thrusters",
        "distractor_1": "boosters",
        "distractor_2": "propellant",
        "distractor_3": "liftoff"
      },
      {
        "id": "6714",
        "question": "Who is was in charge of developing the V-2 rocket used during World War II?",
        "answer": "Wernher von Braun",
        "distractor_1": "Sir Isaac Newton",
        "distractor_2": "Dr. Robert H. Goddard",
        "distractor_3": "John Milton"
      },
      {
        "id": "6715",
        "question": "What is the point on the rocket where all mass appears to be concentrated?",
        "answer": "center of gravity",
        "distractor_1": "center of pressure",
        "distractor_2": "propellant",
        "distractor_3": "total impulse"
      },
      {
        "id": "6716",
        "question": "What is the center of all of the drag forces acting upon the rocket?",
        "answer": "center of pressure",
        "distractor_1": "center of gravity",
        "distractor_2": "total impulse",
        "distractor_3": "propellant"
      },
      {
        "id": "6717",
        "question": "What contains both fuel and an oxidizer?",
        "answer": "propellant",
        "distractor_1": "gas",
        "distractor_2": "ballast",
        "distractor_3": "fuel"
      },
      {
        "id": "6718",
        "question": "What is the thrust and duration of the rocket engine burn?",
        "answer": "total impulse",
        "distractor_1": "total takeoff",
        "distractor_2": "liftoff",
        "distractor_3": "propellant"
      },
      {
        "id": "6719",
        "question": "What is a unit of force equal to the force required to impart an acceleration of one meter per second per second to a mass of one kilogram?",
        "answer": "newton",
        "distractor_1": "propellant",
        "distractor_2": "ohm",
        "distractor_3": "drag"
      },
      {
        "id": "6720",
        "question": "What is something that adds weight in order to improve stability or performance?",
        "answer": "ballast",
        "distractor_1": "newton",
        "distractor_2": "drag",
        "distractor_3": "liftoff"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "134",
    "name": "Computer Technology",
    "weight": "80",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1590",
        "question": "What type of card is a printed circuit board that connects internally to the computer and adds various functionalities?",
        "answer": "expansion",
        "distractor_1": "transistor",
        "distractor_2": "optical",
        "distractor_3": "memory"
      },
      {
        "id": "1593",
        "question": "Which of the following circuit types, made of electronic components, was a major development in computer technology?",
        "answer": "integrated",
        "distractor_1": "electronic",
        "distractor_2": "hardware",
        "distractor_3": "ballistic"
      },
      {
        "id": "1595",
        "question": "What are the terms for converting digital information into analog information and converting it back the other way?",
        "answer": "modulation and demodulation",
        "distractor_1": "retranslation and translation",
        "distractor_2": "remodulation and modulation",
        "distractor_3": "translation and reformation"
      },
      {
        "id": "1597",
        "question": "What is the most important software program running on a computer?",
        "answer": "operating system",
        "distractor_1": "expansion system",
        "distractor_2": "input/output system",
        "distractor_3": "processing system"
      },
      {
        "id": "1598",
        "question": "What is the program or piece of computer code, that when loaded, intentionally damages your computer system?",
        "answer": "virus",
        "distractor_1": "stylus",
        "distractor_2": "port",
        "distractor_3": "disease"
      },
      {
        "id": "1575",
        "question": "Computer memory stores information in binary form and is commonly measured in bytes. How many bits make up a single byte?",
        "answer": "8",
        "distractor_1": "2",
        "distractor_2": "4",
        "distractor_3": "6"
      },
      {
        "id": "1577",
        "question": "What must you have to connect to the Internet from a home computer? It is also known as an ISP.",
        "answer": "Internet Service Provider",
        "distractor_1": "Internet Service Program",
        "distractor_2": "Internet Service Process",
        "distractor_3": "Internet Service Password"
      },
      {
        "id": "1579",
        "question": "What determines the main characteristics of the motherboard, such as what processors it supports, what RAM types it can use, the bus speeds, and whether it supports current standards like USB?",
        "answer": "chipset",
        "distractor_1": "multiplier",
        "distractor_2": "cache",
        "distractor_3": "BIOS"
      },
      {
        "id": "1580",
        "question": "What technology enables the computer to automatically configure I/O devices and expansion cards?",
        "answer": "plug and play",
        "distractor_1": "hot plugging",
        "distractor_2": "user-friendly",
        "distractor_3": "graphical user interface"
      },
      {
        "id": "1581",
        "question": "What is considered to be one of the greatest breakthroughs in the development of computer input devices?",
        "answer": "mouse",
        "distractor_1": "keyboard",
        "distractor_2": "monitor",
        "distractor_3": "speakers"
      },
      {
        "id": "1583",
        "question": "Which of the following devices displays computer information in one form or another?",
        "answer": "output",
        "distractor_1": "input",
        "distractor_2": "ergonomic",
        "distractor_3": "technical"
      },
      {
        "id": "1585",
        "question": "What computer component deals with programs or instructions that make a computer operate or perform useful work?",
        "answer": "software",
        "distractor_1": "peripherals",
        "distractor_2": "devices",
        "distractor_3": "hardware"
      },
      {
        "id": "1588",
        "question": "What is a global network connecting millions of computers together?",
        "answer": "Internet",
        "distractor_1": "Intranet",
        "distractor_2": "LAN",
        "distractor_3": "DSL"
      },
      {
        "id": "1589",
        "question": "Which of the following ports allows for daisy-chaining devices and supports hot plugging technology?",
        "answer": "USB",
        "distractor_1": "serial",
        "distractor_2": "unidirectional",
        "distractor_3": "parallel"
      },
      {
        "id": "6256",
        "question": "What is the term for computer components that you can actually touch?",
        "answer": "hardware",
        "distractor_1": "keyboard and mouse",
        "distractor_2": "monitor",
        "distractor_3": "buttons"
      },
      {
        "id": "6259",
        "question": "What is a programmable electronic device that can store, retrieve, and process data?",
        "answer": "computer",
        "distractor_1": "mother board",
        "distractor_2": "input device",
        "distractor_3": "microprocessor"
      },
      {
        "id": "6260",
        "question": "What was the first successful digital computer?",
        "answer": "ENIAC",
        "distractor_1": "Mac",
        "distractor_2": "PC",
        "distractor_3": "Dell"
      },
      {
        "id": "6261",
        "question": "What is a solid-state electronic device that controls the flow of electricity in electronic equipment?",
        "answer": "transistor",
        "distractor_1": "power source",
        "distractor_2": "electrostatic discharge",
        "distractor_3": "system board"
      },
      {
        "id": "6267",
        "question": "What is the correct term for the brain of the computer?",
        "answer": "central processing unit",
        "distractor_1": "system board",
        "distractor_2": "microprocessor",
        "distractor_3": "expansion card"
      },
      {
        "id": "6269",
        "question": "What is the main circuit board that contains the CPU, memory modules, ports, expansion slots, and other important computer components?",
        "answer": "system board",
        "distractor_1": "output device",
        "distractor_2": "keyboard",
        "distractor_3": "expansion card"
      },
      {
        "id": "6274",
        "question": "What is the device that sends data to the computer?",
        "answer": "input card",
        "distractor_1": "internet",
        "distractor_2": "system board",
        "distractor_3": "microprocessor"
      },
      {
        "id": "6278",
        "question": "What is the rapid discharge of static electricity from one conductor to another?",
        "answer": "electrostatic discharge",
        "distractor_1": "transistor discharge",
        "distractor_2": "network surge",
        "distractor_3": "virus"
      },
      {
        "id": "6279",
        "question": "What is the one I/O device that the user comes in contact with the most?",
        "answer": "keyboard",
        "distractor_1": "mouse",
        "distractor_2": "monitor",
        "distractor_3": "internet"
      },
      {
        "id": "6280",
        "question": "What is the physical memory that can read and write data?",
        "answer": "random access memory",
        "distractor_1": "read only memory",
        "distractor_2": "expansion card",
        "distractor_3": "microprocessor"
      },
      {
        "id": "6281",
        "question": "What is the type of memory that contains instructions the computer needs for starting up?",
        "answer": "read-only memory",
        "distractor_1": "random access memory",
        "distractor_2": "system board",
        "distractor_3": "input device"
      },
      {
        "id": "6282",
        "question": "What is the printed circuit board that adds functionality to the computer?",
        "answer": "expansion card",
        "distractor_1": "user-friendly mode",
        "distractor_2": "system board",
        "distractor_3": "transistor"
      },
      {
        "id": "6283",
        "question": "What is an applied science concerned with designing and arranging things people use so that the people and things interact efficiently and safely?",
        "answer": "ergonomics",
        "distractor_1": "user-friendly research",
        "distractor_2": "plug and play",
        "distractor_3": "operating system"
      },
      {
        "id": "6285",
        "question": "What is the term for an electronic circuit that functions as the central processing unit of a computer?",
        "answer": "microprocessor",
        "distractor_1": "chip",
        "distractor_2": "system board",
        "distractor_3": "expansion card"
      },
      {
        "id": "6286",
        "question": "What is a term used to describe something as easy to learn and easy to use?",
        "answer": "user-friendly",
        "distractor_1": "ergonomics",
        "distractor_2": "operating system",
        "distractor_3": "foolproof"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "125",
    "name": "Dynamic Earth",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "2506",
        "question": "Which layer of Earth contains both solid and semimolten layers?",
        "answer": "upper mantle",
        "distractor_1": "lower mantle",
        "distractor_2": "outer core",
        "distractor_3": "inner core"
      },
      {
        "id": "2507",
        "question": "At convergent boundaries, which type of force moves plates toward each other?",
        "answer": "compressional",
        "distractor_1": "tensional",
        "distractor_2": "shear",
        "distractor_3": "perpendicular"
      },
      {
        "id": "2508",
        "question": "The semimolten asthenosphere is found in which Earth layer?",
        "answer": "upper mantle",
        "distractor_1": "lower mantle",
        "distractor_2": "outer core",
        "distractor_3": "inner core"
      },
      {
        "id": "2509",
        "question": "Which of the following is an example of diverging lithospheric plates?",
        "answer": "mid-ocean ridge",
        "distractor_1": "volcano",
        "distractor_2": "fault-block mountain",
        "distractor_3": "horst"
      },
      {
        "id": "2510",
        "question": "Earth's outer core is thought to be in which state of matter?",
        "answer": "liquid",
        "distractor_1": "solid",
        "distractor_2": "plasma",
        "distractor_3": "gas"
      },
      {
        "id": "2511",
        "question": "Dimensional analysis is a process used to change units in an equation. What is this change called?",
        "answer": "conversion",
        "distractor_1": "calibration",
        "distractor_2": "relocation",
        "distractor_3": "elimination"
      },
      {
        "id": "2512",
        "question": "Earthquakes generally occur along which of the following areas?",
        "answer": "plate boundaries",
        "distractor_1": "parallels of latitude",
        "distractor_2": "flood plains",
        "distractor_3": "meridians of longitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "2513",
        "question": "Dimensional analysis is a process used to change units in an equation. What is this change called?",
        "answer": "conversion",
        "distractor_1": "calibration",
        "distractor_2": "relocation",
        "distractor_3": "elimination"
      },
      {
        "id": "2514",
        "question": "A mid-ocean ridge is an example of which type of lithospheric plate?",
        "answer": "diverging",
        "distractor_1": "converging",
        "distractor_2": "transforming",
        "distractor_3": "strike-slipping"
      },
      {
        "id": "2515",
        "question": "Which layer of Earth is thought to be the only liquid layer?",
        "answer": "outer core",
        "distractor_1": "upper mantle",
        "distractor_2": "lower mantle",
        "distractor_3": "inner core"
      },
      {
        "id": "2516",
        "question": "Which type of map shows the actual shape of the land, not only in the two dimensions of length and width but also in the third, or vertical, dimension?",
        "answer": "topographic map",
        "distractor_1": "profile map",
        "distractor_2": "focus map",
        "distractor_3": "digital map"
      },
      {
        "id": "2517",
        "question": "What is the term for a fracture in the continuity of Earth's crust that is generally caused by the stress created when lithospheric plates converge, diverge, or slip by one another?",
        "answer": "fault",
        "distractor_1": "cave",
        "distractor_2": "valley",
        "distractor_3": "river"
      },
      {
        "id": "2518",
        "question": "Which process or factor in the mantle is thought to keep the plates in motion?",
        "answer": "convection currents",
        "distractor_1": "pressure columns",
        "distractor_2": "heat flares",
        "distractor_3": "radioactive decay"
      },
      {
        "id": "2519",
        "question": "Convection currents in which Earth layer are thought to keep tectonic plates in motion?",
        "answer": "mantle",
        "distractor_1": "inner core",
        "distractor_2": "outer core",
        "distractor_3": "crust"
      },
      {
        "id": "2520",
        "question": "Which type of map has contour lines that show the actual shape of the land in all three dimensions?",
        "answer": "topographic",
        "distractor_1": "profile",
        "distractor_2": "focus",
        "distractor_3": "digital"
      },
      {
        "id": "2521",
        "question": "Compressional forces move plates toward each other at which of the following types of boundaries?",
        "answer": "convergent",
        "distractor_1": "strike-slip",
        "distractor_2": "divergent",
        "distractor_3": "transform"
      },
      {
        "id": "2522",
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a process in the rock cycle?",
        "answer": "nitrification",
        "distractor_1": "weathering",
        "distractor_2": "crystallization",
        "distractor_3": "melting"
      },
      {
        "id": "2523",
        "question": "Where do earthquakes generally occur?",
        "answer": "along plate boundaries",
        "distractor_1": "along parallels of latitude",
        "distractor_2": "along meridians of longitude",
        "distractor_3": "along flood plains"
      },
      {
        "id": "2524",
        "question": "Which of the following are fractures in Earth's crust caused by stress created when lithospheric plates converge, diverge, or slip by one another?",
        "answer": "faults",
        "distractor_1": "caves",
        "distractor_2": "valleys",
        "distractor_3": "rivers"
      },
      {
        "id": "2525",
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a process in the rock cycle?",
        "answer": "nitrification",
        "distractor_1": "weathering",
        "distractor_2": "crystallization",
        "distractor_3": "melting"
      },
      {
        "id": "6291",
        "question": "What is a body wave that can pass through only solid material",
        "answer": "S wave",
        "distractor_1": "P wave",
        "distractor_2": "Normal fault",
        "distractor_3": "Convection currents"
      },
      {
        "id": "6292",
        "question": "What is an area where the footwall has moved up in relation to the hanging wall?",
        "answer": "Normal fault",
        "distractor_1": "Abnormal fault",
        "distractor_2": "Reverse fault",
        "distractor_3": "Plate boundaries"
      },
      {
        "id": "6293",
        "question": "What is data recorded by a seismograph?",
        "answer": "Seismogram",
        "distractor_1": "Plate boundaries",
        "distractor_2": "Dimensional analysis",
        "distractor_3": "Transform boundaries"
      },
      {
        "id": "6294",
        "question": "What is an area where the hanging wall has moved up in relation to the footwall?",
        "answer": "Reverse fault",
        "distractor_1": "Normal fault",
        "distractor_2": "Divergent boundaries",
        "distractor_3": "Transform boundaries"
      },
      {
        "id": "6287",
        "question": "What is the process of converting one unit to another?",
        "answer": "Dimensional analysis",
        "distractor_1": "Divergent analysis",
        "distractor_2": "Topographic map",
        "distractor_3": "Seismogram"
      },
      {
        "id": "6288",
        "question": "What are locations where tensional forces work to move plates away from each other?",
        "answer": "Divergent boundaries",
        "distractor_1": "Transform boundaries",
        "distractor_2": "Normal fault",
        "distractor_3": "Reverse fault"
      },
      {
        "id": "6289",
        "question": "What are locations where shear forces are exerted as two parallel plates slip past one another?",
        "answer": "Transform boundaries",
        "distractor_1": "Divergent boundaries",
        "distractor_2": "Normal fault",
        "distractor_3": "Reverse fault"
      },
      {
        "id": "6290",
        "question": "What is a body wave that moves the fastest and can pass through both solids and liquids?",
        "answer": "P wave",
        "distractor_1": "S wave",
        "distractor_2": "Convection currents",
        "distractor_3": "Normal fault"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "135",
    "name": "Webmaster",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "3277",
        "question": "What is the first page of a Web site called?",
        "answer": "Home page",
        "distractor_1": "About page",
        "distractor_2": "Search page",
        "distractor_3": "Signature page"
      },
      {
        "id": "3256",
        "question": "To what does a modem allow you to connect a computer?",
        "answer": "Internet",
        "distractor_1": "printer",
        "distractor_2": "CD",
        "distractor_3": "disk drive"
      },
      {
        "id": "3257",
        "question": "Which of the following are used to browse the Web, newsgroups, and other sources looking for words rather than subjects?",
        "answer": "search engines",
        "distractor_1": "hosts",
        "distractor_2": "servers",
        "distractor_3": "directories"
      },
      {
        "id": "3258",
        "question": "What is a computer program that lets you store information to be sorted through later called?",
        "answer": "database",
        "distractor_1": "word processor",
        "distractor_2": "memory bank",
        "distractor_3": "holding tank"
      },
      {
        "id": "3259",
        "question": "What are the two most common graphic file types on the Web?",
        "answer": "GIF and JPEG",
        "distractor_1": "TIFF and PICT",
        "distractor_2": "BMP and PCX",
        "distractor_3": "WMF and PNT"
      },
      {
        "id": "3260",
        "question": "What is the term for the first page of a Web site?",
        "answer": "Home page",
        "distractor_1": "Signature page",
        "distractor_2": "About page",
        "distractor_3": "Search page"
      },
      {
        "id": "3261",
        "question": "Which of the following is the current term for the communication network consisting of more than 65 million computers in more than 100 countries?",
        "answer": "Internet",
        "distractor_1": "Internet Service Provider",
        "distractor_2": "ARPANET",
        "distractor_3": "World Wide Web"
      },
      {
        "id": "3262",
        "question": "What is the term for the speed at which a modem can interpret data?",
        "answer": "baud rate",
        "distractor_1": "digital",
        "distractor_2": "analog",
        "distractor_3": "magic"
      },
      {
        "id": "3263",
        "question": "Which of the following are the two most common graphic file types on the Web?",
        "answer": "GIF and JPEG",
        "distractor_1": "WMF and PNT",
        "distractor_2": "BMP and PCX",
        "distractor_3": "TIFF and PICT"
      },
      {
        "id": "3265",
        "question": "Into what shape does a mouse pointer turn when it is positioned over a Web page link?",
        "answer": "little hand",
        "distractor_1": "crosshair",
        "distractor_2": "hourglass",
        "distractor_3": "big arrow"
      },
      {
        "id": "3269",
        "question": "File size refers to which of the following?",
        "answer": "disk space",
        "distractor_1": "screen area",
        "distractor_2": "bit depth",
        "distractor_3": "RAM"
      },
      {
        "id": "3271",
        "question": "Which of the following actions would you take to jump directly from one Web site to another?",
        "answer": "click a hyperlink",
        "distractor_1": "click the letters 'www'",
        "distractor_2": "type directory name",
        "distractor_3": "type a domain name"
      },
      {
        "id": "3273",
        "question": "Which of the following is a computer program that lets you store information to be sorted through later?",
        "answer": "database",
        "distractor_1": "holding tank",
        "distractor_2": "word processor",
        "distractor_3": "memory bank"
      },
      {
        "id": "3274",
        "question": "What type of files are Web pages?",
        "answer": "HTML",
        "distractor_1": "Explorer",
        "distractor_2": "data",
        "distractor_3": "browser"
      },
      {
        "id": "3275",
        "question": "The first step in Web site development is to determine which of the following?",
        "answer": "purpose of the site",
        "distractor_1": "size of the site",
        "distractor_2": "download time of the site",
        "distractor_3": "media elements of the site"
      },
      {
        "id": "6498",
        "question": "What is described as a software program used to navigate the Internet and view Web pages?",
        "answer": "browser",
        "distractor_1": "server",
        "distractor_2": "FTP",
        "distractor_3": "URL"
      },
      {
        "id": "6499",
        "question": "What is a markup language used to create hypertext documents that are cross-platform?",
        "answer": "HTML ",
        "distractor_1": "FTP",
        "distractor_2": "URL",
        "distractor_3": "HTM"
      },
      {
        "id": "6500",
        "question": "What is defined as a collection of files or documents working together in a meaningful way?",
        "answer": "Web site",
        "distractor_1": "Web page",
        "distractor_2": "server",
        "distractor_3": "World Wide Web"
      },
      {
        "id": "6501",
        "question": "What is known as a file that displays text or pictures in a Web browser?",
        "answer": "Web page",
        "distractor_1": "Web site",
        "distractor_2": "hyperlink",
        "distractor_3": "URL"
      },
      {
        "id": "6502",
        "question": "What is a method of transferring files from one place to another on the Internet?",
        "answer": "File Transfer Protocol (FTP)",
        "distractor_1": "downloading",
        "distractor_2": "uploading",
        "distractor_3": "hyperlinking"
      },
      {
        "id": "6503",
        "question": "Which of the following are described as a computer and software that maintains information and applications accessed by distributed users?",
        "answer": "server",
        "distractor_1": "client",
        "distractor_2": "browser",
        "distractor_3": "Internet"
      },
      {
        "id": "6504",
        "question": "What is known as the end user's computer?",
        "answer": "client",
        "distractor_1": "customer",
        "distractor_2": "browser",
        "distractor_3": "URL "
      },
      {
        "id": "6505",
        "question": "What is defined as a segment of text or graphic that, when clicked, jumps the user to a new location?",
        "answer": "hyperlink",
        "distractor_1": "frame",
        "distractor_2": "form",
        "distractor_3": "URL"
      },
      {
        "id": "6506",
        "question": "What is defined as sending something from your computer to another computer?",
        "answer": "uploading",
        "distractor_1": "downloading",
        "distractor_2": "email",
        "distractor_3": "hyperlinking"
      },
      {
        "id": "6507",
        "question": "What is defined as the process of copying a file from an online service, FTP site, Web site, or remote computer to your own computer?",
        "answer": "download",
        "distractor_1": "upload",
        "distractor_2": "hyperlinking",
        "distractor_3": "using bandwidth"
      },
      {
        "id": "6508",
        "question": "What is known as the amount of data transferred over a set amount of time?",
        "answer": "bandwidth",
        "distractor_1": "frame",
        "distractor_2": "download time",
        "distractor_3": "upload time"
      },
      {
        "id": "6509",
        "question": "What is a stationary part of a Web page that stays put while the user scrolls through another part of the page?",
        "answer": "frame",
        "distractor_1": "table",
        "distractor_2": "web page",
        "distractor_3": "hyperlink"
      },
      {
        "id": "6510",
        "question": "What is described as a layout element that allows a Webmaster to put things in rows and columns?",
        "answer": "tables",
        "distractor_1": "forms",
        "distractor_2": "browser",
        "distractor_3": "software"
      },
      {
        "id": "6511",
        "question": "What is referred to as a layout element that allows a Webmaster to create interactive fields in order to collect data?",
        "answer": "forms",
        "distractor_1": "tables",
        "distractor_2": "web pages",
        "distractor_3": "web site"
      },
      {
        "id": "6512",
        "question": "What is a globally interconnected network of Web pages?",
        "answer": "World Wide Web",
        "distractor_1": "URL",
        "distractor_2": "HTML",
        "distractor_3": "HTM"
      },
      {
        "id": "6513",
        "question": "What is known as a Web address containing the domain name, path, and file name for a Web page?",
        "answer": "URL (Uniform Resource Locator)",
        "distractor_1": "HTML",
        "distractor_2": "FTP",
        "distractor_3": "home page"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "139",
    "name": "Alternative Energy",
    "weight": "80",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "3282",
        "question": "Which of the terms best fits the following definition: usable heat or power that comes in the forms of electrical, mechanical, chemical, thermal, or nuclear?",
        "answer": "energy",
        "distractor_1": "fuel",
        "distractor_2": "efficiency",
        "distractor_3": "thermal"
      },
      {
        "id": "3283",
        "question": "Which of the following energy resources has been used for centuries to grind grain and pump water?",
        "answer": "wind",
        "distractor_1": "geothermal",
        "distractor_2": "coal",
        "distractor_3": "hydropower"
      },
      {
        "id": "3284",
        "question": "Identify the device that produces electrical power as the result of a chemical reaction.",
        "answer": "fuel cell",
        "distractor_1": "chemical reaction cell",
        "distractor_2": "conversion cell",
        "distractor_3": "solar cell"
      },
      {
        "id": "3285",
        "question": "Which energy device converts sunlight directly into electrical power?",
        "answer": "solar cell",
        "distractor_1": "fuel cell",
        "distractor_2": "plasma cell",
        "distractor_3": "conversion cell"
      },
      {
        "id": "3290",
        "question": "The Sun is powered by which form of nuclear energy?",
        "answer": "fusion",
        "distractor_1": "fission",
        "distractor_2": "uranium",
        "distractor_3": "plutonium"
      },
      {
        "id": "3291",
        "question": "Stored energy in any form is referred to as what type of energy?",
        "answer": "potential energy",
        "distractor_1": "kinetic energy",
        "distractor_2": "concentrated energy",
        "distractor_3": "possible energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "3293",
        "question": "Solar, wind, geothermal, hydropower, and fuel cell technologies are classified as what type of energy resource?",
        "answer": "perpetual",
        "distractor_1": "renewable",
        "distractor_2": "nonrenewable",
        "distractor_3": "collectable"
      },
      {
        "id": "3295",
        "question": "Name the scientific law that states: 'When one form of energy is used, it changes into one or more other forms. The amount of energy at the start is the same total amount after the change occurs. Energy cannot be created or destroyed.'",
        "answer": "Law of Conservation of Energy",
        "distractor_1": "Law of Cancellation of Energy",
        "distractor_2": "Newton's First Law of Motion",
        "distractor_3": "Law of Thermodynamics"
      },
      {
        "id": "3297",
        "question": "Identify the solar technology that uses mechanical systems to capture solar energy and convert it to heat energy.",
        "answer": "active solar",
        "distractor_1": "passive solar",
        "distractor_2": "solar cell",
        "distractor_3": "solar thermal"
      },
      {
        "id": "3298",
        "question": "Identify the solar energy technology based upon the idea of focusing vast amounts of sunlight to a collector.",
        "answer": "solar thermal",
        "distractor_1": "active solar",
        "distractor_2": "solar cells",
        "distractor_3": "passive solar"
      },
      {
        "id": "8132",
        "question": "Which of the following is best defined as the series of chemical reactions by which microorganisms such as yeast or bacteria convert plant sugars into ethanol and carbon dioxide? ",
        "answer": "fermentation",
        "distractor_1": "photosynthesis",
        "distractor_2": "evaporation",
        "distractor_3": "electrolysis"
      },
      {
        "id": "8133",
        "question": "Which of the following is best defined as a charged particle? ",
        "answer": "ion",
        "distractor_1": "atom",
        "distractor_2": "energy",
        "distractor_3": "electricity"
      },
      {
        "id": "8134",
        "question": "Which of the following is best defined as a dissolved substance that allows charged particles to pass through it? ",
        "answer": "electrolyte",
        "distractor_1": "catalyst",
        "distractor_2": "ion",
        "distractor_3": "fuel"
      },
      {
        "id": "8135",
        "question": "Which of the following is best defined as a substance that speeds the rate of a chemical reaction?",
        "answer": "catalyst",
        "distractor_1": "electrolyte",
        "distractor_2": "ion",
        "distractor_3": "fuel"
      },
      {
        "id": "8136",
        "question": "Which of the following is best defined as a resource that can be replenished in a short time? ",
        "answer": "renewable resource",
        "distractor_1": "nonrenewable resource",
        "distractor_2": "perpetual resource",
        "distractor_3": "energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "8141",
        "question": "What energy resource is identified with organic matter used to provide heat, generate electricity, and provide fuel for transportation systems?",
        "answer": "biomass",
        "distractor_1": "geothermal",
        "distractor_2": "solar",
        "distractor_3": "hydropower"
      },
      {
        "id": "8142",
        "question": "Which word is best defined as the capacity for doing work?",
        "answer": "energy",
        "distractor_1": "fuel",
        "distractor_2": "potential",
        "distractor_3": "ion"
      },
      {
        "id": "3299",
        "question": "Identify the energy device that is made from thin slices of silicon and converts sunlight directly into electrical power.",
        "answer": "solar cell",
        "distractor_1": "solar collector",
        "distractor_2": "silicon cell",
        "distractor_3": "fuel cell"
      },
      {
        "id": "3301",
        "question": "Fossil fuels such as coal, natural gas, and petroleum are classified as what type of energy resource?",
        "answer": "nonrenewable",
        "distractor_1": "collectable",
        "distractor_2": "renewable",
        "distractor_3": "perpetual"
      },
      {
        "id": "3302",
        "question": "Energy is best described by which one of the following definitions?",
        "answer": "usable heat and power that comes in the forms of electrical, mechanical, chemical, thermal, or nuclear",
        "distractor_1": "any of the natural influences that exist especially between particles and determine the structure of the universe",
        "distractor_2": "a branch of physical science",
        "distractor_3": "intensity of action or effect"
      },
      {
        "id": "3303",
        "question": "Energy in motion, or movement, is referred to as what type of energy?",
        "answer": "kinetic energy",
        "distractor_1": "action energy",
        "distractor_2": "concentrated energy",
        "distractor_3": "potential energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "3306",
        "question": "When one form of energy is used, it changes into one or more other energy forms. Energy cannot be destroyed or created. Identify this scientific law.",
        "answer": "Law of Conservation of Energy",
        "distractor_1": "Newton's First law of Motion",
        "distractor_2": "Law of Thermodynamics",
        "distractor_3": "Law of Cancellation of Energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "8118",
        "question": "Which of the following is best defined as a resource that cannot be replaced after use?",
        "answer": "nonrenewable resource",
        "distractor_1": "renewable resource",
        "distractor_2": "perpetual resource",
        "distractor_3": "energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "8146",
        "question": "Which of the following forms of energy can be used to generate electricity through the use of photovoltaic cells?",
        "answer": "solar energy",
        "distractor_1": "hydroelectric energy",
        "distractor_2": "geothermal energy",
        "distractor_3": "nuclear energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "8147",
        "question": "Assume a fuel cell car can store hydrogen in a pressurized tank at 5,000 pounds per square inch and can travel 150 miles at this pressure. What is the range of a hydrogen car that has a tank pressure of 8,500 pounds per square inch?",
        "answer": "255 miles",
        "distractor_1": "160 miles",
        "distractor_2": "250 miles",
        "distractor_3": "300 miles"
      },
      {
        "id": "8148",
        "question": "Photovoltaic cells, such as those used to power satellites that orbit Earth, operate by carrying out which of the following types of energy conversions?",
        "answer": "solar to electrical energy",
        "distractor_1": "electrical to solar energy",
        "distractor_2": "wind to solar energy",
        "distractor_3": "wind to electrical energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "8149",
        "question": "Wind turbines can generate 500 kilowatts of power. New wind turbines are designed to generate three megawatts of power. How many wind turbines are required to generate the same amount of power as a new wind turbine?",
        "answer": "6",
        "distractor_1": "15",
        "distractor_2": "60",
        "distractor_3": "1,500"
      },
      {
        "id": "8150",
        "question": "Which type of electrical power-related transformer steps up the voltage to several hundred thousand volts in order to reduce energy losses?",
        "answer": "transmission transformer",
        "distractor_1": "home supply transformer",
        "distractor_2": "conversion transformer",
        "distractor_3": "distribution transformer"
      },
      {
        "id": "8151",
        "question": "The price of electricity is $0.07 per kWh. Wind power costs $0.085 per kWh. If an electric bill was $22.20, how much would the bill be if wind power had been used instead?",
        "answer": "$26.95",
        "distractor_1": "$35.00",
        "distractor_2": "$22.20",
        "distractor_3": "$15.65"
      },
      {
        "id": "8119",
        "question": "Which of the following is best defined as a substance that contains stored energy?",
        "answer": "fuel ",
        "distractor_1": "ion",
        "distractor_2": "electrolyte",
        "distractor_3": "catalyst"
      },
      {
        "id": "8120",
        "question": "Which of the following is best defined as the remains of once-living organisms that were gradually covered by rock and soil deposits that are now used as fuel?",
        "answer": "fossil fuel",
        "distractor_1": "geothermal energy",
        "distractor_2": "biomass",
        "distractor_3": "hydropower"
      },
      {
        "id": "8121",
        "question": "Which of the following is best defined as energy produced through the flow of water; usually the water turns turbines, generating electricity?",
        "answer": "hydropower",
        "distractor_1": "geothermal energy",
        "distractor_2": "biomass",
        "distractor_3": "fossil fuel"
      },
      {
        "id": "8122",
        "question": "Which of the following is best defined as organic matter used as fuel to provide heat and generate electricity?",
        "answer": "biomass ",
        "distractor_1": "geothermal energy",
        "distractor_2": "hydropower",
        "distractor_3": "fossil fuel"
      },
      {
        "id": "8123",
        "question": "Which of the following is best defined as power produced from the natural heat in the earth; the heat is used to produce steam which turns turbines to produce energy?",
        "answer": "geothermal energy",
        "distractor_1": "hydropower",
        "distractor_2": "biomass",
        "distractor_3": "fossil fuel"
      },
      {
        "id": "8124",
        "question": "Which of the following is best defined as a device that converts chemical energy in a fuel into electricity?",
        "answer": "fuel cell",
        "distractor_1": "anode",
        "distractor_2": "cathode",
        "distractor_3": "solar cell"
      },
      {
        "id": "8125",
        "question": "Which of the following is best defined as a device that absorbs light and transforms it into electrical energy?",
        "answer": "solar cell",
        "distractor_1": "anode",
        "distractor_2": "cathode",
        "distractor_3": "fuel cell"
      },
      {
        "id": "8126",
        "question": "Which of the following is best defined as stored energy?",
        "answer": "potential energy",
        "distractor_1": "kinetic energy",
        "distractor_2": "greater energy",
        "distractor_3": "dynamic energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "8127",
        "question": "Which of the following is best defined as energy in motion?",
        "answer": "kinetic energy",
        "distractor_1": "potential energy",
        "distractor_2": "greater energy",
        "distractor_3": "dynamic energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "8128",
        "question": "Which of the following is best defined as the positive end of an electrical current?",
        "answer": "anode ",
        "distractor_1": "solar cell",
        "distractor_2": "fuel cell",
        "distractor_3": "cathode"
      },
      {
        "id": "8129",
        "question": "Which of the following is best defined as the negative end of an electrical current?",
        "answer": "cathode ",
        "distractor_1": "anode",
        "distractor_2": "solar cell",
        "distractor_3": "fuel cell"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "129",
    "name": "CNC Mill",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "3947",
        "question": "What axis on a milling machine moves up and down?",
        "answer": "z",
        "distractor_1": "y",
        "distractor_2": "x",
        "distractor_3": "d"
      },
      {
        "id": "3948",
        "question": "What term is defined as the turning of industrial standard stock into useful finished products?",
        "answer": "secondary processing",
        "distractor_1": "extracting",
        "distractor_2": "primary processing",
        "distractor_3": "harvesting "
      },
      {
        "id": "3949",
        "question": "What term is defined as the revolutions per minute (rpm) of the main spindle and the cutting tool?",
        "answer": "spindle speed",
        "distractor_1": "feed rate ",
        "distractor_2": "rapid traverse",
        "distractor_3": "production rate"
      },
      {
        "id": "3950",
        "question": "What does the acronym CNC stand for?",
        "answer": "Computer Numerical Control ",
        "distractor_1": "Coordinated Numerical Computer",
        "distractor_2": "Controlled Network Computer",
        "distractor_3": "Computer Network Center"
      },
      {
        "id": "3951",
        "question": "What system is defined as the method of locating addresses or locations identified by x, y, and z values?",
        "answer": "Cartesian coordinate",
        "distractor_1": "xyz",
        "distractor_2": "binary ",
        "distractor_3": "computer numerical control"
      },
      {
        "id": "3952",
        "question": "With the development of CNC machines, how would the current jobs of factory workers be described?",
        "answer": "highly skilled and computer-oriented",
        "distractor_1": "dull and repetitive ",
        "distractor_2": "automated",
        "distractor_3": "involve making a complete product by hand"
      },
      {
        "id": "3953",
        "question": "Why is it necessary to set tolerance limits for each piece of a product to be milled?",
        "answer": "will fit together as accurately as possible",
        "distractor_1": "will fit on the milling machine",
        "distractor_2": "can be milled more quickly",
        "distractor_3": "can be viewed using the virtual reality program"
      },
      {
        "id": "3954",
        "question": "What term is also referred to as stock, billet, and workpiece?",
        "answer": "material from which you manufacture projects",
        "distractor_1": "mill machine parts",
        "distractor_2": "CAD drawings ",
        "distractor_3": "mill axes"
      },
      {
        "id": "3955",
        "question": "The last step in the design process before a product is manufactured is preparing what item(s)?",
        "answer": "CAD drawing and specifications list",
        "distractor_1": "refined drawing",
        "distractor_2": "3-D model",
        "distractor_3": "rough sketch "
      },
      {
        "id": "3956",
        "question": "The rise of mass production as a manufacturing process was most dependent on what development?",
        "answer": "assembly line",
        "distractor_1": "computer",
        "distractor_2": "Cartesian coordinate system",
        "distractor_3": "Model T Ford"
      },
      {
        "id": "3957",
        "question": "Within which manufacturing process category does milling fall?",
        "answer": "separating",
        "distractor_1": "forming",
        "distractor_2": "conditioning",
        "distractor_3": "casting and molding "
      },
      {
        "id": "3958",
        "question": "To produce manufactured products with very specific uses, what form of metals are usually used?",
        "answer": "alloys",
        "distractor_1": "ores",
        "distractor_2": "ceramics",
        "distractor_3": "polymers"
      },
      {
        "id": "3959",
        "question": "What term is defined as the approach that includes all steps in producing a product, from recognition of need for the product through its design, manufacture, and marketing?",
        "answer": "CIM",
        "distractor_1": "CAM",
        "distractor_2": "CAD ",
        "distractor_3": "automation"
      },
      {
        "id": "3960",
        "question": "Which tool should be used when making very precise measurements of linear distances, such as length, width, and thickness?",
        "answer": "micrometer",
        "distractor_1": "machinist's square",
        "distractor_2": "tape rule ",
        "distractor_3": "protractor"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "141",
    "name": "Logic & Reasoning",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "4055",
        "question": "What is the term for an if-then statement?",
        "answer": "conditional",
        "distractor_1": "conjunction",
        "distractor_2": "conclusion",
        "distractor_3": "conjecture"
      },
      {
        "id": "4056",
        "question": "What is the term for a statement, opinion, or conclusion based on observation?",
        "answer": "conjecture",
        "distractor_1": "conditional",
        "distractor_2": "conclusion",
        "distractor_3": "hypothesis"
      },
      {
        "id": "4058",
        "question": "What is the term for using facts, definitions, logic, and accepted rules and properties to reach conclusions?",
        "answer": "deductive reasoning",
        "distractor_1": "conclusion",
        "distractor_2": "mutually exclusive",
        "distractor_3": "conjunction"
      },
      {
        "id": "4059",
        "question": "What is the term for a statement resulting from the premises of a logical argument?",
        "answer": "conclusion",
        "distractor_1": "conjecture",
        "distractor_2": "mutually exclusive",
        "distractor_3": "deductive reasoning"
      },
      {
        "id": "4062",
        "question": "What is the term for the if part of an if-then statement?",
        "answer": "hypothesis",
        "distractor_1": "conditional",
        "distractor_2": "conclusion",
        "distractor_3": "invalid argument"
      },
      {
        "id": "4064",
        "question": "What is the term for a method of reasoning in which a conjecture is made based on several observations?",
        "answer": "inductive reasoning",
        "distractor_1": "conditional",
        "distractor_2": "mutual exclusion",
        "distractor_3": "conclusion"
      },
      {
        "id": "4065",
        "question": "What is the term for an argument that does not use rules of logic?",
        "answer": "invalid argument",
        "distractor_1": "deductive reasoning",
        "distractor_2": "inductive reasoning",
        "distractor_3": "mutual exclusion"
      },
      {
        "id": "4066",
        "question": "What is the term for two events that cannot happen at the same time?",
        "answer": "mutually exclusive events",
        "distractor_1": "premises",
        "distractor_2": "hypotheses",
        "distractor_3": "invalid events"
      },
      {
        "id": "4067",
        "question": "What is the term for a given statement in an argument?",
        "answer": "premise",
        "distractor_1": "conclusion",
        "distractor_2": "conjecture",
        "distractor_3": "theorem"
      },
      {
        "id": "4068",
        "question": "What is the term for a statement that is proven?",
        "answer": "theorem",
        "distractor_1": "premise",
        "distractor_2": "distractor",
        "distractor_3": "hypothesis"
      },
      {
        "id": "4069",
        "question": "What is the term for an argument that uses rules of logic?",
        "answer": "valid argument",
        "distractor_1": "conjecture",
        "distractor_2": "hypothesis",
        "distractor_3": "premise"
      },
      {
        "id": "4070",
        "question": "What is the term for an example that shows that a statement is not always true?",
        "answer": "counterexample",
        "distractor_1": "conclusion",
        "distractor_2": "conjecture",
        "distractor_3": "premise"
      },
      {
        "id": "4073",
        "question": "What is the term for a statement involving NOT?",
        "answer": "negation",
        "distractor_1": "invalid argument",
        "distractor_2": "conclusion",
        "distractor_3": "premise"
      },
      {
        "id": "4075",
        "question": "What is the term for two angles whose measures have the sum of 90 degrees?",
        "answer": "complementary angles",
        "distractor_1": "supplementary angles",
        "distractor_2": "obtuse angles",
        "distractor_3": "right angles"
      },
      {
        "id": "4076",
        "question": "What is the term for two angles whose measures have the sum of 180 degrees?",
        "answer": "supplementary angles",
        "distractor_1": "complementary angles",
        "distractor_2": "obtuse angles",
        "distractor_3": "right angles"
      },
      {
        "id": "4077",
        "question": "Either Mary drives her car to work or she rides the bus to work. 'Drives her car or rides the bus' are examples or what type of events?",
        "answer": "mutually exclusive",
        "distractor_1": "conjunctives",
        "distractor_2": "simultaneous",
        "distractor_3": "symbiotic"
      },
      {
        "id": "4078",
        "question": "Which numbers are the first numbers in the Fibonacci sequence?",
        "answer": "1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8",
        "distractor_1": "1, 2, 3, 5, 7, 11",
        "distractor_2": "2, 4, 8, 16, 32",
        "distractor_3": "3, 5, 7, 11, 17"
      },
      {
        "id": "4080",
        "question": "Who was a hypochondriac yet a brilliant mathematician and a physician?",
        "answer": "Cardano",
        "distractor_1": "Aristotle",
        "distractor_2": "Ptolemy",
        "distractor_3": "Newton"
      },
      {
        "id": "4081",
        "question": "Who was considered to be one of the wise men of Greece?",
        "answer": "Thales",
        "distractor_1": "Galileo",
        "distractor_2": "Gauss",
        "distractor_3": "Einstein"
      },
      {
        "id": "4082",
        "question": "All squares are rectangles. All rectangles are quadrilaterals. If these premises are true, what conclusion can be drawn?",
        "answer": "All squares are quadrilaterals.",
        "distractor_1": "All rectangles are squares.",
        "distractor_2": "All quadrilaterals are squares.",
        "distractor_3": "All quadrilaterals are rectangles."
      },
      {
        "id": "4083",
        "question": "What is the term for using reasoning to move from general principles to specifics?",
        "answer": "deductive reasoning",
        "distractor_1": "inductive reasoning",
        "distractor_2": "hypothesizing",
        "distractor_3": "implicating"
      },
      {
        "id": "4084",
        "question": "All squares are rectangles. All rectangles are quadrilaterals. If these premises are true, what conclusion can be drawn?",
        "answer": "All squares are quadrilaterals.",
        "distractor_1": "All rectangles are squares.",
        "distractor_2": "All quadrilaterals are squares.",
        "distractor_3": "All quadrilaterals are rectangles."
      },
      {
        "id": "4085",
        "question": "Either George rides his bike to work or he walks. 'Rides his bike or walks' are examples of what type of events?",
        "answer": "mutually exclusive",
        "distractor_1": "conjunctives",
        "distractor_2": "simultaneous",
        "distractor_3": "symbiotic"
      },
      {
        "id": "4086",
        "question": "Which number would be next in the sequence 1, -1, 2, 0, 3, 1",
        "answer": "4",
        "distractor_1": "2",
        "distractor_2": "3",
        "distractor_3": "-1"
      },
      {
        "id": "4088",
        "question": "Which of the following sequences would have the number 9 written next?",
        "answer": "1, 3, 5, 7",
        "distractor_1": "2, 4, 6, 8",
        "distractor_2": "-1, 1, 3, 5",
        "distractor_3": "-1, 3, 2, 6"
      },
      {
        "id": "4089",
        "question": "Six dots are drawn in the shape of a triangle. How many dots would be needed to add a new row to create an even larger triangle?",
        "answer": "4",
        "distractor_1": "3",
        "distractor_2": "5",
        "distractor_3": "6"
      },
      {
        "id": "4091",
        "question": "Which sequence is the prime number sequence?",
        "answer": "2, 3, 5, 7, 11",
        "distractor_1": "1, 2, 3, 5, 7",
        "distractor_2": "1, 2, 3, 5, 8",
        "distractor_3": "11, 13, 15, 17"
      },
      {
        "id": "4092",
        "question": "What does the mathematical model represent?",
        "answer": "the number of accidents involving drunken drivers",
        "distractor_1": "the total number of accidents per year",
        "distractor_2": "the number of drivers who are drunk",
        "distractor_3": "the number of drunken drivers who died"
      },
      {
        "id": "4093",
        "question": "Three dots are drawn in the shape of a triangle. A new row is added to the bottom using an additional three dots to create a larger triangle. How many dots would be needed to add a new row to create an even larger triangle?",
        "answer": "4",
        "distractor_1": "3",
        "distractor_2": "5",
        "distractor_3": "6"
      },
      {
        "id": "4094",
        "question": "Which of the following belongs to the set of prime numbers?",
        "answer": "2, 3, 5, 7, 11",
        "distractor_1": "1, 2, 3, 5, 7",
        "distractor_2": "1, 2, 3, 5, 8",
        "distractor_3": "11, 13, 15, 17"
      },
      {
        "id": "4095",
        "question": "What is the term for using reasoning to draw a general conclusion based on particular facts?",
        "answer": "inductive reasoning",
        "distractor_1": "deductive reasoning",
        "distractor_2": "hypothesizing",
        "distractor_3": "conjecturing"
      },
      {
        "id": "4096",
        "question": "What are complementary angles?",
        "answer": "Angles whose measurements add to 90 degrees.",
        "distractor_1": "Angles that have the same measurement.",
        "distractor_2": "Angles whose measurements add to 180 degrees.",
        "distractor_3": "Angles whose measurements are never the same."
      },
      {
        "id": "4097",
        "question": "A sequence begins with 1, 1, 2, 3, 5. Based on the Fibonacci sequence, what would the next number be?",
        "answer": "8",
        "distractor_1": "6",
        "distractor_2": "7",
        "distractor_3": "9"
      },
      {
        "id": "4098",
        "question": "What are complementary angles?",
        "answer": "Angles whose measurements add to 90 degrees.",
        "distractor_1": "Angles that have the same measurement.",
        "distractor_2": "Angles whose measurements add to 180 degrees.",
        "distractor_3": "Angles whose measurements are never the same."
      },
      {
        "id": "4099",
        "question": "How many combinations are possible to get a total roll of six when using two dice?",
        "answer": "3",
        "distractor_1": "1",
        "distractor_2": "2",
        "distractor_3": "4"
      },
      {
        "id": "4115",
        "question": "Which of the following statements is true when two mutually exclusive events are compared?",
        "answer": "They both cannot occur.",
        "distractor_1": "They are identical.",
        "distractor_2": "They happen simultaneously.",
        "distractor_3": "They are expensive."
      },
      {
        "id": "4116",
        "question": "Select the term that results from 'given' statements.",
        "answer": "conclusion",
        "distractor_1": "premise",
        "distractor_2": "conditional",
        "distractor_3": "conjecture"
      },
      {
        "id": "4119",
        "question": "What term means conclusion?",
        "answer": "resulting statement",
        "distractor_1": "premise",
        "distractor_2": "conditional",
        "distractor_3": "conjecture"
      },
      {
        "id": "4426",
        "question": "What are complementary angles?",
        "answer": "angles whose measurements add to 90 degrees",
        "distractor_1": "angles that have the same measurement",
        "distractor_2": "angles whose measurements add to 180 degrees",
        "distractor_3": "angles whose measurements are never the same"
      },
      {
        "id": "4427",
        "question": "What is the term for using reasoning to move from general principles to specifics?",
        "answer": "deductive reasoning",
        "distractor_1": "inductive reasoning",
        "distractor_2": "hypothesizing",
        "distractor_3": "implicating"
      },
      {
        "id": "4428",
        "question": "A sequence begins with 1, 1, 2, 3, 5. Based on the Fibonacci sequence, what would the next number be?",
        "answer": "8",
        "distractor_1": "6",
        "distractor_2": "7",
        "distractor_3": "9"
      },
      {
        "id": "4429",
        "question": "What term means conclusion?",
        "answer": "resulting statement",
        "distractor_1": "premise",
        "distractor_2": "conditional",
        "distractor_3": "conjecture"
      },
      {
        "id": "4430",
        "question": "Either Mary drives her car to work or she rides the bus to work. 'Drives her car or rides the bus' are examples of what type of events?",
        "answer": "mutually exclusive",
        "distractor_1": "conjunctives",
        "distractor_2": "simultaneous",
        "distractor_3": "symbiotic"
      },
      {
        "id": "4431",
        "question": "Which of the following is a whole number greater than one that has exactly two factors, 1 and the number itself?",
        "answer": "prime number",
        "distractor_1": "triangular number",
        "distractor_2": "perfect square",
        "distractor_3": "irrational number"
      },
      {
        "id": "4432",
        "question": "Which of the following are perfect squares?",
        "answer": "1, 4, 9, 16, 25",
        "distractor_1": "1, 3, 5, 7, 9",
        "distractor_2": "2, 4, 6, 8, 10",
        "distractor_3": "1, -1, 9, -9, 5, -5"
      },
      {
        "id": "4433",
        "question": "Which of the following belongs to the set of prime numbers?",
        "answer": "2, 3, 5, 7, 11",
        "distractor_1": "1, 2, 3, 5, 7",
        "distractor_2": "1, 2, 3, 5, 8",
        "distractor_3": "11, 13, 15, 17"
      },
      {
        "id": "4434",
        "question": "What results from given statements?",
        "answer": "conclusion",
        "distractor_1": "conjecture",
        "distractor_2": "conditional",
        "distractor_3": "premise"
      },
      {
        "id": "4435",
        "question": "Either George rides his bike to work or he walks. 'Rides his bike or walks' are examples of what type of events?",
        "answer": "mutually exclusive",
        "distractor_1": "conjunctives",
        "distractor_2": "simultaneous",
        "distractor_3": "symbiotic"
      },
      {
        "id": "4436",
        "question": "Which one of the following statements about prime numbers and perfect squares is correct?",
        "answer": "No number can be both a prime number and a perfect square.",
        "distractor_1": "Only the number one is both a prime number and a perfect square.",
        "distractor_2": "Nine is both prime and a perfect square.",
        "distractor_3": "All perfect squares are prime numbers."
      },
      {
        "id": "6654",
        "question": "What term describes when two statements connected by the word and, is true when both statements are true?",
        "answer": "conjunction",
        "distractor_1": "conclusion",
        "distractor_2": "conjecture",
        "distractor_3": "condition"
      },
      {
        "id": "6655",
        "question": "What rule of logic states if P is true, then Q is true; P is true, therefore Q is true?",
        "answer": "direct argument",
        "distractor_1": "indirect argument",
        "distractor_2": "inductive reasoning",
        "distractor_3": "deductive reasoning"
      },
      {
        "id": "6656",
        "question": "What term describes when two statements connected by the word or, is true when at least one of the statements is true?",
        "answer": "disjunction",
        "distractor_1": "conjunction",
        "distractor_2": "conclusion",
        "distractor_3": "conjecture"
      },
      {
        "id": "6657",
        "question": "What rule of logic states if P is true, then Q is true; Q is not true, therefore P is not true?",
        "answer": "indirect argument",
        "distractor_1": "direct argument",
        "distractor_2": "deductive reasoning",
        "distractor_3": "inductive reasoning"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "142",
    "name": "Statistical Analysis",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "5322",
        "question": "Which of the following represents the frequency of items in a data set?",
        "answer": "histogram",
        "distractor_1": "line graph",
        "distractor_2": "box-and-whisker plot",
        "distractor_3": "circle graph"
      },
      {
        "id": "4048",
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT an average?",
        "answer": "range",
        "distractor_1": "median",
        "distractor_2": "mode",
        "distractor_3": "mean"
      },
      {
        "id": "4049",
        "question": "What are the two types of probability?",
        "answer": "theoretical and experimental",
        "distractor_1": "exact and approximate",
        "distractor_2": "likely and unlikely",
        "distractor_3": "hypothetical and fictional"
      },
      {
        "id": "4050",
        "question": "Identify the term which refers to the likelihood of an event happening.",
        "answer": "probability",
        "distractor_1": "Murphy's law",
        "distractor_2": "fate",
        "distractor_3": "statistics"
      },
      {
        "id": "4039",
        "question": "Which of the following values is found by adding the numbers in a data set and dividing the sum by the number of items in the set?",
        "answer": "mean",
        "distractor_1": "mode",
        "distractor_2": "median",
        "distractor_3": "range"
      },
      {
        "id": "4040",
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT an average?",
        "answer": "range",
        "distractor_1": "median",
        "distractor_2": "mode",
        "distractor_3": "mean"
      },
      {
        "id": "4041",
        "question": "How is the median of a data set found?",
        "answer": "placing the numbers in order and finding the number in the middle of the set",
        "distractor_1": "adding the numbers and dividing by the number of items in the set",
        "distractor_2": "finding the number that occurs the most often",
        "distractor_3": "adding the values and rounding the sum to the nearest whole number"
      },
      {
        "id": "4042",
        "question": "Which of the following terms refers to the likelihood of an event happening?",
        "answer": "probability",
        "distractor_1": "statistics",
        "distractor_2": "karma",
        "distractor_3": "Murphy's law"
      },
      {
        "id": "4043",
        "question": "Which of the following types of graphs is best used to display changes over time?",
        "answer": "line graph",
        "distractor_1": "bar graph",
        "distractor_2": "stem-and-leaf plot",
        "distractor_3": "histogram"
      },
      {
        "id": "4044",
        "question": "What are the two types of probability?",
        "answer": "theoretical and experimental ",
        "distractor_1": "likely and unlikely",
        "distractor_2": "exact and approximate",
        "distractor_3": "hypothetical and fictional"
      },
      {
        "id": "4045",
        "question": "Identify the term for events in which the second outcome is affected by the first.",
        "answer": "dependent events",
        "distractor_1": "independent events",
        "distractor_2": "exclusive events",
        "distractor_3": "nonexclusive events"
      },
      {
        "id": "4046",
        "question": "Identify the term for events in which the second outcome is NOT affected by the first.",
        "answer": "independent events",
        "distractor_1": "dependent events",
        "distractor_2": "exclusive events",
        "distractor_3": "nonexclusive events"
      },
      {
        "id": "5323",
        "question": "Identify the mean of the following data set: 67, 119, 83, 26, 48, and 14.",
        "answer": "59.5",
        "distractor_1": "52.5",
        "distractor_2": "49.6",
        "distractor_3": "102"
      },
      {
        "id": "5324",
        "question": "Which of the following is a way to represent data in which the tens and hundreds digits are arranged in columns and the ones digit are arranged in rows?",
        "answer": "stem-and-leaf plot",
        "distractor_1": "histogram",
        "distractor_2": "circle graph",
        "distractor_3": "box-and-whisker plot"
      },
      {
        "id": "5325",
        "question": "Which of the following represents the spread of data from upper quartile to lower quartile?",
        "answer": "interquartile range",
        "distractor_1": "interquartile median",
        "distractor_2": "interquartile mean",
        "distractor_3": "interquartile number"
      },
      {
        "id": "5326",
        "question": "A student has a mean of 88% after taking three tests. What does the student need to score on the next test to raise the mean to 90%?",
        "answer": "96%",
        "distractor_1": "100%",
        "distractor_2": "94%",
        "distractor_3": "92%"
      },
      {
        "id": "5327",
        "question": "When a coin is tossed, one of the two events will occur. Either the coin will land on heads or it will land on tails. What is the term used to describe these events?",
        "answer": "independent events",
        "distractor_1": "executive events",
        "distractor_2": "dependent events",
        "distractor_3": "inclusive events"
      },
      {
        "id": "5328",
        "question": "Jennifer and Nathaniel are drawing cards to see who will go first in a game of cards. Jennifer draws a Jack from the deck. She does not replace her card in the deck. What are the odds that Nathaniel will draw a card higher than Jennifer?",
        "answer": "12 to 39",
        "distractor_1": "15 to 36",
        "distractor_2": "12 to 36",
        "distractor_3": "15 to 39"
      },
      {
        "id": "5329",
        "question": "Which of the following types of graphs is best used to display data in continuous intervals?",
        "answer": "histogram",
        "distractor_1": "bar graph",
        "distractor_2": "stem-and-leaf plot",
        "distractor_3": "line graph"
      },
      {
        "id": "6022",
        "question": "What is the middle number in a set of data when the data is arranged in numerical order?",
        "answer": "Median",
        "distractor_1": "Mode",
        "distractor_2": "Mean",
        "distractor_3": "Upper quartile marker"
      },
      {
        "id": "6025",
        "question": "What is the data item that appears the most often called?",
        "answer": "Mode",
        "distractor_1": "Range",
        "distractor_2": "Median",
        "distractor_3": "Average"
      },
      {
        "id": "6027",
        "question": "What type of graph displays the lower extreme, lower quartile, median, upper quartile, and upper extreme values of a data set?",
        "answer": "box-and-whisker plot",
        "distractor_1": "line graph",
        "distractor_2": "normal distribution graph",
        "distractor_3": "bar graph"
      },
      {
        "id": "6028",
        "question": "What is used to compare favorable outcomes to unfavorable outcomes?",
        "answer": "odds",
        "distractor_1": "probability",
        "distractor_2": "pros and cons list",
        "distractor_3": "potentiality"
      },
      {
        "id": "6033",
        "question": "What is a statement of probability based on the results of a series of trials?",
        "answer": "experimental probability",
        "distractor_1": "theoretical probability",
        "distractor_2": "pilot test analysis",
        "distractor_3": "repeat probability"
      },
      {
        "id": "6036",
        "question": "What would be used to find the probability of an event without doing an experiment or analyzing data?",
        "answer": "theoretical probability",
        "distractor_1": "experimental probability",
        "distractor_2": "generalization probability ",
        "distractor_3": "pilot test"
      },
      {
        "id": "6038",
        "question": "What graph is best used to compare data, bars are separated by equal spaces?",
        "answer": "bar graph",
        "distractor_1": "line graph",
        "distractor_2": "histogram",
        "distractor_3": "box-and-whisker plot"
      },
      {
        "id": "6039",
        "question": "What is the median of the upper 50% of a set of data?",
        "answer": "upper quartile",
        "distractor_1": "raised mean",
        "distractor_2": "average of increase",
        "distractor_3": "lower quartile"
      },
      {
        "id": "6040",
        "question": "What is the median of the lower 50% of a set of data.",
        "answer": "lower quartile",
        "distractor_1": "average of decrease",
        "distractor_2": "upper quartile",
        "distractor_3": "low mean"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "130",
    "name": "CNC Lathe",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "4124",
        "question": "What development was the rise of mass production as a manufacturing process most dependent upon?",
        "answer": "assembly line",
        "distractor_1": "computer",
        "distractor_2": "Cartesian coordinate system",
        "distractor_3": "Model T Ford"
      },
      {
        "id": "4125",
        "question": "What device is used to secure stock on a lathe?",
        "answer": "chuck",
        "distractor_1": "wrench",
        "distractor_2": "turret",
        "distractor_3": "tool holder"
      },
      {
        "id": "4126",
        "question": "What determines the shape of the cut on a turned part?",
        "answer": "cutter profile",
        "distractor_1": "tool holder",
        "distractor_2": "cutter speed",
        "distractor_3": "spindle speed"
      },
      {
        "id": "4127",
        "question": "What system is described as the method of locating addresses or locations identified by x, y, and z values?",
        "answer": "Cartesian coordinate system",
        "distractor_1": "XYZ",
        "distractor_2": "binary",
        "distractor_3": "computer numerical control"
      },
      {
        "id": "4128",
        "question": "A lathe produces parts that are what shape?",
        "answer": "round",
        "distractor_1": "square",
        "distractor_2": "flat",
        "distractor_3": "spherical"
      },
      {
        "id": "4129",
        "question": "With the development of CNC machines, which description fits the majority of jobs held by factory worker today?",
        "answer": "highly skilled and computer oriented",
        "distractor_1": "involve making a complete product by hand",
        "distractor_2": "automated",
        "distractor_3": "dull and repetitive"
      },
      {
        "id": "4130",
        "question": "What is the function of the chuck?",
        "answer": "secure stock on a lathe",
        "distractor_1": "cut the stock",
        "distractor_2": "spin the stock",
        "distractor_3": "move the stock back and forth"
      },
      {
        "id": "4131",
        "question": "What determines the shape of the cut on a turned part?",
        "answer": "cutter speed",
        "distractor_1": "tool holder",
        "distractor_2": "cutter profile",
        "distractor_3": "spindle speed"
      },
      {
        "id": "4132",
        "question": "What does the acronym CNC stand for?",
        "answer": "Computer Numerical Control",
        "distractor_1": "Coordinated Numerical Computer",
        "distractor_2": "Controlled Network Computer",
        "distractor_3": "Computer Network Center"
      },
      {
        "id": "4133",
        "question": "What development was the rise of mass production as a manufacturing process most dependent upon?",
        "answer": "assembly line",
        "distractor_1": "computer",
        "distractor_2": "Model T Ford",
        "distractor_3": "Cartesian coordinate system"
      },
      {
        "id": "4134",
        "question": "What are the two axes on a CNC lathe?",
        "answer": "x-axis, z-axis",
        "distractor_1": "y-axis, z-axis",
        "distractor_2": "a-axis, b-axis",
        "distractor_3": "y-axis, x-axis"
      },
      {
        "id": "4135",
        "question": "What is the part of a lathe machine that holds and spins the workpiece?",
        "answer": "chuck",
        "distractor_1": "spindle",
        "distractor_2": "bed",
        "distractor_3": "tool"
      },
      {
        "id": "4136",
        "question": "In which direction does the x-axis on a lathe move?",
        "answer": "backward and forward",
        "distractor_1": "up and down",
        "distractor_2": "in and out",
        "distractor_3": "left and right"
      },
      {
        "id": "4137",
        "question": "What term is defined as the process in which you change resources into products?",
        "answer": "manufacturing",
        "distractor_1": "turning",
        "distractor_2": "stocking",
        "distractor_3": "milling"
      },
      {
        "id": "4138",
        "question": "What are the two types of operations that a turning machine can complete?",
        "answer": "straight turning, face turning",
        "distractor_1": "drilling, face turning",
        "distractor_2": "reaming, drilling",
        "distractor_3": "milling, rotating"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "145",
    "name": "Farm Management",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "4195",
        "question": "What period of time is covered by a balance sheet?",
        "answer": "one moment",
        "distractor_1": "one month",
        "distractor_2": "one year",
        "distractor_3": "varies from report to report"
      },
      {
        "id": "4196",
        "question": "What is the term for the difference between total assets and total liabilities?",
        "answer": "equity",
        "distractor_1": "long-term liabilities",
        "distractor_2": "current assets",
        "distractor_3": "expenses"
      },
      {
        "id": "4197",
        "question": "Which of the following are operating expenses?",
        "answer": "depreciation",
        "distractor_1": "COGS",
        "distractor_2": "current assets",
        "distractor_3": "current liabilities"
      },
      {
        "id": "4198",
        "question": "If the yield for one acre is 125 bushels, what is the total yield for 5,000 acres?",
        "answer": "625,000 bushels",
        "distractor_1": "125,000 bushels",
        "distractor_2": "525,000 bushels",
        "distractor_3": "125 bushels"
      },
      {
        "id": "4199",
        "question": "Which of the following are contained in a business plan?",
        "answer": "marketing plan, operational plan, financial plan",
        "distractor_1": "production schedule, marketing plan, income statement",
        "distractor_2": "description of products and services, balance sheet, income statement",
        "distractor_3": "organizational chart, product description, income statement"
      },
      {
        "id": "4200",
        "question": "In addition to the worms, what product is produced in a vermiculture operation?",
        "answer": "compost",
        "distractor_1": "top soil",
        "distractor_2": "recycled newspapers",
        "distractor_3": "fishing bait"
      },
      {
        "id": "4201",
        "question": "What major headings are included in an income statement?",
        "answer": "Sales, Cost of Goods Sold, Gross Profit",
        "distractor_1": "Sales, Gross Expenses, Net Expenses",
        "distractor_2": "Sales, Gross Profit, Operational Profit",
        "distractor_3": "Sales, Cost of Goods Sold, Net Operational Profit"
      },
      {
        "id": "4202",
        "question": "If the sales for a company are $100,000 and the cost of goods sold are 28% of sales, what is the gross profit?",
        "answer": "$72,000",
        "distractor_1": "$28,000",
        "distractor_2": "$2,800",
        "distractor_3": "$7,200"
      },
      {
        "id": "4203",
        "question": "What is the term that refers to the amount a company owes?",
        "answer": "liabilities",
        "distractor_1": "assets",
        "distractor_2": "balance sheet",
        "distractor_3": "depreciation"
      },
      {
        "id": "4204",
        "question": "What are assets?",
        "answer": "what the company owns",
        "distractor_1": "what the company owes",
        "distractor_2": "what the company wants to own",
        "distractor_3": "what the company wants to buy"
      },
      {
        "id": "4205",
        "question": "What time period is covered by a balance sheet?",
        "answer": "one moment",
        "distractor_1": "one month",
        "distractor_2": "one hour",
        "distractor_3": "one day"
      },
      {
        "id": "4206",
        "question": "Equity is the difference between what two values?",
        "answer": "total assets and total liabilities ",
        "distractor_1": "current assets and expected liabilities",
        "distractor_2": "income and expenses",
        "distractor_3": "projected assets and total  expenses"
      },
      {
        "id": "4207",
        "question": "Which of the following are operating expenses?",
        "answer": "depreciation and utilities ",
        "distractor_1": "COGS",
        "distractor_2": "current assets",
        "distractor_3": "current liabilities"
      },
      {
        "id": "4208",
        "question": "If the yield for one acre is 125 bushels, what is the total yield for 6,500 acres?",
        "answer": "812,500 bushels ",
        "distractor_1": "750,500 bushels",
        "distractor_2": "650,000 bushels",
        "distractor_3": "125,000 bushels"
      },
      {
        "id": "4209",
        "question": "Which of the following are contained in a business plan?",
        "answer": "marketing plan, operational plan, financial plan  ",
        "distractor_1": "production schedule, marketing plan, income statement",
        "distractor_2": "description of products and services, balance sheet, income statement",
        "distractor_3": "organizational chart, product description, income statement"
      },
      {
        "id": "4210",
        "question": "A vermiculture operation yields what two products?",
        "answer": "worms and compost ",
        "distractor_1": "worms and top soil",
        "distractor_2": "worms and recycled newspapers",
        "distractor_3": "worms and fishing bait"
      },
      {
        "id": "4211",
        "question": "Income statements include what major headings?",
        "answer": "Sales, Cost of Goods Sold, Gross Profit ",
        "distractor_1": "Sales, Gross Profit, Operational Profit",
        "distractor_2": "Sales, Cost of Goods Sold, Net Operational Profit",
        "distractor_3": "Sales, Gross Expenses, Net Expenses"
      },
      {
        "id": "4212",
        "question": "If the sales for a company are $100,000 and the cost of goods sold are 35% of sales, what is the gross profit?",
        "answer": "$65,000",
        "distractor_1": "$35,000",
        "distractor_2": "$6,500",
        "distractor_3": "$3,500"
      },
      {
        "id": "4213",
        "question": "Which of the following terms refers to the process of choosing plants and animals with desirable traits to be used to produce offspring?",
        "answer": "selective breeding",
        "distractor_1": "genetic enhancement",
        "distractor_2": "gene selection",
        "distractor_3": "selective stocking"
      },
      {
        "id": "4214",
        "question": "Which of the following refers to the farming of worms?",
        "answer": "vermiculture ",
        "distractor_1": "horticulture",
        "distractor_2": "aquaculture",
        "distractor_3": "zooculture"
      },
      {
        "id": "4215",
        "question": "Which of the following would be considered a long-term asset?",
        "answer": "tractor ",
        "distractor_1": "cattle",
        "distractor_2": "seeds",
        "distractor_3": "corn crop"
      },
      {
        "id": "4216",
        "question": "Chandra produces 355 containers of worms per month. Each container costs her $ 0.60 to make. She sells each container at a price of $0.95. In a month when she sells all her containers, what is her percent profit?",
        "answer": "37% ",
        "distractor_1": "36%",
        "distractor_2": "63%",
        "distractor_3": "64%"
      },
      {
        "id": "4217",
        "question": "What is meant by the term equity?",
        "answer": "The difference between assets and liabilities.",
        "distractor_1": "The difference between stocks and bonds.",
        "distractor_2": "The difference between assets and property.",
        "distractor_3": "The difference between debts and expenses."
      },
      {
        "id": "4218",
        "question": "A tractor purchased for $175,000 depreciates 15% of the total cost each year. After three years of use, what is the value of the tractor?",
        "answer": "$96,250.00",
        "distractor_1": "$148,750.00",
        "distractor_2": "$107,471.87",
        "distractor_3": "$126,437.50"
      },
      {
        "id": "4219",
        "question": "What are liabilities?",
        "answer": "what the company owes  ",
        "distractor_1": "what the company owns",
        "distractor_2": "what the company wants to own",
        "distractor_3": "what the company wants to buy"
      },
      {
        "id": "4220",
        "question": "What is the term for what the company owns?",
        "answer": "assets",
        "distractor_1": "liabilities",
        "distractor_2": "balance sheet",
        "distractor_3": "depreciation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6382",
        "question": "What is known as how much of something is available?",
        "answer": "Supply",
        "distractor_1": "Demand",
        "distractor_2": "Producer",
        "distractor_3": "Consumer"
      },
      {
        "id": "6383",
        "question": "What is known as how much of something people want?",
        "answer": "Demand",
        "distractor_1": "Supply",
        "distractor_2": "Consumer",
        "distractor_3": "Producer"
      },
      {
        "id": "6384",
        "question": "What shows a company's financial position a particular point in time?",
        "answer": "Balance sheet",
        "distractor_1": "Income statement",
        "distractor_2": "Business plan",
        "distractor_3": "Cash flow statement"
      },
      {
        "id": "6385",
        "question": "What shows the cash that came into a company and the cash that was paid by the company?",
        "answer": "Cash flow statement",
        "distractor_1": "Income statement",
        "distractor_2": "Balance sheet",
        "distractor_3": "Business plan"
      },
      {
        "id": "6386",
        "question": "What shows income and expenses and the amount of profit or loss for a period of time?",
        "answer": "Income statement",
        "distractor_1": "Business plan",
        "distractor_2": "Cash flow statement",
        "distractor_3": "Balance sheet"
      },
      {
        "id": "6387",
        "question": "What is a plan to see if a business will be viable?",
        "answer": "Business plan",
        "distractor_1": "Cash flow plan",
        "distractor_2": "Income statement",
        "distractor_3": "Balance sheet"
      },
      {
        "id": "6388",
        "question": "What is considered the buyer?",
        "answer": "Consumer",
        "distractor_1": "Demand",
        "distractor_2": "Producer",
        "distractor_3": "Supply"
      },
      {
        "id": "6389",
        "question": "What is someone or something that creates a product; a supplier?",
        "answer": "Producer",
        "distractor_1": "Consumer",
        "distractor_2": "Supply",
        "distractor_3": "Demand"
      },
      {
        "id": "6390",
        "question": "What businesses that allow people to pay at a point in the future for items purchased today?",
        "answer": "Creditors",
        "distractor_1": "Banks",
        "distractor_2": "Loan offices",
        "distractor_3": "Landlords"
      },
      {
        "id": "6391",
        "question": "What is the amount of production from a given quantity of resources; for example, bushels per acre?",
        "answer": "Yield",
        "distractor_1": "Crop",
        "distractor_2": "Supply",
        "distractor_3": "Producer"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "143",
    "name": "Aquaculture",
    "weight": "85",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "5451",
        "question": "What is the term for the controlled culture, or farming, of aquatic organisms for sale?",
        "answer": "aquaculture",
        "distractor_1": "ectothermic",
        "distractor_2": "milt",
        "distractor_3": "roe"
      },
      {
        "id": "5452",
        "question": "What chemical maintains the pH of water at a relatively constant level?",
        "answer": "buffer",
        "distractor_1": "acid",
        "distractor_2": "roe",
        "distractor_3": "milt"
      },
      {
        "id": "5453",
        "question": "What is the term for a cold-blooded organism; that is, one that cannot maintain a constant high body temperature?",
        "answer": "ectothermic",
        "distractor_1": "endothermic",
        "distractor_2": "metabolic rate",
        "distractor_3": "stocking rate"
      },
      {
        "id": "5454",
        "question": "What is the term for the release of eggs and sperm by fish?",
        "answer": "spawning",
        "distractor_1": "hatching",
        "distractor_2": "stocking rate",
        "distractor_3": "fertilization"
      },
      {
        "id": "5455",
        "question": "Which of the following is a baby fish up to one inch in length?",
        "answer": "fry",
        "distractor_1": "fingerling",
        "distractor_2": "calf ",
        "distractor_3": "infant"
      },
      {
        "id": "5456",
        "question": "Which of the following is a young fish from one to 10 inches long?",
        "answer": "fingerling",
        "distractor_1": "fry",
        "distractor_2": "small fish",
        "distractor_3": "milt"
      },
      {
        "id": "4221",
        "question": "Which of the following is an example of a cold-water fish species?",
        "answer": "rainbow trout",
        "distractor_1": "tilapia",
        "distractor_2": "striped bass",
        "distractor_3": "catfish"
      },
      {
        "id": "4222",
        "question": "Which fish characteristic makes them more efficient than cattle at converting food to salable meat?",
        "answer": "ectothermic temperature regulation",
        "distractor_1": "higher metabolism",
        "distractor_2": "higher feeding rate",
        "distractor_3": "smaller size"
      },
      {
        "id": "4223",
        "question": "Which fish species has a body shape that is well adapted for moving very quickly in short bursts?",
        "answer": "longnose gar",
        "distractor_1": "freshwater angelfish",
        "distractor_2": "cowfish",
        "distractor_3": "seahorse"
      },
      {
        "id": "4224",
        "question": "What is the best pH range for a healthy aquarium?",
        "answer": "pH 6.5-7.5",
        "distractor_1": "pH 4-6",
        "distractor_2": "pH 4-11",
        "distractor_3": "pH 9-10"
      },
      {
        "id": "4225",
        "question": "Which of the following chemical factors should be maintained at a level of approximately 7 to 8 parts per million in a fish habitat?",
        "answer": "dissolved oxygen",
        "distractor_1": "total alkalinity",
        "distractor_2": "chlorinity",
        "distractor_3": "ammonia"
      },
      {
        "id": "4226",
        "question": "How does the fact that fish are ectothermic affect their food conversion ratio, or FCR?",
        "answer": "decreases FCR by channeling energy into growth",
        "distractor_1": "decreases FCR by increasing amount of food consumed",
        "distractor_2": "increases FCR by channeling energy into temperature regulation",
        "distractor_3": "increases FCR by decreasing amount of food consumed"
      },
      {
        "id": "4227",
        "question": "When water temperature decreases, how is the dissolved oxygen (DO) concentration of the water affected?",
        "answer": "DO increases.",
        "distractor_1": "DO decreases.",
        "distractor_2": "DO does not change.",
        "distractor_3": "DO increases, then decreases."
      },
      {
        "id": "4228",
        "question": "What are the pH 'death points' below and above which fish cannot survive?",
        "answer": "pH 4-11",
        "distractor_1": "pH 6.5-7.5",
        "distractor_2": "pH 4-6",
        "distractor_3": "pH 9-10"
      },
      {
        "id": "4229",
        "question": "If you increase the stocking rate in an aquaculture tank above the recommended level, but change no other factors, how will this affect dissolved oxygen (DO) and fish growth rate?",
        "answer": "Both DO and growth rate will decrease.",
        "distractor_1": "Both DO and growth rate will increase.",
        "distractor_2": "DO will increase; growth rate will decrease.",
        "distractor_3": "DO will decrease; growth rate will increase."
      },
      {
        "id": "4230",
        "question": "What happens to the dissolved oxygen (DO) concentration of water when the water temperature increases?",
        "answer": "DO decreases.",
        "distractor_1": "DO increases.",
        "distractor_2": "DO fluctuates randomly.",
        "distractor_3": "DO does not change."
      },
      {
        "id": "4231",
        "question": "What is the top aquaculture-producing country in the world?",
        "answer": "China",
        "distractor_1": "Japan",
        "distractor_2": "United States",
        "distractor_3": "Philippines"
      },
      {
        "id": "4232",
        "question": "Which of the following structures helps maintain balance in fish?",
        "answer": "lateral line",
        "distractor_1": "operculum",
        "distractor_2": "gills",
        "distractor_3": "air bladder"
      },
      {
        "id": "4233",
        "question": "Which of the following sets of conditions would result in the most rapid goldfish growth?",
        "answer": "high-protein food; warm, aerated tank",
        "distractor_1": "high-protein food; warm, non-aerated tank",
        "distractor_2": "low-protein food; cool, non-aerated tank",
        "distractor_3": "low-protein food; cool, aerated tank"
      },
      {
        "id": "4234",
        "question": "Which of the following chemical factors should be maintained at zero in a healthy aquarium?",
        "answer": "chlorinity",
        "distractor_1": "dissolved oxygen",
        "distractor_2": "total alkalinity",
        "distractor_3": "nitrates"
      },
      {
        "id": "5457",
        "question": "What is the term for a facility producing seed for aquaculture operations? ",
        "answer": "hatchery",
        "distractor_1": "fishery",
        "distractor_2": "hatching plant",
        "distractor_3": "fish production plant"
      },
      {
        "id": "5458",
        "question": "What is the term for the number of fish introduced per unit of water, or the stocking density?",
        "answer": "stocking rate",
        "distractor_1": "yield",
        "distractor_2": "metabolic rate feed conversion ratio",
        "distractor_3": "feeding rate"
      },
      {
        "id": "5459",
        "question": "What is the rate at which organisms break down food to carry out life functions?",
        "answer": "metabolic rate",
        "distractor_1": "feeding rate",
        "distractor_2": "taxonomy",
        "distractor_3": "yield"
      },
      {
        "id": "4235",
        "question": "What is the term for baby fish produced when fish eggs hatch after spawning?",
        "answer": "fry",
        "distractor_1": "milt",
        "distractor_2": "roe",
        "distractor_3": "fingerlings"
      },
      {
        "id": "4236",
        "question": "When new goldfish are purchased, how long should you isolate them from other fish to be sure they are free of disease and parasites?",
        "answer": "10-14 days",
        "distractor_1": "24 hours",
        "distractor_2": "5-10 days",
        "distractor_3": "3 weeks"
      },
      {
        "id": "4237",
        "question": "At 70ºF, quarter-pound channel catfish are fed 2.7 percent of their body weight daily. There are 20,000 pounds of catfish in a pond. How many pounds of food per day should they be fed?",
        "answer": "540 lb/day",
        "distractor_1": "135 lb/day",
        "distractor_2": "250 lb/day",
        "distractor_3": "5,000 lb/day"
      },
      {
        "id": "4238",
        "question": "In the United States, what is the major type of crustacean cultured and sold commercially?",
        "answer": "crawfish",
        "distractor_1": "shrimp",
        "distractor_2": "crab",
        "distractor_3": "lobster"
      },
      {
        "id": "4239",
        "question": "Which of the following is an example of a warm-water fish species?",
        "answer": "catfish",
        "distractor_1": "salmon",
        "distractor_2": "rainbow trout",
        "distractor_3": "hybrid striped bass"
      },
      {
        "id": "4240",
        "question": "Keeping accurate records of fish growth rates would be least helpful in answering which type of question",
        "answer": "cause of fish illness",
        "distractor_1": "maximum stocking density",
        "distractor_2": "amount of food needed",
        "distractor_3": "approximate time for fish harvest"
      },
      {
        "id": "4241",
        "question": "Which of the following is a unique characteristic of fish?",
        "answer": "lateral line",
        "distractor_1": "nerve cord",
        "distractor_2": "vertebral column",
        "distractor_3": "fins"
      },
      {
        "id": "4242",
        "question": "What are the two major factors that typically limit goldfish growth rates?",
        "answer": "temperature; amount of food",
        "distractor_1": "pH; stocking rate",
        "distractor_2": "temperature; toxic chemicals",
        "distractor_3": "dissolved oxygen; amount of food"
      },
      {
        "id": "4243",
        "question": "Keeping records on physical and chemical factors in an aquaculture tank will be most helpful in answering which type of question?",
        "answer": "cause of fish illness",
        "distractor_1": "amount of food needed",
        "distractor_2": "fish growth rate",
        "distractor_3": "fish species tolerance levels"
      },
      {
        "id": "4244",
        "question": "If the dissolved oxygen concentration in a stream is 10 parts per million (ppm), the stream contains what percentage of oxygen? (Hint: Remember that percentage = parts per hundred.)",
        "answer": "0.001% (one-thousandth of one percent)",
        "distractor_1": "1% (one percent)",
        "distractor_2": "0.1% (one-tenth of one percent)",
        "distractor_3": "0.01% (one-hundredth of one percent)"
      },
      {
        "id": "4245",
        "question": "What is the correct order in which fish life cycle stages occur?",
        "answer": "spawn, zygote, fry, fingerling",
        "distractor_1": "zygote, spawn, fingerling, fry",
        "distractor_2": "fry, spawn, fingerling, zygote",
        "distractor_3": "fingerling, fry, spawn, zygote"
      },
      {
        "id": "4246",
        "question": "If stocking rate in an aquaculture operation is increased, what other change would help ensure that fish productivity also increases?",
        "answer": "increased water volume and flow rate",
        "distractor_1": "decreased protein content in food",
        "distractor_2": "decreased dissolved oxygen",
        "distractor_3": "increased temperature"
      },
      {
        "id": "5460",
        "question": "What is the term for the amount of food a fish will eat in one day, or percentage of fish biomass per day?",
        "answer": "feeding rate",
        "distractor_1": "stocking rate",
        "distractor_2": "yield",
        "distractor_3": "spawning"
      },
      {
        "id": "5461",
        "question": "What is the proportion of food consumed to weight gained?",
        "answer": "feed conversion ratio",
        "distractor_1": "yield",
        "distractor_2": "stocking rate",
        "distractor_3": "metabolic rate"
      },
      {
        "id": "5462",
        "question": "What is the term for the productivity, or mass of fish produced per unit space per unit time?",
        "answer": "yield",
        "distractor_1": "milt",
        "distractor_2": "roe",
        "distractor_3": "feed conversion ratio"
      },
      {
        "id": "5463",
        "question": "What is a biological resource that can be harvested indefinitely because it is continually replenished by reproduction?",
        "answer": "renewable resource",
        "distractor_1": "non-renewable resource",
        "distractor_2": "limited resource",
        "distractor_3": "buffer"
      },
      {
        "id": "5465",
        "question": "What is another term for fish eggs, or spawn?",
        "answer": "roe",
        "distractor_1": "milt",
        "distractor_2": "fingerling",
        "distractor_3": "hatchling"
      },
      {
        "id": "5464",
        "question": "What is the term for fish semen containing sperm?",
        "answer": "milt",
        "distractor_1": "roe",
        "distractor_2": "fry",
        "distractor_3": "fingerling"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "144",
    "name": "Horticulture",
    "weight": "85",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8164",
        "question": "The production of one liter of rose oil, used to make perfume, requires the blooms of 100,000 roses. How much rose oil does a single rose produce?",
        "answer": "0.01 (one one-hundredth) ml",
        "distractor_1": "0.000001 (one one-millionth) ml",
        "distractor_2": "0.0001 (one ten-thousandth) ml",
        "distractor_3": "0.001 (one one-thousandth) ml"
      },
      {
        "id": "4247",
        "question": "What are the three major plant organs?",
        "answer": "root, stem, and leaf",
        "distractor_1": "xylem, phloem, and meristem",
        "distractor_2": "ovary, style, and stigma",
        "distractor_3": "seed, fruit, and pollen"
      },
      {
        "id": "4248",
        "question": "What type of tissue transports water and dissolved substances through a plant?",
        "answer": "xylem",
        "distractor_1": "phloem",
        "distractor_2": "cambium",
        "distractor_3": "pith"
      },
      {
        "id": "4250",
        "question": "The gametophyte generation is dominant in which major plant group?",
        "answer": "mosses",
        "distractor_1": "ferns",
        "distractor_2": "flowering plants",
        "distractor_3": "coniferous plants"
      },
      {
        "id": "4251",
        "question": "What term describes a flower having both male and female reproductive structures?",
        "answer": "perfect",
        "distractor_1": "imperfect",
        "distractor_2": "dioecious",
        "distractor_3": "monoecious"
      },
      {
        "id": "4252",
        "question": "For what purpose would a forester use a dichotomous key?",
        "answer": "to identify trees by species or type",
        "distractor_1": "to determine correct names for tree structures",
        "distractor_2": "to better understand forest processes",
        "distractor_3": "to locate trees of a specific size for harvesting"
      },
      {
        "id": "4253",
        "question": "Which three essential nutrients do plants require in the largest amounts?",
        "answer": "nitrogen, phosphorus, and potassium",
        "distractor_1": "nitrogen, carbon, and sulfur",
        "distractor_2": "calcium, magnesium, and sulfur",
        "distractor_3": "calcium, potassium, and magnesium"
      },
      {
        "id": "8165",
        "question": "Egg and sperm cells are formed during which stage of a plant's life cycle?",
        "answer": "gametophyte",
        "distractor_1": "sporophyte",
        "distractor_2": "zygophyte",
        "distractor_3": "epiphyte"
      },
      {
        "id": "8166",
        "question": "Which of the following is an adaptation that helps plants retain water in dry environments?",
        "answer": "waxy cuticles on leaves",
        "distractor_1": "many stomata on leaves",
        "distractor_2": "large, flat leaves",
        "distractor_3": "roots that rise aboveground"
      },
      {
        "id": "4254",
        "question": "Sexual reproduction in plants is important because it produces which of the following?",
        "answer": "genetic variation",
        "distractor_1": "exact duplicates",
        "distractor_2": "cultivars",
        "distractor_3": "hybrids"
      },
      {
        "id": "4255",
        "question": "Which of the following tissues transport water and nutrients from the soil in an upward direction toward a plant's stems and leaves?",
        "answer": "xylem",
        "distractor_1": "cotyledons",
        "distractor_2": "phloem",
        "distractor_3": "sepals"
      },
      {
        "id": "4256",
        "question": "What function does phloem tissue serve in a plant?",
        "answer": "transports sugars down from the leaves",
        "distractor_1": "transports water up from the roots",
        "distractor_2": "stores plant food as starch",
        "distractor_3": "serves as a site of new plant growth"
      },
      {
        "id": "4257",
        "question": "Which description fits the process of grafting?",
        "answer": "One plant provides a root system; a second provides the stem and leaves.",
        "distractor_1": "A stem is wounded and attached to soil, where roots form.",
        "distractor_2": "A large clump of plants is split into two clumps.",
        "distractor_3": "A stem is cut below a leaf node and treated to form roots."
      },
      {
        "id": "4258",
        "question": "How does horticulture differ from forestry or agriculture in its treatment of individual plants?",
        "answer": "Each plant is individually tended and sold.",
        "distractor_1": "Each plant is grown in a relatively large area.",
        "distractor_2": "Each plant is sold for a relatively low price.",
        "distractor_3": "Each plant requires relatively little labor input."
      },
      {
        "id": "4259",
        "question": "Which part of the plant life cycle dominates in ferns, conifers, and flowering plants?",
        "answer": "sporophyte",
        "distractor_1": "annual",
        "distractor_2": "perennial",
        "distractor_3": "gametophyte"
      },
      {
        "id": "4260",
        "question": "Which form of vegetative propagation is used to produce large quantities of identical offspring under sterile conditions?",
        "answer": "micropropagation",
        "distractor_1": "layering",
        "distractor_2": "cuttings",
        "distractor_3": "grafting"
      },
      {
        "id": "4261",
        "question": "Which of the following businesses would NOT be considered a part of horticulture?",
        "answer": "timber harvesting company",
        "distractor_1": "florist shop",
        "distractor_2": "gardening supply store",
        "distractor_3": "landscaping business"
      },
      {
        "id": "4262",
        "question": "A giant saguaro cactus is 250 years old and 50 feet tall. If it has grown at the same rate throughout its life, how many inches per year has it grown?",
        "answer": "2.4 inches",
        "distractor_1": "0.2 inches",
        "distractor_2": "0.4 inches",
        "distractor_3": "5.0 inches"
      },
      {
        "id": "4263",
        "question": "The earliest plant fossils date from the Silurian period, 420 million years ago. The earliest flowering plants appeared 120 million years ago. Approximately how long did it take for flowering plants to evolve?",
        "answer": "300 million years",
        "distractor_1": "540 million years",
        "distractor_2": "420 million years",
        "distractor_3": "120 million years"
      },
      {
        "id": "4264",
        "question": "The root, stem, and leaf of a plant are similar to which type of animal structures?",
        "answer": "organs",
        "distractor_1": "cells",
        "distractor_2": "tissues",
        "distractor_3": "organ systems"
      },
      {
        "id": "4265",
        "question": "Which three elements are plant macronutrients needed in only moderate amounts?",
        "answer": "calcium, magnesium, and sulfur",
        "distractor_1": "nitrogen, carbon, and sulfur",
        "distractor_2": "nitrogen, phosphorus, and potassium",
        "distractor_3": "calcium, potassium, and magnesium"
      },
      {
        "id": "4266",
        "question": "What two structures must a perfect flower contain?",
        "answer": "carpels and stamens",
        "distractor_1": "calyx and corolla",
        "distractor_2": "carpels and pistil",
        "distractor_3": "filaments and anthers"
      },
      {
        "id": "4267",
        "question": "Which of the following aids would a forester use to identify tree species in the field?",
        "answer": "dichotomous key",
        "distractor_1": "field experiment",
        "distractor_2": "binoculars",
        "distractor_3": "photography"
      },
      {
        "id": "4268",
        "question": "Which of the following conditions is NOT required for seed germination?",
        "answer": "light",
        "distractor_1": "warm or moderate temperature",
        "distractor_2": "oxygen",
        "distractor_3": "moisture"
      },
      {
        "id": "4269",
        "question": "The world's largest plant, the giant sequoia, grows to 310 feet. The smallest plant, the duckweed, is 0.01 inch long. How many times larger is the sequoia than the duckweed?",
        "answer": "372,000 times",
        "distractor_1": "310 times",
        "distractor_2": "3,720 times",
        "distractor_3": "31,000 times"
      },
      {
        "id": "4271",
        "question": "Scaling and chipping are vegetative propagation methods used to reproduce what type of plants?",
        "answer": "bulbs",
        "distractor_1": "trees and shrubs",
        "distractor_2": "climbing plants",
        "distractor_3": "succulents"
      },
      {
        "id": "4273",
        "question": "Genetic variation in plants is produced by which process?",
        "answer": "sexual reproduction",
        "distractor_1": "germination",
        "distractor_2": "self-pollination",
        "distractor_3": "micropropagation"
      },
      {
        "id": "4274",
        "question": "What three conditions are required for seed germination?",
        "answer": "oxygen, moisture, and warm temperature",
        "distractor_1": "nutrients, moisture, and oxygen",
        "distractor_2": "nutrients, light, and warm temperature",
        "distractor_3": "oxygen, moisture, and light"
      },
      {
        "id": "6625",
        "question": "What branch of agriculture involves garden and ornamental plants?",
        "answer": "horticulture",
        "distractor_1": "forestry",
        "distractor_2": "topography",
        "distractor_3": "decorative seeding"
      },
      {
        "id": "6626",
        "question": "What is asexual reproduction of plants?",
        "answer": "vegetative propagation",
        "distractor_1": "regeneration",
        "distractor_2": "pollination",
        "distractor_3": "germination"
      },
      {
        "id": "6627",
        "question": "What is the growth of plants in a non-soil medium?",
        "answer": "hydroponics",
        "distractor_1": "dry farming",
        "distractor_2": "horticulture",
        "distractor_3": "water transplanting"
      },
      {
        "id": "6628",
        "question": "What plant structure contains the egg cell?",
        "answer": "ovule",
        "distractor_1": "seed",
        "distractor_2": "meristem",
        "distractor_3": "stamen"
      },
      {
        "id": "6629",
        "question": "What plant structure contains the sperm cell?",
        "answer": "pollen grain",
        "distractor_1": "meristem",
        "distractor_2": "stamen",
        "distractor_3": "carpel"
      },
      {
        "id": "6630",
        "question": "What term describes the beginning of plant growth from a seed?",
        "answer": "germination",
        "distractor_1": "pollination",
        "distractor_2": "hydroponics",
        "distractor_3": "vegetative propagation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6631",
        "question": "What structure contains a plant embryo formed by sexual reproduction?",
        "answer": "seed",
        "distractor_1": "meristem",
        "distractor_2": "stamen",
        "distractor_3": "carpel"
      },
      {
        "id": "6632",
        "question": "What region of plant tissue does new growth occurs?",
        "answer": "meristem",
        "distractor_1": "seed",
        "distractor_2": "pollen grain",
        "distractor_3": "ovule"
      },
      {
        "id": "6633",
        "question": "What is the male reproductive organ of a plant?",
        "answer": "stamen",
        "distractor_1": "meristem",
        "distractor_2": "ovule",
        "distractor_3": "carpel"
      },
      {
        "id": "6634",
        "question": "What is the female reproductive organ of a plant?",
        "answer": "carpel",
        "distractor_1": "stamen",
        "distractor_2": "meristem",
        "distractor_3": "ovule"
      },
      {
        "id": "6635",
        "question": "What is the term for a cultivated variety of a plant species?",
        "answer": "cultivar",
        "distractor_1": "hybrid",
        "distractor_2": "vegetative propagation",
        "distractor_3": "specialized"
      },
      {
        "id": "6636",
        "question": "What plant type is produced by crossing two genetic strains?",
        "answer": "hybrid",
        "distractor_1": "cultivar",
        "distractor_2": "perennial",
        "distractor_3": "biennial"
      },
      {
        "id": "6637",
        "question": "What is a broad-leaved deciduous tree, such as oak?",
        "answer": "hardwood",
        "distractor_1": "softwood",
        "distractor_2": "redwood",
        "distractor_3": "leafwood"
      },
      {
        "id": "6638",
        "question": "What is a coniferous evergreen tree, such as pine?",
        "answer": "softwood",
        "distractor_1": "hardwood",
        "distractor_2": "redwood",
        "distractor_3": "pinewood"
      },
      {
        "id": "6639",
        "question": "What type of plant species lives three or more years?",
        "answer": "perennial",
        "distractor_1": "annual",
        "distractor_2": "biennial",
        "distractor_3": "long term"
      },
      {
        "id": "6640",
        "question": "What type of plant species has a life cycle lasting two years?",
        "answer": "biennial",
        "distractor_1": "perennial",
        "distractor_2": "annual",
        "distractor_3": "fading cycle"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "0",
    "name": "Module Orientation",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "6866",
        "question": "Who publishes the 'Occupational Outlook Handbook'?",
        "answer": "JIST Works",
        "distractor_1": "Bureau of Labor Statistics",
        "distractor_2": "Glencoe McGraw-Hill",
        "distractor_3": "Reader's Digest"
      },
      {
        "id": "4325",
        "question": "In which session(s) is the Post Test completed?",
        "answer": "Session 7 ",
        "distractor_1": "Sessions 2-5",
        "distractor_2": "Session 6",
        "distractor_3": "Session 1"
      },
      {
        "id": "4326",
        "question": "In which session(s) is the Module Guide completed?",
        "answer": "Session 1",
        "distractor_1": "Sessions 2-5",
        "distractor_2": "Session 6",
        "distractor_3": "Session 7"
      },
      {
        "id": "4327",
        "question": "Module activities are performed in what area?",
        "answer": "workstation",
        "distractor_1": "hall ",
        "distractor_2": "seating",
        "distractor_3": "lecture"
      },
      {
        "id": "4328",
        "question": "What activities are typically completed after finishing a session?",
        "answer": "enrichments",
        "distractor_1": "RCAs",
        "distractor_2": "Module Guide",
        "distractor_3": "Post Test"
      },
      {
        "id": "4329",
        "question": "Answering an RCA question correctly on the first attempt is worth how many points?",
        "answer": "10",
        "distractor_1": "5",
        "distractor_2": "30",
        "distractor_3": "120"
      },
      {
        "id": "4330",
        "question": "Answering an RCA question correctly on the second attempt is worth how many points?",
        "answer": "5",
        "distractor_1": "10",
        "distractor_2": "30",
        "distractor_3": "120"
      },
      {
        "id": "4331",
        "question": "RCA is the acronym for which of the following?",
        "answer": "Research, Challenge, and Application",
        "distractor_1": "Resource, Challenge, and Application",
        "distractor_2": "Research, Chart, and Application ",
        "distractor_3": "Research, Challenge, and Approximation"
      },
      {
        "id": "4332",
        "question": "What term refers to the time spent learning the information in one Module and is made up of seven sessions or class periods?",
        "answer": "rotation",
        "distractor_1": "session ",
        "distractor_2": "application",
        "distractor_3": "semester"
      },
      {
        "id": "4334",
        "question": "What term refers to seven sessions of engaging activities designed to teach concepts related to a specific topic?",
        "answer": "Module",
        "distractor_1": "application",
        "distractor_2": "session ",
        "distractor_3": "semester"
      },
      {
        "id": "4335",
        "question": "What term is defined as the act of working together toward a common end or purpose?",
        "answer": "cooperation",
        "distractor_1": "partnership",
        "distractor_2": "orientation",
        "distractor_3": "goal"
      },
      {
        "id": "4336",
        "question": "What term is defined as introductory instruction concerning a new situation?",
        "answer": "orientation",
        "distractor_1": "performance ",
        "distractor_2": "goal",
        "distractor_3": "cooperation"
      },
      {
        "id": "4337",
        "question": "What term is defined as the interaction of two or more forces so that their combined effect is greater than the sum of their individual effects?",
        "answer": "synergy",
        "distractor_1": "goal",
        "distractor_2": "performance",
        "distractor_3": "cooperation"
      },
      {
        "id": "4338",
        "question": "What activity is completed at the beginning of Session 1?",
        "answer": "Module Guide",
        "distractor_1": "Research, Challenge, and Application",
        "distractor_2": "Test Review",
        "distractor_3": "Post Test"
      },
      {
        "id": "4339",
        "question": "What activity is completed at the beginning of Session 7?",
        "answer": "Post Test",
        "distractor_1": "Research, Challenge, and Application",
        "distractor_2": "Test Review",
        "distractor_3": "Module Guide "
      },
      {
        "id": "4346",
        "question": "What activity takes about 45 minutes to complete and covers a group of closely related ideas that are explained in a series of pages?",
        "answer": "session",
        "distractor_1": "Module",
        "distractor_2": "rotation",
        "distractor_3": "application "
      },
      {
        "id": "6873",
        "question": "This term is defined as a movable window used whenever third-party software instructions are given.",
        "answer": "Agent",
        "distractor_1": "Coach",
        "distractor_2": "Windows",
        "distractor_3": "Explorer"
      },
      {
        "id": "6869",
        "question": "What term is defined as a group of elements or parts that interact to form a complex whole?",
        "answer": "system",
        "distractor_1": "cooperation",
        "distractor_2": "performance",
        "distractor_3": "partnership"
      },
      {
        "id": "6870",
        "question": "What term is defined as an interactive competition completed during Session 6 in order to review Module Guide questions and Module-specific vocabulary words?",
        "answer": "Test Review",
        "distractor_1": "Module Guide",
        "distractor_2": "Post Test",
        "distractor_3": "Enrichments"
      },
      {
        "id": "6871",
        "question": "What term is defined as a consequence taken for misbehavior in a Module lab?",
        "answer": "personal step",
        "distractor_1": "demerit",
        "distractor_2": "blemish",
        "distractor_3": "virus"
      },
      {
        "id": "6872",
        "question": "This term is defined as a folder specially designed for students in a Module lab used to record personal information and store Module documents.",
        "answer": "student portfolio",
        "distractor_1": "grade book",
        "distractor_2": "Student Module Notebook",
        "distractor_3": "Module Guide"
      },
      {
        "id": "6874",
        "question": "This term is defined as a Module feature that offers additional hints on a page in addition to the instructions already presented.",
        "answer": "Student Tip",
        "distractor_1": "Bonus round",
        "distractor_2": "Test Review",
        "distractor_3": "Freebies"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "146",
    "name": "Forensic Science",
    "weight": "85",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8263",
        "question": "What is DNA fingerprinting?",
        "answer": "the process of isolating and analyzing unique areas along a strand of DNA",
        "distractor_1": "the separation of chemical compounds into molecular components",
        "distractor_2": "the collection of hair, fibers dust particles, sand, dirt, and residue from substances",
        "distractor_3": "manipulating DNA to fit a particular pattern "
      },
      {
        "id": "4493",
        "question": "What is forensic science?",
        "answer": "the application of science to law",
        "distractor_1": "the application of reasoning to law",
        "distractor_2": "the application of evidence to law",
        "distractor_3": "the application of testing to law"
      },
      {
        "id": "4494",
        "question": "What principle states that with contact comes the exchange of material?",
        "answer": "Locard’s Exchange Principle",
        "distractor_1": "Grissom’s Exchange Principle",
        "distractor_2": "Faulds' Exchange Principle",
        "distractor_3": "Henry’s Exchange Principle"
      },
      {
        "id": "5990",
        "question": "If a scale of 1/4' = 1' is used in creating a scaled drawing, what is the length of a line representing an 8' long wall?",
        "answer": "2'",
        "distractor_1": "8'",
        "distractor_2": "4'",
        "distractor_3": "1/2'"
      },
      {
        "id": "5991",
        "question": "A classroom is vandalized. The room is 16' 6' x 24' 6'. What is the crime scene's total area in square feet?",
        "answer": "406.7",
        "distractor_1": "408.36",
        "distractor_2": "404.25",
        "distractor_3": "405.9"
      },
      {
        "id": "5992",
        "question": "If a scale of 1/4' = 1' is used in creating a scaled drawing, what is the length of a line representing a wall that is 12' long?",
        "answer": "3'",
        "distractor_1": "4'",
        "distractor_2": "2'",
        "distractor_3": "1/2'"
      },
      {
        "id": "5994",
        "question": "In a scaled crime scene drawing, a piece of evidence is drawn 4' from a fixed reference point. If the scale is 1/8' = 1', what is the actual distance between the evidence and the fixed point?",
        "answer": "32'",
        "distractor_1": "2'",
        "distractor_2": "1/2'",
        "distractor_3": "4'"
      },
      {
        "id": "5995",
        "question": "In a scaled crime scene drawing, a piece of evidence is drawn 4.25' from a fixed reference point. If the scale is 1/8' = 1', what is the actual distance between the evidence and the fixed point?",
        "answer": "34'",
        "distractor_1": "53'",
        "distractor_2": "0.5'",
        "distractor_3": "32.25'"
      },
      {
        "id": "4503",
        "question": "Loop, whorl, and arch are examples of what?",
        "answer": "friction ridge patterns",
        "distractor_1": "ridge-type minutiae",
        "distractor_2": "friction furrow patterns",
        "distractor_3": "furrow-type minutiae"
      },
      {
        "id": "4504",
        "question": "Bifurcation is one type of what?",
        "answer": "ridge-type minutiae",
        "distractor_1": "friction ridge patterns",
        "distractor_2": "friction furrow patterns",
        "distractor_3": "furrow-type minutiae"
      },
      {
        "id": "4505",
        "question": "What is the first step in obtaining a DNA fingerprint?",
        "answer": "DNA extraction",
        "distractor_1": "DNA sequencing",
        "distractor_2": "DNA amplification",
        "distractor_3": "DNA electrophoresis"
      },
      {
        "id": "4506",
        "question": "Which of the following scale patterns is typical of cat hair?",
        "answer": "spinous",
        "distractor_1": "imbricate",
        "distractor_2": "flattened",
        "distractor_3": "coronal"
      },
      {
        "id": "4507",
        "question": "A table is represented in a scaled drawing by a rectangle that is 0.5' x 1.25'. If the scale of the drawing is 1/4' = 1', what are the dimensions of the table?",
        "answer": "2' x 5'",
        "distractor_1": "5' x 15'",
        "distractor_2": "0.125' x 0.337'",
        "distractor_3": "20' x 60'"
      },
      {
        "id": "4508",
        "question": "Three percent of the population has the blood type AB. If there are 487 students in Running Well High School, how many of those students have Type AB blood? Round to the nearest whole student.",
        "answer": "15",
        "distractor_1": "162",
        "distractor_2": "146",
        "distractor_3": "14"
      },
      {
        "id": "4510",
        "question": "A sample of extracted DNA weighs 0.02 grams. The sample is 33% sugar. How many grams of sugar are in the sample?",
        "answer": "0.0066",
        "distractor_1": "0.06",
        "distractor_2": "0.006",
        "distractor_3": "0.067"
      },
      {
        "id": "4512",
        "question": "Locard's Exchange Principle states what?",
        "answer": "When objects come into contact, material is exchanged.",
        "distractor_1": "When objects touch, trace evidence is ruined.",
        "distractor_2": "When objects touch, fingerprints are left behind.",
        "distractor_3": "When objects come into contact with each other, they get broken."
      },
      {
        "id": "4514",
        "question": "What is DNA?",
        "answer": "deoxyribonucleic acid",
        "distractor_1": "deoxyribose nuclear additive",
        "distractor_2": "deoxyribose nucleus arrangement",
        "distractor_3": "deoxyribonucleic agarose"
      },
      {
        "id": "4515",
        "question": "Which of the following identifying traits can be categorized as having loops, whorls, or arches?",
        "answer": "fingerprints",
        "distractor_1": "DNA",
        "distractor_2": "blood",
        "distractor_3": "hair"
      },
      {
        "id": "4516",
        "question": "Separation of chemical compounds into molecular components is a result of what process?",
        "answer": "chromatography",
        "distractor_1": "sublimation",
        "distractor_2": "photography",
        "distractor_3": "osmosis"
      },
      {
        "id": "4520",
        "question": "Hair strands, clothing threads, carpet fibers, dust, and powders are all examples of what type of evidence?",
        "answer": "trace",
        "distractor_1": "transient",
        "distractor_2": "liquid",
        "distractor_3": "biological"
      },
      {
        "id": "6439",
        "question": "What is the application of scientific knowledge to legal problems?",
        "answer": "forensic science",
        "distractor_1": "legal science",
        "distractor_2": "the scientific method",
        "distractor_3": "justice science"
      },
      {
        "id": "6440",
        "question": "What is the term for the loop, whorl, and arch of finger prints?",
        "answer": "friction ridge patterns",
        "distractor_1": "ridge-type minutiae",
        "distractor_2": "identifying design",
        "distractor_3": "composition pattern"
      },
      {
        "id": "6441",
        "question": "What is the term for bifurcation, dot, island, and lake of fingerprints?",
        "answer": "ridge-type minutiae",
        "distractor_1": "friction ridge patterns",
        "distractor_2": "fingerprint error",
        "distractor_3": "identifying features"
      },
      {
        "id": "6442",
        "question": "What method of identification is done by determining the sequence of base pairs in the DNA of a person?",
        "answer": "DNA fingerprinting",
        "distractor_1": "DNA testing",
        "distractor_2": "chromosome matching",
        "distractor_3": "DNA examination"
      },
      {
        "id": "6443",
        "question": "What is the term for something that furnishes proof?",
        "answer": "evidence",
        "distractor_1": "DNA",
        "distractor_2": "trace",
        "distractor_3": "witness"
      },
      {
        "id": "6444",
        "question": "What are segments of DNA within the chromosomes of a cell that determine inheritance and expression of a trait?",
        "answer": "genes",
        "distractor_1": "genetic code",
        "distractor_2": "trait code",
        "distractor_3": "DNA sequence"
      },
      {
        "id": "6445",
        "question": "What is the structure in the nucleus that contains DNA?",
        "answer": "chromosome",
        "distractor_1": "genes",
        "distractor_2": "protein strands",
        "distractor_3": "deoxyribonucleic acid"
      },
      {
        "id": "7793",
        "question": "What is a large double-helix molecule present in living organisms? ",
        "answer": "deoxyribonucleic acid",
        "distractor_1": "gene",
        "distractor_2": "chromosome",
        "distractor_3": "molecule"
      },
      {
        "id": "7794",
        "question": "What is the process that separates substances into individual chemical components?",
        "answer": "chromatography ",
        "distractor_1": "chemisorption",
        "distractor_2": "chromatograph",
        "distractor_3": "absorptiometry"
      },
      {
        "id": "7795",
        "question": "What is defined as the application of science to law?",
        "answer": "forensic science",
        "distractor_1": "biology",
        "distractor_2": "crime scene investigation",
        "distractor_3": "forensic evidence"
      },
      {
        "id": "7796",
        "question": "A pattern of lines, or ridges, along the tips of your fingers is known as which of the following?",
        "answer": "friction ridge pattern",
        "distractor_1": "ridge-type minutiae",
        "distractor_2": "bifurcated patterns",
        "distractor_3": "ridge-end minutiae"
      },
      {
        "id": "7797",
        "question": "What are traits used to classify tiny fingerprint patterns such as lakes, islands, and bridges?",
        "answer": "ridge-type minutiae",
        "distractor_1": "friction ridge patterns",
        "distractor_2": "radial loop minutiae",
        "distractor_3": "tented-arch patterns"
      },
      {
        "id": "7798",
        "question": "What is known as isolating and analyzing DNA to discover distinctions between individuals?",
        "answer": "DNA fingerprinting",
        "distractor_1": "DNA mapping",
        "distractor_2": "DNA amplification",
        "distractor_3": "DNA extraction"
      },
      {
        "id": "7799",
        "question": "What are items such as liquid, hair, and fingerprints at a crime scene that may help identify suspects?",
        "answer": "evidence ",
        "distractor_1": "indirect evidence",
        "distractor_2": "traces",
        "distractor_3": "clues"
      },
      {
        "id": "7800",
        "question": "What gives the cell instructions on how to make one protein?",
        "answer": "gene",
        "distractor_1": "chromosome",
        "distractor_2": "deoxyribonucleic acid",
        "distractor_3": "molecule"
      },
      {
        "id": "7801",
        "question": "What is formed by one molecule of DNA?",
        "answer": "chromosome ",
        "distractor_1": "deoxyribonucleic acid",
        "distractor_2": "gene",
        "distractor_3": "molecule"
      },
      {
        "id": "7802",
        "question": "What is defined as small evidence at a crime scene such as hair, fibers, dust, sand, and dirt?",
        "answer": "trace evidence",
        "distractor_1": "transient evidence",
        "distractor_2": "liquid evidence",
        "distractor_3": "wet evidence"
      },
      {
        "id": "8324",
        "question": "Which of the following identifying traits would not be the same in identical twins?",
        "answer": "fingerprints",
        "distractor_1": "DNA fingerprints",
        "distractor_2": "natural eye color",
        "distractor_3": "natural hair color"
      },
      {
        "id": "8325",
        "question": "What is the process of isolating and analyzing unique areas along a strand of DNA?",
        "answer": "DNA fingerprinting",
        "distractor_1": "DNA extraction",
        "distractor_2": "chromatography analysis",
        "distractor_3": "trace analysis"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "147",
    "name": "Natural Disasters",
    "weight": "85",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "4742",
        "question": "Which of the following is a constructive geological process?",
        "answer": "volcanic activity",
        "distractor_1": "erosion",
        "distractor_2": "weathering",
        "distractor_3": "topography"
      },
      {
        "id": "4743",
        "question": "What theory describes the process by which Earth’s crust floats on the semi-molten mantle?",
        "answer": "theory of plate tectonics",
        "distractor_1": "theory of seismicity",
        "distractor_2": "plate boundary theory",
        "distractor_3": "strike-slip fault theory"
      },
      {
        "id": "4744",
        "question": "What area is considered to be the hottest place in the United States and possibly in the world?",
        "answer": "Death Valley, California",
        "distractor_1": "Key West, Florida",
        "distractor_2": "Honolulu, Hawaii",
        "distractor_3": "Rio Grande Valley, Texas"
      },
      {
        "id": "4745",
        "question": "The theory of plate tectonics best explains which of the following?",
        "answer": "how and why individual plates on Earth’s crust remain in motion",
        "distractor_1": "what keeps individual plates on Earth’s crust from moving",
        "distractor_2": "causes of destructive geological processes on Earth’s surface",
        "distractor_3": "location and magnitude of upcoming earthquakes and volcanoes"
      },
      {
        "id": "4746",
        "question": "People in which agency are NOT part of the field of disaster risk management?",
        "answer": "National Weather Service",
        "distractor_1": "Red Cross",
        "distractor_2": "FEMA",
        "distractor_3": "local police, fire, and rescue units"
      },
      {
        "id": "4747",
        "question": "Of the following types of storms, which has the strongest winds?",
        "answer": "tornado",
        "distractor_1": "hurricane",
        "distractor_2": "dust devil",
        "distractor_3": "typhoon"
      },
      {
        "id": "4748",
        "question": "Which federal agency is in charge of providing assistance to the public after a natural disaster?",
        "answer": "FEMA",
        "distractor_1": "EPA",
        "distractor_2": "Red Cross",
        "distractor_3": "National Guard"
      },
      {
        "id": "4749",
        "question": "In which region of Earth is a tornado most likely to occur?",
        "answer": "Midwest United States",
        "distractor_1": "Mexico",
        "distractor_2": "Central Asia",
        "distractor_3": "Europe"
      },
      {
        "id": "4750",
        "question": "A hurricane frequently produces which of the following types of floods?",
        "answer": "storm surge",
        "distractor_1": "tsunami",
        "distractor_2": "regional flood",
        "distractor_3": "flash flood"
      },
      {
        "id": "4751",
        "question": "Most earthquakes occur at which type of geological location?",
        "answer": "at the boundaries of moving tectonic plates",
        "distractor_1": "in the centers of tectonic plates",
        "distractor_2": "at the boundaries of stationary tectonic plates",
        "distractor_3": "in Earth’s core, far below the crust"
      },
      {
        "id": "4752",
        "question": "A tsunami is triggered by which of the following processes?",
        "answer": "undersea earthquakes",
        "distractor_1": "surface winds",
        "distractor_2": "tidal waves",
        "distractor_3": "hurricanes"
      },
      {
        "id": "4753",
        "question": "What is the most common type of natural disaster in the U.S.?",
        "answer": "flood",
        "distractor_1": "earthquake",
        "distractor_2": "hurricane",
        "distractor_3": "tornado"
      },
      {
        "id": "4754",
        "question": "Tiltmeters and creep meters are instruments used to measure which of the following?",
        "answer": "degree of horizontal or vertical movement along a fault line",
        "distractor_1": "rate of movement of a landslide",
        "distractor_2": "rate of erosion on a slope",
        "distractor_3": "degree of horizontal or vertical movement of lava from a volcano"
      },
      {
        "id": "4755",
        "question": "Which scale relates the wind speed of a hurricane to the amount of damage it causes?",
        "answer": "Saffir-Simpson scale",
        "distractor_1": "Richter scale",
        "distractor_2": "Fujita-Pearson scale",
        "distractor_3": "Modified Mercalli scale"
      },
      {
        "id": "4756",
        "question": "A tropical storm is officially classified as a hurricane when it reaches which wind speed?",
        "answer": "74 miles per hour",
        "distractor_1": "23 miles per hour",
        "distractor_2": "40 miles per hour",
        "distractor_3": "98 miles per hour"
      },
      {
        "id": "4757",
        "question": "In an earthquake, which type or types of seismic waves are most destructive?",
        "answer": "large waves",
        "distractor_1": "primary waves",
        "distractor_2": "secondary waves",
        "distractor_3": "All types are about equally destructive."
      },
      {
        "id": "4758",
        "question": "Which scale is used to measure the amount of damage caused by an earthquake?",
        "answer": "Modified Mercalli scale",
        "distractor_1": "Richter scale",
        "distractor_2": "Fujita-Pearson scale",
        "distractor_3": "Saffir-Simpson scale"
      },
      {
        "id": "4759",
        "question": "Where in the U.S. is a hurricane most likely to occur?",
        "answer": "Gulf Coast",
        "distractor_1": "West Coast",
        "distractor_2": "Midwest",
        "distractor_3": "Northeast Coast"
      },
      {
        "id": "4760",
        "question": "In an earthquake, which type or types of seismic waves travel over Earth’s surface?",
        "answer": "large waves only",
        "distractor_1": "all three wave types",
        "distractor_2": "primary and secondary waves only",
        "distractor_3": "primary waves only"
      },
      {
        "id": "4761",
        "question": "How does the wave height of a tsunami near shore compare with its wave height in the open ocean?",
        "answer": "It is low in the open ocean and high near shore.",
        "distractor_1": "It is high in both places.",
        "distractor_2": "It is low in both places.",
        "distractor_3": "It is high in the open ocean and low near shore."
      },
      {
        "id": "4762",
        "question": "Which of the following is a destructive geological process?",
        "answer": "weathering",
        "distractor_1": "volcanic activity",
        "distractor_2": "earthquake",
        "distractor_3": "mountain-building"
      },
      {
        "id": "4763",
        "question": "Near-surface earthquakes occur at which type or types of plate boundaries?",
        "answer": "transform fault boundaries, where one plate slides over another",
        "distractor_1": "divergent boundaries, or spreading zones",
        "distractor_2": "convergent boundaries, or subduction zones",
        "distractor_3": "both divergent and convergent boundaries"
      },
      {
        "id": "4764",
        "question": "Which of the following disasters has the lowest probability of causing fatalities in the U.S.?",
        "answer": "tsunami",
        "distractor_1": "earthquake",
        "distractor_2": "flood",
        "distractor_3": "tornado"
      },
      {
        "id": "4816",
        "question": "Based on the amount of ash emitted, which of the following is the largest recorded volcanic eruption?",
        "answer": "Tambora, Indonesia, 1815",
        "distractor_1": "Mount St. Helens, Washington, 1980",
        "distractor_2": "Mount Vesuvius, Italy, 79 C.E.",
        "distractor_3": "Krakatoa, Indonesia, 1883"
      },
      {
        "id": "6658",
        "question": "What is a segment of Earth's crust that floats on the semi-molten mantle?",
        "answer": "tectonic plate",
        "distractor_1": "fault",
        "distractor_2": "epicenter",
        "distractor_3": "eyewall"
      },
      {
        "id": "6659",
        "question": "What is a fracture in Earth's crust along which movement has occurred?",
        "answer": "fault",
        "distractor_1": "tectonic plate",
        "distractor_2": "pyroclast",
        "distractor_3": "vortex"
      },
      {
        "id": "6660",
        "question": "What is a region around the Pacific Ocean rim where most of Earth's seismic activity occurs?",
        "answer": "Ring of Fire",
        "distractor_1": "epicenter",
        "distractor_2": "wind field",
        "distractor_3": "eyewall"
      },
      {
        "id": "6661",
        "question": "What is a sudden, rapid vibration of Earth's crust caused by abrupt release of stored energy from Earth's interior?",
        "answer": "earthquake",
        "distractor_1": "volcano",
        "distractor_2": "wave",
        "distractor_3": "jet stream"
      },
      {
        "id": "6662",
        "question": "What is a strong vibration of energy radiating out from an earthquake and traveling on or through Earth's surface?",
        "answer": "seismic wave",
        "distractor_1": "earthquake",
        "distractor_2": "tsunami",
        "distractor_3": "wave"
      },
      {
        "id": "6663",
        "question": "What is a spot on Earth's surface directly above the place where an earthquake originates?",
        "answer": "epicenter",
        "distractor_1": "eye",
        "distractor_2": "eyewall",
        "distractor_3": "vortex"
      },
      {
        "id": "6664",
        "question": "What is an opening in Earth's crust through which gases and molten rock from Earth's mantle escape to the surface?",
        "answer": "volcano",
        "distractor_1": "jet stream",
        "distractor_2": "wave",
        "distractor_3": "pyroclast"
      },
      {
        "id": "6665",
        "question": "What is extremely hot, molten rock inside Earth's mantle?",
        "answer": "magma",
        "distractor_1": "lava",
        "distractor_2": "jet stream",
        "distractor_3": "epicenter"
      },
      {
        "id": "6666",
        "question": "What is extremely hot, molten rock that has been expelled from Earth in a volcano?",
        "answer": "lava",
        "distractor_1": "magma",
        "distractor_2": "jet stream",
        "distractor_3": "seismic wave"
      },
      {
        "id": "6667",
        "question": "What is a solid piece of rock expelled by a volcano?",
        "answer": "pyroclast",
        "distractor_1": "magma",
        "distractor_2": "lava",
        "distractor_3": "viscosity"
      },
      {
        "id": "6668",
        "question": "What is a measure of how thick or thin a fluid is, which determines how freely it flows?",
        "answer": "viscosity",
        "distractor_1": "vortex",
        "distractor_2": "jet stream",
        "distractor_3": "fault"
      },
      {
        "id": "6669",
        "question": "What is a disturbance produced when energy flows through a medium, such as air or water?",
        "answer": "wave",
        "distractor_1": "seismic wave",
        "distractor_2": "eyewall",
        "distractor_3": "fault"
      },
      {
        "id": "6670",
        "question": "What is a rapid spiral or rotation around a centerline, such as that occurring in tornado and hurricane winds?",
        "answer": "vortex",
        "distractor_1": "eye",
        "distractor_2": "eyewall",
        "distractor_3": "epicenter"
      },
      {
        "id": "6671",
        "question": "What is a band of very strong, horizontal winds above the troposphere that affects storm formation?",
        "answer": "jet stream ",
        "distractor_1": "current",
        "distractor_2": "pyroclast",
        "distractor_3": "wind field"
      },
      {
        "id": "6672",
        "question": "What is a pendulum-based instrument used to record earthquake waves?",
        "answer": "seismograph",
        "distractor_1": "pyroclast",
        "distractor_2": "tectonic plate",
        "distractor_3": "seismic wave"
      },
      {
        "id": "6673",
        "question": "What is a circular regions inside a hurricane where winds of specific speeds are found?",
        "answer": "wind field",
        "distractor_1": "eyewall",
        "distractor_2": "jet stream",
        "distractor_3": "fault"
      },
      {
        "id": "6674",
        "question": "What is a calm center of a hurricane or tornado, where no updraft, winds, or clouds are found?",
        "answer": "eye",
        "distractor_1": "eyewall",
        "distractor_2": "epicenter",
        "distractor_3": "wind field"
      },
      {
        "id": "6675",
        "question": "What is a region immediately surrounding the eye of a hurricane, where the strongest winds are found?",
        "answer": "eyewall",
        "distractor_1": "eye",
        "distractor_2": "epicenter",
        "distractor_3": "vortex"
      },
      {
        "id": "6676",
        "question": "What is a likelihood, or chance, that a given event will occur; measured as a ratio, fraction, or percentage?",
        "answer": "probability",
        "distractor_1": "viscosity",
        "distractor_2": "pyroclast",
        "distractor_3": "fault"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "148",
    "name": "Construction Management",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "4787",
        "question": "When companies need a construction project completed, they often release a document to contractors asking for responses. What is this document called?",
        "answer": "request for proposal (RFP)",
        "distractor_1": "request for bid (RFB)",
        "distractor_2": "required formal bid (RFB)",
        "distractor_3": "required formal proposal (RFP)"
      },
      {
        "id": "4788",
        "question": "What type of construction work is completed by general contractors?",
        "answer": "commercial and residential construction, heavy construction, and civil engineering",
        "distractor_1": "residential construction only",
        "distractor_2": "roads, dams, and bridges only",
        "distractor_3": "commercial construction only"
      },
      {
        "id": "4789",
        "question": "What is the area of a 400 ft x 400 ft square plot of land?",
        "answer": "160,000 sq ft",
        "distractor_1": "1,600,000 sq ft",
        "distractor_2": "16,000 sq ft",
        "distractor_3": "1,600 sq ft"
      },
      {
        "id": "4790",
        "question": "What are the dimensions of a scale drawing of a 100 ft x 300 ft building drawn at a scale of 1/4 inch = 25 feet?",
        "answer": "1 inch x 3 inches",
        "distractor_1": "2 inches x 3 inches",
        "distractor_2": "4 inches x 12 inches",
        "distractor_3": "1 inch x 12 inches"
      },
      {
        "id": "4791",
        "question": "How many square feet of asphalt are required for a parking space that is 9 feet wide and 18 feet long?",
        "answer": "162 square feet",
        "distractor_1": "81 square feet",
        "distractor_2": "144 square feet",
        "distractor_3": "27 square feet "
      },
      {
        "id": "4792",
        "question": "What is a budget?",
        "answer": "an itemized description of estimated or expected expenses for a project",
        "distractor_1": "the amount of money spent on a project",
        "distractor_2": "an itemized description of actual expense incurred during a project",
        "distractor_3": "the amount of profit expected from a project"
      },
      {
        "id": "4793",
        "question": "If a $1.1 million project has a 6% finance charge, what is the cost of the project after the finance charge?",
        "answer": "$1.166 million",
        "distractor_1": "$66,000 ",
        "distractor_2": "$1.76 million",
        "distractor_3": "$6.6 million"
      },
      {
        "id": "4794",
        "question": "What is the cost of a 250-square-foot office if it adds $40 per square foot to the cost of the project?",
        "answer": "$10,000",
        "distractor_1": "$8,000",
        "distractor_2": "$1,000 ",
        "distractor_3": "$100,000"
      },
      {
        "id": "4795",
        "question": "In a drawing that uses the scale 1/4 inch = 20 feet, how long is a wall represented by a 2-inch line?",
        "answer": "160 feet",
        "distractor_1": "80 feet",
        "distractor_2": "40 feet",
        "distractor_3": "5 feet"
      },
      {
        "id": "4796",
        "question": "What is the cost of borrowing money to build a project called?",
        "answer": "finance cost",
        "distractor_1": "prime interest rate ",
        "distractor_2": "fixed costs",
        "distractor_3": "overhead costs"
      },
      {
        "id": "4797",
        "question": "What is the statistical term for the difference between the price and the cost of a project?",
        "answer": "profit",
        "distractor_1": "revenue",
        "distractor_2": "margin",
        "distractor_3": "income"
      },
      {
        "id": "4798",
        "question": "Of every 10 carpenters, how many are self-employed?",
        "answer": "3",
        "distractor_1": "1 ",
        "distractor_2": "2",
        "distractor_3": "4"
      },
      {
        "id": "4799",
        "question": "What is the job title of the person who calculates the costs of materials and labor for a construction project?",
        "answer": "estimator",
        "distractor_1": "foreman",
        "distractor_2": "architect ",
        "distractor_3": "accountant"
      },
      {
        "id": "4800",
        "question": "What is the job title for those who prepare all the written information needed to describe materials, methods, and fixtures to be used in a construction project?",
        "answer": "specifications writer",
        "distractor_1": "construction manager",
        "distractor_2": "RFP writer",
        "distractor_3": "architect "
      },
      {
        "id": "4801",
        "question": "A contractor receives five estimates of construction costs for a project: $1,367,750; $1,738,250; $1,474,750; $1,523,250; and $1,676,250. What is the average estimate?",
        "answer": "$1,556,050",
        "distractor_1": "$1,367,750 ",
        "distractor_2": "$1,676,250",
        "distractor_3": "$1,474,750"
      },
      {
        "id": "4802",
        "question": "What is the area of a 500 ft x 700 ft rectangular plot of land?",
        "answer": "350,000 sq ft",
        "distractor_1": "35,000 sq ft",
        "distractor_2": "3,500 sq ft ",
        "distractor_3": "3,500,000 sq ft"
      },
      {
        "id": "4803",
        "question": "Suppose a 100 ft x 200 ft rectangular commercial building has a concrete slab foundation. If the foundation costs $5 per square foot, what is the cost of the foundation?",
        "answer": "$100,000",
        "distractor_1": "$10,000",
        "distractor_2": "$1,000 ",
        "distractor_3": "$1,000,000"
      },
      {
        "id": "4804",
        "question": "A 17,350-square-foot commercial building is being proposed for construction. The estimated cost is $85 per square foot. What is the estimated cost of the project?",
        "answer": "$1,474,750",
        "distractor_1": "$1,523,250",
        "distractor_2": "$1,676,250",
        "distractor_3": "$1,367,750 "
      },
      {
        "id": "8175",
        "question": "The cost of loans including closing costs and interest charges are called?",
        "answer": "finance charges",
        "distractor_1": "expected value",
        "distractor_2": "fixed costs",
        "distractor_3": "overhead costs"
      },
      {
        "id": "4807",
        "question": "What is the area of a 500 ft x 500 ft square plot of land?",
        "answer": "250,000 sq ft",
        "distractor_1": "2,500,000 sq ft ",
        "distractor_2": "25,000 sq ft",
        "distractor_3": "2,500 sq ft"
      },
      {
        "id": "4808",
        "question": "What are the dimensions of a scale drawing of a 100 ft x 300 ft building drawn at a scale of 1/2 inch = 25 feet?",
        "answer": "2 inches x 6 inches",
        "distractor_1": "2 inches x 3 inches",
        "distractor_2": "4 inches x 12 inches",
        "distractor_3": "1 inch x 12 inches"
      },
      {
        "id": "4810",
        "question": "What is an itemized description of estimated or expected expenses for a project?",
        "answer": "a budget",
        "distractor_1": "an RFP",
        "distractor_2": "a timeline",
        "distractor_3": "a proposal"
      },
      {
        "id": "4811",
        "question": "If a $1.2 million project has an 8% finance charge, what is the cost of the project after the finance charge?",
        "answer": "$1.296 million",
        "distractor_1": "$96,000 ",
        "distractor_2": "$2.16 million",
        "distractor_3": "$9.6 million"
      },
      {
        "id": "4812",
        "question": "What is the additional project cost of a 350 sq ft office figured at $50 per square foot?",
        "answer": "$17,500",
        "distractor_1": "$7,500",
        "distractor_2": "$1,750 ",
        "distractor_3": "$175,000"
      },
      {
        "id": "4813",
        "question": "In a drawing that uses the scale 1/4 inch = 25 feet, how long is a wall represented by a 2-inch line?",
        "answer": "200 feet",
        "distractor_1": "180 feet",
        "distractor_2": "160 feet ",
        "distractor_3": "50 feet"
      },
      {
        "id": "5397",
        "question": "What is the measure of the 2-D amount of space in a region?",
        "answer": "area",
        "distractor_1": "volume",
        "distractor_2": "square footage",
        "distractor_3": "acre"
      },
      {
        "id": "5398",
        "question": "What is the sum of the probability times the value of each outcome? ",
        "answer": "expected value",
        "distractor_1": "anticipated value",
        "distractor_2": "actual value",
        "distractor_3": "fixed value"
      },
      {
        "id": "5399",
        "question": "What is the name given to the person who is contracted to take full responsibility for the completion of a construction job?",
        "answer": "general contractor",
        "distractor_1": "subcontractor",
        "distractor_2": "person in charge",
        "distractor_3": "builder"
      },
      {
        "id": "5400",
        "question": "What is referred to as the schedule of events?",
        "answer": "timeline",
        "distractor_1": "schedule",
        "distractor_2": "plan",
        "distractor_3": "blueprint"
      },
      {
        "id": "5401",
        "question": "Who is the specialty trade contractor hired by the general contractor?",
        "answer": "subcontractor",
        "distractor_1": "substitute",
        "distractor_2": "carpenter",
        "distractor_3": "construction specialist"
      },
      {
        "id": "5404",
        "question": "What does RFP stand for?",
        "answer": "request for proposal",
        "distractor_1": "request for payment",
        "distractor_2": "removed from project",
        "distractor_3": "request for production"
      },
      {
        "id": "5405",
        "question": "What does CAD stand for?",
        "answer": "computer-aided drafting",
        "distractor_1": "computer-aided design",
        "distractor_2": "computer-aided drawing",
        "distractor_3": "computer-aided draftsmanship"
      },
      {
        "id": "8176",
        "question": "How many square feet of asphalt are required for a parking space that is 9 feet wide and 19 feet long?",
        "answer": "171 square feet",
        "distractor_1": "28 square feet",
        "distractor_2": "85.5 square feet",
        "distractor_3": "162 square feet"
      },
      {
        "id": "8317",
        "question": "What is the area of a 500 ft x 500 ft square plot of land?",
        "answer": "25,000 sq ft",
        "distractor_1": "2,500,000 sq ft",
        "distractor_2": "250,000 sq ft",
        "distractor_3": "2,500 sq ft"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "149",
    "name": "Hotel Management",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "4879",
        "question": "What item spurred the growth of new hotels and motels during the 1940s, 1950s, and 1960s?",
        "answer": "automobiles",
        "distractor_1": "computers",
        "distractor_2": "airplanes",
        "distractor_3": "factories"
      },
      {
        "id": "4880",
        "question": "Which of the options listed is the best choice for improving revenue per available room (RevPAR)?",
        "answer": "sell additional rooms",
        "distractor_1": "increase salaries",
        "distractor_2": "reduce costs",
        "distractor_3": "downsize hotel staff"
      },
      {
        "id": "4881",
        "question": "What is the formula used for calculating occupancy rate (OR)?",
        "answer": "Total Rooms Sold ÷ Total Rooms Available",
        "distractor_1": "Occupancy % × Average Daily Rate",
        "distractor_2": "Revenue - Expenses",
        "distractor_3": "Total Room Revenue ÷ Total Number of Rooms Sold"
      },
      {
        "id": "4882",
        "question": "What is the most common method for making online payments?",
        "answer": "credit card",
        "distractor_1": "debit card",
        "distractor_2": "P2P card",
        "distractor_3": "digital cash"
      },
      {
        "id": "4884",
        "question": "What is the formula used for calculating average daily rate (ADR)?",
        "answer": "Total Room Revenue ÷ Total Number of Rooms Sold",
        "distractor_1": "Occupancy % × Average Daily Rate",
        "distractor_2": "Revenue - Expenses",
        "distractor_3": "Total Rooms Sold ÷ Total Rooms Available"
      },
      {
        "id": "4885",
        "question": "This hotel, built in 1793, was the first hotel built Washington, D.C.",
        "answer": "Union Public House",
        "distractor_1": "Random House",
        "distractor_2": "Merchant's Inn",
        "distractor_3": "Colonial Inn"
      },
      {
        "id": "4886",
        "question": "What term is used when a hotel has more room reservations than it has available rooms?",
        "answer": "overbooking",
        "distractor_1": "forecasting",
        "distractor_2": "walking",
        "distractor_3": "yielding"
      },
      {
        "id": "4887",
        "question": "What is the formula used for calculating revenue per available room (RevPAR)?",
        "answer": "Occupancy % × Average Daily Rate",
        "distractor_1": "Total Rooms Sold ÷ Total Rooms Available",
        "distractor_2": "Revenue - Expenses",
        "distractor_3": "Total Room Revenue ÷ Total Number of Rooms Sold"
      },
      {
        "id": "4888",
        "question": "What does it mean to forecast?",
        "answer": "to predict future sales and expenses",
        "distractor_1": "to balance assets and liabilities",
        "distractor_2": "to please customers",
        "distractor_3": "to slow incoming revenue"
      },
      {
        "id": "4890",
        "question": "This award is the highest level of national recognition for quality in the United States. The Ritz-Carlton Hotel company earned this award in 1992 and 1999. What is the name of this award?",
        "answer": "Malcolm Baldrige Award",
        "distractor_1": "Better Homes and Gardens Award",
        "distractor_2": "Martha Stewart Award",
        "distractor_3": "Quality Service Award"
      },
      {
        "id": "4892",
        "question": "What term is defined as controlling room rates and restricting occupancy in order to maximize gross revenue from all sources?",
        "answer": "yield management",
        "distractor_1": "queuing theory",
        "distractor_2": "floor limit",
        "distractor_3": "spread rate"
      },
      {
        "id": "4895",
        "question": "What is the difference between 'front of the house' and 'back of the house'?",
        "answer": "amount of contact a department has with the customers",
        "distractor_1": "the structure of the building",
        "distractor_2": "the number of doors available for public use",
        "distractor_3": "physical location of specific rooms within the hotel"
      },
      {
        "id": "4897",
        "question": "Which of the following is defined as predicting the expected income from potential sales and the expected expenditures and costs for a specified future period?",
        "answer": "forecasting",
        "distractor_1": "confirmed reservation",
        "distractor_2": "guest cycle",
        "distractor_3": "occupancy rate"
      },
      {
        "id": "4898",
        "question": "Which of the following is computed by dividing room revenue by the number of rooms occupied?",
        "answer": "average daily rate (ADR)",
        "distractor_1": "occupancy rate (OR)",
        "distractor_2": "revenue per available room (RevPAR)",
        "distractor_3": "revenue"
      },
      {
        "id": "4899",
        "question": "Which of the following shows the relationships between the assets, liabilities, and owners' equity of a business at any given time?",
        "answer": "balance sheet",
        "distractor_1": "guest cycle",
        "distractor_2": "income statement",
        "distractor_3": "yield management"
      },
      {
        "id": "4900",
        "question": "Which of the following is determined by multiplying the average daily room rate by the occupancy rate?",
        "answer": "revenue per available room (RevPAR)",
        "distractor_1": "average daily rate (ADR)",
        "distractor_2": "occupancy rate (OR)",
        "distractor_3": "revenue"
      },
      {
        "id": "4901",
        "question": "Which of the following refers to a plan for how a business will spend and make money?",
        "answer": "business budget",
        "distractor_1": "guaranteed reservation",
        "distractor_2": "forecasting",
        "distractor_3": "revenue per available room"
      },
      {
        "id": "4903",
        "question": "This term refers to all the events that occur between the time a guest initially makes a reservation and finally checks out of the property.",
        "answer": "guest cycle",
        "distractor_1": "yield management",
        "distractor_2": "business budget",
        "distractor_3": "ratio"
      },
      {
        "id": "4904",
        "question": "This term refers to hotel products and services designed to attract guests.",
        "answer": "amenities",
        "distractor_1": "local attractions",
        "distractor_2": "guest cycle",
        "distractor_3": "forecasting"
      },
      {
        "id": "4905",
        "question": "What is determined by dividing the total number of rooms sold by the total number of rooms available?",
        "answer": "occupancy rate",
        "distractor_1": "average daily rate",
        "distractor_2": "revenue per available room",
        "distractor_3": "revenue"
      },
      {
        "id": "4908",
        "question": "Who is the person renting a hotel room?",
        "answer": "guest",
        "distractor_1": "occupant",
        "distractor_2": "company",
        "distractor_3": "business associate"
      },
      {
        "id": "4909",
        "question": "This document lists revenue and expenses during a certain period of time indicating whether a company has earned a profit or suffered a loss.",
        "answer": "income statement",
        "distractor_1": "business budget",
        "distractor_2": "forecasting model",
        "distractor_3": "balance sheet"
      },
      {
        "id": "5340",
        "question": "This term is defined as requests for rooms from prospective guests who intend to arrive sometime in the future.",
        "answer": "reservations",
        "distractor_1": "overbookings",
        "distractor_2": "forecastings",
        "distractor_3": "yielding"
      },
      {
        "id": "5341",
        "question": "This term is defined as a ratio that compares a number to 100.",
        "answer": "percent",
        "distractor_1": "proportion",
        "distractor_2": "rate",
        "distractor_3": "decimal"
      },
      {
        "id": "5342",
        "question": "What is the comparison of two numbers by division?",
        "answer": "ratio",
        "distractor_1": "proportion",
        "distractor_2": "percent",
        "distractor_3": "rate"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "152",
    "name": "Forensic Math",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "5330",
        "question": "Which of the following is the slant of a graphed line as you look at it from left to right?",
        "answer": "slope",
        "distractor_1": "function",
        "distractor_2": "point",
        "distractor_3": "ordered pair"
      },
      {
        "id": "5331",
        "question": "If y = x • 8.75, what is the value of x when y = 43.75?",
        "answer": "5",
        "distractor_1": "4",
        "distractor_2": "382.81",
        "distractor_3": ".2"
      },
      {
        "id": "4911",
        "question": "What is the slope of a line with points (-2, 1) and (0, 2)?",
        "answer": "1/2",
        "distractor_1": "-1/2",
        "distractor_2": "2",
        "distractor_3": "-2"
      },
      {
        "id": "4912",
        "question": "Which of the following is the slope-intercept formula?",
        "answer": "y = mx + b",
        "distractor_1": "x = my + b",
        "distractor_2": "b = my + x",
        "distractor_3": "m = bx + y"
      },
      {
        "id": "4913",
        "question": "If y = 1.5x + 3, and x = 7.2, what is the value of y?",
        "answer": "13.8",
        "distractor_1": "15.3",
        "distractor_2": "2.8",
        "distractor_3": "10.8"
      },
      {
        "id": "4914",
        "question": "If y = 3.7x + 0, what is the value of x when y = 5?",
        "answer": "1.35",
        "distractor_1": "0.74",
        "distractor_2": "18.5",
        "distractor_3": "8.7"
      },
      {
        "id": "4916",
        "question": "The value of y at the point where a graphed line crosses the y-axis is called what?",
        "answer": "y-intercept",
        "distractor_1": "height",
        "distractor_2": "x-intercept",
        "distractor_3": "slope"
      },
      {
        "id": "4917",
        "question": "A final crime scene drawing has a scale of 5 mm/1 m. The distance between two cars in the drawing is 12 mm. What is the actual distance between the cars? Hint: D • S = L",
        "answer": "2.4 m",
        "distractor_1": "60 mm ",
        "distractor_2": "2.4 mm",
        "distractor_3": "60 m"
      },
      {
        "id": "4918",
        "question": "An ordered pair is written in what form?",
        "answer": "horizontal coordinate, vertical coordinate",
        "distractor_1": "vertical coordinate, horizontal coordinate",
        "distractor_2": "vertical coordinate, zero coordinate",
        "distractor_3": "horizontal coordinate, zero coordinate"
      },
      {
        "id": "4919",
        "question": "What is the slope of a line with points (0, -1) and (4, 4)?",
        "answer": "5/4",
        "distractor_1": "-4/5",
        "distractor_2": "-5/4",
        "distractor_3": "4/5"
      },
      {
        "id": "4921",
        "question": "If y = 1.4x + 2, and x = 6.2, what is the value of y?",
        "answer": "10.68",
        "distractor_1": "7.6",
        "distractor_2": "3.4",
        "distractor_3": "8.68"
      },
      {
        "id": "4922",
        "question": "If y = 3.4x + 0, what is the value of x when y = 4.01?",
        "answer": "1.18 ",
        "distractor_1": "0.85",
        "distractor_2": "13.63",
        "distractor_3": "7.41"
      },
      {
        "id": "4923",
        "question": "What two measurement methods are used in creating crime scene sketches?",
        "answer": "triangulation and polar coordinates ",
        "distractor_1": "final and triangulation",
        "distractor_2": "final and scale",
        "distractor_3": "rough and polar coordinates"
      },
      {
        "id": "4925",
        "question": "A final crime scene drawing has a scale of 5 mm/1 m. The distance between two cars in the drawing is 21 mm. What is the actual distance between the cars? Hint: D • S = L",
        "answer": "4.2 m",
        "distractor_1": "105 mm",
        "distractor_2": "4.2 mm",
        "distractor_3": "105 m"
      },
      {
        "id": "4927",
        "question": "Which of the following is a ratio between two sets of measurements?",
        "answer": "scale",
        "distractor_1": "coordinate",
        "distractor_2": "triangulation",
        "distractor_3": "function"
      },
      {
        "id": "4928",
        "question": "Twenty meters is equal to how many centimeters?",
        "answer": "2,000 cm",
        "distractor_1": "200 cm",
        "distractor_2": "2 cm",
        "distractor_3": "0.2 cm"
      },
      {
        "id": "4930",
        "question": "Two cars at a crime scene are 22 meters apart. Using the scale 5 mm/1 m, how long would the line between them be on a final drawing?",
        "answer": "110 mm",
        "distractor_1": "4.4 m",
        "distractor_2": "4.4 mm",
        "distractor_3": "110 m"
      },
      {
        "id": "4931",
        "question": "Which of the following is a relation in which every x value has one and only one y value?",
        "answer": "function",
        "distractor_1": "variable",
        "distractor_2": "slope",
        "distractor_3": "graph"
      },
      {
        "id": "4932",
        "question": "If y = x • 7.26, what is the value of y when x = 6.2?",
        "answer": "45.01",
        "distractor_1": "0.85",
        "distractor_2": "13.46",
        "distractor_3": "42"
      },
      {
        "id": "4934",
        "question": "If y = x • 7.26, what is the value of x when y = 37.03?",
        "answer": "5.1",
        "distractor_1": "44.29",
        "distractor_2": "268.84",
        "distractor_3": ".02"
      },
      {
        "id": "5413",
        "question": "Which of the following is a pair of numbers that gives the coordinates of a point on a grid in this order (horizontal coordinate, vertical coordinate)?",
        "answer": "ordered pair",
        "distractor_1": "polar coordinates",
        "distractor_2": "slope-intercept",
        "distractor_3": "slope"
      },
      {
        "id": "5414",
        "question": "Which of the following is a symbol, usually a letter, that can stand for an unknown quantity?",
        "answer": "variable",
        "distractor_1": "constant",
        "distractor_2": "y-intercept",
        "distractor_3": "vertical coordinate"
      },
      {
        "id": "5416",
        "question": "Which of the following is a method used in surveying in which a region is divided into a set of triangular elements based on a line of known length, so that an accurate determination of distances and directions can be made by using trigonometry?",
        "answer": "triangulation",
        "distractor_1": "slope-intercept",
        "distractor_2": "Avogadro's method",
        "distractor_3": "square root"
      },
      {
        "id": "5417",
        "question": "Which of the following are coordinates based on the rotation of a segment about a pole, or center point?",
        "answer": "polar coordinates",
        "distractor_1": "vertical coordinates",
        "distractor_2": "horizontal coordinates",
        "distractor_3": "perpendicular coordinates"
      },
      {
        "id": "5418",
        "question": "Which of the following is a form of a linear equation, y = mx + b, where m is the slope of the line and b is the y-intercept?",
        "answer": "slope-intercept",
        "distractor_1": "square root",
        "distractor_2": "triangulation",
        "distractor_3": "chord"
      },
      {
        "id": "5420",
        "question": "Which of the following is always written second in an ordered pair? ",
        "answer": "vertical coordinate",
        "distractor_1": "horizontal coordinate",
        "distractor_2": "y-intercept",
        "distractor_3": "square root"
      },
      {
        "id": "5421",
        "question": "Which of the following is always written first in an ordered pair?",
        "answer": "horizontal coordinate",
        "distractor_1": "vertical coordinate",
        "distractor_2": "slope",
        "distractor_3": "constant"
      },
      {
        "id": "5422",
        "question": "Which of the following is one of the two equal factors of a number?",
        "answer": "square root",
        "distractor_1": "slope",
        "distractor_2": "diameter",
        "distractor_3": "constant"
      },
      {
        "id": "5423",
        "question": "Which of the following is a line segment with end points on a circle?",
        "answer": "chord",
        "distractor_1": "y-intercept",
        "distractor_2": "ray",
        "distractor_3": "diameter"
      },
      {
        "id": "5424",
        "question": "Which of the following is a straight line segment that passes through the center of a circle or sphere from one side to the other?",
        "answer": "diameter",
        "distractor_1": "chord",
        "distractor_2": "function",
        "distractor_3": "slope-intercept"
      },
      {
        "id": "5425",
        "question": "What are lines that intersect to form right angles?",
        "answer": "perpendicular",
        "distractor_1": "variable",
        "distractor_2": "vertical",
        "distractor_3": "horizontal"
      },
      {
        "id": "5426",
        "question": "What is a term without a variable?",
        "answer": "constant",
        "distractor_1": "ordered pair",
        "distractor_2": "polar coordinate",
        "distractor_3": "square root"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "150",
    "name": "Chemical Math",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "4935",
        "question": "What is the name for a mathematical expression having two or more terms?",
        "answer": "binomial",
        "distractor_1": "monomial",
        "distractor_2": "trinomial",
        "distractor_3": "polynomial"
      },
      {
        "id": "4936",
        "question": "When solving a word problem, which of the following represents the unknown value?",
        "answer": "a variable",
        "distractor_1": "a constant",
        "distractor_2": "an equation",
        "distractor_3": "a coefficient"
      },
      {
        "id": "4937",
        "question": "Which of the following equations is balanced?",
        "answer": "2 Al2O3  --> 4 Al + 3 O2",
        "distractor_1": "CH4 + O2  --> CO2 + 2 H2O",
        "distractor_2": "2 HCl + NaOH  --> H2O + NaCl",
        "distractor_3": "H2O --> O2 + H2"
      },
      {
        "id": "4938",
        "question": "Which factor determines the reactivity of a compound?",
        "answer": "number of valence electrons",
        "distractor_1": "atomic mass",
        "distractor_2": "total number of electrons",
        "distractor_3": "presence of an electron cloud"
      },
      {
        "id": "4939",
        "question": "Balancing a chemical equation illustrates which of the following principles?",
        "answer": "conservation of mass",
        "distractor_1": "principle of equality",
        "distractor_2": "conservation of energy",
        "distractor_3": "principle of reactivity"
      },
      {
        "id": "4940",
        "question": "A Lewis dot structure is used to show which of the following?",
        "answer": "sharing of electrons in covalent bonds",
        "distractor_1": "type of isotope present in a molecule",
        "distractor_2": "number of bonds in a molecule",
        "distractor_3": "loss or gain of electrons in ionic bonds"
      },
      {
        "id": "4941",
        "question": "What factor determines the atomic number of an element?",
        "answer": "number of protons",
        "distractor_1": "number of valence electrons",
        "distractor_2": "number of neutrons",
        "distractor_3": "mass of nucleus"
      },
      {
        "id": "4942",
        "question": "Which of the following represents a physical change in matter?",
        "answer": "changing water from ice to liquid to steam ",
        "distractor_1": "converting water to hydrogen and oxygen gases",
        "distractor_2": "combining baking soda and vinegar",
        "distractor_3": "rusting iron"
      },
      {
        "id": "4943",
        "question": "What is the standard form of the number 5.5 * 10^3?",
        "answer": "5,500",
        "distractor_1": "0.055",
        "distractor_2": "550",
        "distractor_3": ".0055"
      },
      {
        "id": "4944",
        "question": "How many molecules are there in one mole of water?",
        "answer": "Avogadro’s number (6.022 * 10^23)",
        "distractor_1": "pi (3.14159)",
        "distractor_2": "varies depending on the temperature",
        "distractor_3": "cannot be determined"
      },
      {
        "id": "4945",
        "question": "Lead has a density of 11.34 g/cu cm. A piece of lead weighs 520 grams. What is the volume of this piece of lead? Round to hundredths. Note: d = m/v",
        "answer": "45.86 cu cm",
        "distractor_1": ".022 cu cm",
        "distractor_2": "458.55 cu cm",
        "distractor_3": "5,896.80 cu cm"
      },
      {
        "id": "4946",
        "question": "Which scientist is responsible for the model of the atom that shows electrons moving in specific layers, or shells, around the nucleus?",
        "answer": "Niels Bohr, a Danish physicist, in 1913",
        "distractor_1": "John Dalton, a British chemist, in 1808",
        "distractor_2": "J. J. Thomson, a British scientist, in 1897",
        "distractor_3": "Ernest Rutherford, a British physicist, in 1911"
      },
      {
        "id": "4947",
        "question": "What is the correct scientific notation for the following standard number: 0.0000000045",
        "answer": "4.5 * 10^9",
        "distractor_1": "4.5 * 10^9",
        "distractor_2": "45 * 10^-10",
        "distractor_3": "45 * 10^-10"
      },
      {
        "id": "4948",
        "question": "Which scientist discovered the elements polonium and radium?",
        "answer": "Marie Curie",
        "distractor_1": "Dmitri Mendeleev",
        "distractor_2": "Sir William Ramsey",
        "distractor_3": "Glenn Seaborg"
      },
      {
        "id": "4949",
        "question": "Boron has two naturally occurring isotopes. B-10 has an atomic mass of 10.013 and makes up 19.9 percent of naturally occurring boron. B-11 has an atomic mass of 11.009 and makes up the other 80.1 percent. What is the average atomic mass of boron?",
        "answer": "10.81",
        "distractor_1": "1.99",
        "distractor_2": "8.82",
        "distractor_3": "9.81"
      },
      {
        "id": "4950",
        "question": "A binomial is a mathematical term containing how many expressions?",
        "answer": "exactly two",
        "distractor_1": "exactly one",
        "distractor_2": "exactly three",
        "distractor_3": "two or more"
      },
      {
        "id": "4952",
        "question": "What is the first step in solving a multistep equation having an expression in parentheses?",
        "answer": "use the Distributive Property",
        "distractor_1": "use inverses to undo addition or subtraction",
        "distractor_2": "use inverses to undo multiplication or division",
        "distractor_3": "combine like terms"
      },
      {
        "id": "4953",
        "question": "What is the name for a method of expressing very large or very small numbers as a product of two factors, the first factor being greater than or equal to one and less than ten, and the second being a power of ten?",
        "answer": "scientific notation",
        "distractor_1": "Avogadro's number",
        "distractor_2": "inequality",
        "distractor_3": "mole"
      },
      {
        "id": "4954",
        "question": "What is the name for a charged particle formed when an atom gains or loses electrons from its outer shell?",
        "answer": "ion",
        "distractor_1": "mole",
        "distractor_2": "electron",
        "distractor_3": "Avogadro's number"
      },
      {
        "id": "4956",
        "question": "Which of the following is an equation in which the expressions on the left and right are unequal and are connected by an inequality sign, such as “greater than” or “less than”?",
        "answer": "inequality",
        "distractor_1": "chemical equation",
        "distractor_2": "variable",
        "distractor_3": "polynomial"
      },
      {
        "id": "4960",
        "question": "What is the quantity of a substance having a mass in grams equivalent to its formula mass and having Avogadro’s number of particles?",
        "answer": "mole",
        "distractor_1": "scientific notation",
        "distractor_2": "polynomial",
        "distractor_3": "valence electron"
      },
      {
        "id": "4961",
        "question": "What is the number of particles in one mole of any substance, equivalent to the constant 6.022 * 10^23?",
        "answer": "Avogadro's number",
        "distractor_1": "scientific notation",
        "distractor_2": "mass",
        "distractor_3": "molecule"
      },
      {
        "id": "4963",
        "question": "Which of the following terms is described as anything that has mass and takes up space?",
        "answer": "matter",
        "distractor_1": "mass",
        "distractor_2": "mole",
        "distractor_3": "neutron"
      },
      {
        "id": "4964",
        "question": "Which of the following is an electron orbiting in the outer shell of an atom and determining the atom’s reactivity?",
        "answer": "valence electron",
        "distractor_1": "element",
        "distractor_2": "ion",
        "distractor_3": "isotope"
      },
      {
        "id": "4965",
        "question": "Which of the following is one of several forms of an element having different numbers of neutrons?",
        "answer": "isotope",
        "distractor_1": "ion",
        "distractor_2": "element",
        "distractor_3": "valence electron"
      },
      {
        "id": "4966",
        "question": "Which of the following is described as the amount of matter contained in an object?",
        "answer": "mass",
        "distractor_1": "matter",
        "distractor_2": "atom",
        "distractor_3": "element"
      },
      {
        "id": "4967",
        "question": "What is the sum or difference of two or more monomials, such as 5x + y + 3?",
        "answer": "polynomial",
        "distractor_1": "mole",
        "distractor_2": "Avogadro's number",
        "distractor_3": "exponent"
      },
      {
        "id": "4968",
        "question": "What is the term for a structure composed of two or more atoms and held together by chemical bonds?",
        "answer": "molecule",
        "distractor_1": "mole",
        "distractor_2": "atom",
        "distractor_3": "proton"
      },
      {
        "id": "4969",
        "question": "Which of the following is a substance that cannot be separated into simpler substances without changing its chemical structure?",
        "answer": "element",
        "distractor_1": "mole",
        "distractor_2": "proton",
        "distractor_3": "nucleus"
      },
      {
        "id": "4970",
        "question": "Which of the following is a characteristic property of a substance, determined as mass divided by volume?",
        "answer": "density",
        "distractor_1": "mass",
        "distractor_2": "matter",
        "distractor_3": "Avogadro's number"
      },
      {
        "id": "4971",
        "question": "Which of the following is a single mathematical term or expression, such as 5x?",
        "answer": "monomial",
        "distractor_1": "polynomial",
        "distractor_2": "chemical equation",
        "distractor_3": "scientific notation"
      },
      {
        "id": "4972",
        "question": "Which of the following is the smallest unit of an element that contains all chemical properties unique to that element?",
        "answer": "atom",
        "distractor_1": "neutron",
        "distractor_2": "proton",
        "distractor_3": "electron"
      },
      {
        "id": "4973",
        "question": "What factor determines the atomic mass of an element?",
        "answer": "number of protons and neutrons",
        "distractor_1": "number of protons",
        "distractor_2": "number of electrons",
        "distractor_3": "number of protons and electrons"
      },
      {
        "id": "4974",
        "question": "Which of the following is used to show the sharing of electrons in a covalent bond?",
        "answer": "Lewis dot structure",
        "distractor_1": "chemical formula",
        "distractor_2": "chemical equation",
        "distractor_3": "octet rule"
      },
      {
        "id": "4975",
        "question": "The number of valence electrons in an element determines which characteristic of the element?",
        "answer": "reactivity",
        "distractor_1": "atomic mass",
        "distractor_2": "density",
        "distractor_3": "number of isotopes"
      },
      {
        "id": "4976",
        "question": "One mole of ethane contains how many molecules? ",
        "answer": "6.022 * 10^23",
        "distractor_1": "30",
        "distractor_2": "30.048",
        "distractor_3": "3.25 * 10^12"
      },
      {
        "id": "4977",
        "question": "Which of the following expressions is a trinomial?",
        "answer": "3x – (-4) + 2y",
        "distractor_1": "2x",
        "distractor_2": "y + 5",
        "distractor_3": "4x^2 + 38"
      },
      {
        "id": "5161",
        "question": "Which of the following is the number that tells how many equal factors there are?",
        "answer": "exponent",
        "distractor_1": "equation",
        "distractor_2": "valence electron",
        "distractor_3": "chemical equation"
      },
      {
        "id": "5162",
        "question": "Which of the following is a statement that two mathematical expressions are equal?",
        "answer": "equation",
        "distractor_1": "exponent",
        "distractor_2": "variable",
        "distractor_3": "constant"
      },
      {
        "id": "5163",
        "question": "Which of the following is a term without a variable?",
        "answer": "constant",
        "distractor_1": "monomial",
        "distractor_2": "polynomial",
        "distractor_3": "variable"
      },
      {
        "id": "5164",
        "question": "Which of the following is a symbol, usually a letter, that stands for different values?",
        "answer": "variable",
        "distractor_1": "equation",
        "distractor_2": "constant",
        "distractor_3": "exponent"
      },
      {
        "id": "4978",
        "question": "Which of the following equations is NOT balanced?",
        "answer": "2 HCl  +  NaOH  --> H2O  +  NaCl",
        "distractor_1": "CH4 + 2 O2  -->  CO2  +  2 H2O",
        "distractor_2": "2 H2O  -->  O2  +  2 H2",
        "distractor_3": "2 Al2O3 -->  4 Al  +  3 O2"
      },
      {
        "id": "4979",
        "question": "How is the number .000065 expressed in scientific notation?",
        "answer": "6.5 * 10^-5",
        "distractor_1": "65 * 10^-6",
        "distractor_2": "6.5 * 10^-6",
        "distractor_3": "65 * 10^-5"
      },
      {
        "id": "4980",
        "question": "In the following equation, which term, if any, is a constant? Equation: 4x + y + 6 = 7",
        "answer": "6",
        "distractor_1": "4x",
        "distractor_2": "y",
        "distractor_3": "none"
      },
      {
        "id": "4981",
        "question": "Which of the following represents a chemical change in matter?",
        "answer": "converting water to the gases hydrogen and oxygen ",
        "distractor_1": "weathering of rocks",
        "distractor_2": "changing water from ice to liquid to steam",
        "distractor_3": "dissolving salt in water"
      },
      {
        "id": "4982",
        "question": "Which of the following is a correct statement of the law of conservation of mass?",
        "answer": "Matter can neither be created nor destroyed. ",
        "distractor_1": "Reactants in a chemical reaction remain unchanged.",
        "distractor_2": "Energy can neither be created nor destroyed.",
        "distractor_3": "Products in a chemical reaction are different from reactants."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "151",
    "name": "Environmental Math",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "4995",
        "question": "You have a land area of 3,600 m². You wish to construct a square quadrat having an area 0.5 percent of the total. What will be the dimensions of the quadrat, rounded to the nearest tenth?",
        "answer": "4.2 meters",
        "distractor_1": "4.24 meters",
        "distractor_2": "42.4 meters",
        "distractor_3": "42.43 meters"
      },
      {
        "id": "4996",
        "question": "In a triangle with angles of 30, 60, and 90 degrees, what is the length of the hypotenuse?",
        "answer": "twice the length of the shorter leg",
        "distractor_1": "three times the square root of two",
        "distractor_2": "two times the square root of three",
        "distractor_3": "shorter leg times the square root of three"
      },
      {
        "id": "4997",
        "question": "A student stands 15 meters from the base of a tree. At ground level, his protractor makes a 45º angle with the top of the tree. How tall is the tree?",
        "answer": "15 meters",
        "distractor_1": "30 • sqrt(3) meters",
        "distractor_2": "15 • sqrt(2) meters",
        "distractor_3": "30 meters"
      },
      {
        "id": "4998",
        "question": "A person is observing an animal at the base of a cliff. What is the name of the angle between the horizontal and the person's line of sight?",
        "answer": "angle of depression",
        "distractor_1": "angle of depth",
        "distractor_2": "angle of sight",
        "distractor_3": "angle of elevation"
      },
      {
        "id": "4999",
        "question": "A girl scout is using a transit for orienteering. She takes four consecutive bearings of 90º each and travels 10 meters in each direction. What will be her ending point?",
        "answer": "at the starting point",
        "distractor_1": "10 meters either left or right of the starting point",
        "distractor_2": "20 meters either left or right of the starting point",
        "distractor_3": "straight ahead and 40 meters from the starting point"
      },
      {
        "id": "5000",
        "question": "The distance formula, used to find the distance between two points on the coordinate plane, is based on which mathematical concept?",
        "answer": "Pythagorean theorem",
        "distractor_1": "formula for slope of a line",
        "distractor_2": "midpoint formula",
        "distractor_3": "square root"
      },
      {
        "id": "5003",
        "question": "Which term refers to a set of numbers that can be expressed as fractions and form decimals that either terminate or repeat?",
        "answer": "rational number",
        "distractor_1": "surveying",
        "distractor_2": "midpoint formula",
        "distractor_3": "congruent triangles"
      },
      {
        "id": "5005",
        "question": "What is the largest set of numbers containing both rational and irrational numbers?",
        "answer": "real numbers",
        "distractor_1": "negative numbers",
        "distractor_2": "positive numbers",
        "distractor_3": "whole numbers"
      },
      {
        "id": "5006",
        "question": "Which triangles have the same size and shape?",
        "answer": "congruent triangles",
        "distractor_1": "matching triangles",
        "distractor_2": "right triangles",
        "distractor_3": "similar triangles"
      },
      {
        "id": "5007",
        "question": "Which type of triangles have the same angles and sides with different, but proportional, lengths?",
        "answer": "similar triangles",
        "distractor_1": "congruent triangles",
        "distractor_2": "matching triangles",
        "distractor_3": "right triangles"
      },
      {
        "id": "5008",
        "question": "What is the square of an integer?",
        "answer": "perfect square",
        "distractor_1": "bearing",
        "distractor_2": "hypotenuse",
        "distractor_3": "angle of elevation"
      },
      {
        "id": "5011",
        "question": "What is the clockwise angle between an object of interest and magnetic North?",
        "answer": "bearing",
        "distractor_1": "formula",
        "distractor_2": "angle of depression",
        "distractor_3": "surveying"
      },
      {
        "id": "5014",
        "question": "What is the formula used to calculate the length of a line segment as the distance between two points on the coordinate plane?",
        "answer": "distance formula",
        "distractor_1": "slope formula",
        "distractor_2": "midpoint formula",
        "distractor_3": "length formula"
      },
      {
        "id": "5015",
        "question": "What is the angle formed as you look upward from the horizontal to an object?",
        "answer": "angle of elevation",
        "distractor_1": "midpoint formula",
        "distractor_2": "angle of depth",
        "distractor_3": "perfect square"
      },
      {
        "id": "5016",
        "question": "What is the square or rectangular plot marked off in a natural area for sampling purposes?",
        "answer": "quadrat",
        "distractor_1": "area",
        "distractor_2": "perfect square",
        "distractor_3": "hypotenuse"
      },
      {
        "id": "5017",
        "question": "What is the technique used to determine precise location of points on Earth by measuring distances, heights, and angles?",
        "answer": "surveying",
        "distractor_1": "whole number",
        "distractor_2": "bearing",
        "distractor_3": "perfect square"
      },
      {
        "id": "5018",
        "question": "What is the longest side of a right triangle, which is opposite the right angle?",
        "answer": "hypotenuse",
        "distractor_1": "slope",
        "distractor_2": "straight angle",
        "distractor_3": "whole number"
      },
      {
        "id": "5134",
        "question": "What is an equation that shows two equal ratios?",
        "answer": "proportion",
        "distractor_1": "similar triangles",
        "distractor_2": "bearing",
        "distractor_3": "right angle"
      },
      {
        "id": "5135",
        "question": "What is one of the two equal factors of a number?",
        "answer": "square root",
        "distractor_1": "slope",
        "distractor_2": "obtuse angle",
        "distractor_3": "equilateral triangle"
      },
      {
        "id": "5136",
        "question": "Which angle is a 90º angle?",
        "answer": "right angle",
        "distractor_1": "acute angle",
        "distractor_2": "obtuse angle",
        "distractor_3": "straight angle"
      },
      {
        "id": "5137",
        "question": "Which angle measures between 0º and 90º?",
        "answer": "acute angle",
        "distractor_1": "obtuse angle",
        "distractor_2": "right angle",
        "distractor_3": "straight angle"
      },
      {
        "id": "5138",
        "question": "Which angle measures more than 90º and less than 180º?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle",
        "distractor_1": "acute angle",
        "distractor_2": "right angle",
        "distractor_3": "straight angle"
      },
      {
        "id": "5139",
        "question": "Which of the following terms refers to a number within the set of positive and negative whole numbers and zero?",
        "answer": "integer",
        "distractor_1": "square root",
        "distractor_2": "similar triangles",
        "distractor_3": "obtuse angle"
      },
      {
        "id": "5140",
        "question": "Which of the following terms refers to the slant of a line as you look at it from left to right?",
        "answer": "slope",
        "distractor_1": "integer",
        "distractor_2": "right angle",
        "distractor_3": "acute angle"
      },
      {
        "id": "5343",
        "question": "Which term describes two triangles whose corresponding sides and angles are equal?",
        "answer": "congruent",
        "distractor_1": "similar",
        "distractor_2": "scalene",
        "distractor_3": "equilateral"
      },
      {
        "id": "5344",
        "question": "Which term describes two triangles whose corresponding angles are equal and whose corresponding sides are proportional, but not equal?",
        "answer": "similar",
        "distractor_1": "proportional",
        "distractor_2": "scalene",
        "distractor_3": "congruent"
      },
      {
        "id": "4983",
        "question": "Which of the following is a technique used in many professions to determine precise locations on Earth?",
        "answer": "surveying",
        "distractor_1": "orienteering",
        "distractor_2": "mapmaking ",
        "distractor_3": "triangulation"
      },
      {
        "id": "4984",
        "question": "In environmental science, a quadrat might be used for which purpose?",
        "answer": "isolating a precisely measured area for study",
        "distractor_1": "determining the height of an object ",
        "distractor_2": "measuring the total size of an area",
        "distractor_3": "determining the distance to an object "
      },
      {
        "id": "4985",
        "question": "If the area of a square piece of land is known, what mathematical calculation is used to determine the length of each side?",
        "answer": "square root",
        "distractor_1": "proportion",
        "distractor_2": "perfect square",
        "distractor_3": "triangulation"
      },
      {
        "id": "4986",
        "question": "Which of the following is an indirect method for determining length or distance in the outdoors?",
        "answer": "use similar triangles",
        "distractor_1": "use the distance formula",
        "distractor_2": "measure the slope",
        "distractor_3": "measure the midpoint"
      },
      {
        "id": "4987",
        "question": "A transit is most likely to be used for which purpose?",
        "answer": "determining the soil type of an area",
        "distractor_1": "isolating a precisely measured area for study",
        "distractor_2": "determining the distance to an object",
        "distractor_3": "measuring the total size of an area "
      },
      {
        "id": "4988",
        "question": "What is the correct name for a triangle having one 90º angle and two 45º angles?",
        "answer": "isosceles right triangle",
        "distractor_1": "isosceles acute triangle",
        "distractor_2": "equilateral right triangle",
        "distractor_3": "scalene obtuse triangle"
      },
      {
        "id": "4989",
        "question": "Which of the following number sets contains the numbers pi, 47, and 2.2?",
        "answer": "set of real numbers",
        "distractor_1": "set of whole numbers",
        "distractor_2": "set of rational numbers",
        "distractor_3": "set of integers"
      },
      {
        "id": "4990",
        "question": "Which of the following formulas is used to determine the length of the hypotenuse of a right triangle?",
        "answer": "Pythagorean theorem",
        "distractor_1": "conversion factor ",
        "distractor_2": "square root formula",
        "distractor_3": "midpoint formula"
      },
      {
        "id": "4991",
        "question": "Two right angles placed side by side will form which of the following figures?",
        "answer": "straight angle",
        "distractor_1": "obtuse angle",
        "distractor_2": "scalene triangle",
        "distractor_3": "equilateral triangle"
      },
      {
        "id": "4992",
        "question": "Which mathematical expression is used to convert a value from one unit to another?",
        "answer": "proportion",
        "distractor_1": "square root",
        "distractor_2": "perfect square ",
        "distractor_3": "product"
      },
      {
        "id": "4993",
        "question": "If an integer is not a perfect square, its square root will fit into which of the following number sets?",
        "answer": "irrational numbers",
        "distractor_1": "rational numbers",
        "distractor_2": "whole numbers",
        "distractor_3": "natural numbers"
      },
      {
        "id": "4994",
        "question": "A square cornfield has an area of 0.25 km². What is the length of each side of the field, in meters?",
        "answer": "500 meters",
        "distractor_1": "5 meters",
        "distractor_2": "50 meters",
        "distractor_3": ".5 meters"
      },
      {
        "id": "5019",
        "question": "What is the formula used to calculate the midpoint of the hypotenuse of a right triangle by averaging the x and y values of its endpoints?",
        "answer": "midpoint formula",
        "distractor_1": "distance formula",
        "distractor_2": "slope formula",
        "distractor_3": "triangle formula"
      },
      {
        "id": "5020",
        "question": "What is the set of numbers containing all the positive counting numbers plus zero?",
        "answer": "whole numbers",
        "distractor_1": "similar triangles",
        "distractor_2": "formula",
        "distractor_3": "hypotenuse"
      },
      {
        "id": "5021",
        "question": "What is the first step when using a transit to find a horizontal direction?",
        "answer": "determining distance to the object",
        "distractor_1": "determining angle of elevation",
        "distractor_2": "taking a bearing",
        "distractor_3": "leveling the transit"
      },
      {
        "id": "5022",
        "question": "Square roots can be used to calculate the length of sides of an area in which of the following situations?",
        "answer": "when the area is a square of any dimension",
        "distractor_1": "only when the area is a perfect square ",
        "distractor_2": "when the area is any four-sided polygon",
        "distractor_3": "when the area is any type of triangle"
      },
      {
        "id": "5023",
        "question": "Similar and congruent triangles are useful for determining outdoor distances in which of the following situations?",
        "answer": "when one area can be easily measured and the other cannot",
        "distractor_1": "when the areas being measured are the same size",
        "distractor_2": "when elevations vary from one area to the other",
        "distractor_3": "when fences or other straight boundaries are present"
      },
      {
        "id": "5024",
        "question": "The values a, b, and c in the formula a² + b² = c² refer to which of the following?",
        "answer": "the legs and hypotenuse of a right triangle",
        "distractor_1": "the sides and area of a rectangle",
        "distractor_2": "the legs and base of an isosceles triangle",
        "distractor_3": "the legs and base of a scalene triangle"
      },
      {
        "id": "5025",
        "question": "Why do environmental scientists often use quadrats to study natural areas?",
        "answer": "They are used as samples of areas too large to be studied easily.",
        "distractor_1": "They enable scientists to study sites at high elevations.",
        "distractor_2": "They give precise information about conditions in a large area.",
        "distractor_3": "They are used to determine the exact size of an area."
      },
      {
        "id": "5026",
        "question": "If a triangle has one obtuse angle, what must the other two angles be?",
        "answer": "Both must be acute angles.",
        "distractor_1": "Both must be right angles.",
        "distractor_2": "One must be a right angle and one must be acute.",
        "distractor_3": "One must be an acute angle and one must be obtuse."
      },
      {
        "id": "5027",
        "question": "To convert meters to kilometers, which of the following proportions would be used?",
        "answer": "1 km = 1,000 m",
        "distractor_1": "1 m = 100 cm",
        "distractor_2": "1 m = 1,000 km",
        "distractor_3": "1 km = 1,000,000 cm"
      },
      {
        "id": "5028",
        "question": "Which of the following is a technique used by surveyors to find coordinates or distances to a point using triangles?",
        "answer": "triangulation",
        "distractor_1": "orienteering",
        "distractor_2": "surveying",
        "distractor_3": "taking a bearing"
      },
      {
        "id": "5029",
        "question": "The number 2 fits into which of the following sets of numbers?",
        "answer": "real numbers, rational numbers, whole numbers, and integers",
        "distractor_1": "real and whole numbers only",
        "distractor_2": "real, rational, and whole numbers",
        "distractor_3": "real numbers only"
      },
      {
        "id": "5030",
        "question": "An equilateral triangle must have which of the following types of angles?",
        "answer": "all three angles of 60º",
        "distractor_1": "all three angles of 45º",
        "distractor_2": "at least one straight angle",
        "distractor_3": "at least one right angle"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "154",
    "name": "Properties of Math",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "5048",
        "question": "What is the solution to the equation -4x = 16?",
        "answer": "x = -4",
        "distractor_1": "x = 4",
        "distractor_2": "x = 2",
        "distractor_3": "x = -8"
      },
      {
        "id": "5051",
        "question": "The equation 4 + (6 + 2) = (6 + 2) + 4 is an example of which property?",
        "answer": "commutative property of addition",
        "distractor_1": "identity property of addition",
        "distractor_2": "associative property of addition",
        "distractor_3": "substitution property"
      },
      {
        "id": "5052",
        "question": "Which statement illustrates the algebraic expression (5 · m) · 8 using the associative property of multiplication?",
        "answer": "8 • (5 • m)",
        "distractor_1": "5 • m • 8",
        "distractor_2": "5 • (m • 8)",
        "distractor_3": "(5 • m) • 8"
      },
      {
        "id": "5053",
        "question": "Which of the following values is a solution to the equation x - 12 = 37?",
        "answer": "x = 49",
        "distractor_1": "x = -49",
        "distractor_2": "x = 25",
        "distractor_3": "x = 39"
      },
      {
        "id": "5054",
        "question": "What is the solution to the equation 45 = x ÷ 5?",
        "answer": "x = 225",
        "distractor_1": "x = 9",
        "distractor_2": "x = 135",
        "distractor_3": "x = 450"
      },
      {
        "id": "5055",
        "question": "Which of the following equations does not have a solution of 5?",
        "answer": "60 ÷ n = 15",
        "distractor_1": "18 - n = 13",
        "distractor_2": "46 + n = 51",
        "distractor_3": "8n = 40"
      },
      {
        "id": "5056",
        "question": "What is the solution to the equation x + -4 = -9?",
        "answer": "x = -5",
        "distractor_1": "x = 13",
        "distractor_2": "x = 5",
        "distractor_3": "x = -13"
      },
      {
        "id": "5057",
        "question": "What is the value of the expression 5 + 4 · 6 ÷ 3?",
        "answer": "13",
        "distractor_1": "7",
        "distractor_2": "9.7",
        "distractor_3": "18"
      },
      {
        "id": "5058",
        "question": "Margret solved a math problem and came up with the answer 24. Which of the following expressions also has an answer of 24?",
        "answer": "22 + 6 • 3² / 27",
        "distractor_1": "2² • 6 + 8 – 6",
        "distractor_2": "15 • (5 – 3) – 12",
        "distractor_3": "12 + 3 – 10 / 2"
      },
      {
        "id": "5059",
        "question": "What is the value of the expression 3x + 5y when x = 4 and y = 3?",
        "answer": "27",
        "distractor_1": "38",
        "distractor_2": "29",
        "distractor_3": "87"
      },
      {
        "id": "5060",
        "question": "What is the value of the expression 20x - 10 for x = 4?",
        "answer": "70",
        "distractor_1": "14",
        "distractor_2": "34",
        "distractor_3": "94"
      },
      {
        "id": "5061",
        "question": "The equation 5 + (6 + 9) = (5 + 6) + 9 is an example of what property?",
        "answer": "associative property of addition",
        "distractor_1": "identity property of addition ",
        "distractor_2": "commutative property of addition",
        "distractor_3": "associative property of multiplication"
      },
      {
        "id": "5062",
        "question": "Which statement illustrates the algebraic expression (5 · m) · 8 using the commutative property of multiplication?",
        "answer": "8 • (5 • m)",
        "distractor_1": "5 • m • 8",
        "distractor_2": "5 • (m • 8)",
        "distractor_3": "(5 • m) • 8"
      },
      {
        "id": "5063",
        "question": "Which of the following values is a solution to the equation x ÷ -7 = 7?",
        "answer": "x = -49",
        "distractor_1": "x = 25",
        "distractor_2": "x = 39",
        "distractor_3": "x = 49"
      },
      {
        "id": "5064",
        "question": "What is the solution to the equation x ÷ 3 = 12?",
        "answer": "x = 36",
        "distractor_1": "x = 4",
        "distractor_2": "x = -4",
        "distractor_3": "x = -36"
      },
      {
        "id": "5065",
        "question": "What is the solution to the equation x + -9 = -4?",
        "answer": "x = 5",
        "distractor_1": "x = -13",
        "distractor_2": "x = -5",
        "distractor_3": "x = 13"
      },
      {
        "id": "7807",
        "question": "In which numeral system was the concept of zero first used in the Americas? ",
        "answer": "Mayan numeral system",
        "distractor_1": "Roman numeral system",
        "distractor_2": "Babylonian numeral system",
        "distractor_3": "Arabic numeral system"
      },
      {
        "id": "7808",
        "question": "Peter’s goal is to earn $120 a week working odd jobs. Last month he was within $22.50 of his targeted goal. Find the range of amounts that Peter might have earned last month. ",
        "answer": "$457.50-$502.50",
        "distractor_1": "$97.50-$120.00",
        "distractor_2": "$97.50-$142.50",
        "distractor_3": "$30.00-$210.00"
      },
      {
        "id": "7809",
        "question": "What is the identity element for division?",
        "answer": "There isn't one.",
        "distractor_1": "1",
        "distractor_2": "-1",
        "distractor_3": "0"
      },
      {
        "id": "7810",
        "question": "Solve. -6 + 9 + -8 = ?",
        "answer": "-5",
        "distractor_1": "-23",
        "distractor_2": "5",
        "distractor_3": "23"
      },
      {
        "id": "7811",
        "question": "How many positions should you move a decimal point in the dividend if you are dividing a number by 100?",
        "answer": "to the left two places",
        "distractor_1": "to the left one place",
        "distractor_2": "to the right one place",
        "distractor_3": "to the right two places"
      },
      {
        "id": "7812",
        "question": "In how many ways can Samantha fairly distribute 10 apples to 0 people?",
        "answer": "It cannot be done.",
        "distractor_1": "1",
        "distractor_2": "10",
        "distractor_3": "0"
      },
      {
        "id": "7813",
        "question": "Which property describes the statement if a = b and b = c, then a = c?",
        "answer": "Transitive Property",
        "distractor_1": "Commutative Property",
        "distractor_2": "Reflexive Property",
        "distractor_3": "Symmetric Property"
      },
      {
        "id": "7814",
        "question": "Solve. -3(-7) = ?",
        "answer": "21",
        "distractor_1": "-21",
        "distractor_2": "-343",
        "distractor_3": "343"
      },
      {
        "id": "7815",
        "question": "A collection of objects.",
        "answer": "set",
        "distractor_1": "subset",
        "distractor_2": "superset",
        "distractor_3": "quadrant"
      },
      {
        "id": "7816",
        "question": "A set contained within another set. ",
        "answer": "subset",
        "distractor_1": "superset",
        "distractor_2": "set",
        "distractor_3": "quadrant"
      },
      {
        "id": "7817",
        "question": "A set which contains a set.",
        "answer": "superset",
        "distractor_1": "subset",
        "distractor_2": "set",
        "distractor_3": "quadrant"
      },
      {
        "id": "7818",
        "question": "A finite collection of symbols including constants, variables, operations, relations, and other entities.",
        "answer": "expression",
        "distractor_1": "integer",
        "distractor_2": "absolute value",
        "distractor_3": "rational number"
      },
      {
        "id": "7819",
        "question": "Algebraically: the numerical value of a number without regard to its sign. Graphically: The distance of a number from zero.",
        "answer": "absolute value",
        "distractor_1": "expression",
        "distractor_2": "integer",
        "distractor_3": "rational number"
      },
      {
        "id": "7820",
        "question": "The sectors of a two- or three- dimensional coordinate system.",
        "answer": "quadrant",
        "distractor_1": "rational number",
        "distractor_2": "numerator",
        "distractor_3": "denominator"
      },
      {
        "id": "7821",
        "question": "A subset of the real numbers without the fractional or decimal component.",
        "answer": "integer",
        "distractor_1": "expression",
        "distractor_2": "absolute value",
        "distractor_3": "rational number"
      },
      {
        "id": "7822",
        "question": "Any number that can be represented as a ratio of integers.",
        "answer": "rational number",
        "distractor_1": "integer",
        "distractor_2": "expression",
        "distractor_3": "real number"
      },
      {
        "id": "7823",
        "question": "A superset of numbers made of the set of rational and irrational numbers.",
        "answer": "real number",
        "distractor_1": "rational number",
        "distractor_2": "integer",
        "distractor_3": "expression"
      },
      {
        "id": "7803",
        "question": "What is the solution to 16 + 8 (mod 4)?",
        "answer": "0",
        "distractor_1": "1",
        "distractor_2": "4",
        "distractor_3": "24"
      },
      {
        "id": "7804",
        "question": "What is the value of the expression 5 + 4 • 6 ÷ 3?",
        "answer": "13",
        "distractor_1": "7",
        "distractor_2": "9.7",
        "distractor_3": "18"
      },
      {
        "id": "7805",
        "question": "What is the solution to 12 + 4 (mod 3)?",
        "answer": "1",
        "distractor_1": "0",
        "distractor_2": "16",
        "distractor_3": "3"
      },
      {
        "id": "7824",
        "question": "In a common fraction this number represents a number of equal parts. It is always given on top of a fraction.",
        "answer": "numerator",
        "distractor_1": "denominator",
        "distractor_2": "real number",
        "distractor_3": "rational number"
      },
      {
        "id": "7825",
        "question": "In a common fraction this number represents how much makes up a whole.  It is always given on the bottom of a fraction.",
        "answer": "denominator",
        "distractor_1": "numerator",
        "distractor_2": "real number",
        "distractor_3": "rational number"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "153",
    "name": "Home Makeover",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "5332",
        "question": "Which type of spray painting system produces less overspray and applies paint more efficiently?",
        "answer": "high volume, low pressure (HVLP)",
        "distractor_1": "high pressure, low volume (HPLV)",
        "distractor_2": "high volume, high pressure (HVHP)",
        "distractor_3": "airless"
      },
      {
        "id": "5333",
        "question": "Metal roofing is sold by the square, which is 100 square feet. How much metal roofing would be required for a shed roof that is 20 feet wide and 40 feet long?  ",
        "answer": "8 squares",
        "distractor_1": "8,000 squares",
        "distractor_2": "800 squares",
        "distractor_3": "80 squares"
      },
      {
        "id": "5334",
        "question": "Which two factors affect how long paint lasts?",
        "answer": "moisture and age",
        "distractor_1": "air temperature and age",
        "distractor_2": "color and moisture",
        "distractor_3": "color and air temperature"
      },
      {
        "id": "5335",
        "question": "How wide should the main entrance door for a house be?",
        "answer": "36 inches",
        "distractor_1": "32 inches",
        "distractor_2": "40 inches",
        "distractor_3": "48 inches"
      },
      {
        "id": "5337",
        "question": "What is the creation of a dead air space between the warm air inside a structure and the cold air outside a structure called?",
        "answer": "insulation",
        "distractor_1": "sheathing",
        "distractor_2": "roofing",
        "distractor_3": "siding"
      },
      {
        "id": "5338",
        "question": "How much wider can a building with a 4:12 slope roof be if the trusses are built with 2 x 6 lumber rather than 2 x 4 lumber? A.B.C.D.",
        "answer": "12'",
        "distractor_1": "10'",
        "distractor_2": "14'",
        "distractor_3": "7'"
      },
      {
        "id": "5339",
        "question": "A certain brand of wood siding is sold in 12 inch x 16 foot lengths. Each row of siding will cover 11 inches of wall height. How many rows of siding will be needed to cover a wall 31 feet wide and 10 feet high?",
        "answer": "11 rows",
        "distractor_1": "10 rows",
        "distractor_2": "12 rows",
        "distractor_3": "32 rows"
      },
      {
        "id": "5236",
        "question": "What advantage does a gambrel-style roof have over a hip-style roof?",
        "answer": "allows more usable space on the second floor",
        "distractor_1": "requires fewer shingles than a hip roof",
        "distractor_2": "uses longer lumber to build",
        "distractor_3": "uses fewer nails"
      },
      {
        "id": "5237",
        "question": "What is the largest single investment the average person will make?",
        "answer": "buying a house",
        "distractor_1": "buying a car",
        "distractor_2": "buying stock",
        "distractor_3": "buying a computer"
      },
      {
        "id": "5238",
        "question": "When is a truss most useful?",
        "answer": "when you need to span a long distance without support in the middle",
        "distractor_1": "when the home is in an extremely cold area",
        "distractor_2": "when a building is small",
        "distractor_3": "when labor is inexpensive"
      },
      {
        "id": "5239",
        "question": "How many square feet does one square of shingles cover?",
        "answer": "100 square feet",
        "distractor_1": "50 square feet",
        "distractor_2": "33 square feet",
        "distractor_3": "1,000 square feet"
      },
      {
        "id": "5240",
        "question": "How many square feet are in one square yard.",
        "answer": "9 square feet",
        "distractor_1": "27 square feet",
        "distractor_2": "3 square feet",
        "distractor_3": "6 square feet"
      },
      {
        "id": "5243",
        "question": "When is a truss most often used?",
        "answer": "when you need to span a long distance without support in the middle",
        "distractor_1": "when the home is in an extremely cold area",
        "distractor_2": "when a building is small",
        "distractor_3": "when labor is inexpensive"
      },
      {
        "id": "5244",
        "question": "How many years should a new asphalt-shingle roof last?",
        "answer": "15 to 30 years",
        "distractor_1": "30 to 60 years",
        "distractor_2": "10 to 15 years",
        "distractor_3": "5 to 10 years"
      },
      {
        "id": "5245",
        "question": "Which of the following is most likely to cause damage to a house?",
        "answer": "moisture",
        "distractor_1": "dry air",
        "distractor_2": "heat",
        "distractor_3": "cold"
      },
      {
        "id": "5246",
        "question": "What is the most commonly used residential roofing material?",
        "answer": "asphalt shingles",
        "distractor_1": "clay tile",
        "distractor_2": "slate",
        "distractor_3": "expanded metal"
      },
      {
        "id": "5249",
        "question": "What is the largest single investment the average person will make?",
        "answer": "buying a house",
        "distractor_1": "buying mutual funds",
        "distractor_2": "buying a car",
        "distractor_3": "buying a computer"
      },
      {
        "id": "5251",
        "question": "What is the formula for finding the area of a triangle?",
        "answer": "area = 1/2(base * height)",
        "distractor_1": "area = length * width * 2",
        "distractor_2": "area = base * height",
        "distractor_3": "area = pi * r2"
      },
      {
        "id": "5253",
        "question": "One square of shingles covers how many square feet?",
        "answer": "100 square feet",
        "distractor_1": "50 square feet",
        "distractor_2": "1,000 square feet",
        "distractor_3": "33 square feet"
      },
      {
        "id": "5255",
        "question": "What is the slope of a roof?",
        "answer": "the rise divided by the run",
        "distractor_1": "the rise divided by the span",
        "distractor_2": "the width divided by the length",
        "distractor_3": "the rise divided by the height"
      },
      {
        "id": "5434",
        "question": "Which of the following is a layer of material added to framing to increase its strength and provide a surface for attaching finishing materials?",
        "answer": "sheathing",
        "distractor_1": "insulation",
        "distractor_2": "eaves",
        "distractor_3": "foundation"
      },
      {
        "id": "5435",
        "question": "What is the term for the framework made up of triangles used to support a roof or floor?",
        "answer": "truss",
        "distractor_1": "eave",
        "distractor_2": "rafter",
        "distractor_3": "foundation"
      },
      {
        "id": "5427",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a characteristic of latex paint? ",
        "answer": "difficult to clean up",
        "distractor_1": "quick drying",
        "distractor_2": "low odor",
        "distractor_3": "easy soap-and-water cleanup"
      },
      {
        "id": "5428",
        "question": "Which of the following is a very durable fired clay tile used for flooring?",
        "answer": "ceramic tile",
        "distractor_1": "wood laminate",
        "distractor_2": "porcelain tile",
        "distractor_3": "concrete tile"
      },
      {
        "id": "5429",
        "question": "Which of the following is a legal pledge of property to a creditor as security for the payment of a loan or debt?",
        "answer": "mortgage ",
        "distractor_1": "lien",
        "distractor_2": "contract",
        "distractor_3": "agreement"
      },
      {
        "id": "5430",
        "question": "What is the lower part of a roof that projects beyond the walls?",
        "answer": "eave",
        "distractor_1": "sheathing",
        "distractor_2": "rafter",
        "distractor_3": "foundation"
      },
      {
        "id": "5431",
        "question": "Which of the following is defined as the support for a structure?",
        "answer": "foundation",
        "distractor_1": "truss",
        "distractor_2": "roof",
        "distractor_3": "eave"
      },
      {
        "id": "5432",
        "question": "What is the distance from one outside wall to the opposite outside wall?",
        "answer": "span",
        "distractor_1": "width",
        "distractor_2": "truss length",
        "distractor_3": "eave length"
      },
      {
        "id": "5433",
        "question": "Which of the following is a four-sided figure with two parallel sides?",
        "answer": "trapezoid",
        "distractor_1": "parallelogram",
        "distractor_2": "rhombus",
        "distractor_3": "rectangle"
      },
      {
        "id": "8130",
        "question": "What is the name of the structural member used to support a pitched roof?",
        "answer": "rafter",
        "distractor_1": "stud",
        "distractor_2": "header",
        "distractor_3": "foundation"
      },
      {
        "id": "8131",
        "question": "Which of the following paint types is water based?",
        "answer": "latex paint",
        "distractor_1": "alkyd paint",
        "distractor_2": "shellac paint",
        "distractor_3": "lacquer paint"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "155",
    "name": "Creative Problem Solving",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "6885",
        "question": "Which of the following people invented Liquid Paper? ",
        "answer": "Bette Nesmith Graham",
        "distractor_1": "George Washington Carver",
        "distractor_2": "Horace Walpole",
        "distractor_3": "Stephanie Kwolek"
      },
      {
        "id": "5256",
        "question": "During which phase of problem solving are all ideas recorded and considered?",
        "answer": "brainstorming",
        "distractor_1": "taking notes",
        "distractor_2": "testing a solution",
        "distractor_3": "evaluating a solution"
      },
      {
        "id": "5257",
        "question": "The Wright brothers' flights were examples of which part of the Synergistic Problem Solving Model?",
        "answer": "test and evaluate",
        "distractor_1": "quantify and qualify",
        "distractor_2": "brainstorm and implement",
        "distractor_3": "implement and redesign"
      },
      {
        "id": "5258",
        "question": "Edward Ellis started a diary at 16 and wrote 15 million words by the end of his 70th year. Assuming a 365-day-year, on average, about how many words did he write each day? Round to the nearest whole number.",
        "answer": "747",
        "distractor_1": "652",
        "distractor_2": "543",
        "distractor_3": "921"
      },
      {
        "id": "5259",
        "question": "Suppose 18 students take a class that lasts a semester. Creative Problem Solving is offered to two students per rotation and there are eight rotations per semester. How many students would not be able to rotate through this Module?",
        "answer": "2",
        "distractor_1": "8",
        "distractor_2": "10",
        "distractor_3": "16"
      },
      {
        "id": "5260",
        "question": "What nutrient found in grains, peas, and beans helps prevent memory loss?",
        "answer": "thiamine",
        "distractor_1": "calcium",
        "distractor_2": "protein",
        "distractor_3": "niacin"
      },
      {
        "id": "5262",
        "question": "With which of the following roles is George Washington Carver most identified?",
        "answer": "scientist",
        "distractor_1": "civil rights activist",
        "distractor_2": "computer programmer",
        "distractor_3": "lawyer"
      },
      {
        "id": "6886",
        "question": "Why are possible side effects an important consideration in selecting a solution to implement?",
        "answer": "A solution may create new problems. ",
        "distractor_1": "They are not an important consideration. ",
        "distractor_2": "People may not like them. ",
        "distractor_3": "They may not work. "
      },
      {
        "id": "5263",
        "question": "Television pilots are an example of which step of the problem solving model?",
        "answer": "testing",
        "distractor_1": "brainstorming",
        "distractor_2": "evaluating a possible solution",
        "distractor_3": "selecting or redesigning a solution"
      },
      {
        "id": "5264",
        "question": "Which of the following rules does not apply when brainstorming?",
        "answer": "make fun of someone's idea",
        "distractor_1": "communicate openly",
        "distractor_2": "approach the problem from different angles",
        "distractor_3": "record all ideas"
      },
      {
        "id": "5265",
        "question": "What is an important consideration when selecting a solution to implement?",
        "answer": "its possible side effects",
        "distractor_1": "whether it is a good or bad idea",
        "distractor_2": "whether it was the first or last idea brainstormed",
        "distractor_3": "who thought of it"
      },
      {
        "id": "5266",
        "question": "What is the name of the document that gives an inventor the exclusive right to make and sell their invention?",
        "answer": "patent",
        "distractor_1": "trademark",
        "distractor_2": "copyright",
        "distractor_3": "deed"
      },
      {
        "id": "5267",
        "question": "The Wright brothers' first flight lasted 12 seconds and traveled 37 meters. Another flight took 59 seconds and covered 260 meters. Of the two flights, which, if either, had the highest speed? Hint: To find speed, divide distance by time.",
        "answer": "the second flight",
        "distractor_1": "the first flight",
        "distractor_2": "neither flight",
        "distractor_3": "not enough information given to determine"
      },
      {
        "id": "5268",
        "question": "George Washington Carver spent most of his life solving problems related to which of the following areas?",
        "answer": "farming",
        "distractor_1": "civil rights",
        "distractor_2": "computers",
        "distractor_3": "legal cases"
      },
      {
        "id": "5270",
        "question": "Which of the following is not an example of a graphic organizer?",
        "answer": "Möbius band",
        "distractor_1": "web",
        "distractor_2": "mind map",
        "distractor_3": "Venn diagram"
      },
      {
        "id": "5271",
        "question": "Which of the following does not relate to Kevlar, Stephanie Kwolek's invention?",
        "answer": "invented to cover mistakes",
        "distractor_1": "five times stronger than steel",
        "distractor_2": "does not rust or corrode",
        "distractor_3": "used in bulletproof vests"
      },
      {
        "id": "5274",
        "question": "What is the first step in the problem-solving process?",
        "answer": "identify the problem",
        "distractor_1": "brainstorm solutions",
        "distractor_2": "evaluate ideas",
        "distractor_3": "find a solution"
      },
      {
        "id": "5275",
        "question": "Who invented the lightbulb?",
        "answer": "Joseph Wilson Swan",
        "distractor_1": "George Washington Carver",
        "distractor_2": "Thomas Edison",
        "distractor_3": "James Wright"
      },
      {
        "id": "5276",
        "question": "When brainstorming, which of the following rules does not apply?",
        "answer": "make fun of someone's idea",
        "distractor_1": "approach the problem from different angles",
        "distractor_2": "record all ideas",
        "distractor_3": "communicate openly"
      },
      {
        "id": "5277",
        "question": "What is the first step in problem solving?",
        "answer": "identifying the problem",
        "distractor_1": "brainstorming solutions",
        "distractor_2": "evaluating ideas",
        "distractor_3": "finding a solution"
      },
      {
        "id": "5278",
        "question": "Which of the following does not relate to Kevlar, Stephanie Kwolek's invention?",
        "answer": "invented to cover mistakes",
        "distractor_1": "used in bulletproof vests",
        "distractor_2": "does not rust or corrode",
        "distractor_3": "five times stronger than steel"
      },
      {
        "id": "5279",
        "question": "What portion of the brain transfers messages between the nervous system and other parts of the brain?",
        "answer": "brain stem",
        "distractor_1": "cerebrum",
        "distractor_2": "cerebellum",
        "distractor_3": "hippocampus"
      },
      {
        "id": "5280",
        "question": "When brainstorming, how many ideas should be written down and considered?",
        "answer": "all ideas presented",
        "distractor_1": "the first five ideas",
        "distractor_2": "only good ideas",
        "distractor_3": "the five most popular ideas"
      },
      {
        "id": "6887",
        "question": "Bette Nesmith Graham invented which of the following? ",
        "answer": "Liquid Paper",
        "distractor_1": "chocolate chip cookies",
        "distractor_2": "Kevlar",
        "distractor_3": "erasers"
      },
      {
        "id": "5281",
        "question": "Which one of the following is an example of the testing process?",
        "answer": "television pilot",
        "distractor_1": "computer program",
        "distractor_2": "graphic organizer",
        "distractor_3": "solution"
      },
      {
        "id": "5282",
        "question": "The Wright brothers' flights were examples of which part of the Synergistic Problem Solving Model?",
        "answer": "test and evaluate",
        "distractor_1": "implement and redesign",
        "distractor_2": "brainstorm and implement",
        "distractor_3": "quantify and qualify"
      },
      {
        "id": "6231",
        "question": "What is the instance of making discoveries by accident?",
        "answer": "Serendipity",
        "distractor_1": "Hypothesis",
        "distractor_2": "Prediction",
        "distractor_3": "Scientific Theory"
      },
      {
        "id": "6233",
        "question": "What is a possible, but untested, solution for a problem?",
        "answer": "Hypothesis",
        "distractor_1": "Prediction",
        "distractor_2": "Serendipity",
        "distractor_3": "Scientific Theory"
      },
      {
        "id": "6234",
        "question": "What is it called to give information a numerical value?",
        "answer": "Quantify",
        "distractor_1": "Qualify",
        "distractor_2": "Ream",
        "distractor_3": "Predict"
      },
      {
        "id": "6236",
        "question": "What is it to decide the quality of something based on its qualities or characteristics?",
        "answer": "Qualify",
        "distractor_1": "Quantify",
        "distractor_2": "Hypothesis ",
        "distractor_3": "Ream"
      },
      {
        "id": "6238",
        "question": "What is a visual representation of knowledge, concepts, or ideas?",
        "answer": "Graphic Organizer",
        "distractor_1": "Prediction",
        "distractor_2": "Pilot",
        "distractor_3": "Criterion"
      },
      {
        "id": "6239",
        "question": "What is a statement based on observation, experience, or special knowledge made before an event?",
        "answer": "Prediction",
        "distractor_1": "Brainstorm",
        "distractor_2": "Pilot",
        "distractor_3": "Serendipity"
      },
      {
        "id": "6240",
        "question": "What is a television show produced as a sample of a proposed series?",
        "answer": "Pilot",
        "distractor_1": "Prediction",
        "distractor_2": "Criterion",
        "distractor_3": "Try-out"
      },
      {
        "id": "6241",
        "question": "What is a standard by which you judge, decide about, or deal with something?",
        "answer": "Criterion",
        "distractor_1": "Pilot",
        "distractor_2": "Prediction",
        "distractor_3": "Standard"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "160",
    "name": "Population Perspectives",
    "weight": "95",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "5599",
        "question": "If birth and death rates in a country are balanced and immigration is occurring, what is happening to the population size?",
        "answer": "It is increasing.",
        "distractor_1": "It is decreasing.",
        "distractor_2": "It is remaining stable.",
        "distractor_3": "Unknown; too little information is given."
      },
      {
        "id": "5600",
        "question": "Demographers often use which calculation as a shortcut to understand the rate of population growth?",
        "answer": "doubling time",
        "distractor_1": "fertility rate",
        "distractor_2": "death rate",
        "distractor_3": "number added per year"
      },
      {
        "id": "5601",
        "question": "Which term is used to describe groups in a population that are separated to study their differences?",
        "answer": "cohorts",
        "distractor_1": "units",
        "distractor_2": "sets",
        "distractor_3": "combinations"
      },
      {
        "id": "5602",
        "question": "Which of the following countries is the highest-populated, Spanish-speaking country in the world?",
        "answer": "Mexico",
        "distractor_1": "Spain",
        "distractor_2": "Brazil",
        "distractor_3": "United States"
      },
      {
        "id": "5605",
        "question": "What was the change in world population from 1955 to 2005?",
        "answer": "2.78 billion to 6.45 billion",
        "distractor_1": "1.25 billion to 7.85 billion",
        "distractor_2": "4.84 billion to 5.68 billion",
        "distractor_3": "6.07 billion to 6.45 billion"
      },
      {
        "id": "5607",
        "question": "In a country being studied, B equals 20/1,000, D equals 10/1,000, and M equals -2/1,000. What is the country’s growth rate?",
        "answer": "8/1,000",
        "distractor_1": "12/1,000",
        "distractor_2": "28/1,000",
        "distractor_3": "32/1,000"
      },
      {
        "id": "5608",
        "question": "Which two population characteristics would be expected to occur in a highly developed country?",
        "answer": "high life expectancy and low infant mortality",
        "distractor_1": "high life expectancy and high infant mortality",
        "distractor_2": "high emigration rate and low fertility rate",
        "distractor_3": "high emigration rate and high fertility rate"
      },
      {
        "id": "5609",
        "question": "When different groups of population data are represented as separate terms in a polynomial, which population characteristic is probably being studied?",
        "answer": "age cohorts",
        "distractor_1": "infant mortality rate",
        "distractor_2": "total population size",
        "distractor_3": "total fertility rate"
      },
      {
        "id": "5610",
        "question": "In addition to population growth rate, which factor has the greatest effect on the number of people added to a population per year?",
        "answer": "starting population",
        "distractor_1": "migration rate",
        "distractor_2": "fertility rate",
        "distractor_3": "life expectancy"
      },
      {
        "id": "5611",
        "question": "In a rapidly growing population, the change in population size can be shown by which type of graph?",
        "answer": "exponential growth",
        "distractor_1": "quadratic",
        "distractor_2": "exponential decay",
        "distractor_3": "linear"
      },
      {
        "id": "5612",
        "question": "Consider the statement: 'If birth rate is greater than death rate, population size increases.' What type of mathematical statement is this?",
        "answer": "inequality",
        "distractor_1": "equation",
        "distractor_2": "expression",
        "distractor_3": "factor"
      },
      {
        "id": "5613",
        "question": "What process would be used to simplify the expression (3x^2 – 2y + 3x + 4y + 5x)?",
        "answer": "combining like terms",
        "distractor_1": "multiplying like terms",
        "distractor_2": "factoring out constants and multiplying them together",
        "distractor_3": "adding positive terms and subtracting negative terms"
      },
      {
        "id": "5615",
        "question": "What method is often used to study characteristics of a population when every member cannot be counted?",
        "answer": "random sampling",
        "distractor_1": "biased sampling",
        "distractor_2": "census",
        "distractor_3": "estimation"
      },
      {
        "id": "5616",
        "question": "The expression 70 / R, where R is the population growth rate, is used to determine which population characteristic?",
        "answer": "doubling time",
        "distractor_1": "fertility rate",
        "distractor_2": "life expectancy",
        "distractor_3": "migration rate"
      },
      {
        "id": "5617",
        "question": "Which type of function forms a J-shaped curve when graphed?",
        "answer": "exponential",
        "distractor_1": "linear",
        "distractor_2": "logistic",
        "distractor_3": "quadratic"
      },
      {
        "id": "5618",
        "question": "Which method is used to determine population size by counting every member of the population?",
        "answer": "census",
        "distractor_1": "random sampling",
        "distractor_2": "biased sampling",
        "distractor_3": "estimation"
      },
      {
        "id": "5619",
        "question": "The equation y = C(1 + r)^t is an example of which type of function?",
        "answer": "exponential",
        "distractor_1": "linear",
        "distractor_2": "logistic",
        "distractor_3": "quadratic"
      },
      {
        "id": "5623",
        "question": "If growth rates in two countries are equal, what effect does a large starting population have on number of people added per year?",
        "answer": "It increases the number added because more people are available to reproduce.",
        "distractor_1": "It decreases the number added because more deaths occur.",
        "distractor_2": "It decreases the number added because more people emigrate.",
        "distractor_3": "It has no effect because only growth rate determines number of people added."
      },
      {
        "id": "5624",
        "question": "Which country is highly developed, with a zero or slightly negative growth rate?",
        "answer": "Germany",
        "distractor_1": "China",
        "distractor_2": "Haiti",
        "distractor_3": "United States"
      },
      {
        "id": "5625",
        "question": "In a poor, developing country, which population characteristic would typically be low compared to the same characteristic in a developed country?",
        "answer": "life expectancy",
        "distractor_1": "population growth rate",
        "distractor_2": "migration rate",
        "distractor_3": "infant mortality rate"
      },
      {
        "id": "5626",
        "question": "Which type of function forms a parabola when it is graphed?",
        "answer": "quadratic",
        "distractor_1": "linear",
        "distractor_2": "exponential",
        "distractor_3": "logistic"
      },
      {
        "id": "5627",
        "question": "In which of the following situations would you solve a problem using the exponential decay equation?",
        "answer": "change in value of a tractor over 7 years",
        "distractor_1": "compound interest earned on an investment",
        "distractor_2": "number of bacteria reproduced in an hour",
        "distractor_3": "change in household income in the last 30 years"
      },
      {
        "id": "5628",
        "question": "Which country has a positive growth rate that is mostly due to high levels of immigration?",
        "answer": "United States",
        "distractor_1": "Mexico",
        "distractor_2": "Haiti",
        "distractor_3": "China"
      },
      {
        "id": "5629",
        "question": "The equation y = ax^2 + bx + c is an example of which type of function?",
        "answer": "quadratic",
        "distractor_1": "linear",
        "distractor_2": "logistic",
        "distractor_3": "exponential"
      },
      {
        "id": "5630",
        "question": "The change in a car’s value over time or the change in amount of radioactivity in an element over time could best be described using which type of graph?",
        "answer": "exponential decay",
        "distractor_1": "quadratic",
        "distractor_2": "linear",
        "distractor_3": "exponential growth"
      },
      {
        "id": "6077",
        "question": "What is the method of measuring population size by counting every member of the population?",
        "answer": "census",
        "distractor_1": "estimate",
        "distractor_2": "sample",
        "distractor_3": "count"
      },
      {
        "id": "6083",
        "question": "What is the term describing the study of the human population?",
        "answer": "demography",
        "distractor_1": "sociology",
        "distractor_2": "psychology",
        "distractor_3": "carrying capacity"
      },
      {
        "id": "6086",
        "question": "What is a mathematical expression consisting of a monomial or a sum or difference of two or more monomials?",
        "answer": "polynomial",
        "distractor_1": "binomial",
        "distractor_2": "trinomial",
        "distractor_3": "quadranomial"
      },
      {
        "id": "6091",
        "question": "What term describes a change in population size over a period of one year?",
        "answer": "population growth rate",
        "distractor_1": "population size",
        "distractor_2": "population change",
        "distractor_3": "doubling time"
      },
      {
        "id": "6092",
        "question": "What type of mathematical relation has one value of y for every value of x and is expressed as an ordered pair (x, y)?",
        "answer": "function",
        "distractor_1": "domain",
        "distractor_2": "range ",
        "distractor_3": "special relation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6094",
        "question": "What is the term describing the set of the first numbers of an ordered pair (x, y) in a function?",
        "answer": "domain",
        "distractor_1": "range",
        "distractor_2": "cohort",
        "distractor_3": "relation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6095",
        "question": "What is the term describing the set of the second numbers of an ordered pair (x, y) in a function?",
        "answer": "range",
        "distractor_1": "domain",
        "distractor_2": "relation",
        "distractor_3": " cohort"
      },
      {
        "id": "6098",
        "question": "What is the positive form of the exponential equation, in which values of the function increase with time?",
        "answer": "exponential growth function",
        "distractor_1": "exponential decay function",
        "distractor_2": "exponential increase function",
        "distractor_3": "exponential linear function"
      },
      {
        "id": "6100",
        "question": "What is the negative form of the exponential equation, in which values of the function decrease with time?",
        "answer": "exponential decay function",
        "distractor_1": "exponential growth function",
        "distractor_2": "exponential decrease function",
        "distractor_3": "exponential quadratic function"
      },
      {
        "id": "6102",
        "question": "What is the term for a subgroup within a larger group, all of whose members have something in common?",
        "answer": "cohort",
        "distractor_1": "category",
        "distractor_2": "unit",
        "distractor_3": "set"
      },
      {
        "id": "6103",
        "question": "What is a second-degree polynomial equation that takes the form of a parabola when graphed?",
        "answer": "quadratic function",
        "distractor_1": "exponential function",
        "distractor_2": "linear function",
        "distractor_3": "demographic function"
      },
      {
        "id": "6104",
        "question": "What is the rearrangement of the quadratic equation that enables the equation to be solved for x in terms of the constants a, b, and c?",
        "answer": "Quadratic Formula",
        "distractor_1": "Quadratic Function",
        "distractor_2": "Quadratic Process",
        "distractor_3": "Quadratic Property"
      },
      {
        "id": "6105",
        "question": "What is the term describing the number of years required for a country's population to double?",
        "answer": "doubling time",
        "distractor_1": "doubling rate",
        "distractor_2": "demographic transition",
        "distractor_3": "population growth rate"
      },
      {
        "id": "6106",
        "question": "What is the process by which the human population levels off, changing over time from high birth and death rates to low birth and death rates?",
        "answer": "demographic transition",
        "distractor_1": "carrying capacity",
        "distractor_2": "population growth curve",
        "distractor_3": "population development"
      },
      {
        "id": "6107",
        "question": "What is the maximum number of organisms of a given species, including the human species, that can be supported in a given environment?",
        "answer": "carrying capacity",
        "distractor_1": "growth capacity",
        "distractor_2": "population size",
        "distractor_3": "sustainable size"
      },
      {
        "id": "6108",
        "question": "What is the (x, y) coordinate at which a graph crosses the y-axis?",
        "answer": "y-intercept",
        "distractor_1": "y-coordinate",
        "distractor_2": "x-intercept",
        "distractor_3": "x-coordinate"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "162",
    "name": "The Universe",
    "weight": "95",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "6838",
        "question": "When astronomers make maps of the sky, what types of coordinates do they use to pinpoint the locations of stars and other celestial objects?",
        "answer": "declination and right ascension",
        "distractor_1": "latitude and longitude",
        "distractor_2": "magnitude and spectral lines",
        "distractor_3": "occultation and reflection"
      },
      {
        "id": "6839",
        "question": "The concept of parallax in astronomy is used to measure which of the following star characteristics?",
        "answer": "distance",
        "distractor_1": "size",
        "distractor_2": "brightness",
        "distractor_3": "temperature"
      },
      {
        "id": "5631",
        "question": "What units are typically used to measure distance within our solar system?",
        "answer": "miles and AUs",
        "distractor_1": "AUs and light-years",
        "distractor_2": "miles and light-years",
        "distractor_3": "light-years and parsecs"
      },
      {
        "id": "5632",
        "question": "In the life cycle of a star, which of the following stages occurs first?",
        "answer": "nebula",
        "distractor_1": "young stellar object, or YSO",
        "distractor_2": "red giant",
        "distractor_3": "white dwarf"
      },
      {
        "id": "5633",
        "question": "Most galaxies in the universe have which general shape?",
        "answer": "spiral",
        "distractor_1": "elliptical",
        "distractor_2": "bulging",
        "distractor_3": "irregular"
      },
      {
        "id": "5643",
        "question": "When a star’s absolute magnitude is -5 and its apparent magnitude is +5, what can be said about the star’s luminosity and distance?",
        "answer": "It is very bright and far away.",
        "distractor_1": "It is very dim and far away.",
        "distractor_2": "It is very dim and nearby.",
        "distractor_3": "It is very bright and nearby."
      },
      {
        "id": "5644",
        "question": "Which of the following stages occurs in the life cycle of a very large, massive star but does NOT occur in the life cycle of a Sun-like star?",
        "answer": "neutron star",
        "distractor_1": "red giant",
        "distractor_2": "white dwarf",
        "distractor_3": "young stellar object"
      },
      {
        "id": "5645",
        "question": "Stellar spectra are often used to determine which characteristic of stars?",
        "answer": "temperature",
        "distractor_1": "size",
        "distractor_2": "distance",
        "distractor_3": "apparent magnitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "5646",
        "question": "The period-luminosity relation, or relationship between the period and brightness of a variable star, is described by which mathematical function?",
        "answer": "inverse square law",
        "distractor_1": "Fundamental Counting Principle",
        "distractor_2": "Drake Equation",
        "distractor_3": "law of probability"
      },
      {
        "id": "5649",
        "question": "A pulsar is a rapidly spinning type of which of the following celestial objects?",
        "answer": "neutron star",
        "distractor_1": "black hole",
        "distractor_2": "supernova",
        "distractor_3": "brown dwarf"
      },
      {
        "id": "5653",
        "question": "Which of the following characteristics makes the Astroscan a wide-field telescope?",
        "answer": "view of larger section of sky",
        "distractor_1": "high magnification",
        "distractor_2": "close-up views",
        "distractor_3": "slightly fuzzy images"
      },
      {
        "id": "5654",
        "question": "What is the approximate distance light can travel in one year?",
        "answer": "6 • 10^12 miles",
        "distractor_1": "186,000 miles",
        "distractor_2": "300,000,000 miles",
        "distractor_3": "2.45 • 10^9 miles"
      },
      {
        "id": "5655",
        "question": "Based on its x- and y-axes, the H-R diagram classifies stars according to which two characteristics?",
        "answer": "temperature and luminosity",
        "distractor_1": "size and color",
        "distractor_2": "size and distance",
        "distractor_3": "temperature and age"
      },
      {
        "id": "5663",
        "question": "The H-R diagram, showing temperature versus luminosity for a range of stars, is best described as which type of graph?",
        "answer": "scatter plot",
        "distractor_1": "line graph",
        "distractor_2": "bar graph",
        "distractor_3": "box-and-whisker plot"
      },
      {
        "id": "5664",
        "question": "What is the correct solution for the fifth root of 100?",
        "answer": "2.512",
        "distractor_1": "5.024",
        "distractor_2": "20",
        "distractor_3": "25"
      },
      {
        "id": "5666",
        "question": "In astronomy, a scatter plot is used to show which of the following?",
        "answer": "relationship of star temperature and luminosity",
        "distractor_1": "location of stars in the Milky Way",
        "distractor_2": "rate of expansion of the universe",
        "distractor_3": "relationship of wavelength to intensity of light"
      },
      {
        "id": "5667",
        "question": "What is the shape of the Milky Way galaxy?",
        "answer": "spiral ",
        "distractor_1": "bulging",
        "distractor_2": "irregular",
        "distractor_3": "elliptical"
      },
      {
        "id": "5635",
        "question": "Which characteristic of our Sun reappears in fairly predictable cycles of about 11 years?",
        "answer": "sunspots",
        "distractor_1": "solar flares",
        "distractor_2": "solar wind",
        "distractor_3": "solar prominences"
      },
      {
        "id": "5636",
        "question": "The distance from Earth to the star Beta Centauri is approximately 1.92 quadrillion miles. What are the first factor and the exponent, respectively, if this number is expressed in scientific notation?",
        "answer": "1.92 and 15",
        "distractor_1": "1.92 and 18",
        "distractor_2": "19.2 and 14",
        "distractor_3": "192 and 14"
      },
      {
        "id": "5637",
        "question": "The speed of light is approximately 186,000 miles per second. If a star is 20 light-years from Earth, how long does it take the light from that star to reach Earth?",
        "answer": "20 years",
        "distractor_1": "186,000 years",
        "distractor_2": "186,000 / 20, or 9,300 years",
        "distractor_3": "186,000 • 20, or 3,720,000 years"
      },
      {
        "id": "5638",
        "question": "When determining a star’s absolute magnitude, which factor must be corrected for?",
        "answer": "distance",
        "distractor_1": "size",
        "distractor_2": "luminosity",
        "distractor_3": "temperature"
      },
      {
        "id": "5639",
        "question": "The distance from Earth to the star Alpha Centauri is approximately 25.8 trillion miles. Give the correct first factor and exponent, respectively, if this value is expressed in scientific notation.",
        "answer": "2.58 and 13",
        "distractor_1": "2.58 and 12",
        "distractor_2": "25.8 and 12",
        "distractor_3": "25.8 and 13"
      },
      {
        "id": "5660",
        "question": "What units are typically used to measure distances within and between galaxies?",
        "answer": "light-years and parsecs",
        "distractor_1": "miles and AUs",
        "distractor_2": "AUs and light-years",
        "distractor_3": "miles and light-years"
      },
      {
        "id": "5661",
        "question": "The inverse square law relates distance to luminosity of a star. If a star is the same size as the Sun but is 1,000 times farther away, what will its relative luminosity be?",
        "answer": "1,000,000 times dimmer",
        "distractor_1": "1,000 times brighter",
        "distractor_2": "1,000 times dimmer",
        "distractor_3": "1,000,000 times brighter"
      },
      {
        "id": "5662",
        "question": "The Milky Way galaxy contains what type or types of stars?",
        "answer": "a mix of old, young, and newly forming stars",
        "distractor_1": "mostly old stars",
        "distractor_2": "mostly young stars",
        "distractor_3": "a mix of young and newly forming stars"
      },
      {
        "id": "6125",
        "question": "What is a distance measurement used to express distances between galaxies, which is equivalent to about 3.26 LY?",
        "answer": "parsec",
        "distractor_1": "astronomical unit",
        "distractor_2": "light-year",
        "distractor_3": "scientific notation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6126",
        "question": "What is the distance between two troughs or two peaks of a light wave?",
        "answer": "wavelength",
        "distractor_1": "wave form",
        "distractor_2": "wave distance",
        "distractor_3": "wave height"
      },
      {
        "id": "6127",
        "question": "What is an associated group of billions of stars plus the gases and dust between them?",
        "answer": "galaxy",
        "distractor_1": "stellar cluster",
        "distractor_2": "solar system",
        "distractor_3": "extrasolar system"
      },
      {
        "id": "6128",
        "question": "What is the term for the total energy released per second by a star?",
        "answer": "luminosity",
        "distractor_1": "star power",
        "distractor_2": "kelvin temperature",
        "distractor_3": "fusion"
      },
      {
        "id": "6129",
        "question": "What is a graph in which individual (x, y) coordinates are plotted for each data point in a data set?",
        "answer": "scatter plot",
        "distractor_1": "line graph",
        "distractor_2": "line of fit",
        "distractor_3": "extrapolation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6130",
        "question": "What is a cloud of gas and dust in interstellar space from which a new star is formed?",
        "answer": "nebula",
        "distractor_1": "YSO",
        "distractor_2": "supernova",
        "distractor_3": "red dwarf"
      },
      {
        "id": "6131",
        "question": "What is the term for a graph of intensity versus wavelength of an object, which describes the amount of light it produces at each wavelength, or color?",
        "answer": "spectrum",
        "distractor_1": "blackbody",
        "distractor_2": "scatter plot",
        "distractor_3": "spectral analysis"
      },
      {
        "id": "6132",
        "question": "What is a perfect absorber of light, such as a star?",
        "answer": "blackbody",
        "distractor_1": "whitebody",
        "distractor_2": "spectrum",
        "distractor_3": "redshift"
      },
      {
        "id": "6133",
        "question": "What is the mathematical concept stating that the apparent brightness of a star decreases as the square of the distance from it?",
        "answer": "inverse square law",
        "distractor_1": "absolute square law",
        "distractor_2": "blackbody law",
        "distractor_3": "redshift law"
      },
      {
        "id": "6134",
        "question": "What is the perception that, as light moves away from an observer, the wavelengths appear longer?",
        "answer": "redshift",
        "distractor_1": "blueshift",
        "distractor_2": "apparent magnitude",
        "distractor_3": "absolute magnitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "6135",
        "question": "What is the term for the likelihood that a given event will occur?",
        "answer": "probability",
        "distractor_1": "possibility",
        "distractor_2": "outcome",
        "distractor_3": "ratio"
      },
      {
        "id": "6119",
        "question": "What is the term for all the matter and energy that make up everything, including Earth, stars and galaxies, and intergalactic space?",
        "answer": "universe",
        "distractor_1": "spectrum",
        "distractor_2": "magnitude",
        "distractor_3": "galactic center"
      },
      {
        "id": "6120",
        "question": "What is the term for a number that describes how bright a star appears from Earth?",
        "answer": "apparent magnitude",
        "distractor_1": "absolute magnitude",
        "distractor_2": "apparent luminosity",
        "distractor_3": "absolute luminosity"
      },
      {
        "id": "6121",
        "question": "What is the term for a number that describes how bright a star actually is?",
        "answer": "absolute magnitude",
        "distractor_1": "apparent magnitude",
        "distractor_2": "apparent luminosity",
        "distractor_3": "absolute luminosity"
      },
      {
        "id": "6122",
        "question": "What is the term for a superscript number, such as the 3 in x³, that indicates how many times the base, x, is used as a factor?",
        "answer": "exponent",
        "distractor_1": "power",
        "distractor_2": "numeral",
        "distractor_3": "multiple"
      },
      {
        "id": "6123",
        "question": "What is a group of related stars formed at approximately the same time from the same materials?",
        "answer": "stellar cluster",
        "distractor_1": "galaxy",
        "distractor_2": "star group",
        "distractor_3": "galactic cluster"
      },
      {
        "id": "6124",
        "question": "What is the term for the distance light travels in one year, which is approximately equal to 300 million meters per second, or 186,000 miles per second?",
        "answer": "light-year",
        "distractor_1": "parsec",
        "distractor_2": "astronomical unit",
        "distractor_3": "scientific notation"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "161",
    "name": "Climate Change",
    "weight": "90",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "6843",
        "question": "The Keeling Curve illustrates changing concentrations of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere at what location?",
        "answer": "Mauna Loa, Hawaii",
        "distractor_1": "Tokyo, Japan",
        "distractor_2": "London, England",
        "distractor_3": "Larsen B ice shelf, Antarctica"
      },
      {
        "id": "5668",
        "question": "Melting of which of the following ice sources does NOT cause sea levels to rise?",
        "answer": "Arctic sea ice",
        "distractor_1": "Greenland ice sheet",
        "distractor_2": "Antarctic ice sheet",
        "distractor_3": "mountain glaciers and ice caps"
      },
      {
        "id": "5669",
        "question": "As ice cover melts, the bare earth that is exposed absorbs more heat, causing the rate of ice melt to increase further. This is an example of which process?",
        "answer": "positive feedback",
        "distractor_1": "negative feedback",
        "distractor_2": "temperature mitigation",
        "distractor_3": "temperature stabilization"
      },
      {
        "id": "5670",
        "question": "Which of the following sets of terms consist only of like terms?",
        "answer": "2x², 3x², 4x²",
        "distractor_1": "2x, 2x², 2x³",
        "distractor_2": "3x, 3xy, 3z",
        "distractor_3": "5, (5x + 3), (x² + 5x)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5674",
        "question": "Approximately what percentage of the total gases in Earth’s atmosphere are greenhouse gases?",
        "answer": "about 0.04%",
        "distractor_1": "about 1%",
        "distractor_2": "about 21%",
        "distractor_3": "about 78%"
      },
      {
        "id": "5675",
        "question": "The largest rise in sea level would be caused by the complete melting of which ice source?",
        "answer": "Greenland and Antarctic ice sheets",
        "distractor_1": "Arctic and Antarctic sea ice",
        "distractor_2": "glaciers and ice caps",
        "distractor_3": "permafrost"
      },
      {
        "id": "5676",
        "question": "How does the concentration of greenhouse gases, excluding water, compare to the concentration of other gases in the atmosphere?",
        "answer": "They have the lowest concentration.",
        "distractor_1": "They have the highest concentration.",
        "distractor_2": "They have about the same concentration as argon.",
        "distractor_3": "They have about the same concentration as oxygen."
      },
      {
        "id": "5677",
        "question": "What is the correct procedure for multiplying polynomials?",
        "answer": "Multiply coefficients and add exponents.",
        "distractor_1": "Add coefficients and multiply exponents.",
        "distractor_2": "Add both coefficients and exponents.",
        "distractor_3": "Multiply both coefficients and exponents."
      },
      {
        "id": "5680",
        "question": "Which expression is a trinomial?",
        "answer": "3a + b² – c",
        "distractor_1": "a² • b² • c²",
        "distractor_2": "4b(abc² • 3ac)",
        "distractor_3": "(4a + 3b – c²) / 2ac"
      },
      {
        "id": "5682",
        "question": "What is the degree of the polynomial x³ + 3x² – 4xy + 6?",
        "answer": "3",
        "distractor_1": "2",
        "distractor_2": "4",
        "distractor_3": "6"
      },
      {
        "id": "5683",
        "question": "Levels of confidence, percent likelihood of a given outcome, and levels of scientific understanding are all descriptions used by scientists to explain which characteristic of the data they have collected?",
        "answer": "reliability",
        "distractor_1": "amount",
        "distractor_2": "source",
        "distractor_3": "importance"
      },
      {
        "id": "5684",
        "question": "As Earth’s average temperature increases, what happens to albedo in polar areas?",
        "answer": "It decreases.",
        "distractor_1": "It becomes more predictable.",
        "distractor_2": "It is not affected.",
        "distractor_3": "It increases."
      },
      {
        "id": "5689",
        "question": "A conclusion of the IPCC report that is described as “very likely' has what percentage likelihood of being correct?",
        "answer": "90%",
        "distractor_1": "67%",
        "distractor_2": "75%",
        "distractor_3": "95%"
      },
      {
        "id": "5690",
        "question": "As Earth’s average temperature increases, what happens to weather patterns in temperate and tropical regions?",
        "answer": "Storms and precipitation become more extreme.",
        "distractor_1": "Weather doesn’t change, because temperature changes are least in these regions.",
        "distractor_2": "Weather conditions become less variable and more predictable.",
        "distractor_3": "Storms and precipitation become less extreme."
      },
      {
        "id": "5691",
        "question": "An ice-albedo feedback occurs when sunlight is reflected from ice, further decreasing temperatures and causing more ice to form. How does global warming affect this process?",
        "answer": "sets up a new positive feedback system, increasing ice melt",
        "distractor_1": "changes positive to negative feedback, increasing ice melt",
        "distractor_2": "changes negative to positive feedback, decreasing ice melt",
        "distractor_3": "sets up a new negative feedback system, decreasing ice melt"
      },
      {
        "id": "5692",
        "question": "Which expression is a binomial?",
        "answer": "a + b",
        "distractor_1": "abc",
        "distractor_2": "a • b",
        "distractor_3": "(a + b) / c"
      },
      {
        "id": "5693",
        "question": "In what regions of Earth are average temperatures increasing most rapidly?",
        "answer": "polar and tundra regions",
        "distractor_1": "tropical regions",
        "distractor_2": "subtropical regions",
        "distractor_3": "temperate regions"
      },
      {
        "id": "5694",
        "question": "What is the degree of the monomial 4x³y²z?",
        "answer": "6",
        "distractor_1": "3",
        "distractor_2": "4",
        "distractor_3": "5"
      },
      {
        "id": "5696",
        "question": "Which property is used to simplify the expression 10x – 2(3x + y)?",
        "answer": "Distributive Property",
        "distractor_1": "Multiplicative Property",
        "distractor_2": "Commutative Property",
        "distractor_3": "Associative Property"
      },
      {
        "id": "5698",
        "question": "Which area would most likely have the lowest albedo?",
        "answer": "dense, dark green rain forest",
        "distractor_1": "Antarctic ice sheet",
        "distractor_2": "light, sandy desert",
        "distractor_3": "light green spring wheat field"
      },
      {
        "id": "5699",
        "question": "What is the correct procedure for dividing polynomials?",
        "answer": "Divide coefficients and subtract exponents.",
        "distractor_1": "Subtract both coefficients and exponents.",
        "distractor_2": "Divide both coefficients and exponents.",
        "distractor_3": "Subtract coefficients and divide exponents."
      },
      {
        "id": "6136",
        "question": "What is the term for long-lasting changes in temperature, precipitation, storm cycles, and other climatic patterns?",
        "answer": "climate change",
        "distractor_1": "global warming",
        "distractor_2": "greenhouse effect",
        "distractor_3": "weather cycle"
      },
      {
        "id": "6137",
        "question": "What is the situation in which more heat is produced on Earth than can be radiated out of the atmosphere?",
        "answer": "global warming",
        "distractor_1": "greenhouse effect",
        "distractor_2": "climate change",
        "distractor_3": "radiative forcing"
      },
      {
        "id": "6138",
        "question": "What is the term for a gas such as carbon dioxide, methane, ozone, or nitrous oxide that traps and reradiates heat within Earth's atmosphere?",
        "answer": "greenhouse gas",
        "distractor_1": "reactive gas",
        "distractor_2": "radiative forcing gas",
        "distractor_3": "global warming gas"
      },
      {
        "id": "6139",
        "question": "What is the term describing the net effect of all factors that affect global heating and cooling?",
        "answer": "radiative forcing",
        "distractor_1": "global warming",
        "distractor_2": "mitigation",
        "distractor_3": "carbon stabilization"
      },
      {
        "id": "6140",
        "question": "What is the term for a value that is far outside the mean of a data set?",
        "answer": "outlier",
        "distractor_1": "peripheral",
        "distractor_2": "scout",
        "distractor_3": "extrapolation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6141",
        "question": "What is the term that describes a statistical measure of the degree of reliability of a data set?",
        "answer": "level of confidence",
        "distractor_1": "level of reliability",
        "distractor_2": "probability",
        "distractor_3": "likelihood"
      },
      {
        "id": "6142",
        "question": "What is the term describing the percentage of radiation reflected from a surface?",
        "answer": "albedo",
        "distractor_1": "reflectivity",
        "distractor_2": "percent radiation",
        "distractor_3": "percent absorption"
      },
      {
        "id": "6143",
        "question": "What is the process of extending a data line to predict values beyond the existing data?",
        "answer": "extrapolation",
        "distractor_1": "estimation",
        "distractor_2": "interpolation",
        "distractor_3": "mitigation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6144",
        "question": "What is the term for the likelihood of the occurrence of a given event expressed as a percentage?",
        "answer": "probability",
        "distractor_1": "possibility",
        "distractor_2": "outcome",
        "distractor_3": "level of confidence"
      },
      {
        "id": "6146",
        "question": "What is the term describing permanently frozen soil?",
        "answer": "permafrost",
        "distractor_1": "permasoil",
        "distractor_2": "cryosphere",
        "distractor_3": "ice cap"
      },
      {
        "id": "6147",
        "question": "What is the process of reducing the impact of an action or situation?",
        "answer": "mitigation",
        "distractor_1": "stabilization",
        "distractor_2": "extrapolation",
        "distractor_3": "negative feedback"
      },
      {
        "id": "6149",
        "question": "What is the term for a mathematical expression consisting of a monomial or of two or more monomials added to or subtracted from each other?",
        "answer": "polynomial",
        "distractor_1": "binomial",
        "distractor_2": "trinomial",
        "distractor_3": "function"
      },
      {
        "id": "6150",
        "question": "What is the term for the change in a quantity or amount over a given time period?",
        "answer": "rate of change",
        "distractor_1": "rate of increase",
        "distractor_2": "percent of change",
        "distractor_3": "percent of increase"
      },
      {
        "id": "6151",
        "question": "What is the term for all the frozen regions on Earth?",
        "answer": "cryosphere",
        "distractor_1": "ice sheets",
        "distractor_2": "permafrost",
        "distractor_3": "glaciers"
      },
      {
        "id": "6735",
        "question": "What is the structure used to organize data into rows and columns so the data can be added or multiplied?",
        "answer": "matrix",
        "distractor_1": "element",
        "distractor_2": "scalar",
        "distractor_3": "table"
      },
      {
        "id": "8523",
        "question": "According to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, when is the official Atlantic hurricane season?",
        "answer": "June 1 to November 30",
        "distractor_1": "April 1 to September 30",
        "distractor_2": "May 1 to October 31",
        "distractor_3": "July 1 to December 31 "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "156",
    "name": "Projectile Motion",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8264",
        "question": "Which of the equations listed is not a quadratic equation?",
        "answer": "y = 3x - 6             ",
        "distractor_1": "y = 3x² + 2x + 1",
        "distractor_2": "y = 6x² - 9",
        "distractor_3": "y = 3x²"
      },
      {
        "id": "8677",
        "question": "When and by what country were the first mass-produced, long-range rockets developed?",
        "answer": "in 1944 by Germany",
        "distractor_1": "in 1956 by the Soviet Union",
        "distractor_2": "in 1962 by the United States",
        "distractor_3": "in 1978 by China"
      },
      {
        "id": "5720",
        "question": "What angle should you use to launch a straw rocket so that it will travel the farthest horizontal distance before hitting the floor? ",
        "answer": "45 degrees",
        "distractor_1": "15 degrees",
        "distractor_2": "30 degrees",
        "distractor_3": "60 degrees"
      },
      {
        "id": "5722",
        "question": "What is the name for a graph with a curved line?",
        "answer": "parabola",
        "distractor_1": "mandala",
        "distractor_2": "hyperbola",
        "distractor_3": "quadratic "
      },
      {
        "id": "5723",
        "question": "Which of the following equations is a quadratic equation?",
        "answer": "y =-1/4x² + 2x  ",
        "distractor_1": "y = 1/2x³+ 4x",
        "distractor_2": "y = x³ + 2x² + 4",
        "distractor_3": "y = 4x³ + 8"
      },
      {
        "id": "5724",
        "question": "If the x-coordinate of the vertex is 1 for the equation y = 2x² - 4x + 6, what is the y-coordinate of the vertex?",
        "answer": "4",
        "distractor_1": "0",
        "distractor_2": "2",
        "distractor_3": "6"
      },
      {
        "id": "5725",
        "question": "The equation y = -2x² + 12x - 14 has a vertex at (3, 4). How will the graph of this equation open?",
        "answer": "downward with highest point at (3, 4)",
        "distractor_1": "upward with lowest point at (3, 4) ",
        "distractor_2": "downward with lowest point at (3, 4)",
        "distractor_3": "upward with highest point at (3, 4)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5726",
        "question": "The Quadratic Formula is x = -b ± the square root of (b² - 4ac) / 2a. If you want to use the Quadratic Formula to find the roots of the equation 0 = x² + 2x + 3, what number would you substitute for b?",
        "answer": "2",
        "distractor_1": "3",
        "distractor_2": "1",
        "distractor_3": "0"
      },
      {
        "id": "5727",
        "question": "The Chinese are credited with developing the earliest rockets about one thousand years ago. How were these rockets powered?",
        "answer": "burning gunpowder",
        "distractor_1": "burning saltpeter",
        "distractor_2": "burning hydrogen and oxygen",
        "distractor_3": "burning sulfur"
      },
      {
        "id": "5728",
        "question": "In 1926, American Robert Goddard built the first successful rocket with what unique characteristic?",
        "answer": "It was powered by liquid fuel.",
        "distractor_1": "It had multiple stages (engines).",
        "distractor_2": "It carried a human passenger.",
        "distractor_3": "It escaped Earth's atmosphere."
      },
      {
        "id": "5730",
        "question": "In January 1958, this satellite became the first American satellite in space.",
        "answer": "Explorer 1",
        "distractor_1": "Luna 1",
        "distractor_2": "Sputnik 1",
        "distractor_3": "Apollo 1"
      },
      {
        "id": "8678",
        "question": "By whom and when were the first rockets launched?",
        "answer": "by the Chinese 1,000 years ago",
        "distractor_1": "by the Germans 2,000 years ago",
        "distractor_2": "by the Russians 500 years ago",
        "distractor_3": "by the Americans 100 years ago"
      },
      {
        "id": "5965",
        "question": "This term is defined as an equation of the general form ax² + bx + c = 0, where x is the independent variable and a, b, and c are constants.",
        "answer": "quadratic equation",
        "distractor_1": "slope-intercept form",
        "distractor_2": "Quadratic Formula",
        "distractor_3": "Conservation of Mass"
      },
      {
        "id": "5966",
        "question": "This term is defined as s symbol or arrangement of symbols that indicates a mathematical quantity or relationship between quantities.",
        "answer": "expression",
        "distractor_1": "square root",
        "distractor_2": "coefficient",
        "distractor_3": "parabola"
      },
      {
        "id": "5967",
        "question": "This term is defined as a mathematical quantity or a symbol that represents it.",
        "answer": "variable",
        "distractor_1": "constant",
        "distractor_2": "coefficient",
        "distractor_3": "formula"
      },
      {
        "id": "5968",
        "question": "This term is defined as a number that has a fixed value in a specific situation.",
        "answer": "constant",
        "distractor_1": "variable",
        "distractor_2": "expression",
        "distractor_3": "vertex"
      },
      {
        "id": "5969",
        "question": "This term is defined as a number or symbol multiplying a variable or an unknown quantity in an algebraic term.",
        "answer": "coefficient",
        "distractor_1": "inequality",
        "distractor_2": "vertex",
        "distractor_3": "parabola"
      },
      {
        "id": "5970",
        "question": "This term is defined as a divisor of a number that when squared gives the number.",
        "answer": "square root",
        "distractor_1": "vertex",
        "distractor_2": "parabola",
        "distractor_3": "variable"
      },
      {
        "id": "5971",
        "question": "This term is defined as the highest point of something; the apex or summit.",
        "answer": "vertex",
        "distractor_1": "line of symmetry",
        "distractor_2": "parabola",
        "distractor_3": "quadratic expression"
      },
      {
        "id": "5972",
        "question": "This term is defined as a mathematical statement that one number is greater than or less than another number.",
        "answer": "inequality",
        "distractor_1": "variable",
        "distractor_2": "constant",
        "distractor_3": "coefficient"
      },
      {
        "id": "5973",
        "question": "This term is defined as a line that divides a figure into two mirror-image halves. ",
        "answer": "line of symmetry",
        "distractor_1": "line of equilibrium",
        "distractor_2": "equator line",
        "distractor_3": "line dance"
      },
      {
        "id": "5974",
        "question": "This term is defined as a coordinate whose value is determined by measuring parallel to an x-axis.",
        "answer": "x-coordinate",
        "distractor_1": "y-coordinate",
        "distractor_2": "z-coordinate",
        "distractor_3": "coordinate"
      },
      {
        "id": "5975",
        "question": "This term is defined as a coordinate whose value is determined by measuring parallel to a y-axis.",
        "answer": "y-coordinate",
        "distractor_1": "x-coordinate",
        "distractor_2": "z-coordinate",
        "distractor_3": "coordinate"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "157",
    "name": "Nuclear Energy",
    "weight": "90",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8267",
        "question": "This term is defined as energy involved in motion or movement.",
        "answer": "kinetic energy",
        "distractor_1": "heat energy",
        "distractor_2": "nuclear energy",
        "distractor_3": "potential energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "8268",
        "question": "This term is defined as the smallest particle that can still represent an element and consists of three different subatomic particles.",
        "answer": "atom",
        "distractor_1": "proton",
        "distractor_2": "electron",
        "distractor_3": "isotope"
      },
      {
        "id": "8269",
        "question": "This term is defined as an electrically positive subatomic particle that is part of the nucleus of an atom and has a mass slightly less than that of a neutron.",
        "answer": "proton",
        "distractor_1": "isotope",
        "distractor_2": "nucleus",
        "distractor_3": "electron"
      },
      {
        "id": "8270",
        "question": "This term is defined as an element that has atoms with differing numbers of neutrons.",
        "answer": "isotope",
        "distractor_1": "nucleus",
        "distractor_2": "proton",
        "distractor_3": "neutron"
      },
      {
        "id": "8271",
        "question": "This term is defined as the spontaneous emission of radiation coming directly from unstable atomic nuclei.",
        "answer": "radioactivity ",
        "distractor_1": "fission",
        "distractor_2": "fusion",
        "distractor_3": "potential energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "8272",
        "question": "This term is defined as natural resources including solar, wind, and wood energy that can be used over and over again.",
        "answer": "renewable energy",
        "distractor_1": "potential energy",
        "distractor_2": "kinetic energy",
        "distractor_3": "nonrenewable energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "8273",
        "question": "This term is defined as resources including natural gas, petroleum, and coal that are gone once used.",
        "answer": "nonrenewable energy",
        "distractor_1": "potential energy",
        "distractor_2": "renewable energy",
        "distractor_3": "nuclear energy "
      },
      {
        "id": "8257",
        "question": "Which of the following types of radiation is the most dangerous to living things?",
        "answer": "gamma",
        "distractor_1": "alpha",
        "distractor_2": "beta",
        "distractor_3": "background"
      },
      {
        "id": "8482",
        "question": "Which of the following points satisfies the inequality y > -2x + 4? ",
        "answer": "(3, 1)",
        "distractor_1": "(-1, -2) ",
        "distractor_2": "(0, 1) ",
        "distractor_3": "(1, -2) "
      },
      {
        "id": "8483",
        "question": "Which of the following equations represents the data given in the table?",
        "answer": "y = -5x + 6",
        "distractor_1": "y = x² - 1",
        "distractor_2": "y = 2x + 13",
        "distractor_3": "y = 2x^(-1) - 1 "
      },
      {
        "id": "8484",
        "question": "On the graphing calculator, the Y= key allows you to do what?",
        "answer": "enter an equation",
        "distractor_1": "fit the graph to the screen",
        "distractor_2": "determine the y value for any x value",
        "distractor_3": "graph an equation "
      },
      {
        "id": "8485",
        "question": "What is the number 0.0000034 in scientific notation?",
        "answer": "3.4 x 10^(-6)",
        "distractor_1": "34 x 10^(-7)",
        "distractor_2": "34 x 10^7",
        "distractor_3": "3.4 x 10^6 "
      },
      {
        "id": "8486",
        "question": "Which of the following equations is in slope-intercept form? ",
        "answer": "y = 7x - 29",
        "distractor_1": "y = 50x²",
        "distractor_2": "y = 5/x",
        "distractor_3": "y = 3x^(-1) + 3"
      },
      {
        "id": "8487",
        "question": "Which equation has a slope of -3?",
        "answer": "y = -3x + 6",
        "distractor_1": "y = 3x + 6",
        "distractor_2": "y = 6x - 3",
        "distractor_3": "y = -6x + 3 "
      },
      {
        "id": "8488",
        "question": "In an inverse function, what happens to the y value as the x value decreases?",
        "answer": "increases",
        "distractor_1": "remains constant",
        "distractor_2": "decreases",
        "distractor_3": "becomes zero "
      },
      {
        "id": "8489",
        "question": "The energy-mass equivalence, E = mc², where c is the speed of light, is what type of equation? ",
        "answer": "linear",
        "distractor_1": "exponential",
        "distractor_2": "inverse ",
        "distractor_3": "rational "
      },
      {
        "id": "5959",
        "question": "This term is defined as energy that is released by alteration of the nuclei of atoms, as in a fission reaction, by fusion, or by radioactive decay.",
        "answer": "nuclear energy",
        "distractor_1": "heat energy",
        "distractor_2": "sound energy",
        "distractor_3": "mechanical energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "5960",
        "question": "This term is defined as the positively charged central region of an atom, composed of protons and neutrons and containing most of the mass of the atom.",
        "answer": "nucleus",
        "distractor_1": "proton",
        "distractor_2": "neutron",
        "distractor_3": "electron"
      },
      {
        "id": "5961",
        "question": "This term is defined as an electrically neutral subatomic particle that is part of the nucleus of an atom and has a mass slightly greater than that of a proton.",
        "answer": "neutron",
        "distractor_1": "electron",
        "distractor_2": "isotope",
        "distractor_3": "proton"
      },
      {
        "id": "5962",
        "question": "This term is defined as a device in which a nuclear chain reaction is started and controlled, thus producing heat, which is usually used to generate electricity, and a variety of radioactive isotopes.",
        "answer": "nuclear reactor",
        "distractor_1": "radioactivity",
        "distractor_2": "fission",
        "distractor_3": "nucleus"
      },
      {
        "id": "5963",
        "question": "This term is defined as a stable subatomic particle having a negative electric charge of approximately 1.602 · 10^-19 coulombs.",
        "answer": "electron",
        "distractor_1": "proton",
        "distractor_2": "neutron",
        "distractor_3": "nucleon"
      },
      {
        "id": "5964",
        "question": "This term is defined as energy possessed by a body as a result of its position or condition rather than its motion.",
        "answer": "potential energy",
        "distractor_1": "kinetic energy",
        "distractor_2": "heat energy",
        "distractor_3": "nuclear energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "8258",
        "question": "This process occurs when an atomic nucleus is split into two smaller parts.",
        "answer": "fission",
        "distractor_1": "fusion",
        "distractor_2": "transmutation",
        "distractor_3": "half-life"
      },
      {
        "id": "6817",
        "question": "Who discovered that there was a relationship between the force a charge exerts and distance?",
        "answer": "Charles Augustin de Coulomb",
        "distractor_1": "Albert Einstein",
        "distractor_2": "James Prescott Joule",
        "distractor_3": "Blaise Pascal"
      },
      {
        "id": "6818",
        "question": "Which of the following elements has a greater atomic weight than lead?",
        "answer": "radon",
        "distractor_1": "boron",
        "distractor_2": "sodium",
        "distractor_3": "silver"
      },
      {
        "id": "8490",
        "question": "What type of line would be used to graph the inequality y > x + 5? ",
        "answer": "dashed",
        "distractor_1": "horizontal",
        "distractor_2": "solid",
        "distractor_3": "vertical"
      },
      {
        "id": "8491",
        "question": "When graphed on a graphing calculator, which of the following equations will result in a straight line?",
        "answer": "y = 2x - 6",
        "distractor_1": "y = 2 + 3x^(3)",
        "distractor_2": "y =  -3x^(-1)",
        "distractor_3": "y = 300,000,000x²"
      },
      {
        "id": "8492",
        "question": "When graphed on a graphing calculator, which of the following equations will result in a straight line?",
        "answer": "y = 2x + 4 ",
        "distractor_1": "y = 2 + 300x^(4)",
        "distractor_2": "y = 300x^(-1)",
        "distractor_3": "y = 3x² - 5"
      },
      {
        "id": "8493",
        "question": "Which of the following equations is in slope-intercept form? ",
        "answer": "y = 5x + 1",
        "distractor_1": "y = 300,000,000x²",
        "distractor_2": "x = 3 + 7y",
        "distractor_3": "y = (2x - 1) / (3x)"
      },
      {
        "id": "8494",
        "question": "Which key should be pressed to enter an equation on the graphing calculator?",
        "answer": "Y=",
        "distractor_1": "TRACE",
        "distractor_2": "GRAPH",
        "distractor_3": "WINDOW"
      },
      {
        "id": "8495",
        "question": "The speed of light is about 300,000,000 meters per second. What is this number in scientific notation?",
        "answer": "3 x 10^(8)",
        "distractor_1": "3 x 10^(-8)",
        "distractor_2": "0.3 x 10^(9)",
        "distractor_3": "30 x 10^(9)"
      },
      {
        "id": "8496",
        "question": "Identify the slope in the equation y = 12x - 14.",
        "answer": "12",
        "distractor_1": "14",
        "distractor_2": "-14",
        "distractor_3": "x"
      },
      {
        "id": "8497",
        "question": "Which of the following points satisfies the inequality y < 3x - 3? ",
        "answer": "(3, -4) ",
        "distractor_1": "(2, 5) ",
        "distractor_2": "(-2, 1)",
        "distractor_3": "(-4, -1)"
      },
      {
        "id": "8498",
        "question": "In an inverse function, what happens to the y value as the x value increases?",
        "answer": "decreases",
        "distractor_1": "remains constant",
        "distractor_2": "increases",
        "distractor_3": "becomes zero"
      },
      {
        "id": "8499",
        "question": "What type of line would be used to graph the inequality y < -4x + 3?",
        "answer": "dashed",
        "distractor_1": "solid",
        "distractor_2": "bold",
        "distractor_3": "vertical"
      },
      {
        "id": "8500",
        "question": "Which of the following equations represents the data given in the table?",
        "answer": "y = 2x² - 3",
        "distractor_1": "y = x^(-1) - 2",
        "distractor_2": "y = 2x + 5",
        "distractor_3": "y = 4x - 3"
      },
      {
        "id": "8501",
        "question": "The energy-mass equivalence, E = mc², where c is the speed of light is what type of equation? ",
        "answer": "linear",
        "distractor_1": "inverse",
        "distractor_2": "exponential",
        "distractor_3": "rational"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "158",
    "name": "Unsolved Mysteries",
    "weight": "90",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8274",
        "question": "The application of science to law is known as what?",
        "answer": "forensic science",
        "distractor_1": "crirminal justice",
        "distractor_2": "crime scene documentation",
        "distractor_3": "toxicology"
      },
      {
        "id": "8275",
        "question": "A set of ordered pairs is referred to as what?",
        "answer": "relation",
        "distractor_1": "domain",
        "distractor_2": "range",
        "distractor_3": "function"
      },
      {
        "id": "5700",
        "question": "What is the correct notation for points on a coordinate grid?",
        "answer": "(x, y)",
        "distractor_1": "(y, x)",
        "distractor_2": "(z, x)",
        "distractor_3": "(z, y)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5701",
        "question": "Given a scale of 1/4 inch equals one foot, what is the actual distance represented by a three-inch-long scaled line? ",
        "answer": "12 feet",
        "distractor_1": "7 feet",
        "distractor_2": "1.25 feet",
        "distractor_3": "0.75 feet"
      },
      {
        "id": "5702",
        "question": "Which of these terms refers to a relation in which each value of x has one and only one y value?",
        "answer": "function",
        "distractor_1": "equation",
        "distractor_2": "formula",
        "distractor_3": "line graph"
      },
      {
        "id": "5703",
        "question": "Given a scale of 1/4 inch equals one foot, what is the actual distance represented by a 2.75-inch-long scaled line? ",
        "answer": "11 feet",
        "distractor_1": "3 feet",
        "distractor_2": "2.5 feet",
        "distractor_3": "0.68 feet"
      },
      {
        "id": "5704",
        "question": "What is the definition of rate?",
        "answer": "a change in a quantity measured with respect to another measured quantity",
        "distractor_1": "a change in the speed of an object",
        "distractor_2": "a change in time over a change in distance",
        "distractor_3": "the distance something changes"
      },
      {
        "id": "5705",
        "question": "What is the definition of diameter?",
        "answer": "a straight line that passes through the center of a circle from one side to the other",
        "distractor_1": "a line with end points on the edges of a circle",
        "distractor_2": "the distance around the edge of a circle",
        "distractor_3": "the distance from the center of a circle to its edge"
      },
      {
        "id": "5707",
        "question": "What is the definition of forensic science?",
        "answer": "the application of science to law",
        "distractor_1": "using DNA evidence to catch a criminal",
        "distractor_2": "the application of math to crime scene investigation",
        "distractor_3": "the use of science to find people"
      },
      {
        "id": "5708",
        "question": "Which of the following represents the equation y = 3x + 5 in function notation as a function of x?",
        "answer": "f(x) = 3x + 5",
        "distractor_1": "f(x) = y / 3 + 5",
        "distractor_2": "f(x) = (y • 3) – 5",
        "distractor_3": "f(x) = x / 3 – 5"
      },
      {
        "id": "5709",
        "question": "Which of the following is a method that can be used to identify a graph as a function?",
        "answer": "vertical line test",
        "distractor_1": "horizontal line test",
        "distractor_2": "vertical alignment",
        "distractor_3": "horizontal alignment"
      },
      {
        "id": "5976",
        "question": "Which term is defined as a relation in which every value of x has a unique value of y?",
        "answer": "function",
        "distractor_1": "diameter",
        "distractor_2": "quadrant",
        "distractor_3": "cooling rate"
      },
      {
        "id": "5977",
        "question": "Which term is defined as a pair of numbers that gives the coordinates of a point on a grid?",
        "answer": "ordered pair",
        "distractor_1": "domain",
        "distractor_2": "range",
        "distractor_3": "function"
      },
      {
        "id": "5978",
        "question": "Which term is defined as the second number of an ordered pair and the vertical y-axis line in a coordinate grid?",
        "answer": "vertical coordinate",
        "distractor_1": "horizontal coordinate",
        "distractor_2": "quadrant",
        "distractor_3": "diameter"
      },
      {
        "id": "5979",
        "question": "Which term is defined as the first number of an ordered pair and the horizontal x-axis line in a coordinate grid?",
        "answer": "horizontal coordinate",
        "distractor_1": "vertical coordinate",
        "distractor_2": "quadrant",
        "distractor_3": "diameter"
      },
      {
        "id": "5980",
        "question": "Which term is defined as a line segment that passes through the center of a circle and has end points on the circle?",
        "answer": "diameter",
        "distractor_1": "domain",
        "distractor_2": "range",
        "distractor_3": "function"
      },
      {
        "id": "5981",
        "question": "Which term is defined as in a function, f(x), the possible values for x in the given situation?",
        "answer": "domain",
        "distractor_1": "range",
        "distractor_2": "function",
        "distractor_3": "ordered pair"
      },
      {
        "id": "5982",
        "question": "Which term is defined as the possible values for y in a function?",
        "answer": "range",
        "distractor_1": "domain",
        "distractor_2": "cooling rate",
        "distractor_3": "quadrant"
      },
      {
        "id": "5983",
        "question": "Which term is defined as a thing or things helpful in making a judgment or coming to a conclusion?",
        "answer": "evidence",
        "distractor_1": "cooling rate",
        "distractor_2": "function",
        "distractor_3": "range"
      },
      {
        "id": "5984",
        "question": "Which term is defined as the four sections of a coordinate grid that are separated by the axes?",
        "answer": "quadrant",
        "distractor_1": "domain",
        "distractor_2": "range",
        "distractor_3": "function"
      },
      {
        "id": "5985",
        "question": "Which term is defined as a change in temperature over a change in time?",
        "answer": "cooling rate",
        "distractor_1": "evidence",
        "distractor_2": "function",
        "distractor_3": "range"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "164",
    "name": "Lenses & Optics",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8255",
        "question": "What part of the eye allows light to enter?",
        "answer": "pupil",
        "distractor_1": "cornea",
        "distractor_2": "iris",
        "distractor_3": "retina"
      },
      {
        "id": "5764",
        "question": "What term describes a lens that is thinner in the middle than at the edges?",
        "answer": "concave",
        "distractor_1": "convex",
        "distractor_2": "thin",
        "distractor_3": "plano-convex"
      },
      {
        "id": "5765",
        "question": "Which term describes a variation illustrated by the equation y = k/x?",
        "answer": "inverse variation",
        "distractor_1": "direct variation",
        "distractor_2": "irrational variation",
        "distractor_3": "diopter variation"
      },
      {
        "id": "5766",
        "question": "Which term describes a number that can be written as a ratio?",
        "answer": "rational number",
        "distractor_1": "irrational number",
        "distractor_2": "whole number",
        "distractor_3": "prime number"
      },
      {
        "id": "5767",
        "question": "What term is a comparison of two numbers using division?",
        "answer": "ratio",
        "distractor_1": "prime number",
        "distractor_2": "whole number ",
        "distractor_3": "real number"
      },
      {
        "id": "5768",
        "question": "What term describes a lens that has one surface that curves in and one surface that curves out?",
        "answer": "meniscus",
        "distractor_1": "convex",
        "distractor_2": "concave",
        "distractor_3": "plano-concave"
      },
      {
        "id": "5742",
        "question": "Which type of lens is thicker in the middle than at the outside edges? ",
        "answer": "convex",
        "distractor_1": "concave",
        "distractor_2": "plano concave",
        "distractor_3": "divergent"
      },
      {
        "id": "5744",
        "question": "The magnification ratio is the ratio of the height of the image to the height of the object. What magnification is necessary for a lens to produce an image 15 meters high from an object that is 0.05 meters high?",
        "answer": "300",
        "distractor_1": "3",
        "distractor_2": "30",
        "distractor_3": "3,000"
      },
      {
        "id": "5747",
        "question": "What is the focal length of a lens when the object distance is 60 centimeters and the image distance is 300 centimeters? ",
        "answer": "50 cm",
        "distractor_1": "5 cm",
        "distractor_2": "0.2 cm",
        "distractor_3": "75 cm"
      },
      {
        "id": "5748",
        "question": "A convex lens causes light rays from an object to converge at one point. What is this point called? ",
        "answer": "focal point",
        "distractor_1": "image distance",
        "distractor_2": "bright spot",
        "distractor_3": "object distance"
      },
      {
        "id": "5749",
        "question": "What is the magnification of a lens that produces an image height of 500 centimeters from an object height of 5 centimeters? ",
        "answer": "100",
        "distractor_1": "500",
        "distractor_2": "1,000",
        "distractor_3": "10"
      },
      {
        "id": "5750",
        "question": "What is the focal length of a lens with an object distance of 15 centimeters and an image distance of 30 centimeters? ",
        "answer": "10 centimeters",
        "distractor_1": "15 centimeters",
        "distractor_2": "45 centimeters",
        "distractor_3": "30 centimeters"
      },
      {
        "id": "5751",
        "question": "When an object is placed at a distance greater than the focal length of a convex lens, how will the image appear? ",
        "answer": "inverted but larger",
        "distractor_1": "upright but smaller",
        "distractor_2": "inverted but smaller",
        "distractor_3": "upright but larger"
      },
      {
        "id": "5752",
        "question": "What type of lens is a concave lens? ",
        "answer": "divergent",
        "distractor_1": "convergent",
        "distractor_2": "collecting",
        "distractor_3": "enlarging"
      },
      {
        "id": "5753",
        "question": "What type of proportion can be illustrated with the equation y = kx? ",
        "answer": "direct",
        "distractor_1": "complex",
        "distractor_2": "indirect",
        "distractor_3": "simple"
      },
      {
        "id": "5754",
        "question": "Which of the following describes a rational number?",
        "answer": "a real number that can be written as a fraction",
        "distractor_1": " a whole number",
        "distractor_2": "a number that can only be divided by itself and one",
        "distractor_3": "a number greater than zero"
      },
      {
        "id": "5769",
        "question": "What term describes a lens with one surface that curves in and one surface that is flat?",
        "answer": "plano-concave",
        "distractor_1": "plano-convex",
        "distractor_2": "convex",
        "distractor_3": "convergent"
      },
      {
        "id": "5770",
        "question": "What term describes a lens that has one surface flat and one surface that curves out?",
        "answer": "plano-convex",
        "distractor_1": "plano-concave",
        "distractor_2": "divergent",
        "distractor_3": "concave"
      },
      {
        "id": "5755",
        "question": "In which type of variation is the product of both variables equal to a constant (yx = k)?",
        "answer": "inverse",
        "distractor_1": "direct ",
        "distractor_2": "convergent",
        "distractor_3": "simple"
      },
      {
        "id": "5756",
        "question": "Magnification is the ratio of which two measurements? ",
        "answer": "image height over object height",
        "distractor_1": "image height over object distance ",
        "distractor_2": "image distance over object height",
        "distractor_3": "object height over object distance "
      },
      {
        "id": "5757",
        "question": "At what distance would a lens with a focal length of 20 centimeters produce an image if the object is placed 60 centimeters from the lens?",
        "answer": "30 centimeters",
        "distractor_1": "3 centimeters",
        "distractor_2": "40 centimeters",
        "distractor_3": "80 centimeters"
      },
      {
        "id": "5758",
        "question": "Which of the following conditions in the eye causes a person to be nearsighted? ",
        "answer": "The cornea is too curved.",
        "distractor_1": "The lens is misshapen.",
        "distractor_2": "The cornea is not curved enough.",
        "distractor_3": "The eyeball is too short."
      },
      {
        "id": "5760",
        "question": "An object measuring 0.0005 millimeter is magnified 1,200 times by a microscope. What size would the image appear? ",
        "answer": "0.6 mm",
        "distractor_1": "6 mm",
        "distractor_2": "2,000 mm",
        "distractor_3": "2,400,000 mm"
      },
      {
        "id": "5763",
        "question": "If the magnification by a lens is 150, how tall would the image of a 50 cm object be?",
        "answer": "75 m",
        "distractor_1": "3 m ",
        "distractor_2": "0.33 cm",
        "distractor_3": "50 cm"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "163",
    "name": "Math Behind Your Meals",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8266",
        "question": "Which of the following nutrients is made up of amino acids?",
        "answer": "proteins",
        "distractor_1": "carbohydrates",
        "distractor_2": "fats",
        "distractor_3": "vitamins"
      },
      {
        "id": "5783",
        "question": "Which one of these is not an expense for operating a farm today?",
        "answer": "entertainment",
        "distractor_1": "land",
        "distractor_2": "fertilizer ",
        "distractor_3": "fuel"
      },
      {
        "id": "5784",
        "question": "Which of the following best describes integers?",
        "answer": "whole numbers and their opposites ",
        "distractor_1": "cannot be shown on a number line",
        "distractor_2": "irrational numbers",
        "distractor_3": "fractions"
      },
      {
        "id": "5785",
        "question": "Which is the correct order of operations for solving equations?",
        "answer": "parentheses, exponents, multiplication, division, addition, subtraction ",
        "distractor_1": "exponents, parentheses, division, multiplication, addition, subtraction",
        "distractor_2": "exponents, addition, subtraction, multiplication, division, parentheses",
        "distractor_3": "parentheses, exponents, subtraction, addition, division, multiplication"
      },
      {
        "id": "5786",
        "question": "What does BMR measure?",
        "answer": "basal metabolic rate ",
        "distractor_1": "basal mass ratio",
        "distractor_2": "body mass rate",
        "distractor_3": "basic metabolic ratio"
      },
      {
        "id": "5857",
        "question": "A commodity is which of the following?",
        "answer": "partially processed or unprocessed goods for trade or sale",
        "distractor_1": "the measurement of food energy",
        "distractor_2": "a piece of farm machinery",
        "distractor_3": "a farmer's income"
      },
      {
        "id": "5858",
        "question": "Which of the following is an example of the Commutative Property of Addition? ",
        "answer": "a + b = b + a",
        "distractor_1": "a + b = b + c",
        "distractor_2": "a • (b - c) = (ab) - (ac)",
        "distractor_3": "(a + b) + c = a + (b + c)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5859",
        "question": "The fast-food industry began because of which of the following reasons?",
        "answer": "More people had cars.",
        "distractor_1": "People were hungry.",
        "distractor_2": "People got tired of cooking.",
        "distractor_3": "Food was cheaper and easier to fix."
      },
      {
        "id": "5860",
        "question": "Ratios are comparisons of two numbers or measures using which mathematical operation?",
        "answer": "division",
        "distractor_1": "addition",
        "distractor_2": "subtraction",
        "distractor_3": "multiplication"
      },
      {
        "id": "5862",
        "question": "Which of the following formulas determines the percent of change in weight between 1 oz hamburgers in the '50s and 6 oz hamburgers now?",
        "answer": "100 • (amount of increase / original amount)",
        "distractor_1": "100 • (original amount / amount of increase)",
        "distractor_2": "100 • (amount of decrease / original amount)",
        "distractor_3": "100 • (original amount / amount of decrease)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5863",
        "question": "A percent is a special ratio that compares which of the following?",
        "answer": "a number to 100",
        "distractor_1": "positive and negative numbers",
        "distractor_2": "rational and irrational numbers",
        "distractor_3": "numbers using addition"
      },
      {
        "id": "5864",
        "question": "How can you tell if ratios form a true proportion?",
        "answer": "cross multiply to see if the products are equal",
        "distractor_1": "multiply the numerators together",
        "distractor_2": "multiply the denominators together",
        "distractor_3": "cross multiply to see if the quotients are equal"
      },
      {
        "id": "5787",
        "question": "Which of these reasons for America's weight gain is false?",
        "answer": "portion sizes have decreased ",
        "distractor_1": "amount of exercise has decreased",
        "distractor_2": "food advertisements have increased",
        "distractor_3": "amount of television watching has increased"
      },
      {
        "id": "5788",
        "question": "Which of these is information not found on a nutrition label?",
        "answer": "cost per item ",
        "distractor_1": "calories from fat",
        "distractor_2": "total carbohydrates",
        "distractor_3": "serving size"
      },
      {
        "id": "5789",
        "question": "What formula is used to figure a person's body mass index?",
        "answer": "weight divided by height squared ",
        "distractor_1": "waist measurement divided by hip measurement",
        "distractor_2": "activity level times calories divided by height",
        "distractor_3": "weight divided by calories burned"
      },
      {
        "id": "5792",
        "question": "Which of these does the waist-to-hip ratio determine?",
        "answer": "risk for heart disease ",
        "distractor_1": "body mass index",
        "distractor_2": "basal metabolic rate",
        "distractor_3": "activity level"
      },
      {
        "id": "5837",
        "question": "Which of the following is an example of an irrational number?",
        "answer": "sqrt(7)",
        "distractor_1": "20/1",
        "distractor_2": "sqrt(4)",
        "distractor_3": "3.33..."
      },
      {
        "id": "5865",
        "question": "There are 200 calories in a doughnut, and 110 of those are from fat. In simplified form, what is the ratio of fat calories to total calories?",
        "answer": "11:20",
        "distractor_1": "1:20",
        "distractor_2": "11:200",
        "distractor_3": "110:210"
      },
      {
        "id": "6801",
        "question": "What is an algebraic expression? ",
        "answer": "a variable or combination of variables, numbers, or symbols that show a math relationship",
        "distractor_1": "a combination of variables, numbers, or words that show a math relationship",
        "distractor_2": "a combination numbers and letters that show a math and science relationship",
        "distractor_3": "a combination letters and symbols that show a variable relationship"
      },
      {
        "id": "6802",
        "question": "What are commodities?",
        "answer": "partially processed or unprocessed goods for trade or sale",
        "distractor_1": "processed goods for trade or sale",
        "distractor_2": "unprocessed goods for sale only",
        "distractor_3": "partially processed or unprocessed goods for trade only"
      },
      {
        "id": "6803",
        "question": "What is inflation?",
        "answer": "a continual increase in the price of goods and services",
        "distractor_1": "a sudden increase in the price of goods and services",
        "distractor_2": "a continual increase in the demand for goods and services",
        "distractor_3": "a gradual increase in the price of goods and services"
      },
      {
        "id": "6804",
        "question": "What is a percent?",
        "answer": "a decimal that compares a number to 100",
        "distractor_1": "a decimal that compares a number to a property",
        "distractor_2": "an irrational number that compares a number to 100",
        "distractor_3": "a decimal that compares a number to zero"
      },
      {
        "id": "6805",
        "question": "What is a constant?",
        "answer": "Constants are numbers that always stay the same. ",
        "distractor_1": "Coefficients are numbers that always stay the same. ",
        "distractor_2": "Variables are numbers that always stay the same. ",
        "distractor_3": "Integers are numbers that always stay the same. "
      },
      {
        "id": "6806",
        "question": "What does it mean to evaluate an expression?",
        "answer": "to find its value",
        "distractor_1": "to find its difference",
        "distractor_2": "to find its opposite",
        "distractor_3": "to find its product "
      },
      {
        "id": "6807",
        "question": "What is an equation?",
        "answer": "a statement that two mathematical expressions are equal",
        "distractor_1": "a statement that two mathematical expressions are different",
        "distractor_2": "a statement that two mathematical expressions are false",
        "distractor_3": "a statement that two mathematical expressions are true"
      },
      {
        "id": "6808",
        "question": "What does an omnivore eat?",
        "answer": "both plants and meat",
        "distractor_1": "only plants",
        "distractor_2": "only meat",
        "distractor_3": "only bread and water"
      },
      {
        "id": "6809",
        "question": "What does BMR stand for?",
        "answer": "basal metabolic rate",
        "distractor_1": "body mass rate",
        "distractor_2": "basal mass ratio",
        "distractor_3": "basic metabolic ratio"
      },
      {
        "id": "6810",
        "question": "What does BMI stand for? ",
        "answer": "body mass index",
        "distractor_1": "basal metabolic index",
        "distractor_2": "body metabolic increase",
        "distractor_3": "basic mathematical index"
      },
      {
        "id": "6811",
        "question": "What is a ratio?",
        "answer": "a comparison of two numbers by division ",
        "distractor_1": "a comparison of two numbers by subtraction ",
        "distractor_2": "a comparison of two numbers by addition ",
        "distractor_3": "a comparison of two numbers by multiplication "
      },
      {
        "id": "6812",
        "question": "What does WHR stand for?",
        "answer": "waist-to-hip ratio",
        "distractor_1": "weight-to-hip rate",
        "distractor_2": "weight-to-height ratio",
        "distractor_3": "waist-to-heart ratio"
      },
      {
        "id": "6813",
        "question": "What is a proportion?",
        "answer": "an equation stating that two ratios are equal",
        "distractor_1": "an expression stating that two ratios are equal",
        "distractor_2": "an equation stating that two ratios are variable",
        "distractor_3": "an equation stating that two radii are equal"
      },
      {
        "id": "6814",
        "question": "What does a calorimeter measure?",
        "answer": "heat energy in food",
        "distractor_1": "heat energy in households",
        "distractor_2": "nutrition in food",
        "distractor_3": "heat energy on farms"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "166",
    "name": "Gravity of Algebra",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "6823",
        "question": "What is the term for the force of attraction that tends to draw together any two objects in the universe?",
        "answer": "gravity",
        "distractor_1": "velocity",
        "distractor_2": "acceleration",
        "distractor_3": "potential energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "6824",
        "question": "Which term describes the rate at which an object moves in a specified direction?",
        "answer": "velocity",
        "distractor_1": "acceleration",
        "distractor_2": "potential energy",
        "distractor_3": "kinetic energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "6825",
        "question": "What term describes the rate of change in the speed or direction of a moving body with respect to time?",
        "answer": "acceleration",
        "distractor_1": "velocity",
        "distractor_2": "gravity",
        "distractor_3": "energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "6826",
        "question": "What type of equation has the form y = kx, where k does not equal zero?",
        "answer": "direct variation",
        "distractor_1": "indirect variation",
        "distractor_2": "constant variation",
        "distractor_3": "constant equation"
      },
      {
        "id": "6827",
        "question": "Which term describes a relationship?",
        "answer": "correlation",
        "distractor_1": "direct variation",
        "distractor_2": "scatter plot",
        "distractor_3": "constant"
      },
      {
        "id": "6828",
        "question": "What type of energy is the energy that a particle or system of particles derives from position or condition rather than from motion?",
        "answer": "potential energy",
        "distractor_1": "kinetic energy",
        "distractor_2": "constant energy ",
        "distractor_3": "conditional energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "6829",
        "question": "What type of energy is the energy possessed by a body because it is in motion?",
        "answer": "kinetic energy",
        "distractor_1": "potential energy",
        "distractor_2": "constant energy",
        "distractor_3": "moving energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "6830",
        "question": "What term is used to describe the rise over the run of a line?",
        "answer": "slope",
        "distractor_1": "scatter plot",
        "distractor_2": "correlation",
        "distractor_3": "acceleration"
      },
      {
        "id": "6831",
        "question": "Which is the horizontal axis of a two-dimensional coordinate system?",
        "answer": "x-axis",
        "distractor_1": "y-axis",
        "distractor_2": "graph",
        "distractor_3": "slope"
      },
      {
        "id": "6832",
        "question": "Which describes the vertical axis of a two-dimensional coordinate system?",
        "answer": "y-axis",
        "distractor_1": "x-axis",
        "distractor_2": "graph",
        "distractor_3": "slope"
      },
      {
        "id": "6833",
        "question": "What term describes symbols used to represent unspecified numbers or values?",
        "answer": "variable",
        "distractor_1": "coefficient",
        "distractor_2": "exponent",
        "distractor_3": "factor"
      },
      {
        "id": "6834",
        "question": "What is the term for a monomial that is a real number?",
        "answer": "constant",
        "distractor_1": "variable",
        "distractor_2": "exponent",
        "distractor_3": "rational number"
      },
      {
        "id": "6835",
        "question": "What type of graph is a graph in which two sets of data are plotted as ordered pairs in a coordinate plane?",
        "answer": "scatter plot",
        "distractor_1": "box-and-whisker plots",
        "distractor_2": "bar graph",
        "distractor_3": "line graph"
      },
      {
        "id": "6836",
        "question": "What type of variation occurs when one value increases as the other decreases and the product of the two values remains constant?",
        "answer": "inverse variation",
        "distractor_1": "constant variation",
        "distractor_2": "direct variation",
        "distractor_3": "reverse variation"
      },
      {
        "id": "5798",
        "question": "The total energy of a basketball falling through the hoop and hitting the ground is given by the equation y = 2 on an energy versus height graph. What is the slope of this line and what does the line look like on a graph?",
        "answer": "slope = 0 and the line is a horizontal line",
        "distractor_1": "slope = 0 and the line is a vertical line",
        "distractor_2": "slope = 2 and the line slopes up",
        "distractor_3": "slope = 2 and the line slopes down"
      },
      {
        "id": "5799",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a type of force?",
        "answer": "quantum force",
        "distractor_1": "gravitational force",
        "distractor_2": "magnetic force",
        "distractor_3": "strong nuclear force"
      },
      {
        "id": "5800",
        "question": "An eagle in its nest 28 meters above the ground spots a mouse in the field below. It leaves the nest and dives straight for the ground, covering the 28 meters in 3.5 seconds. What was the average velocity of the eagle as it dove in meters per second?",
        "answer": "8 m/s",
        "distractor_1": "98 m/s",
        "distractor_2": "24.5 m/s",
        "distractor_3": "5 m/s"
      },
      {
        "id": "5801",
        "question": "What is an association or relationship between two variables called?",
        "answer": "correlation",
        "distractor_1": "equation",
        "distractor_2": "variation",
        "distractor_3": "graph"
      },
      {
        "id": "5802",
        "question": "The space shuttle sits on its launchpad at Johnson Space Center, which is 15 feet above sea level. Two seconds after liftoff it is at a height of 51 feet above sea level. Calculate the shuttle’s average velocity for the first two seconds of its flight.",
        "answer": "18 ft/s",
        "distractor_1": "25.5 ft/s",
        "distractor_2": "33 ft/s",
        "distractor_3": "36 ft/s"
      },
      {
        "id": "5803",
        "question": "What is the rate of change in the velocity of an object with respect to time?",
        "answer": "acceleration",
        "distractor_1": "average velocity",
        "distractor_2": "distance",
        "distractor_3": "speed"
      },
      {
        "id": "5805",
        "question": "A golf ball falling back to the ground after being hit off a tee does not have which of the following types of energy?",
        "answer": "electromagnetic potential energy",
        "distractor_1": "gravitational potential energy",
        "distractor_2": "kinetic energy",
        "distractor_3": "mechanical energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "5807",
        "question": "What is the slope of the line y = 6x - 2?",
        "answer": "6",
        "distractor_1": "2",
        "distractor_2": "4",
        "distractor_3": "-2"
      },
      {
        "id": "5808",
        "question": "A person in a car is traveling at 50 miles per hour. The distance a car travels is given by the equation d equals 50 times the time of travel (d = 50t). What kind of variation is this?",
        "answer": "direct",
        "distractor_1": "indirect",
        "distractor_2": "inverse",
        "distractor_3": "opposite"
      },
      {
        "id": "5809",
        "question": "Which of the following equations is an equation in point-slope format?",
        "answer": "y - 1 = -3(x - 4)",
        "distractor_1": "y = 3x + 1",
        "distractor_2": "2y + x - 4 = 0",
        "distractor_3": "x = 2 - y"
      },
      {
        "id": "5810",
        "question": "On a velocity versus time graph, what is the slope of the line equal to?",
        "answer": "acceleration",
        "distractor_1": "instantaneous velocity",
        "distractor_2": "distance",
        "distractor_3": "average time"
      },
      {
        "id": "5811",
        "question": "Which of the following equations represents a line that is perpendicular to the line y = 3x + 1?",
        "answer": "y = -1/3x - 8",
        "distractor_1": "y = 1/3x + 1",
        "distractor_2": "y = -3x + 3",
        "distractor_3": "y = -x + 3"
      },
      {
        "id": "5812",
        "question": "A line has an equation of y = 0x - 2. What does the graph of this line look like?",
        "answer": "a horizontal line passing through the y-axis at -2",
        "distractor_1": "a line with a slope of 2 passing through the y-axis at the origin.",
        "distractor_2": "a vertical line passing through the x-axis at -2",
        "distractor_3": "a line sloping down passing through the y-axis at -2"
      },
      {
        "id": "5794",
        "question": "A person in a car needs to travel 80 miles. The velocity of the car is given by the equation velocity equals 80 divided by the time of travel (v = 80 / t). What kind of variation is this?",
        "answer": "inverse",
        "distractor_1": "direct",
        "distractor_2": "indirect",
        "distractor_3": "opposite"
      },
      {
        "id": "5795",
        "question": "What is the slope of the line y = 4x - 3?",
        "answer": "4",
        "distractor_1": "3",
        "distractor_2": "-3",
        "distractor_3": "1"
      },
      {
        "id": "5796",
        "question": "Which of the following equations is an equation in point-slope format?",
        "answer": "y - 3 = -2(x + 2)",
        "distractor_1": "y = 2x - 3",
        "distractor_2": "2y + 3x - 1 = 0",
        "distractor_3": "x = 5 - 2y"
      },
      {
        "id": "5797",
        "question": "Which of the following equations represents a line that is perpendicular to the line y = 2x - 4?",
        "answer": "y = -1/2x + 1",
        "distractor_1": "y = 2x + 3",
        "distractor_2": "y = 1/2x - 1",
        "distractor_3": "y = 4x - 2"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "169",
    "name": "Factoring & Polynomials",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "5813",
        "question": "Identify the property that is being used to multiply the binomials.  (y + 2)(y + 3) = y(y + 3) + 2(y + 3)",
        "answer": "Distributive Property",
        "distractor_1": "Associative Property",
        "distractor_2": "Commutative Property",
        "distractor_3": "Zero Property"
      },
      {
        "id": "5814",
        "question": "Use the greatest common factor (GCF) to factor the polynomial.  40n^5 + 70n^4 - 30n^3",
        "answer": "10n^3(4n^3 + 7n - 3)",
        "distractor_1": "n^3(40n^2 + 70n - 30)",
        "distractor_2": "10n^3(4n^2 + 7n + 3)",
        "distractor_3": "10(4n^5 + 7n^4 - 3n^3) "
      },
      {
        "id": "5815",
        "question": "Factor the trinomial x² - 6x - 27.",
        "answer": "(x - 9)(x + 3)",
        "distractor_1": "(x + 9)(x + 3)",
        "distractor_2": "(x - 9)(x - 3)",
        "distractor_3": "(x + 3)(x + 3)(x + 3)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5816",
        "question": "Factor the perfect square 81c² - 49d².",
        "answer": "(9c - 7d)(9c + 7d)",
        "distractor_1": "(9c - 7d)(9c - 7d)",
        "distractor_2": "(9c + 7d)(9c + 7d)",
        "distractor_3": "(81 - 49) - (c² - d²)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5817",
        "question": "Which of the following polynomials is also a binomial?",
        "answer": "3x + 4",
        "distractor_1": "x² + 2x - 3",
        "distractor_2": " 2x²",
        "distractor_3": "x²y²"
      },
      {
        "id": "5818",
        "question": "What is the prime factorization of 48?",
        "answer": "2^4 · 3",
        "distractor_1": "3 · 4^2",
        "distractor_2": "2 · 2 · 2 · 3 · 3",
        "distractor_3": "2 · 3 · 4 · 2 · 3"
      },
      {
        "id": "5819",
        "question": "Which of the following terms is prime?",
        "answer": "7",
        "distractor_1": "1,240",
        "distractor_2": "1",
        "distractor_3": "3³"
      },
      {
        "id": "5820",
        "question": "Choose the pair of binomials that represent the trinomial 12x² - 17x + 6.",
        "answer": "(4x - 3)(4x - 2)",
        "distractor_1": "(4x - 3)(4x + 2)",
        "distractor_2": "(4x + 3)(4x - 2)",
        "distractor_3": "(4x + 3)(4x + 2)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5821",
        "question": "What is the greatest common factor (GCF) of 3x²y - 21xy + 3xy²?",
        "answer": "3xy",
        "distractor_1": "3",
        "distractor_2": "21x²y²",
        "distractor_3": "xy"
      },
      {
        "id": "5823",
        "question": "What is the greatest common factor (GCF) of 16xz - 40xz²?",
        "answer": "8xz",
        "distractor_1": "2xz",
        "distractor_2": "4x",
        "distractor_3": "2z"
      },
      {
        "id": "5824",
        "question": "What is the degree of the polynomial 2x³ - 4y + 7x²y²?",
        "answer": "4",
        "distractor_1": "8",
        "distractor_2": "7",
        "distractor_3": "3"
      },
      {
        "id": "5831",
        "question": "What is the product of 3x and 4x² - 2x + 5?",
        "answer": "12x³ - 6x² + 15x",
        "distractor_1": "4x² - 5x + 5",
        "distractor_2": "-12x³ + 6x² - 15x",
        "distractor_3": "7x³ - 6x² + 15x"
      },
      {
        "id": "5834",
        "question": "One way to organize how you multiply two binomials is to use the FOIL method. The term FOIL is a memory device for applying the Distributive Property. What do the letters in  FOIL stand for?",
        "answer": "first, outer, inner, last",
        "distractor_1": "fast, outer, inner, last",
        "distractor_2": "first, over, inner, last",
        "distractor_3": "first, outer, inner, long"
      },
      {
        "id": "5835",
        "question": "The area of the square is 1/4d² + d + 1. Find the length of one side of the square.",
        "answer": "(1/2d + 1)",
        "distractor_1": "(1/8d + 1)",
        "distractor_2": "(1/2d - 1)",
        "distractor_3": "(1/8d - 1)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5836",
        "question": "Describe the error in factoring the polynomial. 18x^8 - 9x^4 - 6x^3 = 3x(6x^7 - 3x^3 - 2x^2)",
        "answer": "The greatest common factor needs to be 3x^3.",
        "distractor_1": "The greatest common factor needs to be x^3.",
        "distractor_2": "The greatest common factor needs to be 6x^2.",
        "distractor_3": "No error. This is correct."
      },
      {
        "id": "5944",
        "question": "Which term is defined as the product of constants and variables?",
        "answer": "monomial",
        "distractor_1": "factor",
        "distractor_2": "binomial",
        "distractor_3": "root"
      },
      {
        "id": "5945",
        "question": "Which term is defined as a polynomial made up of two terms?",
        "answer": "binomial",
        "distractor_1": "factor",
        "distractor_2": "monomial",
        "distractor_3": "constant"
      },
      {
        "id": "5946",
        "question": "Which term is defined as a polynomial made up of three terms?",
        "answer": "trinomial",
        "distractor_1": "binomial",
        "distractor_2": "factor",
        "distractor_3": "monomial"
      },
      {
        "id": "5947",
        "question": "Which term is defined as a number or symbol that stays the same?",
        "answer": "constant",
        "distractor_1": "monomial",
        "distractor_2": "factor",
        "distractor_3": "root"
      },
      {
        "id": "5948",
        "question": "Which term is defined as the highest power of any term or a polynomial?",
        "answer": "degree of a polynomial",
        "distractor_1": "prime factorization",
        "distractor_2": "prime number",
        "distractor_3": "composite number"
      },
      {
        "id": "5949",
        "question": "Which term is defined as a term or the sum or difference of two or more terms?",
        "answer": "polynomial",
        "distractor_1": "monomial",
        "distractor_2": "trinomial",
        "distractor_3": "binomial"
      },
      {
        "id": "5951",
        "question": "Which term is defined as either the product of numbers and variables, just a number, or just a variable?",
        "answer": "term",
        "distractor_1": "root",
        "distractor_2": "monomial",
        "distractor_3": "factor"
      },
      {
        "id": "5952",
        "question": "Which term is defined as a positive number greater than one whose only factors are one and itself?",
        "answer": "prime numbers",
        "distractor_1": "composite numbers",
        "distractor_2": "polynomials",
        "distractor_3": "perfect squares"
      },
      {
        "id": "5953",
        "question": "Which term is defined as a positive integer that has factors other than one and themselves?",
        "answer": "composite numbers",
        "distractor_1": "prime numbers",
        "distractor_2": "perfect squares",
        "distractor_3": "polynomials"
      },
      {
        "id": "5954",
        "question": "Which term is defined as numbers that are multiplied together to get another number?",
        "answer": "factors",
        "distractor_1": "roots",
        "distractor_2": "constants",
        "distractor_3": "monomials"
      },
      {
        "id": "5955",
        "question": "Which term is defined as the process of finding the prime numbers of a given composite number?",
        "answer": "prime factorization",
        "distractor_1": "ascending order",
        "distractor_2": "degree of a polynomial",
        "distractor_3": "composite numbers"
      },
      {
        "id": "5956",
        "question": "Which term is defined as the product of an integer and itself?",
        "answer": "perfect squares",
        "distractor_1": "prime factorization",
        "distractor_2": "descending order",
        "distractor_3": "factors"
      },
      {
        "id": "5957",
        "question": "Which term is defined as the process of writing factors or numbers in order from least to greatest?",
        "answer": "ascending order",
        "distractor_1": "degree of a polynomial",
        "distractor_2": "descending order",
        "distractor_3": "prime factorization"
      },
      {
        "id": "5958",
        "question": "Which term is defined as the process of writing factors or numbers in order from greatest to least?",
        "answer": "descending order",
        "distractor_1": "prime factorization",
        "distractor_2": "greatest common factor",
        "distractor_3": "ascending order"
      },
      {
        "id": "6821",
        "question": "Choose the pair of binomials that represent the trinomial t² - 10t + 25.",
        "answer": "(t - 5)( t - 5) ",
        "distractor_1": "(t - 5)( t + 5) ",
        "distractor_2": "(t + 25)( t - 1) ",
        "distractor_3": "(t - 25)( t - 1) "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "168",
    "name": "Sports Statistics",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "5848",
        "question": "Which of the following describes the number of outcomes that can occur in a series of events?",
        "answer": "fundamental counting principle",
        "distractor_1": "fundamental theorem of algebra ",
        "distractor_2": "fundamental theorem of arithmetic",
        "distractor_3": "principle of multiplication"
      },
      {
        "id": "5850",
        "question": "A box-and-whisker plot is a graph of data points that highlights which of the following?",
        "answer": "quartiles",
        "distractor_1": "trend line",
        "distractor_2": "average",
        "distractor_3": "magnitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "5851",
        "question": "Which intervals would be appropriate for using to make a frequency table?",
        "answer": "1-5, 6-10, and 11-15 ",
        "distractor_1": "1-4, 4-5, and 6-15",
        "distractor_2": "1-5, 8-9, and 15 and over",
        "distractor_3": "1-3, 3-7, 7-10, and 10-14"
      },
      {
        "id": "5852",
        "question": "Which of the following is a graph of frequency distribution made with adjacent rectangles whose widths correspond to interval sizes and whose heights correspond to frequencies?",
        "answer": "histogram",
        "distractor_1": "bar graph",
        "distractor_2": "scatter plot",
        "distractor_3": "box-and-whisker plot"
      },
      {
        "id": "5854",
        "question": "Calculate the slope of a trend line containing points (1, 3) and (4, 9).",
        "answer": "2",
        "distractor_1": "0.5",
        "distractor_2": "2.4",
        "distractor_3": "3"
      },
      {
        "id": "5855",
        "question": "What is a straight line that is a linear approximation of the data averages in a scatter plot called?",
        "answer": "trend line",
        "distractor_1": "histogram",
        "distractor_2": "correlation",
        "distractor_3": "line of demarcation"
      },
      {
        "id": "5838",
        "question": "In a scatter plot with positive correlation, as the x values of the trend line increase, what happens to the y values?",
        "answer": "increase",
        "distractor_1": "decrease",
        "distractor_2": "change from negative to positive",
        "distractor_3": "stay the same"
      },
      {
        "id": "5839",
        "question": "A baseball coach has three starting pitchers, four catchers, and two closers to choose from in a game. How many different starting pitcher, catcher, and closer combinations can the coach make?",
        "answer": "24",
        "distractor_1": "12",
        "distractor_2": "48",
        "distractor_3": "7"
      },
      {
        "id": "5840",
        "question": "In a scatter plot, both the x and y values increase. Which type of correlation does this represent?",
        "answer": "positive",
        "distractor_1": "negative",
        "distractor_2": "no correlation",
        "distractor_3": "infinite correlation"
      },
      {
        "id": "5841",
        "question": "Which of the following graph types is most closely related to a histogram?",
        "answer": "bar graph",
        "distractor_1": "circle graph",
        "distractor_2": "line graph",
        "distractor_3": "scatter plot"
      },
      {
        "id": "5843",
        "question": "How many different first-through-fifth-place final standings are possible in a five-team race?",
        "answer": "120",
        "distractor_1": "5",
        "distractor_2": "15",
        "distractor_3": "60"
      },
      {
        "id": "5844",
        "question": "How many different foursomes of golfers can be selected from a group of 10 golfers?",
        "answer": "210",
        "distractor_1": "24",
        "distractor_2": "5,040",
        "distractor_3": "604,800"
      },
      {
        "id": "6748",
        "question": "Which of the following is a rectangular arrangement of numbers?",
        "answer": "matrix",
        "distractor_1": "scatter plot",
        "distractor_2": "ordinate",
        "distractor_3": "grid"
      },
      {
        "id": "6749",
        "question": "Which of the following is the process of multiplying a matrix by a number?",
        "answer": "scalar multiplication ",
        "distractor_1": "cross multiplication",
        "distractor_2": "dilation",
        "distractor_3": "evaluating"
      },
      {
        "id": "6750",
        "question": "Which of the following is a straight line that comes closest to connecting the points on a scatter plot?",
        "answer": "trend line ",
        "distractor_1": "diagonal line",
        "distractor_2": "bisecting line",
        "distractor_3": "line of symmetry"
      },
      {
        "id": "6751",
        "question": "Which of the following is a graph in which the values of two variables are plotted along two different axes?",
        "answer": "scatter plot ",
        "distractor_1": "bar graph",
        "distractor_2": "box-and-whisker plot",
        "distractor_3": "histogram"
      },
      {
        "id": "6752",
        "question": "Which of the following is the measure of steepness of a line as you look at it from left to right?",
        "answer": "slope ",
        "distractor_1": "angle",
        "distractor_2": "deviation",
        "distractor_3": "capacity"
      },
      {
        "id": "6753",
        "question": "Which of the following terms describes the ordering of data from the least amount to the greatest amount?",
        "answer": "ascending order ",
        "distractor_1": "descending order",
        "distractor_2": "collecting terms",
        "distractor_3": "diagramming"
      },
      {
        "id": "6754",
        "question": "Which of the following describes something that is parallel to or in the plane of the horizon?",
        "answer": "horizontal ",
        "distractor_1": "vertical ",
        "distractor_2": "diagonal ",
        "distractor_3": "cross line"
      },
      {
        "id": "6755",
        "question": "Which of the following describes something that is at right angles to the horizon?",
        "answer": "vertical ",
        "distractor_1": "horizontal",
        "distractor_2": "diagonal",
        "distractor_3": "cross line"
      },
      {
        "id": "6756",
        "question": "Which of the following is determined by the difference between the upper quartile and the lower quartile?",
        "answer": "interquartile range ",
        "distractor_1": "absolute value",
        "distractor_2": "mode",
        "distractor_3": "range"
      },
      {
        "id": "6757",
        "question": "Which of the following is a piece of numerical data that is much smaller or larger than the rest of the data in a set?",
        "answer": "outlier",
        "distractor_1": "median",
        "distractor_2": "mean",
        "distractor_3": "factorial"
      },
      {
        "id": "6758",
        "question": "Which of the following states that if one event can happen in a ways and a second, independent event can happen in b ways, the two can occur together in a * b ways?",
        "answer": "fundamental counting principle ",
        "distractor_1": "permutation",
        "distractor_2": "combination",
        "distractor_3": "experimental probability"
      },
      {
        "id": "6759",
        "question": "Which of the following is the team with the ball that is trying to score?",
        "answer": "offense ",
        "distractor_1": "defense",
        "distractor_2": "opponent",
        "distractor_3": "special teams"
      },
      {
        "id": "6760",
        "question": "Which of the following is the team not in possession of the ball whose objective is to keep the opponent from scoring?",
        "answer": "defense",
        "distractor_1": "offense",
        "distractor_2": "special teams",
        "distractor_3": "opponent"
      },
      {
        "id": "6761",
        "question": "Which of the following is an athletic contest consisting of five different events?",
        "answer": "pentathlon ",
        "distractor_1": "marathon",
        "distractor_2": "race",
        "distractor_3": "triathlon"
      },
      {
        "id": "6762",
        "question": "Which of the following is the product of a whole number and every natural number less than itself?",
        "answer": "factorial ",
        "distractor_1": "exponent",
        "distractor_2": "cross product",
        "distractor_3": "divisor"
      },
      {
        "id": "6763",
        "question": "Which of the following describes possible orders, or arrangements, of a set of events or items that result in a different outcome each time the order is changed? ",
        "answer": "permutation ",
        "distractor_1": "combination",
        "distractor_2": "rotation",
        "distractor_3": "set"
      },
      {
        "id": "6764",
        "question": "Which of the following is a group of items or events in which placing the items or events in a different order does not create a new outcome?",
        "answer": "combination",
        "distractor_1": "permutation",
        "distractor_2": "set",
        "distractor_3": "rotation"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "165",
    "name": "Where in the World",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "6844",
        "question": "Which of following is not a correct descriptor for GPS?",
        "answer": "It is the acronym for Global Positioning Service.",
        "distractor_1": "It is a navigation system.",
        "distractor_2": "It tracks positions on Earth using satellites and a radio reciever.",
        "distractor_3": "It can be used for many different kinds of navigation."
      },
      {
        "id": "5907",
        "question": "Find the distance between point A located at (47.83, 82.54) and point B located at (-6.4, -22.47).",
        "answer": "118.186",
        "distractor_1": "118.18",
        "distractor_2": "118.187",
        "distractor_3": "118.1"
      },
      {
        "id": "5908",
        "question": "Simplify sqrt(13/9).",
        "answer": "sqrt(13/3)",
        "distractor_1": "sqrt(13/9)",
        "distractor_2": "sqrt13/sqrt9",
        "distractor_3": "sqrt(1.667)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5909",
        "question": "Simplify the equation sqrt(16x²) + sqrt(x²y) + 4sqrt(x²).",
        "answer": "8x + (x)sqrt(y)",
        "distractor_1": "(9x)sqrt(y)",
        "distractor_2": "6x + (x)sqrt(y)",
        "distractor_3": "20x + (x)sqrt(y)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5910",
        "question": "Simplify sqrt19.",
        "answer": "sqrt19",
        "distractor_1": "sqrt10 + sqrt9",
        "distractor_2": "6",
        "distractor_3": "3sqrt10"
      },
      {
        "id": "5911",
        "question": "Simplify sqrt12 + 6 - 8.",
        "answer": "sqrt10",
        "distractor_1": "sqrt12 + sqrt6 - sqrt8 ",
        "distractor_2": "sqrt2 · sqrt5",
        "distractor_3": "3sqrt3 + sqrt6 - 2sqrt2 "
      },
      {
        "id": "5912",
        "question": "Which of the following is not an example of a metropolis?",
        "answer": "Sarcoxie, MO",
        "distractor_1": "Los Angeles, CA",
        "distractor_2": "New York, NY",
        "distractor_3": "Kansas City, MO"
      },
      {
        "id": "5913",
        "question": "Which of the following contains a radicand?",
        "answer": "2sqrt(x)",
        "distractor_1": "2x",
        "distractor_2": "2xy",
        "distractor_3": "2x²"
      },
      {
        "id": "5914",
        "question": "Geocaching does not involve which of the following?",
        "answer": "cash prizes",
        "distractor_1": "GPS",
        "distractor_2": "Internet",
        "distractor_3": "travel"
      },
      {
        "id": "5915",
        "question": "The hypotenuse is labeled as which of the following when using the Pythagorean Theorem?",
        "answer": "c",
        "distractor_1": "a",
        "distractor_2": "b",
        "distractor_3": "none of these"
      },
      {
        "id": "5916",
        "question": "A prime number can be defined as which of the following?",
        "answer": "a number only divisible by itself and 1",
        "distractor_1": "the largest number in a group of numbers",
        "distractor_2": "a number only divisible by itself and 2",
        "distractor_3": "the middle number in a group of numbers"
      },
      {
        "id": "5917",
        "question": "A square root is the opposite of which of the following?",
        "answer": "x²",
        "distractor_1": "2x",
        "distractor_2": "sqrt2",
        "distractor_3": "2/2"
      },
      {
        "id": "5891",
        "question": "What is the distance between point A located at (1.3, 5.7) and point B located at (-12.2, 6.4)?",
        "answer": "13.52",
        "distractor_1": "10.88",
        "distractor_2": "3.41",
        "distractor_3": "10.92"
      },
      {
        "id": "5892",
        "question": "Simplify sqrt(50/8). Select the simplified expression.",
        "answer": "5/2",
        "distractor_1": "sqrt50/sqrt8",
        "distractor_2": "sqrt2 · sqrt(25/4) · sqrt2",
        "distractor_3": "sqrt6.25"
      },
      {
        "id": "5893",
        "question": "Simplify 8sqrt(x²y) + sqrt(4x²y). ",
        "answer": "10xsqrt(y)",
        "distractor_1": "4sqrt(x²y)",
        "distractor_2": "8xsqrt(y) + 2xsqrt(y)",
        "distractor_3": "12sqrt(x²y)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5894",
        "question": "What is the term that refers to the measurement of a point in degrees north or south of the equator?",
        "answer": "latitude",
        "distractor_1": "international date line",
        "distractor_2": "longitude",
        "distractor_3": "prime meridian"
      },
      {
        "id": "5895",
        "question": "What is the term that refers to the measurement of a point in degrees east or west of the prime meridian?",
        "answer": "longitude",
        "distractor_1": "international date line",
        "distractor_2": "latitude",
        "distractor_3": "equator"
      },
      {
        "id": "5896",
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct definition of the term radical expression?",
        "answer": "an expression containing a radical sign",
        "distractor_1": "an expression containing a multiplication symbol",
        "distractor_2": "an expression containing a variable",
        "distractor_3": "an expression containing an exponent"
      },
      {
        "id": "5897",
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct definition of the term exponential expression?",
        "answer": "an expression containing an exponent",
        "distractor_1": "an expression containing a radical sign",
        "distractor_2": "an expression containing a variable",
        "distractor_3": "an expression containing a multiplication symbol"
      },
      {
        "id": "5898",
        "question": "Simplify the expression sqrt27.",
        "answer": "3sqrt3",
        "distractor_1": "sqrt27",
        "distractor_2": "sqrt2 · sqrt7",
        "distractor_3": "sqrt9 · sqrt3"
      },
      {
        "id": "5899",
        "question": "Simplify the expression sqrt(36 - 6).",
        "answer": "sqrt30",
        "distractor_1": "sqrt36 - sqrt6",
        "distractor_2": "sqrt(36 - 6)",
        "distractor_3": "6 - sqrt6"
      },
      {
        "id": "5900",
        "question": "Which of the following equations represents the Pythagorean Theorem?",
        "answer": "c² = a² + b²",
        "distractor_1": "c = a + b",
        "distractor_2": "a² = c² + b²",
        "distractor_3": "sqrt(c) = sqrt(a) + sqrt(b)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5901",
        "question": "What does the Product Property of Square Roots state?",
        "answer": "The square root of the product ab is equal to the product of each square root.",
        "distractor_1": "The square root of the product ab is equal to the quotient of each square root.",
        "distractor_2": "The square root of the product ab is equal to the substrand of each square root.",
        "distractor_3": "The square root of the product ab is equal to the sum of each square root."
      },
      {
        "id": "5902",
        "question": "Simplify the expression sqrt8.",
        "answer": "2sqrt2",
        "distractor_1": "sqrt8",
        "distractor_2": "sqrt4",
        "distractor_3": "4"
      },
      {
        "id": "5903",
        "question": "What does the Quotient Property of Square Roots state?",
        "answer": "The square root of the quotient a over b is equal to the quotient of each square root.",
        "distractor_1": "The square root of the quotient a over b is equal to the product of each square root.",
        "distractor_2": "The square root of the quotient a over b is equal to the substrand of each square root.",
        "distractor_3": "The square root of the quotient a over b is equal to the sum of each square root."
      },
      {
        "id": "5904",
        "question": "What is the distance between (4.85, 6.72) and (3.16, -10.43)?",
        "answer": "17.23",
        "distractor_1": "17.3",
        "distractor_2": "17.24",
        "distractor_3": "18"
      },
      {
        "id": "5906",
        "question": "Simplify 3sqrt(x³y) - sqrt(9xy) + 5sqrt(x³y).",
        "answer": "(8x)sqrt(xy) - 3sqrt(xy)",
        "distractor_1": "8sqrt(x³y) - 3sqrt(xy)",
        "distractor_2": "5sqrt(x³y)",
        "distractor_3": "3x²sqrt(xy) - 3sqrt(xy) + 5x²sqrt(xy)"
      },
      {
        "id": "6781",
        "question": "Which of the following is a great circle that divides Earth into Northern and Southern Hemispheres?",
        "answer": "equator",
        "distractor_1": "prime meridian",
        "distractor_2": "Tropic of Capricorn",
        "distractor_3": "Tropic of Cancer"
      },
      {
        "id": "6782",
        "question": "Which of the following is a great circle that divides Earth into Eastern and Western Hemispheres?",
        "answer": "prime meridian",
        "distractor_1": "equator",
        "distractor_2": "Tropic of Cancer",
        "distractor_3": "Tropic of Capricorn"
      },
      {
        "id": "6783",
        "question": "What is the name of the process of determining the location of one place by measuring the angles and distances of others?",
        "answer": "trilateration",
        "distractor_1": "Distance Formula",
        "distractor_2": "Pythagorean Theorem",
        "distractor_3": "map scale"
      },
      {
        "id": "6784",
        "question": "What is the distance from any point on a circle to the center called?",
        "answer": "radius",
        "distractor_1": "circumference",
        "distractor_2": "diameter",
        "distractor_3": "pi"
      },
      {
        "id": "6785",
        "question": "Which of the following is an ordered pair of numbers that would represent location?",
        "answer": "coordinates",
        "distractor_1": "degrees",
        "distractor_2": "variables",
        "distractor_3": "points"
      },
      {
        "id": "6786",
        "question": "Which of the following is an exact measurement?",
        "answer": "absolute location",
        "distractor_1": "relative location",
        "distractor_2": "approximation",
        "distractor_3": "estimated distance"
      },
      {
        "id": "6787",
        "question": "Which of the following terms best describes the location of something as described by its surroundings?",
        "answer": "relative",
        "distractor_1": "absolute",
        "distractor_2": "approximate",
        "distractor_3": "exact"
      },
      {
        "id": "6788",
        "question": "Which of the following terms best describes a drawing done in proportion to an original object?",
        "answer": "scaled",
        "distractor_1": "laddered",
        "distractor_2": "graduated",
        "distractor_3": "fitted"
      },
      {
        "id": "6789",
        "question": "Which term best describes a slightly elongated and bulging circle, like Earth?",
        "answer": "oblate spheroid",
        "distractor_1": "sphere",
        "distractor_2": "ellipse",
        "distractor_3": "flattened ellipse"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "159",
    "name": "Water Quality",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "6845",
        "question": "Sove the inequality -5/2x < 25.",
        "answer": "x > -10",
        "distractor_1": "x = -5",
        "distractor_2": "x < -10",
        "distractor_3": "x < 50"
      },
      {
        "id": "6846",
        "question": "Solve the inequality -8y > 48.",
        "answer": "y < -6",
        "distractor_1": "y = -6",
        "distractor_2": "y > -6",
        "distractor_3": "y > 6"
      },
      {
        "id": "6736",
        "question": "Which of the following is an expression that has a range of answers rather than a single solution?",
        "answer": "inequality ",
        "distractor_1": "equation",
        "distractor_2": "deviation",
        "distractor_3": "cardinal number"
      },
      {
        "id": "6737",
        "question": "Which of the following describes the alkali concentration or alkaline quantity of a substance?",
        "answer": "alkalinity ",
        "distractor_1": "transparency",
        "distractor_2": "salinity",
        "distractor_3": "range"
      },
      {
        "id": "6738",
        "question": "Which of the following is a chemical element used as a disinfectant in drinking water and wastewater treatment processes?",
        "answer": "chlorine ",
        "distractor_1": "Lysol",
        "distractor_2": "sodium",
        "distractor_3": "ammonia"
      },
      {
        "id": "6739",
        "question": "Which of the following is the measure of the amount of minerals in water?",
        "answer": "water hardness",
        "distractor_1": "porosity",
        "distractor_2": "Mohs’ scale",
        "distractor_3": "humidity"
      },
      {
        "id": "6740",
        "question": "Which of the following is the measure of the acidity or alkalinity of a substance?",
        "answer": "pH",
        "distractor_1": "porosity",
        "distractor_2": "velocity",
        "distractor_3": "viscosity"
      },
      {
        "id": "6741",
        "question": "Which of the following is a chemical element essential to the growth of plants and animals?",
        "answer": "nitrogen ",
        "distractor_1": "potassium",
        "distractor_2": "chromium",
        "distractor_3": "magnesium"
      },
      {
        "id": "5866",
        "question": "Which of the following terms describes an expression that has more than one solution?",
        "answer": " inequality",
        "distractor_1": "function",
        "distractor_2": "equation",
        "distractor_3": "absolute value"
      },
      {
        "id": "5871",
        "question": "The pH of a liquid can be described by which of the following?",
        "answer": "acidic, basic, or neutral",
        "distractor_1": "volatile, inactive, or harmless",
        "distractor_2": "organic, human-made, or caustic",
        "distractor_3": "polluted, drinkable, or pure"
      },
      {
        "id": "5875",
        "question": "An inequality expression has which of the following?",
        "answer": "more than one solution",
        "distractor_1": "one answer that is bigger than another",
        "distractor_2": "no solution",
        "distractor_3": "one solution"
      },
      {
        "id": "5878",
        "question": "Which of the following defines absolute value?",
        "answer": "the distance a number is from zero on a number line",
        "distractor_1": "the maximum value a number can have",
        "distractor_2": "the sum of two numbers",
        "distractor_3": "the square root of a number"
      },
      {
        "id": "5880",
        "question": "Which of the following chemicals is added to drinking water as a disinfectant?",
        "answer": "chlorine",
        "distractor_1": "Lysol",
        "distractor_2": "hydrogen peroxide",
        "distractor_3": "sodium chloride"
      },
      {
        "id": "5883",
        "question": "Water hardness is the measure of which two minerals?",
        "answer": "calcium and magnesium",
        "distractor_1": "chromium and iron",
        "distractor_2": "fluoride and sodium",
        "distractor_3": "lead and iron"
      },
      {
        "id": "6742",
        "question": "Which of the following is a line or curve that separates the coordinate plane into regions?",
        "answer": "boundary line ",
        "distractor_1": "line of symmetry",
        "distractor_2": "perpendicular line",
        "distractor_3": "line of best fit"
      },
      {
        "id": "6743",
        "question": "Which of the following describes the region of the graph of an inequality on one side of a boundary?",
        "answer": "half-plane ",
        "distractor_1": "grid",
        "distractor_2": "coplanar",
        "distractor_3": "perimeter"
      },
      {
        "id": "6744",
        "question": "Which of the following is the distance a number is from zero on a number line?",
        "answer": "absolute value ",
        "distractor_1": "place value",
        "distractor_2": "line plot",
        "distractor_3": "difference"
      },
      {
        "id": "6745",
        "question": "Which of the following describes a set of two or more inequalities with the same variable?",
        "answer": "system of inequalities",
        "distractor_1": "common inequalities",
        "distractor_2": "linear inequalities",
        "distractor_3": "compound inequalities"
      },
      {
        "id": "6746",
        "question": "Which of the following is a line that has alternating marks and white space?",
        "answer": "dashed line ",
        "distractor_1": "diagonal line",
        "distractor_2": "half line",
        "distractor_3": "trend line"
      },
      {
        "id": "6747",
        "question": "Which of the following describes two or more inequalities that are connected by the words 'and' or 'or'?",
        "answer": "compound inequality",
        "distractor_1": "linear inequalities",
        "distractor_2": "combination inequalities",
        "distractor_3": "symmetrical inequalities"
      },
      {
        "id": "5885",
        "question": "The chlorine found in bleach is how many times more concentrated than the chlorine used in drinking water?",
        "answer": "50,000",
        "distractor_1": "350",
        "distractor_2": "1,000,000",
        "distractor_3": "1,000"
      },
      {
        "id": "5886",
        "question": "A plumber has estimated that a job will take at least two hours to complete, and the parts for the job are $36. The plumber charges $35 an hour. What is the minimum amount he will charge his customer?",
        "answer": "$106",
        "distractor_1": "$71",
        "distractor_2": "$1,260",
        "distractor_3": "$107"
      },
      {
        "id": "5887",
        "question": "The pH measurement of a substance is based on which factors?",
        "answer": "the number of hydrogen and hydroxyl ions in the substance",
        "distractor_1": "oxygen and acid interactions within the substance",
        "distractor_2": "the corrosiveness of the substance",
        "distractor_3": "the smell of the substance"
      },
      {
        "id": "5889",
        "question": "Which of the following accounts for the single largest use of water in the United States?",
        "answer": "farming",
        "distractor_1": "manufacturing ",
        "distractor_2": "human consumption",
        "distractor_3": "sewage treatment"
      },
      {
        "id": "8250",
        "question": "Choose the inequality that represents the following problem. Kristina has signed up to bring 20 brownies for the school carnival. One batch makes 12 brownies. How many batches will she need to make?",
        "answer": "12b > 20",
        "distractor_1": "20 - 12 > b",
        "distractor_2": "12 - b < 20",
        "distractor_3": "b + 20 = 12"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "167",
    "name": "Supply & Demand",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "6837",
        "question": "What term can be defined as the change in the y-coordinates to the corresponding change in the x-coordinates as you move from one point to another along a line?",
        "answer": "slope",
        "distractor_1": "y-intercept",
        "distractor_2": "x-intercept",
        "distractor_3": "differential"
      },
      {
        "id": "6790",
        "question": "Which of the terms below is defined as that state of being sought after? ",
        "answer": "demand",
        "distractor_1": "supply",
        "distractor_2": "profit",
        "distractor_3": "economics"
      },
      {
        "id": "6791",
        "question": "Which term refers to a particular group of buyers?",
        "answer": "market",
        "distractor_1": "economics",
        "distractor_2": "demand",
        "distractor_3": "supply"
      },
      {
        "id": "6792",
        "question": "Which of the following is described as a person or thing that consumes, especially a person who buys and uses goods and services? ",
        "answer": "consumer",
        "distractor_1": "producer",
        "distractor_2": "supply",
        "distractor_3": "demand"
      },
      {
        "id": "6793",
        "question": "What is defined as a person, an organization, or thing that produces, especially one that makes something for sale?",
        "answer": "producer",
        "distractor_1": "consumer",
        "distractor_2": "economist",
        "distractor_3": "marketing"
      },
      {
        "id": "6794",
        "question": "What is defined as money made in a business venture, sale, or investment after all expenses have been met? ",
        "answer": "profit",
        "distractor_1": "net pay",
        "distractor_2": "gross pay",
        "distractor_3": "supply"
      },
      {
        "id": "6795",
        "question": "Which of the following is defined as making available for use? ",
        "answer": "supply",
        "distractor_1": "demand",
        "distractor_2": "economics",
        "distractor_3": "market"
      },
      {
        "id": "6796",
        "question": "Which term is defined as how much the quantity changes when the price changes?",
        "answer": "elasticity",
        "distractor_1": "economics",
        "distractor_2": "demand",
        "distractor_3": "profit"
      },
      {
        "id": "5918",
        "question": "What term can be defined as a change in the price of a product with regard to the quantity of supply or demand?",
        "answer": "elasticity",
        "distractor_1": "surplus",
        "distractor_2": "shortage",
        "distractor_3": "supply"
      },
      {
        "id": "5919",
        "question": "A system of equations is composed of the equations 3y + 2x = 3 and y = x. Which method is the easiest method to solve this system?",
        "answer": "substitution",
        "distractor_1": "elimination by addition",
        "distractor_2": "elimination by subtraction",
        "distractor_3": "elimination by multiplication"
      },
      {
        "id": "5920",
        "question": "A demand line is defined by the equation 2y - 6x = 10. What is the slope of this line?",
        "answer": "3",
        "distractor_1": "5",
        "distractor_2": "6",
        "distractor_3": "10"
      },
      {
        "id": "5921",
        "question": "A supply line is defined by the equation x + y = 8 and the demand line is defined by the equation x - y = 4. What is the equilibrium point of this system?",
        "answer": "(6, 2)",
        "distractor_1": "(2, 6)",
        "distractor_2": "(3, 1)",
        "distractor_3": "(8, 4)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5922",
        "question": "On a supply and demand chart, what variable is usually represented on the x-axis?",
        "answer": "quantity",
        "distractor_1": "supply",
        "distractor_2": "demand",
        "distractor_3": "price"
      },
      {
        "id": "5923",
        "question": "In a typical supply and demand situation, as supply increases, what happens to the demand?",
        "answer": "decreases",
        "distractor_1": "remains constant",
        "distractor_2": "increases",
        "distractor_3": "increases and then decreases"
      },
      {
        "id": "5924",
        "question": "A system of equations is composed of the equations y - x^3 + 27 = 0 and y - 2x^2 = 9. What is the maximum number of solutions for this system?",
        "answer": "3",
        "distractor_1": "0",
        "distractor_2": "1",
        "distractor_3": "2"
      },
      {
        "id": "5925",
        "question": "A system of equations has one solution. What type of system is this?",
        "answer": "consistent-independent",
        "distractor_1": "consistent-dependent",
        "distractor_2": "inconsistent-independent",
        "distractor_3": "inconsistent-dependent"
      },
      {
        "id": "5926",
        "question": "How many solutions does the system of equations composed of the equations 2x + 5y = 4 and 4x + 10y = 8 have?",
        "answer": "infinity",
        "distractor_1": "0",
        "distractor_2": "1",
        "distractor_3": "2"
      },
      {
        "id": "5927",
        "question": "What occurs when the amount demanded by the consumer is greater than the amount supplied by the producer?",
        "answer": "shortage",
        "distractor_1": "surplus",
        "distractor_2": "equilibrium",
        "distractor_3": "elasticity"
      },
      {
        "id": "5928",
        "question": "The number of hours a part-time employee can work in one week is defined by the equation 2x + 72 - 3(x + 12). If x is equal to 3, how many hours can a part-time employee work in a week?",
        "answer": "33 hours",
        "distractor_1": "22 hours",
        "distractor_2": "70 hours",
        "distractor_3": "40 hours"
      },
      {
        "id": "5929",
        "question": "What term refers to the part of economics that studies an individual business, how it behaves, and how it competes against other businesses in markets?",
        "answer": "microeconomics",
        "distractor_1": "macroeconomics",
        "distractor_2": "nanoeconomics",
        "distractor_3": "market economics"
      },
      {
        "id": "5930",
        "question": "The demand line of a supply and demand system is defined by the equation 2y + 8x – 10 = 0. What is the slope of the demand line?",
        "answer": "-4",
        "distractor_1": "-8",
        "distractor_2": "8",
        "distractor_3": "4"
      },
      {
        "id": "5931",
        "question": "What term refers to a situation where only one business is the seller of a certain product?",
        "answer": "monopoly",
        "distractor_1": "cartel",
        "distractor_2": "oligopoly",
        "distractor_3": "recession"
      },
      {
        "id": "5933",
        "question": "What occurs when sellers in all parts of the economy raise their prices?",
        "answer": "inflation",
        "distractor_1": "recession",
        "distractor_2": "deflation",
        "distractor_3": "opportunity cost"
      },
      {
        "id": "5935",
        "question": "A system of equations is composed of the equations y + x^2 = 9 and y - 2x^4 = 16. What is the maximum number of solutions for this system?",
        "answer": "4",
        "distractor_1": "1",
        "distractor_2": "2",
        "distractor_3": "3"
      },
      {
        "id": "5936",
        "question": "On a supply and demand chart, what variable is usually represented on the y-axis?",
        "answer": "price",
        "distractor_1": "quantity",
        "distractor_2": "supply",
        "distractor_3": "demand"
      },
      {
        "id": "5937",
        "question": "In supply and demand, as the supply for a product increases, what tends to happen to the price of the product?",
        "answer": "increases",
        "distractor_1": "decreases",
        "distractor_2": "stays the same",
        "distractor_3": "depends on the product"
      },
      {
        "id": "5938",
        "question": "A system of equations is composed of the equations 6y + 4x = 3 and 3y - 4x = 12. Which of the following is the easiest method to solve this system?",
        "answer": "elimination by addition",
        "distractor_1": "elimination by subtraction",
        "distractor_2": "elimination by multiplication",
        "distractor_3": "substitution"
      },
      {
        "id": "5939",
        "question": "What term can be defined as a change in the price of a product with regard to the quantity of supply or demand?",
        "answer": "elasticity",
        "distractor_1": "surplus",
        "distractor_2": "supply",
        "distractor_3": "shortage"
      },
      {
        "id": "5940",
        "question": "A supply line is defined by the equation 6x - 2y = 24, and the demand line is given by the equation 3x + 4y = 27. What is the equilibrium point of this system?",
        "answer": "(5, 3)",
        "distractor_1": "(3, 5)",
        "distractor_2": "(2, 6)",
        "distractor_3": "(7, 9)"
      },
      {
        "id": "5941",
        "question": "A supply line is defined by the equation 2y + 6x = 2. What is the slope of this line?",
        "answer": "-3",
        "distractor_1": "1",
        "distractor_2": "-6",
        "distractor_3": "2"
      },
      {
        "id": "5942",
        "question": "How many solutions does the system of equations composed of the equations 3x + y = 4 and 3x + y = 8 have?",
        "answer": "0",
        "distractor_1": "2",
        "distractor_2": "1",
        "distractor_3": "infinity"
      },
      {
        "id": "5943",
        "question": "A system of equations has one solution. What type of system is this?",
        "answer": "consistent-independent",
        "distractor_1": "consistent-dependent",
        "distractor_2": "inconsistent-dependent",
        "distractor_3": "inconsistent-independent"
      },
      {
        "id": "6797",
        "question": "Which term is defined as of or relating to the production, development, and management of wealth, as of a country, household, or business?",
        "answer": "economics",
        "distractor_1": "elasticity",
        "distractor_2": "market",
        "distractor_3": "consumer"
      },
      {
        "id": "6798",
        "question": "Which of the following is defined as a set of equations with the same variables?",
        "answer": "system of equations",
        "distractor_1": "system of inequalities",
        "distractor_2": "y-intercept",
        "distractor_3": "slope"
      },
      {
        "id": "6799",
        "question": "Which of the following refers to the coordinate at which a graph intersects the y-axis? ",
        "answer": "y-intercept",
        "distractor_1": "x-intercept",
        "distractor_2": "slope-intercept",
        "distractor_3": "slope"
      },
      {
        "id": "6800",
        "question": "What is a mathematical statement asserting the equality of two expressions?",
        "answer": "equation",
        "distractor_1": "system of equations",
        "distractor_2": "y-intercept",
        "distractor_3": "x-intercept"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "170",
    "name": "Rocks & Resources",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "7352",
        "question": "Which are the most common types of igneous rock?",
        "answer": "granite and basalt",
        "distractor_1": "obsidian and pumice",
        "distractor_2": "sandstone and shale",
        "distractor_3": "slate and marble"
      },
      {
        "id": "7353",
        "question": "Lead and zinc ore in the Picher, Oklahoma, area was mined by which process?",
        "answer": "room-and-pillar mining",
        "distractor_1": "mountaintop removal",
        "distractor_2": "open-pit mining",
        "distractor_3": "in situ mining"
      },
      {
        "id": "7380",
        "question": "What is the name of the process in which ore is melted to separate the useful metal from other substances in the ore?",
        "answer": "smelting",
        "distractor_1": "mining",
        "distractor_2": "refining",
        "distractor_3": "melting"
      },
      {
        "id": "7381",
        "question": "A carat is a unit of weight for gemstones that equals 200 milligrams. The Jonker diamond weighs 726 carats. It recently sold for $2,259,400.00. What was its sale price per carat?",
        "answer": "$3,112.12",
        "distractor_1": "$11,297.00",
        "distractor_2": "$451,880.00",
        "distractor_3": "$1,640,324.00"
      },
      {
        "id": "7355",
        "question": "Which two characteristics are often found in sedimentary rock?",
        "answer": "layering and fossils",
        "distractor_1": "vesicles and large particles",
        "distractor_2": "crystals and gas bubbles",
        "distractor_3": "glass-like texture and bright color"
      },
      {
        "id": "7356",
        "question": "A deposit of copper ore contains 1% copper. This statement describes what characteristic of the ore deposit?",
        "answer": "grade",
        "distractor_1": "density",
        "distractor_2": "hardness",
        "distractor_3": "value"
      },
      {
        "id": "7357",
        "question": "Which type of rock is formed when material erupts from Earth's core, cools, and forms crystals?",
        "answer": "igneous",
        "distractor_1": "magma",
        "distractor_2": "metamorphic",
        "distractor_3": "sedimentary"
      },
      {
        "id": "7358",
        "question": "Which type of rock is most likely to show layers?",
        "answer": "sandstone",
        "distractor_1": "granite",
        "distractor_2": "obsidian",
        "distractor_3": "marble"
      },
      {
        "id": "7359",
        "question": "Which of the following is a nonrenewable, mined resource but is not a metal or a mineral?",
        "answer": "coal",
        "distractor_1": "sand",
        "distractor_2": "copper",
        "distractor_3": "halite"
      },
      {
        "id": "7360",
        "question": "A certain mineral is very soft and has a slightly greasy texture. These properties make it useful for writing, so it is used in pencils. What mineral is this?",
        "answer": "graphite",
        "distractor_1": "lead",
        "distractor_2": "gypsum",
        "distractor_3": "corundum"
      },
      {
        "id": "7361",
        "question": "Which of the following is an example of metamorphic rock?",
        "answer": "slate",
        "distractor_1": "shale",
        "distractor_2": "breccia",
        "distractor_3": "obsidian"
      },
      {
        "id": "7362",
        "question": "When a mineral reflects light, it appears shiny like polished metal. What property of the mineral does this describe?",
        "answer": "luster",
        "distractor_1": "color",
        "distractor_2": "streak",
        "distractor_3": "fluorescence"
      },
      {
        "id": "7363",
        "question": "Heavy metals such as copper, iron, and gold are often mined by which process?",
        "answer": "open-pit mining",
        "distractor_1": "dredging",
        "distractor_2": "mountaintop removal",
        "distractor_3": "in situ mining"
      },
      {
        "id": "7364",
        "question": "Which of the following is a destructive process in the rock cycle?",
        "answer": "weathering",
        "distractor_1": "crystallization",
        "distractor_2": "lithification",
        "distractor_3": "metamorphism"
      },
      {
        "id": "7365",
        "question": "A mineral is said to break neatly in two directions. Which property is being described?",
        "answer": "cleavage",
        "distractor_1": "density",
        "distractor_2": "hardness",
        "distractor_3": "fracture"
      },
      {
        "id": "7366",
        "question": "Which of the following problems is directly caused by release of particulate pollution from mining?",
        "answer": "lung diseases",
        "distractor_1": "acid mine drainage",
        "distractor_2": "mine tailings piles",
        "distractor_3": "mine cave-ins"
      },
      {
        "id": "7367",
        "question": "The alloy pewter is composed of 91% tin, 7% antimony, and 2% copper by weight. What is the total weight of copper plus antimony found in a 5 lb pewter vase?",
        "answer": "0.45 lb",
        "distractor_1": "0.1 lb",
        "distractor_2": "0.35 lb",
        "distractor_3": "1.35 lb"
      },
      {
        "id": "7368",
        "question": "Which of the following is a constructive process in the rock cycle?",
        "answer": "crystallization",
        "distractor_1": "weathering",
        "distractor_2": "erosion",
        "distractor_3": "melting"
      },
      {
        "id": "7369",
        "question": "Which of the following is a nonrenewable, mined resource but is not a metal?",
        "answer": "gypsum",
        "distractor_1": "copper",
        "distractor_2": "gold",
        "distractor_3": "iron"
      },
      {
        "id": "7370",
        "question": "Mine tailings piles, such as the chat piles around Picher, Oklahoma, have caused which type of pollution that has led to lung disease and other health problems?",
        "answer": "particulate pollution",
        "distractor_1": "acid mine drainage",
        "distractor_2": "mine cave-ins",
        "distractor_3": "damaged agricultural land"
      },
      {
        "id": "7371",
        "question": "Which of the following is true of a mineral but not of a rock?",
        "answer": "It has a definite chemical composition.",
        "distractor_1": "It is a solid.",
        "distractor_2": "It is inorganic.",
        "distractor_3": "It is made of several different substances."
      },
      {
        "id": "7372",
        "question": "The grade of an ore refers to which of the following?",
        "answer": "the percentage by weight of ore in the rock",
        "distractor_1": "the type of useful product it contains",
        "distractor_2": "the depth at which it is found",
        "distractor_3": "the total amount of ore in the rock"
      },
      {
        "id": "7374",
        "question": "If you view an object through a transparent piece of the mineral calcite, the object appears doubled. What property of calcite does this show?",
        "answer": "double refraction",
        "distractor_1": "duplicity",
        "distractor_2": "duplication",
        "distractor_3": "double reflection"
      },
      {
        "id": "7375",
        "question": "A country mined 600,000 metric tons of copper in a year. If there are 2,204.6 pounds of copper in a metric ton and copper sells for $1.80 per pound, how much money did the copper bring in?",
        "answer": "$2,380,968,000",
        "distractor_1": "$1,080,000",
        "distractor_2": "$238,096,800",
        "distractor_3": "$1,322,760,000"
      },
      {
        "id": "7376",
        "question": "Which type of rock is formed when weathered material is compacted into layers and cemented together?",
        "answer": "sedimentary",
        "distractor_1": "magma",
        "distractor_2": "igneous",
        "distractor_3": "metamorphic"
      },
      {
        "id": "7377",
        "question": "Which of the following properties is true of metals but not true of other minerals?",
        "answer": "They conduct heat and electricity.",
        "distractor_1": "They are solids.",
        "distractor_2": "They are inorganic.",
        "distractor_3": "They have definite chemical structures."
      },
      {
        "id": "7378",
        "question": "Carbonic acid dissolves limestone inside caverns, forming icicle-like structures called stalactites. Which process is responsible for making stalactites?",
        "answer": "chemical weathering",
        "distractor_1": "erosion",
        "distractor_2": "deposition",
        "distractor_3": "mechanical weathering"
      },
      {
        "id": "7379",
        "question": "Molten lava from Hawaii's Mount Kilauea has a temperature of about 1,000ºC. What is this temperature in degrees Fahrenheit? The conversion factor for Celsius to Fahrenheit is F = 1.8C + 32.",
        "answer": "1,832ºF",
        "distractor_1": "524ºF",
        "distractor_2": "1,000ºF",
        "distractor_3": "1,032ºF"
      },
      {
        "id": "7410",
        "question": "rock type formed when molten magma from Earth's core erupts, cools, and crystallizes",
        "answer": "igneous",
        "distractor_1": "sedimentary",
        "distractor_2": "metamorphic",
        "distractor_3": "crystalline"
      },
      {
        "id": "7411",
        "question": "rock type formed when sediment layers compact, compress, and cement together",
        "answer": "sedimentary",
        "distractor_1": "igneous",
        "distractor_2": "metamorphic",
        "distractor_3": "crystalline"
      },
      {
        "id": "7412",
        "question": "rock type formed when another type of rock changes due to extreme heat or pressure",
        "answer": "metamorphic",
        "distractor_1": "sedimentary",
        "distractor_2": "igneous",
        "distractor_3": "crystalline"
      },
      {
        "id": "7413",
        "question": "a solid, inorganic, naturally occurring substance with a crystalline structure and a specific chemical composition",
        "answer": "mineral",
        "distractor_1": "rock",
        "distractor_2": "ore",
        "distractor_3": "alloy"
      },
      {
        "id": "7414",
        "question": "a property of minerals based on arrangement of atoms into specific angles and faces",
        "answer": "crystal",
        "distractor_1": "hardness",
        "distractor_2": "cleavage",
        "distractor_3": "texture"
      },
      {
        "id": "7415",
        "question": "a property of minerals that causes them to glow when exposed to ultraviolet light",
        "answer": "fluorescence",
        "distractor_1": "phosphorescence",
        "distractor_2": "luster",
        "distractor_3": "grade"
      },
      {
        "id": "7416",
        "question": "the ability of a mineral to resist scratching by another mineral or by an object",
        "answer": "hardness",
        "distractor_1": "texture",
        "distractor_2": "fracture",
        "distractor_3": "cleavage"
      },
      {
        "id": "7417",
        "question": "removal of a valuable resource, such as a metal or mineral, from the ground for use",
        "answer": "mining",
        "distractor_1": "smelting",
        "distractor_2": "dredging",
        "distractor_3": "drilling"
      },
      {
        "id": "7418",
        "question": "a rock or mineral containing a valuable material that can be mined and sold for profit",
        "answer": "ore",
        "distractor_1": "alloy",
        "distractor_2": "chat",
        "distractor_3": "sediment"
      },
      {
        "id": "7419",
        "question": "a material found in nature that people can use and that has economic value",
        "answer": "natural resource",
        "distractor_1": "rock",
        "distractor_2": "crystal",
        "distractor_3": "alloy"
      },
      {
        "id": "7420",
        "question": "nonliving, or unable to be replaced by reproduction, for example, metal resources",
        "answer": "nonrenewable",
        "distractor_1": "renewable",
        "distractor_2": "perpetual",
        "distractor_3": "organic"
      },
      {
        "id": "7421",
        "question": "a mixture of two or more metals having properties not found in the original metals",
        "answer": "alloy",
        "distractor_1": "ore",
        "distractor_2": "mineral",
        "distractor_3": "rock"
      },
      {
        "id": "7422",
        "question": "piles of waste rock, often containing toxic materials, produced during mining",
        "answer": "tailings",
        "distractor_1": "sediment",
        "distractor_2": "acid mine drainage",
        "distractor_3": "particulates"
      },
      {
        "id": "7423",
        "question": "solid soil-like material, produced by weathering of rock or by mining, which in the short term enters water bodies and smothers life and in the long term becomes compressed into rock",
        "answer": "sediment",
        "distractor_1": "overburden",
        "distractor_2": "drift",
        "distractor_3": "halite"
      },
      {
        "id": "7424",
        "question": "a volcanic opening on the ocean floor that releases hot, black smoke and that contains ore deposits rich in gold, copper, manganese, and other metals",
        "answer": "black smoker",
        "distractor_1": "manganese nodule",
        "distractor_2": "seabed crawler",
        "distractor_3": "ring of fire"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "171",
    "name": "Changing Oceans",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "7450",
        "question": "all of the connected ocean water on Earth, consisting of the five main oceans and other connected seas",
        "answer": "world ocean ",
        "distractor_1": "super ocean",
        "distractor_2": "connected ocean",
        "distractor_3": "super seas"
      },
      {
        "id": "7451",
        "question": "saltiness, or ratio of dissolved salts to water, by weight",
        "answer": "salinity",
        "distractor_1": "density",
        "distractor_2": "pH",
        "distractor_3": "acidity"
      },
      {
        "id": "7452",
        "question": "mass of a substance contained in a given space, for example, grams per milliliter",
        "answer": "density",
        "distractor_1": "salinity",
        "distractor_2": "pressure",
        "distractor_3": "volume"
      },
      {
        "id": "7453",
        "question": "shallowest part of the ocean, nearest the shore, with the most light and life  ",
        "answer": "continental shelf ",
        "distractor_1": "continental slope",
        "distractor_2": "coastline",
        "distractor_3": "abyssal plain"
      },
      {
        "id": "7454",
        "question": "flattest part of the deep ocean floor, with occasional trenches, mountains, and mountain ridges",
        "answer": "abyssal plain ",
        "distractor_1": "continental shelf",
        "distractor_2": "continental slope",
        "distractor_3": "twilight zone"
      },
      {
        "id": "7455",
        "question": "organisms that make their own food by photosynthesis; in the oceans, these are phytoplankton and algae",
        "answer": "producers",
        "distractor_1": "consumers",
        "distractor_2": "feeders",
        "distractor_3": "zooplankton"
      },
      {
        "id": "7456",
        "question": "animals and other organisms that cannot make their own food, but depend on producers for energy",
        "answer": "consumers",
        "distractor_1": "eaters",
        "distractor_2": "feeders",
        "distractor_3": "phytoplankton"
      },
      {
        "id": "7457",
        "question": "series of organisms that feed on one another and are connected by the flow of energy",
        "answer": "food chain ",
        "distractor_1": "food link",
        "distractor_2": "energy web",
        "distractor_3": "energy flow"
      },
      {
        "id": "7458",
        "question": "any product of human activity that contaminates the environment",
        "answer": "pollution",
        "distractor_1": "impurity",
        "distractor_2": "sewage",
        "distractor_3": "pathogen"
      },
      {
        "id": "7459",
        "question": "shallow, partly enclosed area of ocean near the shore, having one or more rivers opening into it and forming productive nursery areas for marine animals",
        "answer": "estuary",
        "distractor_1": "continental shelf",
        "distractor_2": "coral reef",
        "distractor_3": "abyss"
      },
      {
        "id": "7460",
        "question": "large body of ocean water moving in a certain direction; a river in the ocean",
        "answer": "current",
        "distractor_1": "wave",
        "distractor_2": "gyre",
        "distractor_3": "tide"
      },
      {
        "id": "7461",
        "question": "all the interconnected food chains in an ecosystem",
        "answer": "food web ",
        "distractor_1": "food graph",
        "distractor_2": "energy web",
        "distractor_3": "energy flow"
      },
      {
        "id": "7462",
        "question": "large body of ocean water moving in a circle between continents",
        "answer": "gyre",
        "distractor_1": "wave",
        "distractor_2": "current",
        "distractor_3": "tide"
      },
      {
        "id": "7463",
        "question": "a giant world current that continuously moves cold Arctic water deep into the ocean and south to the equator and replaces it with warm equatorial water",
        "answer": "ocean conveyor belt ",
        "distractor_1": "upwelling",
        "distractor_2": "El Niño",
        "distractor_3": "Gulf Stream"
      },
      {
        "id": "7464",
        "question": "upward movement of water from the deep ocean",
        "answer": "upwelling",
        "distractor_1": "surface current",
        "distractor_2": "deep current",
        "distractor_3": "ocean conveyor belt"
      },
      {
        "id": "7465",
        "question": "trapping of heat by greenhouse gases in the atmosphere; responsible for maintaining Earth's temperature warm enough to support life",
        "answer": "greenhouse effect ",
        "distractor_1": "global warming",
        "distractor_2": "climate change",
        "distractor_3": "heat sink"
      },
      {
        "id": "7466",
        "question": "increase in average global temperature above normal levels",
        "answer": "global warming ",
        "distractor_1": "greenhouse effect",
        "distractor_2": "climate change",
        "distractor_3": "heat sink"
      },
      {
        "id": "7467",
        "question": "tiny algae that live inside coral polyps and provide them with part of their food; death of zooxanthellae causes coral bleaching",
        "answer": "zooxanthellae",
        "distractor_1": "zooplankton",
        "distractor_2": "kelp",
        "distractor_3": "mollusks"
      },
      {
        "id": "7468",
        "question": "increase in acid levels in the ocean, currently happening because of the increased atmospheric carbon dioxide dissolving into the water",
        "answer": "ocean acidification ",
        "distractor_1": "ocean pH",
        "distractor_2": "acid-base balance",
        "distractor_3": "ocean density"
      },
      {
        "id": "7469",
        "question": "an active volcano on the ocean floor; it forms a tall chimney containing high concentrations of heavy metals and has unique animal life",
        "answer": "black smoker ",
        "distractor_1": "manganese nodule",
        "distractor_2": "abyssal spout",
        "distractor_3": "seabed crawler"
      },
      {
        "id": "7470",
        "question": "energy to generate electricity obtained by using dams or turbines to tap the power of ocean tides ",
        "answer": "tidal energy ",
        "distractor_1": "turbine energy",
        "distractor_2": "nuclear energy",
        "distractor_3": "biomass energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "7489",
        "question": "Water tends to sink the most when it is which of the following?",
        "answer": "cold and salty",
        "distractor_1": "cold and fresh",
        "distractor_2": "warm and salty",
        "distractor_3": "warm and fresh"
      },
      {
        "id": "7490",
        "question": "Most life in the oceans occurs in which of the following zones?",
        "answer": "light zone",
        "distractor_1": "twilight zone",
        "distractor_2": "midnight zone",
        "distractor_3": "abyssal zone"
      },
      {
        "id": "7491",
        "question": "Which of the following types of organisms form the base of most ocean food webs?",
        "answer": "phytoplankton",
        "distractor_1": "bottom-dwellers such as mollusks and crustaceans",
        "distractor_2": "whales and large fish",
        "distractor_3": "zooplankton"
      },
      {
        "id": "7492",
        "question": "What is the best description of the condition of most present-day world fisheries?",
        "answer": "Most fish populations are decreasing due to overfishing.",
        "distractor_1": "Most fish populations are decreasing due to ocean pollution.",
        "distractor_2": "Most fish populations are stable because fishing pressure has not changed.",
        "distractor_3": "Most fish populations are increasing because fishing pressure has decreased."
      },
      {
        "id": "7493",
        "question": "Which types of pollution cause loss of oxygen in coastal waters, followed by death of fish and other animals?",
        "answer": "sewage and nutrients",
        "distractor_1": "silt and litter",
        "distractor_2": "sewage and toxins",
        "distractor_3": "heavy metals and heat"
      },
      {
        "id": "7494",
        "question": "Off the coasts of the United States, which type of ecosystem is very important as a nursery area for baby fish and invertebrates?",
        "answer": "estuaries",
        "distractor_1": "coral reefs",
        "distractor_2": "sea grass beds",
        "distractor_3": "gyres"
      },
      {
        "id": "7495",
        "question": "Which of the following is a major pollution problem in the open ocean, particularly in the Pacific?",
        "answer": "plastics",
        "distractor_1": "sewage",
        "distractor_2": "heavy metals",
        "distractor_3": "disease-causing organisms"
      },
      {
        "id": "7496",
        "question": "Which of the following weather patterns recurs in cycles, causing severe weather in much of the Western Hemisphere?",
        "answer": "El Niño and La Niña",
        "distractor_1": "global warming",
        "distractor_2": "greenhouse effect",
        "distractor_3": "Gulf Stream"
      },
      {
        "id": "7497",
        "question": "In what two major ways do the oceans act to limit the effects of global warming?",
        "answer": "absorb heat and absorb carbon dioxide",
        "distractor_1": "absorb heat and raise sea levels",
        "distractor_2": "release heat and absorb carbon dioxide",
        "distractor_3": "release heat and lower sea levels"
      },
      {
        "id": "7498",
        "question": "Which of the following is currently causing the greatest danger to large Arctic animals such as seals and polar bears?",
        "answer": "melting sea ice",
        "distractor_1": "increased predation",
        "distractor_2": "more severe winters",
        "distractor_3": "ocean acidification"
      },
      {
        "id": "7499",
        "question": "In the circulation of the ocean conveyor belt, water of the highest density tends to sink. This occurs in which location?",
        "answer": "Arctic, where water is cold and most salty",
        "distractor_1": "Arctic, where water is cold and most fresh",
        "distractor_2": "tropics, where water is warm and most salty",
        "distractor_3": "tropics, where water is warm and least salty"
      },
      {
        "id": "7500",
        "question": "Most life in the oceans occurs in the top 650 feet because this area has which characteristic?",
        "answer": "the most light",
        "distractor_1": "the most pressure",
        "distractor_2": "the highest salinity",
        "distractor_3": "the highest density"
      },
      {
        "id": "7501",
        "question": "Which of the following organisms are usually top predators in ocean food webs?",
        "answer": "sharks and orcas",
        "distractor_1": "phytoplankton",
        "distractor_2": "zooplankton",
        "distractor_3": "fish and invertebrates"
      },
      {
        "id": "7502",
        "question": "Why are populations of most commercial fish stocks currently declining?",
        "answer": "People have overharvested until the fish can no longer replace themselves.",
        "distractor_1": "Aquaculture is replacing fisheries; they are no longer needed.",
        "distractor_2": "Ocean pollution is causing fish to die before they can reproduce.",
        "distractor_3": "People are more interested in harvesting bycatch than commercial species."
      },
      {
        "id": "7503",
        "question": "Excess nutrients in coastal waters come from which source?",
        "answer": "sewage and fertilizer runoff",
        "distractor_1": "fertilizer factories",
        "distractor_2": "coastal industries",
        "distractor_3": "coastal development"
      },
      {
        "id": "7504",
        "question": "Which tropical ecosystem is the most productive and most diverse ecosystem on Earth?",
        "answer": "coral reef",
        "distractor_1": "estuary",
        "distractor_2": "sea grass bed",
        "distractor_3": "kelp bed"
      },
      {
        "id": "7505",
        "question": "Plastics and other trash are caught and kept in the North Pacific Ocean because of which type of ocean circulation pattern?",
        "answer": "gyre",
        "distractor_1": "warm current",
        "distractor_2": "upwelling",
        "distractor_3": "ocean conveyor belt"
      },
      {
        "id": "7506",
        "question": "When an El Niño event occurs off the coast of South America, it prevents which of the following ocean events from occurring?",
        "answer": "upwellings",
        "distractor_1": "hurricanes",
        "distractor_2": "current flow",
        "distractor_3": "increased water temperatures"
      },
      {
        "id": "7507",
        "question": "When oceans absorb carbon dioxide, this limits global warming, but it causes a change in the oceans themselves. What is this change?",
        "answer": "They become more acidic.",
        "distractor_1": "They become less acidic.",
        "distractor_2": "They become more salty.",
        "distractor_3": "They become less salty."
      },
      {
        "id": "7508",
        "question": "How does melting sea ice affect polar bears?",
        "answer": "It hurts them because they need ice as a platform from which to hunt seals.",
        "distractor_1": "It does not affect them.",
        "distractor_2": "It helps them by making the water warmer. ",
        "distractor_3": "It helps them by making it easier for them to swim after seals."
      },
      {
        "id": "7509",
        "question": "Which of the following organisms forms a rich underwater 'forest' along rocky coasts, such as the coast of California?",
        "answer": "kelp",
        "distractor_1": "coral",
        "distractor_2": "sea grass",
        "distractor_3": "mangrove"
      },
      {
        "id": "7511",
        "question": "In 1990, the shipping vessel 'Hansa Carrier' lost 21 cargo containers in a storm. Five of these contained 80,000 Nike sneakers. This accidental sneaker spill was used to study which of the following ocean features?",
        "answer": "movements of ocean currents",
        "distractor_1": "levels of ocean pollution",
        "distractor_2": "rate at which objects sink",
        "distractor_3": "toxicity of ocean trash"
      },
      {
        "id": "7513",
        "question": "The Sargasso Sea is a huge seaweed-filled area of the Atlantic Ocean that provides ocean animals with food and protection. Which animals enter the Gulf Stream as babies and follow it to the Sargasso Sea?",
        "answer": "loggerhead turtles",
        "distractor_1": "gray whales",
        "distractor_2": "blue sharks ",
        "distractor_3": "bluefin tuna"
      },
      {
        "id": "7515",
        "question": "Which of the following ocean regions have the saltiest seawater?",
        "answer": "Red Sea and Persian Gulf",
        "distractor_1": "Arctic and Antarctic Oceans",
        "distractor_2": "mouth of the Amazon River",
        "distractor_3": "currents such as the Gulf Stream"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "172",
    "name": "Going Green",
    "weight": "10",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "7425",
        "question": "This occurs when more heat is produced on Earth than can bounce back out of the atmosphere, causing Earth's average temperature to rise.",
        "answer": "global warming",
        "distractor_1": "greenhouse effect",
        "distractor_2": "low tides",
        "distractor_3": "full moon"
      },
      {
        "id": "7426",
        "question": "These energy resources can be replenished in a short amount of time, usually by reproduction.",
        "answer": "renewable energy ",
        "distractor_1": "nonrenewable energy",
        "distractor_2": "fossil fuels ",
        "distractor_3": "perpetual energy "
      },
      {
        "id": "7427",
        "question": "This term is defined as the amount of carbon dioxide emitted as a direct or indirect result from an activity. ",
        "answer": "carbon footprint",
        "distractor_1": "greenhouse effect ",
        "distractor_2": "global warming ",
        "distractor_3": "kilowatt"
      },
      {
        "id": "7428",
        "question": "This acronym represents heavy metals or formaldehyde released from some paint, carpets, laminated furniture, and cleaning solvents.",
        "answer": "VOCs",
        "distractor_1": "GHGs",
        "distractor_2": "CFLs",
        "distractor_3": "LEDs"
      },
      {
        "id": "7429",
        "question": "One of the three major greenhouse gases, this gas was the first one determined to be increasing in atmospheric concentration. ",
        "answer": "carbon dioxide",
        "distractor_1": "methane",
        "distractor_2": "water vapor",
        "distractor_3": "nitrous oxide"
      },
      {
        "id": "7430",
        "question": "This natural process is the result of heat absorption by certain gases in the atmosphere and reradiation downward of some of that heat, allowing life to be supported on Earth. ",
        "answer": "greenhouse effect ",
        "distractor_1": "global warming",
        "distractor_2": "ultraviolet light",
        "distractor_3": "carbon footprint"
      },
      {
        "id": "7431",
        "question": "These energy resources cannot be replaced after they have been used.",
        "answer": "nonrenewable energy",
        "distractor_1": "renewable energy",
        "distractor_2": "fossil fuels",
        "distractor_3": "perpetual energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "7432",
        "question": "These gases allow direct sunlight to reach Earth's surface unimpeded.",
        "answer": "greenhouse gases",
        "distractor_1": "real gases",
        "distractor_2": "ideal gases",
        "distractor_3": "cloud gases"
      },
      {
        "id": "7433",
        "question": "This term is defined as usable heat or power. ",
        "answer": "energy",
        "distractor_1": "calorie",
        "distractor_2": "fat",
        "distractor_3": "muscle"
      },
      {
        "id": "7434",
        "question": "This term is defined as natural resources found deep within Earth and made from ancient plant and animal remains, which turn into fuels that release energy when burned.",
        "answer": "fossil fuels",
        "distractor_1": "greenhouse gases",
        "distractor_2": "root berries",
        "distractor_3": "magma"
      },
      {
        "id": "7471",
        "question": "North America is the largest consumer of fossil fuels, using what percentage of the world’s total resources?",
        "answer": "25%",
        "distractor_1": "15%",
        "distractor_2": "50%",
        "distractor_3": "65%"
      },
      {
        "id": "7472",
        "question": "This term describes chemicals that evaporate, or get into the air easily at room temperature, and are used in the manufacture of certain building materials, interior furnishings, cleaning products, and personal care products. ",
        "answer": "volatile organic compounds (VOCs)",
        "distractor_1": "greenhouse gases (GHGs) ",
        "distractor_2": "nuclear fuels",
        "distractor_3": "fossil fuels"
      },
      {
        "id": "7473",
        "question": "This type of grass can be used as an alternative to hardwood, is very strong, grows incredibly fast nearly anywhere, and doesn’t require a lot of pesticides.",
        "answer": "bamboo",
        "distractor_1": "hemp",
        "distractor_2": "fescue",
        "distractor_3": "teak"
      },
      {
        "id": "7474",
        "question": "What are the three fuels most commonly used in homes? ",
        "answer": "natural gas, liquid propane gas, and oil",
        "distractor_1": "oil, solar, and wood",
        "distractor_2": "natural gas, liquid propane oil, and solar",
        "distractor_3": "coal, oil, and natural gas"
      },
      {
        "id": "7475",
        "question": "What percent of energy used around the world comes from fossil fuels? ",
        "answer": "90%",
        "distractor_1": "25%",
        "distractor_2": "50%",
        "distractor_3": "0%"
      },
      {
        "id": "7476",
        "question": "What term defines hydrocarbon-containing natural resources such as coal, petroleum, and natural gas? ",
        "answer": "fossil fuels",
        "distractor_1": "greenhouse gases",
        "distractor_2": "VOCs",
        "distractor_3": "nuclear fuels"
      },
      {
        "id": "7477",
        "question": "Which of the following gases contributes the most to global warming? ",
        "answer": "carbon dioxide",
        "distractor_1": "ozone",
        "distractor_2": "methane",
        "distractor_3": "nitrous oxide"
      },
      {
        "id": "7478",
        "question": "Which of the following items should not go into the composter? ",
        "answer": "plastic water bottles ",
        "distractor_1": "coffee grounds",
        "distractor_2": "egg shells",
        "distractor_3": "banana peels"
      },
      {
        "id": "7479",
        "question": "Which of the listed energy resources is nonrenewable?",
        "answer": "petroleum",
        "distractor_1": "solar",
        "distractor_2": "hydropower",
        "distractor_3": "wind"
      },
      {
        "id": "7480",
        "question": "Which of the listed energy resources is renewable?",
        "answer": "wood",
        "distractor_1": "coal",
        "distractor_2": "oil",
        "distractor_3": "natural gas "
      },
      {
        "id": "7481",
        "question": "Coal is used to generate approximately how much of the electricity used in the United States? ",
        "answer": "50%",
        "distractor_1": "25%",
        "distractor_2": "80%",
        "distractor_3": "93%"
      },
      {
        "id": "7482",
        "question": "In order for prepared foods to be labeled as organic, what percentage of the ingredients used to make the food must be organic?",
        "answer": "95%",
        "distractor_1": "65%",
        "distractor_2": "80%",
        "distractor_3": "45%"
      },
      {
        "id": "7483",
        "question": "The use of electricity accounts for approximately how much of the average home’s annual energy consumption?",
        "answer": "27%",
        "distractor_1": "15%",
        "distractor_2": "7%",
        "distractor_3": "45%"
      },
      {
        "id": "7670",
        "question": "This term refers to water that has already been used in the home.",
        "answer": "graywater",
        "distractor_1": "rainwater",
        "distractor_2": "groundwater",
        "distractor_3": "potable water"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "173",
    "name": "Green Machines",
    "weight": "25",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "7654",
        "question": "What type of driving will result in the reduction in fuel mileage of up to 33%?",
        "answer": "aggressive",
        "distractor_1": "start and stop",
        "distractor_2": "underage",
        "distractor_3": "illegal"
      },
      {
        "id": "7663",
        "question": "The measure of how far a car can travel on one gallon of gas.",
        "answer": "fuel economy ",
        "distractor_1": "transportation",
        "distractor_2": "combustion",
        "distractor_3": "hydrocarbon"
      },
      {
        "id": "7485",
        "question": "Which of the following is the most eco-friendly way to get around if you are going to travel?",
        "answer": "mass transit",
        "distractor_1": "family car",
        "distractor_2": "airplane",
        "distractor_3": "car pool"
      },
      {
        "id": "7486",
        "question": "Doing this burns up the most fuel when driving a car.",
        "answer": "starting it",
        "distractor_1": "speeding",
        "distractor_2": "idling",
        "distractor_3": "carrying extra weight"
      },
      {
        "id": "7487",
        "question": "Hybrid cars run off two different fuel sources. What are they?",
        "answer": "gasoline and electricity",
        "distractor_1": "electricity and sunlight",
        "distractor_2": "sunlight and biofuels",
        "distractor_3": "gasoline and biofuels"
      },
      {
        "id": "7488",
        "question": "What is the primary transportation-related greenhouse gas?",
        "answer": "carbon dioxide",
        "distractor_1": "methane",
        "distractor_2": "nitrous oxide",
        "distractor_3": "ozone"
      },
      {
        "id": "7664",
        "question": "A form of air pollution that results when nitrous oxides and VOCs react in the presence of sunlight. ",
        "answer": "smog",
        "distractor_1": "smoke",
        "distractor_2": "fog",
        "distractor_3": "acid rain"
      },
      {
        "id": "7665",
        "question": "A renewable fuel that is produced using plants such as corn and sugar cane and can be used in any car with only minor modifications being made to the car.",
        "answer": "ethanol",
        "distractor_1": "oxygen",
        "distractor_2": "methane",
        "distractor_3": "nitrous oxide"
      },
      {
        "id": "7655",
        "question": "This term is defined as the process of moving people and products from one place to another. ",
        "answer": "transportation",
        "distractor_1": "mileage ",
        "distractor_2": "intermodalism",
        "distractor_3": "air miles"
      },
      {
        "id": "7666",
        "question": "A power system that converts heat produced by burning fuel into another form of energy that does useful work for people. ",
        "answer": "combustion heat engine",
        "distractor_1": "aerobic system",
        "distractor_2": "respiratory system",
        "distractor_3": "immune system"
      },
      {
        "id": "7667",
        "question": "The simplest hydrocarbon and the principal constituent of natural gas. ",
        "answer": "methane",
        "distractor_1": "oxygen",
        "distractor_2": "ethanol",
        "distractor_3": "biogas"
      },
      {
        "id": "7656",
        "question": "This term is defined as the transporting of people, goods, or services using a variety of travel modes. ",
        "answer": "intermodalism",
        "distractor_1": "transportation",
        "distractor_2": "international",
        "distractor_3": "mileage"
      },
      {
        "id": "7657",
        "question": "The burning of transportation fuels accounts for how much of our total carbon emissions? ",
        "answer": "32%",
        "distractor_1": "27%",
        "distractor_2": "15%",
        "distractor_3": "45%"
      },
      {
        "id": "7658",
        "question": "What term describes a measure of the CO2 emissions generated as a result of your individual actions? ",
        "answer": "carbon footprint ",
        "distractor_1": "transportation footprint",
        "distractor_2": "mpg, or miles per gallon",
        "distractor_3": "EPM, or emissions per mile"
      },
      {
        "id": "7659",
        "question": "This term is defined as the friction of air moving past a vehicle. ",
        "answer": "drag",
        "distractor_1": "draft",
        "distractor_2": "dodge",
        "distractor_3": "drain"
      },
      {
        "id": "7660",
        "question": "In transportation, this term is defined as using less fuel to travel greater distances. ",
        "answer": "fuel efficiency",
        "distractor_1": "fuel mileage ",
        "distractor_2": "fuel economy ",
        "distractor_3": "fuel load"
      },
      {
        "id": "7661",
        "question": "This term is defined as responsible travel to natural areas that conserves the environment and sustains the well-being of local people.",
        "answer": "ecotourism",
        "distractor_1": "intermodalism",
        "distractor_2": "conservation",
        "distractor_3": "naturalism"
      },
      {
        "id": "7662",
        "question": "What term describes the use of magnetic fields to levitate, or float, trains above their tracks? ",
        "answer": "magnetic levitation",
        "distractor_1": "magic",
        "distractor_2": "air waves",
        "distractor_3": "intermodalism"
      },
      {
        "id": "7668",
        "question": "The measure of liquid fuel such as propane or gasoline that converts to approximately 3.785 liters.",
        "answer": "gallon",
        "distractor_1": "pint",
        "distractor_2": "quart",
        "distractor_3": "cup"
      },
      {
        "id": "7669",
        "question": "Gases that trap heat in the atmosphere and have a warming effect on a planet.",
        "answer": "greenhouse gases",
        "distractor_1": "VOCs",
        "distractor_2": "nuclear fuels",
        "distractor_3": "air bubbles"
      },
      {
        "id": "7727",
        "question": "An organic chemical compound of hydrogen and carbon in either gaseous, liquid, or solid phase. ",
        "answer": "hydrocarbon",
        "distractor_1": "petroleum",
        "distractor_2": "bamboo",
        "distractor_3": "sunlight"
      },
      {
        "id": "8682",
        "question": "The U.S. transportation sector is responsible for about what percent of the nation's fossil-fuel related carbon dioxide emissions?",
        "answer": "30%",
        "distractor_1": "20%",
        "distractor_2": "55%",
        "distractor_3": "75%"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "174",
    "name": "Eco-Architecture",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "7382",
        "question": "Which U.S. city was the first to begin requiring that all buildings meet certain LEED rating standards?",
        "answer": "Boston, Massachusetts",
        "distractor_1": "Dallas, Texas",
        "distractor_2": "New York, New York",
        "distractor_3": "Hollywood, California"
      },
      {
        "id": "7383",
        "question": "Flooring specialists want to use reclaimed lumber in a client's living room. The room measures 10' x 12', which is 120 square feet. They have 20 square-foot bundles of reclaimed wood. How many bundles will they need to redo the living room floor?",
        "answer": "6",
        "distractor_1": "3",
        "distractor_2": "4",
        "distractor_3": "5"
      },
      {
        "id": "7384",
        "question": "Every year, the United States generates approximately how many metric tons of solid waste?",
        "answer": "10,000,000,000",
        "distractor_1": "10,000,000",
        "distractor_2": "100,000,000",
        "distractor_3": "100,000,000,000"
      },
      {
        "id": "7385",
        "question": "Builders are putting down the first row of 3' straw bales on the east side of a house. The east side measures 27'. How many straw bales will be needed to complete the first row?",
        "answer": "9",
        "distractor_1": "6",
        "distractor_2": "10",
        "distractor_3": "81"
      },
      {
        "id": "7386",
        "question": "What are the approximate energy savings of a dome-built house compared to a well-insulated wood or metal building?",
        "answer": "25%",
        "distractor_1": "10%",
        "distractor_2": "50%",
        "distractor_3": "75%"
      },
      {
        "id": "7387",
        "question": "An earth-sheltered home needs insulation placed on its southern-exposed wall. The wall measures 8' x 25'. Not accounting for windows and doors, how many square feet of insulation will they need to cover the south wall?",
        "answer": "200 ft^2",
        "distractor_1": "20 ft^2",
        "distractor_2": "160 ft^2",
        "distractor_3": "40,000 ft^2"
      },
      {
        "id": "7388",
        "question": "In the United States, approximately how much of our total energy consumption is residential?",
        "answer": "20%",
        "distractor_1": "40%",
        "distractor_2": "60%",
        "distractor_3": "80%"
      },
      {
        "id": "7390",
        "question": "What term is used to describe a circular process where we reuse items we create rather than throwing these items away?",
        "answer": "cradle to cradle",
        "distractor_1": "cradle to grave",
        "distractor_2": "cradle to table",
        "distractor_3": "table to cradle"
      },
      {
        "id": "7391",
        "question": "What happens to most materials used in construction?",
        "answer": "They are thrown away.",
        "distractor_1": "They are recycled.",
        "distractor_2": "They are reduced. ",
        "distractor_3": "They are reused."
      },
      {
        "id": "7392",
        "question": "Cross ventilation would occur when using which of the following?",
        "answer": "large, south-facing windows and small, high north-facing windows",
        "distractor_1": "small, north-facing windows and small, high south-facing windows",
        "distractor_2": "large, south-facing windows and large, north-facing windows",
        "distractor_3": "small, south-facing windows and large, north-facing windows"
      },
      {
        "id": "7393",
        "question": "Which type of housing has a heating and cooling system that is most likely to harbor bacteria and airborne pollutants?",
        "answer": "traditional housing",
        "distractor_1": "earth-sheltered housing",
        "distractor_2": "rammed-earth housing",
        "distractor_3": "straw-bale housing"
      },
      {
        "id": "7394",
        "question": "In an earth-sheltered house, the earth provides which of the following?",
        "answer": "All of the options are correct.",
        "distractor_1": "heating and cooling",
        "distractor_2": "insulation",
        "distractor_3": "protection"
      },
      {
        "id": "7395",
        "question": "What happens to air molecules when air is heated?",
        "answer": "They move farther apart and rise.",
        "distractor_1": "They move closer together and rise.",
        "distractor_2": "They move farther apart and sink.",
        "distractor_3": "They move closer together and sink."
      },
      {
        "id": "7396",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a good conductor of heat?",
        "answer": "wood",
        "distractor_1": "copper",
        "distractor_2": "iron",
        "distractor_3": "steel"
      },
      {
        "id": "7397",
        "question": "Which of the following is considered the most extreme type of home design?",
        "answer": "Earthship",
        "distractor_1": "earth sheltered",
        "distractor_2": "rammed earth",
        "distractor_3": "straw bale"
      },
      {
        "id": "7398",
        "question": "Evaporation, condensation, precipitation, transpiration, infiltration, and runoff all occur in which of the following?",
        "answer": "water cycle",
        "distractor_1": "atmospheric cycle",
        "distractor_2": "rock cycle",
        "distractor_3": "None of these are correct."
      },
      {
        "id": "7399",
        "question": "Which of the following is considered an environmentally friendly insulation?",
        "answer": "cellulose",
        "distractor_1": "blanket",
        "distractor_2": "loose fill",
        "distractor_3": "rigid board"
      },
      {
        "id": "7400",
        "question": "The term cradle to cradle is used to describe what sort of structure where we reuse items we create rather than throwing these items away?",
        "answer": "circular",
        "distractor_1": "linear",
        "distractor_2": "looping",
        "distractor_3": "wave"
      },
      {
        "id": "7401",
        "question": "What happens to materials that are left over after construction occurs or when buildings are taken down?",
        "answer": "They are taken to dumps and end up in landfills.",
        "distractor_1": "They are taken back to the stores where they were purchased. ",
        "distractor_2": "They are taken to places that will resell the remaining items. ",
        "distractor_3": "They are taken to the recycling center."
      },
      {
        "id": "7402",
        "question": "If an architect designs a home with large, south-facing windows and small, high north-facing windows, the home will do which of the following?",
        "answer": "cross ventilate ",
        "distractor_1": "cross circulate",
        "distractor_2": "cross condition",
        "distractor_3": "cross distribute"
      },
      {
        "id": "7404",
        "question": "Which of the following does not use earth for heating and cooling, insulation, and protection?",
        "answer": "straw-bale houses",
        "distractor_1": "earth-sheltered houses",
        "distractor_2": "Earthship houses",
        "distractor_3": "rammed-earth houses"
      },
      {
        "id": "7405",
        "question": "Air molecules move farther apart and rise when which of the following things happens?",
        "answer": "when the air is heated",
        "distractor_1": "when the air is cooled",
        "distractor_2": "when the air is depressurized",
        "distractor_3": "when the air is pressurized"
      },
      {
        "id": "7406",
        "question": "Copper, iron, and steel are all considered good at doing what with heat?",
        "answer": "conducting",
        "distractor_1": "convecting",
        "distractor_2": "insulating",
        "distractor_3": "All of the options are correct."
      },
      {
        "id": "7407",
        "question": "Why are Earthship homes considered to be the most extreme form of alternative home designs?",
        "answer": "All of the options are correct.",
        "distractor_1": "They are designed to reuse water up to four times.",
        "distractor_2": "They are entirely self-sustained.",
        "distractor_3": "They are made out of used items."
      },
      {
        "id": "7408",
        "question": "Which of the following occurs when the Sun heats water found in oceans, lakes, rivers, and other bodies of water and turns it into water vapor?",
        "answer": "evaporation",
        "distractor_1": "condensation",
        "distractor_2": "precipitation",
        "distractor_3": "transpiration"
      },
      {
        "id": "7409",
        "question": "Which of the following is not considered an environmentally friendly insulation?",
        "answer": "rigid board",
        "distractor_1": "blue jeans",
        "distractor_2": "cellulose",
        "distractor_3": "SIPs"
      },
      {
        "id": "7435",
        "question": "capable of being broken down by living things such as microorganisms",
        "answer": "biodegradable",
        "distractor_1": "constructible",
        "distractor_2": "recyclable",
        "distractor_3": "wearable"
      },
      {
        "id": "7436",
        "question": "relating to the use of natural elements that can be put back into the earth without damaging the planet; relating to our ability to work with the planet rather than against it",
        "answer": "sustainable",
        "distractor_1": "biodegradable",
        "distractor_2": "recyclable",
        "distractor_3": "constructible"
      },
      {
        "id": "7437",
        "question": "the process of making or forming by combining or arranging parts or elements; building ",
        "answer": "construction",
        "distractor_1": "meshing",
        "distractor_2": "sorting",
        "distractor_3": "recycling"
      },
      {
        "id": "7438",
        "question": "to take a material and put it through a process to create something else; to cycle again",
        "answer": "recycle",
        "distractor_1": "retrofit",
        "distractor_2": "reclaim",
        "distractor_3": "biodegrade"
      },
      {
        "id": "7439",
        "question": "to obtain from a waste product or by-product; to recover or rescue",
        "answer": "reclaim",
        "distractor_1": "retrofit",
        "distractor_2": "recycle",
        "distractor_3": "biodegrade"
      },
      {
        "id": "7440",
        "question": "to add something new to something that wasn't designed to use it",
        "answer": "retrofit",
        "distractor_1": "reclaim",
        "distractor_2": "recycle",
        "distractor_3": "biodegrade"
      },
      {
        "id": "7441",
        "question": "energy that is capable of being replaced by natural ecological cycles such as the Sun and wind",
        "answer": "renewable energy",
        "distractor_1": "nonrenewable energy",
        "distractor_2": "constant energy",
        "distractor_3": "cycle energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "7442",
        "question": "the amount of heat produced by large cities due to cars, gas emissions, air pollution, energy use, and so forth",
        "answer": "heat island ",
        "distractor_1": "heat transfer",
        "distractor_2": "carbon footprint",
        "distractor_3": "heat waste"
      },
      {
        "id": "7443",
        "question": "the ability of heat to move from one object to another in the form of conduction, convection, and radiation",
        "answer": "heat transfer ",
        "distractor_1": "heat island",
        "distractor_2": "thermo cycle",
        "distractor_3": "thermo transference"
      },
      {
        "id": "7444",
        "question": "the process of undergoing a drying process",
        "answer": "curing",
        "distractor_1": "setting",
        "distractor_2": "dry setting",
        "distractor_3": "firing"
      },
      {
        "id": "7445",
        "question": "a house with walls made from pressed-together earth",
        "answer": "rammed earth  ",
        "distractor_1": "earth sheltered",
        "distractor_2": "straw bale",
        "distractor_3": "Earthship"
      },
      {
        "id": "7446",
        "question": "a 7- to 10-layered roof that is built to support plant life",
        "answer": "green roof ",
        "distractor_1": "living roof",
        "distractor_2": "garden roof",
        "distractor_3": "oasis roof"
      },
      {
        "id": "7447",
        "question": "the ability to absorb and retain temperature",
        "answer": "thermal mass",
        "distractor_1": "heat transfer",
        "distractor_2": "radiation",
        "distractor_3": "convection"
      },
      {
        "id": "7448",
        "question": "the ability to use solar energy without using mechanical systems",
        "answer": "passive solar",
        "distractor_1": "active solar",
        "distractor_2": "off the grid",
        "distractor_3": "alternative energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "7449",
        "question": "the movement of water from the sky to the land and then to the sky again through a process of six steps",
        "answer": "water cycle",
        "distractor_1": "evaporation",
        "distractor_2": "oceanic cycle ",
        "distractor_3": "condensation"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "175",
    "name": "Carbon Footprint",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8681",
        "question": "In 2012 the United States was able to reduce its carbon dioxide emissions by what percentage?",
        "answer": "3.8%",
        "distractor_1": "2.3%",
        "distractor_2": "34..3%",
        "distractor_3": "67.1%"
      },
      {
        "id": "7541",
        "question": "Which of the following substances are hydrocarbons?",
        "answer": "fossil fuels",
        "distractor_1": "alcohols",
        "distractor_2": "amorphous carbon",
        "distractor_3": "molecules in living organisms"
      },
      {
        "id": "7542",
        "question": "Octane is the major component of which type of substance?",
        "answer": "gasoline",
        "distractor_1": "alcohol",
        "distractor_2": "natural gas",
        "distractor_3": "molecules in living organisms"
      },
      {
        "id": "7543",
        "question": "Which of the following parts of the carbon cycle serve as carbon sinks?",
        "answer": "oceans; soil and rocks",
        "distractor_1": "atmosphere; soil and rocks",
        "distractor_2": "atmosphere; organisms",
        "distractor_3": "oceans; organisms"
      },
      {
        "id": "7544",
        "question": "Which of the following processes add carbon dioxide to the atmosphere?",
        "answer": "burning fossil fuels",
        "distractor_1": "photosynthesis",
        "distractor_2": "growth of forests",
        "distractor_3": "deep-ocean exchange"
      },
      {
        "id": "7545",
        "question": "What effect does planned obsolescence have on the environment?",
        "answer": "negative",
        "distractor_1": "positive",
        "distractor_2": "both positive and negative",
        "distractor_3": "no effect"
      },
      {
        "id": "7546",
        "question": "Which of the following terms describes what you are doing when you make a birdhouse out of a milk carton?",
        "answer": "reuse",
        "distractor_1": "recycle",
        "distractor_2": "repurpose",
        "distractor_3": "redo"
      },
      {
        "id": "7547",
        "question": "Which of the following is the least carbon-friendly way of getting around?",
        "answer": "taking the bus",
        "distractor_1": "riding a bike",
        "distractor_2": "walking",
        "distractor_3": "running"
      },
      {
        "id": "7548",
        "question": "Which of the following is the most common fuel used to make electricity in the United States?",
        "answer": "coal",
        "distractor_1": "gasoline",
        "distractor_2": "natural gas",
        "distractor_3": "carbon dioxide"
      },
      {
        "id": "7549",
        "question": "Which of the following structures is used to increase and decrease voltage?",
        "answer": "transformer",
        "distractor_1": "power line",
        "distractor_2": "meter",
        "distractor_3": "power plant"
      },
      {
        "id": "7550",
        "question": "How does beef production impact the carbon footprint?",
        "answer": "All of the choices contribute to the problem.",
        "distractor_1": "Energy is used to water, feed, butcher, and process cattle. ",
        "distractor_2": "Cattle produce large amounts of methane gas.",
        "distractor_3": "Large companies are cutting down forests to use for cattle."
      },
      {
        "id": "7551",
        "question": "Fossil fuels consist of which of the following types of molecules?",
        "answer": "hydrocarbon",
        "distractor_1": "atomic",
        "distractor_2": "amorphous",
        "distractor_3": "alcohol"
      },
      {
        "id": "7552",
        "question": "Which hydrocarbon is the major component of gasoline?",
        "answer": "octane",
        "distractor_1": "methane ",
        "distractor_2": "propane",
        "distractor_3": "butane"
      },
      {
        "id": "7553",
        "question": "What is Earth's largest and most long-term carbon sink?",
        "answer": "oceans",
        "distractor_1": "atmosphere",
        "distractor_2": "organisms",
        "distractor_3": "soil and rocks"
      },
      {
        "id": "7554",
        "question": "Which of the following processes removes carbon dioxide from the atmosphere?",
        "answer": "photosynthesis",
        "distractor_1": "respiration",
        "distractor_2": "organism decay",
        "distractor_3": "deforestation"
      },
      {
        "id": "7556",
        "question": "Which of the following terms describes the process of using energy to turn old or used materials into new ones?",
        "answer": "recycle",
        "distractor_1": "reuse",
        "distractor_2": "repurpose",
        "distractor_3": "redo"
      },
      {
        "id": "7557",
        "question": "Which of the following is the most carbon-friendly way of getting around?",
        "answer": "walking",
        "distractor_1": "riding a bike",
        "distractor_2": "taking the bus",
        "distractor_3": "carpooling"
      },
      {
        "id": "7558",
        "question": "Currently, what do people use coal for most?",
        "answer": "to make electricity",
        "distractor_1": "to cook food",
        "distractor_2": "to bend metals",
        "distractor_3": "to heat homes"
      },
      {
        "id": "7559",
        "question": "Which of the following is the purpose of a transformer?",
        "answer": "to increase and decrease voltage",
        "distractor_1": "to move electrical current from one place to another",
        "distractor_2": "to generate electrical power",
        "distractor_3": "to keep track of how much electricity is used"
      },
      {
        "id": "7560",
        "question": "Which greenhouse gas is emitted when cows belch?",
        "answer": "methane",
        "distractor_1": "CFC-12",
        "distractor_2": "nitrous oxide",
        "distractor_3": "sulfur dioxide"
      },
      {
        "id": "7561",
        "question": "By 2006, the number of curbside recycling programs in the United States had increased to what number?",
        "answer": "8,660",
        "distractor_1": "75",
        "distractor_2": "247",
        "distractor_3": "3,520"
      },
      {
        "id": "7562",
        "question": "Each day, the average person produces about 4.5 pounds of trash. Over the course of a year, how many pounds of trash does the average family of four produce?",
        "answer": "6,570",
        "distractor_1": "18",
        "distractor_2": "410",
        "distractor_3": "1,642"
      },
      {
        "id": "7563",
        "question": "Between two thousand four and two thousand five, the country of Finland was able to reduce its carbon dioxide emissions by what percentage?",
        "answer": "14.6%",
        "distractor_1": "2.3%",
        "distractor_2": "34.3%",
        "distractor_3": "67.1%"
      },
      {
        "id": "7564",
        "question": "Burning one gallon of gasoline puts how much carbon dioxide into the atmosphere?",
        "answer": "20 pounds",
        "distractor_1": "5 pounds",
        "distractor_2": "10 pounds",
        "distractor_3": "30 pounds"
      },
      {
        "id": "7565",
        "question": "Each gallon of gasoline burned releases 20 pounds of CO2 into the air. If your family uses 17 gallons of gasoline per week, how many pounds of CO2 are released into the atmosphere in a four-week time period?",
        "answer": "1,360",
        "distractor_1": "1,500",
        "distractor_2": "168",
        "distractor_3": "96"
      },
      {
        "id": "7566",
        "question": "What is the source of the carbon used in making a tree?",
        "answer": "carbon dioxide in air",
        "distractor_1": "carbon dioxide in soil",
        "distractor_2": "calcium carbonate in rocks",
        "distractor_3": "carbonic acid in water"
      },
      {
        "id": "7567",
        "question": "Methane is 21 times more powerful a greenhouse gas than carbon dioxide. If 21 billion tons of carbon dioxide are added to the atmosphere each year, about how much methane would have to be added to have the same effect as carbon dioxide?",
        "answer": "1 billion tons",
        "distractor_1": "20 billion tons",
        "distractor_2": "120 billion tons",
        "distractor_3": "441 billion tons"
      },
      {
        "id": "7568",
        "question": "a substance that cannot be separated into simpler substances without changing its chemical structure; all of its atoms are exactly alike",
        "answer": "element",
        "distractor_1": "molecule",
        "distractor_2": "atom",
        "distractor_3": "electron"
      },
      {
        "id": "7569",
        "question": "a family of carbon compounds that contains hydrogen and carbon atoms; fossil fuels such as coal, oil, and natural gas are examples",
        "answer": "hydrocarbon",
        "distractor_1": "carbohydrate",
        "distractor_2": "carbonate",
        "distractor_3": "hydrocortisone"
      },
      {
        "id": "7570",
        "question": "fuel made from the remains of plants and animals that lived hundreds of millions of years ago",
        "answer": "fossil fuel",
        "distractor_1": "biofuel",
        "distractor_2": "biodiesel",
        "distractor_3": "ethanol"
      },
      {
        "id": "7571",
        "question": "the circulation of carbon around Earth",
        "answer": "global carbon cycle",
        "distractor_1": "greenhouse effect",
        "distractor_2": "global warming",
        "distractor_3": "carbon footprint"
      },
      {
        "id": "7572",
        "question": "reservoir that stores large amounts of carbon after CO2 is removed from the atmosphere and chemically changed",
        "answer": "carbon sink",
        "distractor_1": "global sink",
        "distractor_2": "greenhouse sink",
        "distractor_3": "atomic sink"
      },
      {
        "id": "7573",
        "question": "the heating of Earth's atmosphere and surface that occurs when the greenhouse effect becomes stronger because more GHGs are being added to the atmosphere",
        "answer": "global warming",
        "distractor_1": "carbon footprint",
        "distractor_2": "global carbon cycle",
        "distractor_3": "geothermal warming"
      },
      {
        "id": "7574",
        "question": "the amount of greenhouse gases you are personally responsible for producing by the choices you make and the actions you take",
        "answer": "carbon footprint",
        "distractor_1": "global carbon cycle",
        "distractor_2": "global warming",
        "distractor_3": "greenhouse effect"
      },
      {
        "id": "7575",
        "question": "the process that uses energy to make something new out of used or old things",
        "answer": "recycle",
        "distractor_1": "reduce",
        "distractor_2": "reuse",
        "distractor_3": "refurbish"
      },
      {
        "id": "7576",
        "question": "how far food has to travel from the grower to our kitchens",
        "answer": "food mile",
        "distractor_1": "shelf life",
        "distractor_2": "carbon miles",
        "distractor_3": "import distance"
      },
      {
        "id": "7577",
        "question": "any piece of land that is used as a garden by a group of people for members of the community",
        "answer": "community garden",
        "distractor_1": "food cooperative",
        "distractor_2": "farmer's market",
        "distractor_3": "community food bank"
      },
      {
        "id": "7578",
        "question": "chemical used to help plants grow stronger and bigger; many pass to other plants, the soil, and our groundwater",
        "answer": "fertilizer",
        "distractor_1": "pesticide",
        "distractor_2": "herbicide",
        "distractor_3": "additive"
      },
      {
        "id": "7579",
        "question": "toxic chemicals that are meant to kill pests that feed off of the crops; many leak into our groundwater ",
        "answer": "pesticide",
        "distractor_1": "fertilizer",
        "distractor_2": "herbicide",
        "distractor_3": "additive"
      },
      {
        "id": "7580",
        "question": "gas that can trap and hold heat in the atmosphere",
        "answer": "greenhouse gas (GHG)",
        "distractor_1": "radon gas",
        "distractor_2": "argon gas",
        "distractor_3": "neon gas"
      },
      {
        "id": "7581",
        "question": "the smallest unit of an element that contains all chemical properties unique to that element; atoms are the building blocks of all matter",
        "answer": "atom",
        "distractor_1": "molecule",
        "distractor_2": "element",
        "distractor_3": "electron"
      },
      {
        "id": "7582",
        "question": "bond in which electron pairs are shared from one atom to another ",
        "answer": "covalent bond",
        "distractor_1": "ionic bond",
        "distractor_2": "electron bond",
        "distractor_3": "secondary bond"
      },
      {
        "id": "7583",
        "question": "special molecules that make up living organisms; strands of carbon form their backbones",
        "answer": "organic molecules",
        "distractor_1": "protein molecule",
        "distractor_2": "inorganic molecule",
        "distractor_3": "carbonic molecule"
      },
      {
        "id": "7584",
        "question": "all the changes in world climates caused by rising global temperatures, including heat waves, droughts, cold waves, and blizzards",
        "answer": "climate change",
        "distractor_1": "global carbon cycle",
        "distractor_2": "global warming",
        "distractor_3": "greenhouse effect"
      },
      {
        "id": "7585",
        "question": "the process of creating a product such as plastic bags that will become nonfunctional or obsolete after a certain amount of time ",
        "answer": "planned obsolescence",
        "distractor_1": "perceived obsolescence",
        "distractor_2": "timed obsolescence",
        "distractor_3": "observed obsolescence"
      },
      {
        "id": "7586",
        "question": "an idea that is created when products (shoes, televisions, and so forth) remain functional but look outdated",
        "answer": "perceived obsolescence",
        "distractor_1": "planned obsolescence",
        "distractor_2": "timed obsolescence",
        "distractor_3": "observed obsolescence"
      },
      {
        "id": "7587",
        "question": "clean energy that does not contribute to the carbon footprint such as solar, wind, biomass, geothermal, and hydropower",
        "answer": "renewable energy",
        "distractor_1": "ecoenergy",
        "distractor_2": "green energy",
        "distractor_3": "carbon-free energy"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "176",
    "name": "Mission to Mars",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "7671",
        "question": "What do we call all of the matter and energy that exists?",
        "answer": "universe",
        "distractor_1": "nebula",
        "distractor_2": "continuum",
        "distractor_3": "photons"
      },
      {
        "id": "7622",
        "question": "Our solar system has a belt of rocks that orbit the Sun known as the asteroid belt. Between what two planets can you find the asteroid belt?",
        "answer": "Mars and Jupiter",
        "distractor_1": "Earth and Mars",
        "distractor_2": "Jupiter and Saturn",
        "distractor_3": "Mercury and Venus"
      },
      {
        "id": "7623",
        "question": "The definition of an astronomical unit is the distance from Earth to the Sun; therefore, 1 AU = 150,000,000 km. Neptune, the farthest planet in our solar system, is 30 AU from the Sun. How many kilometers is Neptune from the Sun?",
        "answer": "4,500,000,000 km",
        "distractor_1": "45,000,000 km",
        "distractor_2": "450,000 km",
        "distractor_3": "4,500,000 km"
      },
      {
        "id": "7624",
        "question": "Most scientists believe one of the leading causes of global warming is an increase in the production of which of the following?",
        "answer": "carbon dioxide",
        "distractor_1": "carbon monoxide",
        "distractor_2": "UV radiation",
        "distractor_3": "algae"
      },
      {
        "id": "7625",
        "question": "The ratio of the diameter of an asteroid to the diameter of Pluto is 3 to 10. The diameter of Pluto is 2.39 x 10³ km. What is the diameter of the asteroid?",
        "answer": "7.17 x 10² km",
        "distractor_1": "7.17 x 10³ km",
        "distractor_2": "1.26 x 10³ km",
        "distractor_3": "1.26 x 10² km"
      },
      {
        "id": "7626",
        "question": "Spacecraft that have explored Mars looking for water searched for the presence of what element?",
        "answer": "hydrogen",
        "distractor_1": "nitrogen",
        "distractor_2": "oxygen",
        "distractor_3": "helium"
      },
      {
        "id": "7628",
        "question": "NASA launched two rovers to Mars in 2003 and successfully landed them in 2004. They each successfully searched for water in their landing zones. What are the names of these two Mars rovers?",
        "answer": "Spirit and Opportunity",
        "distractor_1": "Mars 1 and Mars 2 Landers",
        "distractor_2": "Beagle 1 and Beagle 2",
        "distractor_3": "Nozomi and Mars Polar Lander"
      },
      {
        "id": "7629",
        "question": "If a mission to Mars needed 20,000 gallons of water for a six-month mission, and the astronauts were able to harvest 7.5 gallons of water per 10 square meters, how big of an area would they need in order to harvest enough water for the mission?",
        "answer": "26,670 m²",
        "distractor_1": "15,000 m²",
        "distractor_2": "267 m²",
        "distractor_3": "1,500,000 m²"
      },
      {
        "id": "7630",
        "question": "Which of the following ranks objects found in the universe from largest to smallest?",
        "answer": "galaxy, nebula, solar system, star",
        "distractor_1": "nebula, galaxy, solar system, star",
        "distractor_2": "galaxy, solar system, nebula, star",
        "distractor_3": "star, solar system, nebula, galaxy"
      },
      {
        "id": "7631",
        "question": "Due to its lack of ozone and a magnetosphere, Mars will expose astronauts to higher levels of what?",
        "answer": "radiation",
        "distractor_1": "dust",
        "distractor_2": "wind",
        "distractor_3": "pressure"
      },
      {
        "id": "7632",
        "question": "The solar energy that is usable for agricultural purposes on Mars falls primarily between what latitudes?",
        "answer": "45 degrees north and 45 degrees south",
        "distractor_1": "60 degrees south and 90 degrees south",
        "distractor_2": "10 degrees north and 10 degrees south",
        "distractor_3": "60 degrees north and 90 degrees north"
      },
      {
        "id": "7633",
        "question": "The telescope was invented in 1608 by what Dutch lens maker?",
        "answer": "Hans Lippershey",
        "distractor_1": "Galileo",
        "distractor_2": "Isaac Newton",
        "distractor_3": "Aristotle"
      },
      {
        "id": "7634",
        "question": "Stars are powered by the process of combining two hydrogen atoms to form a single helium atom in a process known as what?",
        "answer": "nuclear fusion",
        "distractor_1": "nuclear fission",
        "distractor_2": "hydrogen combining",
        "distractor_3": "helium synthesis"
      },
      {
        "id": "7635",
        "question": "What force exerted by the Sun holds the planets in their orbits?",
        "answer": "gravity ",
        "distractor_1": "magnetism",
        "distractor_2": "weight",
        "distractor_3": "momentum"
      },
      {
        "id": "7636",
        "question": "Chlorofluorocarbons, or CFCs, a human-made chemical compound, can deplete what from the atmosphere?",
        "answer": "ozone",
        "distractor_1": "carbon dioxide",
        "distractor_2": "oxygen",
        "distractor_3": "water"
      },
      {
        "id": "7637",
        "question": "Which two energy sources currently seem the most likely to be used for a mission to Mars?",
        "answer": "solar, nuclear",
        "distractor_1": "fossil fuels, nuclear",
        "distractor_2": "solar, fossil fuels",
        "distractor_3": "wind, solar"
      },
      {
        "id": "7638",
        "question": "Photosynthetic plants would solve what two problems that astronauts would face in a mission to Mars? ",
        "answer": "food, oxygen",
        "distractor_1": "power, food",
        "distractor_2": "water, food",
        "distractor_3": "oxygen, power"
      },
      {
        "id": "7639",
        "question": "Radiation shielding failure on a spacecraft bound for Mars is most like which of the following environmental problems faced here on Earth?",
        "answer": "ozone depletion",
        "distractor_1": "global warming",
        "distractor_2": "fuel shortage",
        "distractor_3": "water supply depletion"
      },
      {
        "id": "7640",
        "question": "Which of the following ranks objects found in the universe from smallest to largest?",
        "answer": "star, solar system, nebula, galaxy",
        "distractor_1": "galaxy, nebula, solar system, star",
        "distractor_2": "galaxy, solar system, nebula, star",
        "distractor_3": "nebula, galaxy, solar system, star"
      },
      {
        "id": "7641",
        "question": "Mars lacks two characteristics that Earth has that will expose astronauts to higher levels of radiation. What are they?",
        "answer": "ozone layer, magnetosphere",
        "distractor_1": "water, ozone layer",
        "distractor_2": "magnetosphere, water",
        "distractor_3": "water, moon"
      },
      {
        "id": "7642",
        "question": "What is difficult to find north or south of the 45-degree latitudes?",
        "answer": "solar energy that is useful for agriculture",
        "distractor_1": "water",
        "distractor_2": "power",
        "distractor_3": "ice"
      },
      {
        "id": "7643",
        "question": "What was invented in 1608 by Hans Lippershey, a Dutch lens maker?",
        "answer": "telescope",
        "distractor_1": "hydrogen fusion",
        "distractor_2": "glasses",
        "distractor_3": "rockets"
      },
      {
        "id": "7644",
        "question": "Nuclear fusion is the process of combining two atoms of what element to form a single helium atom?",
        "answer": "hydrogen",
        "distractor_1": "carbon",
        "distractor_2": "nitrogen",
        "distractor_3": "oxygen"
      },
      {
        "id": "7645",
        "question": "Gravity exerted by what object holds the planets in their orbits?",
        "answer": "the Sun",
        "distractor_1": "the asteroid belt",
        "distractor_2": "each planet's moon",
        "distractor_3": "a black hole"
      },
      {
        "id": "7646",
        "question": "What human-made chemical compound can deplete ozone from the atmosphere?",
        "answer": "chlorofluorocarbons, or CFCs",
        "distractor_1": "gasoline",
        "distractor_2": "smog",
        "distractor_3": "uranium"
      },
      {
        "id": "7647",
        "question": "Two energy sources currently seem the most likely to be used for a mission to Mars. What are they?",
        "answer": "solar, nuclear",
        "distractor_1": "solar, fossil fuels",
        "distractor_2": "wind, fossil fuels",
        "distractor_3": "nuclear, wind"
      },
      {
        "id": "7648",
        "question": "Photosynthetic plants would solve what two problems that astronauts would face in a mission to Mars? ",
        "answer": "food, oxygen",
        "distractor_1": "power, food",
        "distractor_2": "water, food",
        "distractor_3": "oxygen, power"
      },
      {
        "id": "7649",
        "question": "Ozone depletion is most like which of the following environmental problems that astronauts could face on a mission to Mars?",
        "answer": "radiation shielding failing on a spacecraft bound for Mars",
        "distractor_1": "oxygen supply depletion",
        "distractor_2": "lack of fuel for return trip",
        "distractor_3": "water supply depletion"
      },
      {
        "id": "7672",
        "question": "What do we call a vast group of stars, gas, and dust held together by the force of gravity?",
        "answer": "galaxy",
        "distractor_1": "solar system",
        "distractor_2": "universe",
        "distractor_3": "planets"
      },
      {
        "id": "7673",
        "question": "What is the name for a celestial body consisting of extremely hot gases that emit radiation?",
        "answer": "star",
        "distractor_1": "planet",
        "distractor_2": "comet",
        "distractor_3": "nebula"
      },
      {
        "id": "7674",
        "question": "What is the name of a celestial body that is larger than a dwarf planet and moves about a star in an orbit?",
        "answer": "planet",
        "distractor_1": "asteroid",
        "distractor_2": "meteor",
        "distractor_3": "comet"
      },
      {
        "id": "7675",
        "question": "What is the force between two objects that make them move toward each other?",
        "answer": "gravity",
        "distractor_1": "magnetism",
        "distractor_2": "static charge",
        "distractor_3": "momentum"
      },
      {
        "id": "7676",
        "question": "What do we call the path a celestial body follows as it travels around another celestial body?",
        "answer": "orbit",
        "distractor_1": "rotation",
        "distractor_2": "accretion",
        "distractor_3": "hyperbole"
      },
      {
        "id": "7677",
        "question": "What do we call the act of turning around on a center or axis?",
        "answer": "rotation",
        "distractor_1": "orbit",
        "distractor_2": "accretion",
        "distractor_3": "hyperbole"
      },
      {
        "id": "7678",
        "question": "What do we call the lines that are north or south of, and run parallel to, the equator?",
        "answer": "latitude",
        "distractor_1": "aurora australis",
        "distractor_2": "longitude",
        "distractor_3": "aurora borealis"
      },
      {
        "id": "7679",
        "question": "What do we call the lines that indicate east and west distances and are perpendicular to the equator?",
        "answer": "longitude",
        "distractor_1": "aurora australis",
        "distractor_2": "aurora borealis",
        "distractor_3": "latitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "7680",
        "question": "What do we call the region of concentrated ozone in the stratosphere?",
        "answer": "ozone layer",
        "distractor_1": "stratozone",
        "distractor_2": "ozone cloud",
        "distractor_3": "ozone disk"
      },
      {
        "id": "7681",
        "question": "What is the region called around a planet where the planet's magnetic field acts on objects?",
        "answer": "magnetosphere",
        "distractor_1": "magnetic layer",
        "distractor_2": "magnetozone",
        "distractor_3": "equatorial magnetic field"
      },
      {
        "id": "7682",
        "question": "What do we call the preservation of resources from loss or damage?",
        "answer": "conservation",
        "distractor_1": "observation",
        "distractor_2": "reservation",
        "distractor_3": "sequestration"
      },
      {
        "id": "7683",
        "question": "What is the process of extracting useful materials from garbage or waste?",
        "answer": "recycling",
        "distractor_1": "mining",
        "distractor_2": "extraction",
        "distractor_3": "restoring"
      },
      {
        "id": "7684",
        "question": "What type of energy can be replenished as quickly as it is used?",
        "answer": "renewable energy",
        "distractor_1": "fossil fuels",
        "distractor_2": "chemical energy",
        "distractor_3": "nuclear energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "7685",
        "question": "What is the process by which plants produce food, in the form of glucose, from carbon dioxide, water, and sunlight?",
        "answer": "photosynthesis",
        "distractor_1": "respiration",
        "distractor_2": "adaptation",
        "distractor_3": "conversion"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "177",
    "name": "Sustainable Agriculture",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "7728",
        "question": "Which occupation revolves around the science of growing and using plants to meet human needs such as food and fuel?",
        "answer": "agronomist ",
        "distractor_1": "mineralogist",
        "distractor_2": "soil conservationist",
        "distractor_3": "geologist"
      },
      {
        "id": "7729",
        "question": "What is DDT?",
        "answer": "a chemical pesticide",
        "distractor_1": "a type of soil used in organic farming",
        "distractor_2": "a chemical herbicide",
        "distractor_3": "a nutrient that aids plant growth"
      },
      {
        "id": "7700",
        "question": "In the process of photosynthesis, plants use light energy to convert carbon dioxide into what useful form of carbon?",
        "answer": "glucose",
        "distractor_1": "carbonitrate",
        "distractor_2": "carbon monoxide",
        "distractor_3": "methane"
      },
      {
        "id": "7701",
        "question": "A soil sample has a pH of 6. How would you describe this soil?",
        "answer": "weak acid",
        "distractor_1": "strong acid",
        "distractor_2": "strong base",
        "distractor_3": "weak base"
      },
      {
        "id": "7702",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a primary nutrient needed by plants to grow?",
        "answer": "lead",
        "distractor_1": "phosphorus",
        "distractor_2": "nitrogen",
        "distractor_3": "potassium"
      },
      {
        "id": "7703",
        "question": "Organic farming does not use which of the following practices?",
        "answer": "pesticide application",
        "distractor_1": "composting",
        "distractor_2": "no-till farming",
        "distractor_3": "water conservation"
      },
      {
        "id": "7704",
        "question": "Urban farming generally does not involve which of the following methods?",
        "answer": "sidewalk farming",
        "distractor_1": "vertical farming",
        "distractor_2": "vacant lot farming",
        "distractor_3": "rooftop gardens"
      },
      {
        "id": "7705",
        "question": "A soil sample was tested and found to have a neutral pH. Which pH value is neutral?",
        "answer": "7",
        "distractor_1": "5",
        "distractor_2": "6",
        "distractor_3": "8"
      },
      {
        "id": "7706",
        "question": "Which of the following is an example of biotechnology?",
        "answer": "bovine growth hormone",
        "distractor_1": "no-till farming",
        "distractor_2": "hydroponics",
        "distractor_3": "soil testing"
      },
      {
        "id": "7707",
        "question": "The process of topsoil being removed by wind and water is called what?",
        "answer": "erosion",
        "distractor_1": "irrigation",
        "distractor_2": "fertilization",
        "distractor_3": "plowing"
      },
      {
        "id": "7708",
        "question": "A compost pile has a temperature of 150° Fahrenheit. What phase is the compost pile in?",
        "answer": "active",
        "distractor_1": "initial",
        "distractor_2": "recycling",
        "distractor_3": "curing"
      },
      {
        "id": "7709",
        "question": "Which of the following is not made of organic material?",
        "answer": "water",
        "distractor_1": "trees",
        "distractor_2": "banana peels",
        "distractor_3": "fish"
      },
      {
        "id": "7710",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a primary nutrient needed by plants to grow?",
        "answer": "helium",
        "distractor_1": "potassium",
        "distractor_2": "phosphorus",
        "distractor_3": "nitrogen "
      },
      {
        "id": "7711",
        "question": "In the process of photosynthesis, plants use what type of energy to convert carbon dioxide into a useful form of carbon called glucose?",
        "answer": "light energy",
        "distractor_1": "nuclear energy",
        "distractor_2": "thermal energy",
        "distractor_3": "chemical energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "7712",
        "question": "Which of the following is an example of biotechnology?",
        "answer": "genetically engineered seeds",
        "distractor_1": "no-till farming",
        "distractor_2": "hydroponics",
        "distractor_3": "aeroponics"
      },
      {
        "id": "7713",
        "question": "Which of the following is not made of organic material?",
        "answer": "salt",
        "distractor_1": "wood",
        "distractor_2": "cows",
        "distractor_3": "apples"
      },
      {
        "id": "7714",
        "question": "A compost pile has a temperature of 101° Fahrenheit. What phase is the compost pile in?",
        "answer": "initial",
        "distractor_1": "inactive",
        "distractor_2": "active",
        "distractor_3": "curing"
      },
      {
        "id": "7715",
        "question": "A soil sample has a pH of 8. How would you describe this soil?",
        "answer": "weak base",
        "distractor_1": "weak acid",
        "distractor_2": "strong base",
        "distractor_3": "strong acid"
      },
      {
        "id": "7716",
        "question": "Organic farming does not use which of the following practices?",
        "answer": "using genetically engineered seeds",
        "distractor_1": "no-till farming",
        "distractor_2": "composting",
        "distractor_3": "water conservation"
      },
      {
        "id": "7717",
        "question": "The growing of crops and raising of livestock is known as what?",
        "answer": "agriculture",
        "distractor_1": "gardening",
        "distractor_2": "biotechnolgy",
        "distractor_3": "value-added farming"
      },
      {
        "id": "7718",
        "question": "If something comes from living organisms it can be considered what?",
        "answer": "organic",
        "distractor_1": "hydroponic",
        "distractor_2": "compost",
        "distractor_3": "acidic"
      },
      {
        "id": "7719",
        "question": "What scale is used to determine how acidic or basic a substance is?",
        "answer": "pH scale",
        "distractor_1": "nitrogen scale",
        "distractor_2": "acid scale",
        "distractor_3": "soil scale"
      },
      {
        "id": "7720",
        "question": "What is the process of growing plants without soil in a mixture of water and nutrients?",
        "answer": "hydroponics",
        "distractor_1": "aeroponics",
        "distractor_2": "ergonomics",
        "distractor_3": "vertical farming"
      },
      {
        "id": "7721",
        "question": "What is the process of growing plants in an air environment with a nutrient filled mist?",
        "answer": "aeroponics",
        "distractor_1": "hydroponics",
        "distractor_2": "oxidation",
        "distractor_3": "photosynthesis"
      },
      {
        "id": "7722",
        "question": "What is the process of transporting water from a source to fields or pastures?",
        "answer": "irrigation",
        "distractor_1": "erosion",
        "distractor_2": "hydration",
        "distractor_3": "germination "
      },
      {
        "id": "7723",
        "question": "What is the process of soil being gradually worn away by wind or water?",
        "answer": "erosion",
        "distractor_1": "irrigation",
        "distractor_2": "eradication",
        "distractor_3": "fertilization"
      },
      {
        "id": "7724",
        "question": "What is the field of science where technology is used to modify living organisms?",
        "answer": "biotechnology",
        "distractor_1": "biology",
        "distractor_2": "agriculture",
        "distractor_3": "technological farming"
      },
      {
        "id": "7725",
        "question": "a mixture of decaying organic material is called what?",
        "answer": "compost",
        "distractor_1": "fertilizer",
        "distractor_2": "herbicide",
        "distractor_3": "legume"
      },
      {
        "id": "7726",
        "question": "What is the process where plants use light energy to convert carbon from the air to a usable form?",
        "answer": "photosynthesis",
        "distractor_1": "irrigation",
        "distractor_2": "immunization",
        "distractor_3": "fertilization"
      },
      {
        "id": "7730",
        "question": "What nutrient is added to the soil by creating fertilizer through the Haber process?",
        "answer": "nitrogen",
        "distractor_1": "potassium",
        "distractor_2": "carbon",
        "distractor_3": "hydrogen"
      },
      {
        "id": "7731",
        "question": "A large body of water located underground is referred to as what?",
        "answer": "aquifer",
        "distractor_1": "watershed",
        "distractor_2": "wetland",
        "distractor_3": "illuviation"
      },
      {
        "id": "7735",
        "question": "Urban farming generally does not involve which of the following methods?",
        "answer": "combine harvesting",
        "distractor_1": "rooftop gardens",
        "distractor_2": "vertical farming",
        "distractor_3": "vacant lot farming"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "178",
    "name": "Future Fuels",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "7732",
        "question": "Which term refers to generating electricity though the use of water power?",
        "answer": "hydroelectric",
        "distractor_1": "nuclear",
        "distractor_2": "photovoltaic",
        "distractor_3": "geothermal"
      },
      {
        "id": "7733",
        "question": "Which term describes an energy source that is capable of being replaced?",
        "answer": "renewable",
        "distractor_1": "nonrenewable",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "7734",
        "question": "Which term describes an energy source that has a finite supply?",
        "answer": "nonrenewable",
        "distractor_1": "renewable",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "7588",
        "question": "What is the name of the process by which plants make food? ",
        "answer": "photosynthesis",
        "distractor_1": "sedimentary",
        "distractor_2": "photovoltaic",
        "distractor_3": "solar farming"
      },
      {
        "id": "7589",
        "question": "Which term best describes potential energy?",
        "answer": "stored energy",
        "distractor_1": "energy in motion",
        "distractor_2": "renewable",
        "distractor_3": "nonrenewable"
      },
      {
        "id": "7590",
        "question": "Which of the following did early humans use for fuel?",
        "answer": "manure, wood, peat",
        "distractor_1": "coal, kerosene, propane",
        "distractor_2": "wood, ethanol, biodiesel",
        "distractor_3": "peat, diesel, coal"
      },
      {
        "id": "7591",
        "question": "Which of the following fuels is classified as nonrenewable?",
        "answer": "nuclear",
        "distractor_1": "biomass",
        "distractor_2": "solar",
        "distractor_3": "wind"
      },
      {
        "id": "7592",
        "question": "Which of these fuels is produced by material decomposing in a landfill? ",
        "answer": "methane",
        "distractor_1": "biodiesel",
        "distractor_2": "ethanol",
        "distractor_3": "hydrogen"
      },
      {
        "id": "7593",
        "question": "A geyser is an example of which energy source? ",
        "answer": "geothermal",
        "distractor_1": "solar",
        "distractor_2": "hydroelectric",
        "distractor_3": "wind"
      },
      {
        "id": "7594",
        "question": "Which of the following activities consumes the most energy in a home?",
        "answer": "home heating",
        "distractor_1": "lighting",
        "distractor_2": "refrigeration",
        "distractor_3": "heating water"
      },
      {
        "id": "7595",
        "question": "What device converts solar radiation directly to electricity?",
        "answer": "photovoltaic cell",
        "distractor_1": "hydroelectric turbine",
        "distractor_2": "hydrogen fuel cell",
        "distractor_3": "tidal wave turbine"
      },
      {
        "id": "7596",
        "question": "Which of the following was not a historical use for natural gas?",
        "answer": "making electricity",
        "distractor_1": "eternal flames",
        "distractor_2": "boiling water",
        "distractor_3": "lighting street lights"
      },
      {
        "id": "7597",
        "question": "Which of the following modern technologies did ancient people use for heating their homes?",
        "answer": "passive solar heating",
        "distractor_1": "nuclear energy",
        "distractor_2": "wind turbines ",
        "distractor_3": "solar cells "
      },
      {
        "id": "7598",
        "question": "A watt is a measure of electrical power. How many watts are in a megawatt?",
        "answer": "1,000,000",
        "distractor_1": "10",
        "distractor_2": "100",
        "distractor_3": "100,000"
      },
      {
        "id": "7600",
        "question": "Biogas, which is a product of the breakdown, or rotting, of wastes such as garbage, agricultural waste, and human waste, contains which of the following gases?",
        "answer": "methane",
        "distractor_1": "propane",
        "distractor_2": "gasoline",
        "distractor_3": "biodiesel"
      },
      {
        "id": "7601",
        "question": "Which of the following is the world's largest geothermal power plant?",
        "answer": "Geysers in California",
        "distractor_1": "Hot Rocks in Australia",
        "distractor_2": "GeoSteams in Iceland",
        "distractor_3": "Old Faithful in Yellowstone"
      },
      {
        "id": "7602",
        "question": "Photosynthesis is the process by which plants make what?",
        "answer": "food",
        "distractor_1": "flowers",
        "distractor_2": "waste",
        "distractor_3": "water"
      },
      {
        "id": "7604",
        "question": "Which of the following did early humans not use for fuel?",
        "answer": "kerosene",
        "distractor_1": "manure",
        "distractor_2": "wood",
        "distractor_3": "peat"
      },
      {
        "id": "7605",
        "question": "Which of the following fuels is classified as renewable?",
        "answer": "biogas ",
        "distractor_1": "nuclear",
        "distractor_2": "coal",
        "distractor_3": "kerosene"
      },
      {
        "id": "7606",
        "question": "What causes methane to form in a landfill?",
        "answer": "decomposing material",
        "distractor_1": "formation of leachate",
        "distractor_2": "geothermal activity",
        "distractor_3": "compression"
      },
      {
        "id": "7607",
        "question": "Which of the following indicates geothermal energy is at work?",
        "answer": "geysers",
        "distractor_1": "strong air currents",
        "distractor_2": "wave movement",
        "distractor_3": "rivers"
      },
      {
        "id": "7608",
        "question": "What produces most of the electricity in the United States?",
        "answer": "coal",
        "distractor_1": "natural gas",
        "distractor_2": "hydroelectric power",
        "distractor_3": "nuclear power"
      },
      {
        "id": "7609",
        "question": "Photovoltaic cells convert which of the following directly to electricity?",
        "answer": "solar radiation ",
        "distractor_1": "air currents",
        "distractor_2": "water power",
        "distractor_3": "hydrogen"
      },
      {
        "id": "7610",
        "question": "What was a historical use for natural gas?",
        "answer": "lighting street lights",
        "distractor_1": "curing diseases",
        "distractor_2": "drying clothes",
        "distractor_3": "filling balloons"
      },
      {
        "id": "7611",
        "question": "Which of the following was not a way ancient people used solar energy?",
        "answer": "solar cells",
        "distractor_1": "drying bodies",
        "distractor_2": "fighting battles",
        "distractor_3": "heating homes"
      },
      {
        "id": "7686",
        "question": "A solar thermal power plant heats water to turn it into steam in order to produce what?",
        "answer": "electricity",
        "distractor_1": "ethanol",
        "distractor_2": "biogas",
        "distractor_3": "propane"
      },
      {
        "id": "7687",
        "question": "What term describes the energy that an object has because it is in motion?",
        "answer": "kinetic energy",
        "distractor_1": "potential energy",
        "distractor_2": "pneumatic energy",
        "distractor_3": "hydraulic energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "7688",
        "question": "What term describes stored energy?",
        "answer": "potential energy",
        "distractor_1": "kinetic energy",
        "distractor_2": "hydraulic energy",
        "distractor_3": "pneumatic energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "7689",
        "question": "Which term is used to describe something that converts energy directly to work?",
        "answer": "prime mover",
        "distractor_1": "prime meridian",
        "distractor_2": "converter",
        "distractor_3": "engine"
      },
      {
        "id": "7690",
        "question": "What is plant material used as a fuel called?",
        "answer": "biomass",
        "distractor_1": "fiber",
        "distractor_2": "biodiesel",
        "distractor_3": "synthetic fuel"
      },
      {
        "id": "7691",
        "question": "What is a machine that converts kinetic energy into rotary motion using vanes or paddles called?",
        "answer": "turbine",
        "distractor_1": "motor",
        "distractor_2": "lever",
        "distractor_3": "penstock"
      },
      {
        "id": "7692",
        "question": "Geothermal energy refers to heat from which source?",
        "answer": "earth",
        "distractor_1": "sun",
        "distractor_2": "falling water",
        "distractor_3": "light"
      },
      {
        "id": "7693",
        "question": "What is the area called that has wet spongy ground made from rotting vegetable matter?",
        "answer": "bog",
        "distractor_1": "strip mine",
        "distractor_2": "overburden",
        "distractor_3": "levee"
      },
      {
        "id": "7694",
        "question": "What material is formed in a bog?",
        "answer": "peat",
        "distractor_1": "blog",
        "distractor_2": "biodiesel",
        "distractor_3": "lava"
      },
      {
        "id": "7695",
        "question": "What type of cell is used to convert sunlight directly into electricity?",
        "answer": "photovoltaic cell",
        "distractor_1": "photosynthesis cell",
        "distractor_2": "photon cell",
        "distractor_3": "DNA cell"
      },
      {
        "id": "7696",
        "question": "What type of solar energy collection system uses no mechanical devices to move the collected heat?",
        "answer": "passive solar",
        "distractor_1": "active solar",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "7697",
        "question": "What type of solar collection system uses mechanical devices to move the heat collected?",
        "answer": "active solar",
        "distractor_1": "passive solar",
        "distractor_2": "",
        "distractor_3": ""
      },
      {
        "id": "7698",
        "question": "What device produces electriciy from the chemical reaction of a fuel and an oxidizer?",
        "answer": "fuel cell",
        "distractor_1": "hybrid engine",
        "distractor_2": "biodiesel generator",
        "distractor_3": "solar cell"
      },
      {
        "id": "7699",
        "question": "What is the term associated with any chemical that provides oxygen molecules for a chemical reaction?",
        "answer": "oxidizer",
        "distractor_1": "fuel",
        "distractor_2": "catalyst",
        "distractor_3": "hydrocarbon"
      },
      {
        "id": "7736",
        "question": "Which word best describes the term stored energy?",
        "answer": "potential",
        "distractor_1": "renewable",
        "distractor_2": "kinetic",
        "distractor_3": "nonrenewable"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "179",
    "name": "Garbology",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "7517",
        "question": "William Rathje is known as the father of which of the following? ",
        "answer": "garbology",
        "distractor_1": "biology",
        "distractor_2": "ecology",
        "distractor_3": "astrology "
      },
      {
        "id": "7518",
        "question": "Which of the following is a reason archeologists study middens? ",
        "answer": "to learn about ancient cultures",
        "distractor_1": "to learn about bones",
        "distractor_2": "to learn how ancient people recycled",
        "distractor_3": "to learn how ancient people kept warm"
      },
      {
        "id": "7519",
        "question": "Which of the following is not an example of hazardous waste?",
        "answer": "compost",
        "distractor_1": "paint thinner",
        "distractor_2": "antifreeze",
        "distractor_3": "motor oil "
      },
      {
        "id": "7520",
        "question": "Leachate is which of the following? ",
        "answer": "water that trickles through a landfill ",
        "distractor_1": "a blood-sucking animal",
        "distractor_2": "another name for a landfill",
        "distractor_3": "a type of e-waste "
      },
      {
        "id": "7521",
        "question": "Which term does not describe cell phones? ",
        "answer": "organic waste",
        "distractor_1": "e-waste",
        "distractor_2": "hazardous waste ",
        "distractor_3": "inorganic waste "
      },
      {
        "id": "7522",
        "question": "Which of the following is the best list of items that could be composted? ",
        "answer": "leaves, newspaper, apple cores",
        "distractor_1": "grass clippings, leaves, oil",
        "distractor_2": "potato peels, soda bottles, sticks",
        "distractor_3": "yard trimmings, foil, grass clippings "
      },
      {
        "id": "7523",
        "question": "Which statement did the Garbage Project prove about landfills?  ",
        "answer": "Waste does not biodegrade quickly. ",
        "distractor_1": "Disposable diapers are the biggest problem.",
        "distractor_2": "Plastic is the biggest problem.",
        "distractor_3": "Fast-food packaging takes up the most space. "
      },
      {
        "id": "7524",
        "question": "Which type of plastic is a milk jug?  ",
        "answer": "#2",
        "distractor_1": "#1",
        "distractor_2": "#3",
        "distractor_3": "#4"
      },
      {
        "id": "7525",
        "question": "Which term best describes the type of waste that was reduced when automobiles became popular? ",
        "answer": "organic waste",
        "distractor_1": "e-waste",
        "distractor_2": "hazardous waste",
        "distractor_3": "waste paper "
      },
      {
        "id": "7526",
        "question": "Which of the following do experts think is an effective way of dealing with our garbage problem? ",
        "answer": "reducing the amount ",
        "distractor_1": "burning it for fuel",
        "distractor_2": "landfilling",
        "distractor_3": "shipping it to other countries"
      },
      {
        "id": "7527",
        "question": "What percentage of a computer is made of toxic, nonferrous metals such as lead and mercury?",
        "answer": "18%",
        "distractor_1": "32%",
        "distractor_2": "23%",
        "distractor_3": "12%"
      },
      {
        "id": "7528",
        "question": "In which decade did PET, a plastic material developed in the 1940's, become commonly used in soda bottles?",
        "answer": "1970s ",
        "distractor_1": "1940s",
        "distractor_2": "1950s",
        "distractor_3": "1960s"
      },
      {
        "id": "7529",
        "question": "Of the observable space objects orbiting Earth, about how many are operational spacecraft?",
        "answer": "700",
        "distractor_1": "7,000,000",
        "distractor_2": "17,000,000",
        "distractor_3": "17,000"
      },
      {
        "id": "7530",
        "question": "When did the Chinese village of Guiyu start to become an e-waste village?",
        "answer": "1995",
        "distractor_1": "1991",
        "distractor_2": "2005",
        "distractor_3": "2001"
      },
      {
        "id": "7531",
        "question": "Who is known as the father of garbology?",
        "answer": "William Rathje",
        "distractor_1": "William McDonough",
        "distractor_2": "William Shakespeare",
        "distractor_3": "William Roberts "
      },
      {
        "id": "7532",
        "question": "Which of the following could be found in an ancient midden?",
        "answer": "old sandals",
        "distractor_1": "computers",
        "distractor_2": "newspaper",
        "distractor_3": "plastic silverware"
      },
      {
        "id": "7533",
        "question": "The introduction of automobiles reduced which type of waste? ",
        "answer": "horse manure",
        "distractor_1": "kitchen waste",
        "distractor_2": "paper ",
        "distractor_3": "wood ashes "
      },
      {
        "id": "7534",
        "question": "Which of the following is an example of hazardous waste?",
        "answer": "paint",
        "distractor_1": "compost",
        "distractor_2": "copy paper",
        "distractor_3": "lumber "
      },
      {
        "id": "7535",
        "question": "Runoff from a landfill is called what?",
        "answer": "leachate",
        "distractor_1": "e-waste",
        "distractor_2": "leaf waste",
        "distractor_3": "methane "
      },
      {
        "id": "7536",
        "question": "In which category does a cell phone fit best?",
        "answer": "e-waste",
        "distractor_1": "organic waste",
        "distractor_2": "inorganic waste",
        "distractor_3": "office waste  "
      },
      {
        "id": "7537",
        "question": "Which of the following is the best list of items that could be recycled? ",
        "answer": "newspaper, magazines, milk jugs",
        "distractor_1": "grass clippings, soda bottles, computers",
        "distractor_2": "cell phones, tin cans, leaves",
        "distractor_3": "aluminum cans, kitchen scraps, steel cans "
      },
      {
        "id": "7538",
        "question": "Which is an example of #1 plastic?",
        "answer": "water bottle ",
        "distractor_1": "milk jug",
        "distractor_2": "detergent bottle",
        "distractor_3": "packing peanuts"
      },
      {
        "id": "7539",
        "question": "Which of the following makes e-waste hazardous to dispose of in landfills?",
        "answer": "It contains heavy metals.",
        "distractor_1": "It contains organic matter. ",
        "distractor_2": "It causes memory loss.",
        "distractor_3": "It causes an increase in the mouse population. "
      },
      {
        "id": "7540",
        "question": "Which of the following is not true about landfills?",
        "answer": "They are becoming smaller.",
        "distractor_1": "They are built in layers.",
        "distractor_2": "They could be mined for valuable materials.",
        "distractor_3": "They may leak and pollute the water and soil in the future."
      },
      {
        "id": "7737",
        "question": "leftover item from the past",
        "answer": "relic",
        "distractor_1": "midden",
        "distractor_2": "dump",
        "distractor_3": "trash"
      },
      {
        "id": "7738",
        "question": "an ancient garbage dump",
        "answer": "midden",
        "distractor_1": "landfill",
        "distractor_2": "trash heap",
        "distractor_3": "compost heap"
      },
      {
        "id": "7739",
        "question": "using numbers, or quantities, to express information",
        "answer": "quantitative",
        "distractor_1": "qualitative",
        "distractor_2": "numerical",
        "distractor_3": "number based"
      },
      {
        "id": "7740",
        "question": "using qualities, descriptions, or non-numerical factors to express information",
        "answer": "qualitative",
        "distractor_1": "quantitative",
        "distractor_2": "descriptive",
        "distractor_3": "quality based"
      },
      {
        "id": "7741",
        "question": "a place where garbage is left out in the open",
        "answer": "dump",
        "distractor_1": "sanitary landfill",
        "distractor_2": "incinerator",
        "distractor_3": "municipal solid waste depository"
      },
      {
        "id": "7742",
        "question": "a place where fresh garbage is buried by covering it with soil ",
        "answer": "sanitary landfill",
        "distractor_1": "dump",
        "distractor_2": "midden",
        "distractor_3": "municipal solid waste depository"
      },
      {
        "id": "7743",
        "question": "materials produced by humans and animals when they live in a place, or material left over when an item is manufactured",
        "answer": "waste ",
        "distractor_1": "trash",
        "distractor_2": "garbage",
        "distractor_3": "leachate"
      },
      {
        "id": "7744",
        "question": "the act of buying things",
        "answer": "consumerism",
        "distractor_1": "recycling",
        "distractor_2": "built-in obsolescence",
        "distractor_3": "cradle-to-cradle philosophy"
      },
      {
        "id": "7745",
        "question": "anything made from plant or animal material",
        "answer": "organic",
        "distractor_1": "inorganic",
        "distractor_2": "vegetative",
        "distractor_3": "chemical"
      },
      {
        "id": "7746",
        "question": "material that is not, and never has been, alive",
        "answer": "inorganic",
        "distractor_1": "organic",
        "distractor_2": "mineral",
        "distractor_3": "chemical"
      },
      {
        "id": "7747",
        "question": "concept of building a product so it lasts only a limited amount of time",
        "answer": "built-in obsolescence",
        "distractor_1": "archaeology",
        "distractor_2": "cradle-to-cradle philosophy",
        "distractor_3": "cradle-to-grave philosophy"
      },
      {
        "id": "7748",
        "question": "make something unfit for use by adding harmful substances",
        "answer": "contaminate",
        "distractor_1": "exterminate",
        "distractor_2": "compost",
        "distractor_3": "damage"
      },
      {
        "id": "7749",
        "question": "items that last a long time, such as cars and appliances",
        "answer": "durable goods",
        "distractor_1": "nondurable goods",
        "distractor_2": "consumer goods",
        "distractor_3": "recycled goods"
      },
      {
        "id": "7750",
        "question": "items that last fewer than three years, such as plastic toys or many clothes",
        "answer": "nondurable goods",
        "distractor_1": "durable goods",
        "distractor_2": "consumer goods",
        "distractor_3": "recycled goods"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "180",
    "name": "Geometric Packing",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "7751",
        "question": "What is the volume of a square pyramid with a base of 4 cm and a height of 3 cm?",
        "answer": "16 cm³",
        "distractor_1": "48 cm²",
        "distractor_2": "16 cm²",
        "distractor_3": "48 cm³"
      },
      {
        "id": "7752",
        "question": "What is a slide of an object along a line in a plane?",
        "answer": "translation",
        "distractor_1": "rotation",
        "distractor_2": "tessellation ",
        "distractor_3": "reflection"
      },
      {
        "id": "7753",
        "question": "What is the approximate surface area of a sphere with a radius of 2 cm? ",
        "answer": "50.27 cm²",
        "distractor_1": "33.51 cm²",
        "distractor_2": "3.14 cm²",
        "distractor_3": "108 cm²"
      },
      {
        "id": "7754",
        "question": "How many faces does a tetrahedron have?",
        "answer": "4",
        "distractor_1": "3",
        "distractor_2": "5",
        "distractor_3": "6"
      },
      {
        "id": "7755",
        "question": "A circle with a center point (3, 2) is reflected across the y = -x axis. What is the center point of the reflected image of the circle?",
        "answer": "(-2, -3)",
        "distractor_1": "(2, -3)",
        "distractor_2": "(2, 3)",
        "distractor_3": " (-2, 3)"
      },
      {
        "id": "7756",
        "question": "What is the approximate ratio of the 11th Fibonacci number divided by the 10th Fibonacci number?",
        "answer": "1.618",
        "distractor_1": "1.5",
        "distractor_2": "3.141",
        "distractor_3": "1.517"
      },
      {
        "id": "7757",
        "question": "What is the gcd(12,16)?",
        "answer": "4",
        "distractor_1": "2",
        "distractor_2": "3",
        "distractor_3": "1"
      },
      {
        "id": "7758",
        "question": "If the two shorter sides of a right triangle measure 3 meters and 4 meters, respectively, what is the length of the hypotenuse?",
        "answer": "5",
        "distractor_1": "4",
        "distractor_2": "3",
        "distractor_3": "9"
      },
      {
        "id": "7759",
        "question": "What is the lcm(4,6)?",
        "answer": "12",
        "distractor_1": "4",
        "distractor_2": "6",
        "distractor_3": "2"
      },
      {
        "id": "7760",
        "question": "What type of object has the property where the number of rotations equals the number of reflections equals the number of sides?",
        "answer": "regular polygon",
        "distractor_1": "trapezoid",
        "distractor_2": "irregular polygon",
        "distractor_3": "simple polygon"
      },
      {
        "id": "7761",
        "question": "What is the gcd(7,8)?",
        "answer": "1",
        "distractor_1": "2",
        "distractor_2": "8",
        "distractor_3": "56"
      },
      {
        "id": "7762",
        "question": "What is the sixth Fibonacci number?",
        "answer": "5",
        "distractor_1": "2",
        "distractor_2": "8",
        "distractor_3": "13"
      },
      {
        "id": "7763",
        "question": "What is the approximate surface area of a cylinder with a height of 4 meters and a radius of 2 meters?",
        "answer": "75.40 m²",
        "distractor_1": "50.26 m²",
        "distractor_2": "16.00 m²",
        "distractor_3": "108.26 m²"
      },
      {
        "id": "7764",
        "question": "How many square faces are contained in a square pyramid?",
        "answer": "1",
        "distractor_1": "4",
        "distractor_2": "6",
        "distractor_3": "10"
      },
      {
        "id": "7765",
        "question": "What is the approximate volume of a sphere with a radius of 2 cm?",
        "answer": "33.51 cm³",
        "distractor_1": "25.01 cm³",
        "distractor_2": "42.14 cm³",
        "distractor_3": "50.26 cm³"
      },
      {
        "id": "7766",
        "question": "If two shorter sides of a right triangle measure 7 decimeters and 24 decimeters, what is the length of the hypotenuse?",
        "answer": "25 decimeters",
        "distractor_1": "31 decimeters",
        "distractor_2": "168 decimeters",
        "distractor_3": "625 decimeters"
      },
      {
        "id": "7767",
        "question": "What is the lcm(2,8)?",
        "answer": "8",
        "distractor_1": "2",
        "distractor_2": "12",
        "distractor_3": "16"
      },
      {
        "id": "7768",
        "question": "If point (4, -2) were translated five units to the left and then two units up, what would be its new coordinates?",
        "answer": "(-1, 0)",
        "distractor_1": "(-1, -2)",
        "distractor_2": "(4, 3)",
        "distractor_3": "(0, 1)"
      },
      {
        "id": "7769",
        "question": "What is the dihedral group for a pentagon?",
        "answer": "D5",
        "distractor_1": "D3",
        "distractor_2": "D2",
        "distractor_3": "D8"
      },
      {
        "id": "7770",
        "question": "In a rotation, what does not change about the object?",
        "answer": "size and shape",
        "distractor_1": "shape and orientation",
        "distractor_2": "size and orientation",
        "distractor_3": "shape and position"
      },
      {
        "id": "7771",
        "question": "In a 3-4-5 right triangle, which numeric value corresponds to the hypotenuse?",
        "answer": "5",
        "distractor_1": "3",
        "distractor_2": "4",
        "distractor_3": "unknown"
      },
      {
        "id": "7773",
        "question": "What is the sum of the measures of interior angles of a hexagon?",
        "answer": "720°",
        "distractor_1": "360°",
        "distractor_2": "180°",
        "distractor_3": "1,440°"
      },
      {
        "id": "7775",
        "question": "What is occurring when a figure is translated?",
        "answer": "It has been slid in any direction.",
        "distractor_1": "Its symmetry has been found.",
        "distractor_2": "Its formula has been found.",
        "distractor_3": "It has been rotated."
      },
      {
        "id": "7776",
        "question": "What is the maximum number of 10 cm x 10 cm x 10 cm cubes that you can fit in a box with dimensions 100 cm x 200 cm x 200 cm?",
        "answer": "4,000 cubes",
        "distractor_1": "400 cubes",
        "distractor_2": "4 cubes",
        "distractor_3": "4,000,000 cubes"
      },
      {
        "id": "7777",
        "question": "What is the slope of a horizontal line?",
        "answer": "0",
        "distractor_1": "undefined",
        "distractor_2": "pi",
        "distractor_3": "1"
      },
      {
        "id": "7778",
        "question": "The volume of a cubic box containing computers measures 8 cubic meters. By finding the surface area of the box, a shipper can find exactly how much bubble wrap is needed to cover the whole box with one layer. What is the overall surface area of the box?",
        "answer": "24 square meters",
        "distractor_1": "64 square meters",
        "distractor_2": "24 cubic meters",
        "distractor_3": "64 cubic meters"
      },
      {
        "id": "7779",
        "question": "Any polygon that on a polyhedron that makes up its boundary.",
        "answer": "faces",
        "distractor_1": "edges",
        "distractor_2": "tessellations",
        "distractor_3": "vertices"
      },
      {
        "id": "7780",
        "question": "A line segment joining vertices in any polygon.",
        "answer": "edges",
        "distractor_1": "faces",
        "distractor_2": "tessellations",
        "distractor_3": "vertices"
      },
      {
        "id": "7781",
        "question": "Any transformation of an object in a circular motion around a fixed point.",
        "answer": "rotation",
        "distractor_1": "reflection",
        "distractor_2": "translation",
        "distractor_3": "transformation"
      },
      {
        "id": "7782",
        "question": "Any transformation of an object about a line or axis which creates a mirror image of that object.",
        "answer": "reflection",
        "distractor_1": "rotation",
        "distractor_2": "translation",
        "distractor_3": "transformation"
      },
      {
        "id": "7783",
        "question": "Any transformation of an object is a movement, or slide, of that object in any direction.",
        "answer": "translation",
        "distractor_1": "reflection",
        "distractor_2": "rotation",
        "distractor_3": "transformation"
      },
      {
        "id": "7784",
        "question": "Any change in position, direction, or size of an object in a coordinate system without an alteration in their relative angles.",
        "answer": "transformation",
        "distractor_1": "reflection",
        "distractor_2": "translation",
        "distractor_3": "rotation"
      },
      {
        "id": "7785",
        "question": "A collection of objects or figures that fills a plane without any overlaps and gaps.",
        "answer": "tessellation",
        "distractor_1": "reflection",
        "distractor_2": "translation",
        "distractor_3": "transformation"
      },
      {
        "id": "7786",
        "question": "Any transformation in an object in which the object becomes resized.",
        "answer": "dilation",
        "distractor_1": "reflection",
        "distractor_2": "translation",
        "distractor_3": "transformation"
      },
      {
        "id": "7787",
        "question": "The measure of the amount of exposed area any solid object has.",
        "answer": "surface area",
        "distractor_1": "volume",
        "distractor_2": "greatest common divisor",
        "distractor_3": "least common multiple"
      },
      {
        "id": "7788",
        "question": "The measure of the amount of three-dimensional space any solid object has.",
        "answer": "volume",
        "distractor_1": "surface area",
        "distractor_2": "greatest common divisor",
        "distractor_3": "least common multiple"
      },
      {
        "id": "7789",
        "question": "Any corner point of a shape or an angle.",
        "answer": "vertices",
        "distractor_1": "Faces",
        "distractor_2": "Edges",
        "distractor_3": "tessellations"
      },
      {
        "id": "7790",
        "question": "The gcd of two or more nonzero rational numbers is the largest positive integer that divides the numbers without a remainder.",
        "answer": "greatest common divisor",
        "distractor_1": "least common multiple",
        "distractor_2": "surface area",
        "distractor_3": "volume"
      },
      {
        "id": "7791",
        "question": "The lcm of two or more nonzero rational numbers is the smallest positive integer that is a multiple of the numbers.",
        "answer": "least common multiple",
        "distractor_1": "greatest common divisor",
        "distractor_2": "surface area",
        "distractor_3": "volume"
      },
      {
        "id": "7792",
        "question": "An irrational number and a mathematical constant whose value is found by the ratio of the circumference of a circle to its diameter, approximately 3.1415.",
        "answer": "pi",
        "distractor_1": "phi",
        "distractor_2": "ohm",
        "distractor_3": "rho"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "181",
    "name": "Laser Geometry",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "7990",
        "question": "What is the constant at which light travels?",
        "answer": "299,792,458 m/s",
        "distractor_1": "300,000 mi/s",
        "distractor_2": "300,000 km/s^2",
        "distractor_3": "186,282 km/s"
      },
      {
        "id": "7991",
        "question": "If the Theta R = 38°, what is the measure of Theta I?",
        "answer": "38°",
        "distractor_1": "15° ",
        "distractor_2": "52°",
        "distractor_3": "142°"
      },
      {
        "id": "7992",
        "question": "The measure of angle ASP = 120°. The measure of angle ASP is bisected by ray SC. What is the measure of CSP?",
        "answer": "60°",
        "distractor_1": "10°",
        "distractor_2": "90°",
        "distractor_3": "120°"
      },
      {
        "id": "7993",
        "question": "What type of lines never intersects?",
        "answer": "parallel",
        "distractor_1": "skewed",
        "distractor_2": "perpendicular",
        "distractor_3": "transversal"
      },
      {
        "id": "8094",
        "question": "What is similar?",
        "answer": "Two shapes where one is an enlargement of the other.",
        "distractor_1": "Two shapes that are exactly the same.",
        "distractor_2": "Two totally different shapes.",
        "distractor_3": "Two shapes that have the same lengths for their corresponding sides. "
      },
      {
        "id": "7994",
        "question": "If the two legs of a triangle measure 3 and 4 respectively, what is always true about the measure of the hypotenuse c?",
        "answer": "c < 7",
        "distractor_1": "c > 7",
        "distractor_2": "c = 5",
        "distractor_3": "c = 7"
      },
      {
        "id": "7995",
        "question": "Which postulate only tells you about the similarity of two triangles?",
        "answer": "AAA",
        "distractor_1": "SSS",
        "distractor_2": "AAS",
        "distractor_3": "ASA"
      },
      {
        "id": "7996",
        "question": "What is the equation of a line connecting points (4, 1) and (3, 2)?",
        "answer": "y = -x + 5 ",
        "distractor_1": "y = -2x + 1",
        "distractor_2": "y = -x – 3",
        "distractor_3": "y = 2x – 1"
      },
      {
        "id": "7997",
        "question": "The measure of angle A = 32° and the measure of angle B = 58°. What are these angles called?",
        "answer": "complementary",
        "distractor_1": "opposite",
        "distractor_2": "adjacent",
        "distractor_3": "supplementary"
      },
      {
        "id": "7998",
        "question": "What is the slope of a line perpendicular to y = -3x + 2?",
        "answer": "1/3",
        "distractor_1": "-3",
        "distractor_2": "-2",
        "distractor_3": "2"
      },
      {
        "id": "7999",
        "question": "Convert the base 10 digit 23 to a base 2 digit.",
        "answer": "10111",
        "distractor_1": "11011",
        "distractor_2": "10110",
        "distractor_3": "11010"
      },
      {
        "id": "8001",
        "question": "Which of the following theorems states that in a triangle the sum of the lengths of any two sides is greater than the length of the remaining side?",
        "answer": "triangle inequality theorem",
        "distractor_1": "mid-segment theorem",
        "distractor_2": "right angles theorem",
        "distractor_3": "base angle theorem"
      },
      {
        "id": "8002",
        "question": "If you weigh 30 pounds (lb) on Earth, how much would you weigh on the Moon?",
        "answer": "5 lb",
        "distractor_1": "0 lb",
        "distractor_2": "30 lb",
        "distractor_3": "60 lb"
      },
      {
        "id": "8003",
        "question": "What is the angle measure of a straight line?",
        "answer": "180°",
        "distractor_1": "90°",
        "distractor_2": "0°",
        "distractor_3": "270°"
      },
      {
        "id": "8004",
        "question": "A ladder that measures 5 meters is resting on a side of a building. The length from the top of the ladder to the base of the building is 4 meters. What is the distance T of the base of the ladder from the base of the building?",
        "answer": "3 meters",
        "distractor_1": "5 meters",
        "distractor_2": "9 meters",
        "distractor_3": "41 meters"
      },
      {
        "id": "8005",
        "question": "What is the slope of the equation x = -2?",
        "answer": "undefined",
        "distractor_1": "0",
        "distractor_2": "-2",
        "distractor_3": "2"
      },
      {
        "id": "8007",
        "question": "The measure of angle A = 32° and the measure of angle B = 148°. What are these angles called?",
        "answer": "supplementary",
        "distractor_1": "complementary",
        "distractor_2": "adjacent",
        "distractor_3": "opposite"
      },
      {
        "id": "8008",
        "question": "Two parallel lines are cut by a transversal. Which of the following is true?",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "distractor_1": "Corresponding angles are equal.",
        "distractor_2": "Alternate interior angles are equal.",
        "distractor_3": "Opposite angles are equal."
      },
      {
        "id": "8009",
        "question": "If Theta I = 89.9°, what is the measure of Theta R?",
        "answer": "89.9°",
        "distractor_1": "0.01°",
        "distractor_2": "90°",
        "distractor_3": "0°"
      },
      {
        "id": "8010",
        "question": "If two triangles follow the SSS postulate, then they are always which of the following?",
        "answer": "congruent",
        "distractor_1": "similar",
        "distractor_2": "the same",
        "distractor_3": "adjacent"
      },
      {
        "id": "8011",
        "question": "What type of lines always intersects at a 90° angle?",
        "answer": "perpendicular",
        "distractor_1": "skewed",
        "distractor_2": "parallel",
        "distractor_3": "transversal"
      },
      {
        "id": "8012",
        "question": "What is the slope of a line parallel to y = -3x + 2?",
        "answer": "-3",
        "distractor_1": "1/3",
        "distractor_2": "-2",
        "distractor_3": "2"
      },
      {
        "id": "8013",
        "question": "Convert the base 2 digit 1101 to a base 10 digit.",
        "answer": "13",
        "distractor_1": "12",
        "distractor_2": "11",
        "distractor_3": "14"
      },
      {
        "id": "8014",
        "question": "Light is considered to be which of the following?",
        "answer": "a wave and a particle",
        "distractor_1": "a particle",
        "distractor_2": "a wave",
        "distractor_3": "none of these"
      },
      {
        "id": "8015",
        "question": "What is the wavelength of a laser light where x = 10 cm, D = 3 cm, m = 10, and L = 10 cm?",
        "answer": "0.3 cm",
        "distractor_1": "0.1 cm",
        "distractor_2": "0 cm",
        "distractor_3": "1 cm"
      },
      {
        "id": "8016",
        "question": "What is the equation of a line connecting points (2, 1) and (6, 3)?",
        "answer": "y = (1/2)x",
        "distractor_1": "y = 2x + 1",
        "distractor_2": "y = -(1/2)x",
        "distractor_3": "y = 2x"
      },
      {
        "id": "8019",
        "question": "What is the angle of reflection?",
        "answer": "the angle that light is reflected with respect to the normal",
        "distractor_1": "the angle that light strikes a surface with respect to the normal",
        "distractor_2": "the angle caused by the change in the direction of a wave due to a change in its speed",
        "distractor_3": "zero degrees"
      },
      {
        "id": "8020",
        "question": "What is the angle of incidence?",
        "answer": "the angle that light strikes a surface with respect to the normal",
        "distractor_1": "the angle that light is reflected with respect to the normal",
        "distractor_2": "the angle caused by the change in the direction of a wave due to a change in its speed",
        "distractor_3": "zero degrees"
      },
      {
        "id": "8022",
        "question": "What is incidence?",
        "answer": "the arrival of something at a surface",
        "distractor_1": "the departure of something at a surface",
        "distractor_2": "the constant of something at a surface",
        "distractor_3": "the consistency of something at a surface"
      },
      {
        "id": "8023",
        "question": "What are opposite angles?",
        "answer": "two nonadjacent angles formed by two intersecting lines ",
        "distractor_1": "two nonadjacent angles in matching corners formed by a transversal intersecting two parallel lines ",
        "distractor_2": "the pairs of angles on opposite sides of a transversal cutting two parallel lines but inside the two lines",
        "distractor_3": "the pairs of angles on one side of a transversal cutting two parallel lines but inside of the two lines"
      },
      {
        "id": "8024",
        "question": "What are corresponding angles?",
        "answer": "two nonadjacent angles in matching corners formed by a transversal intersecting two parallel lines ",
        "distractor_1": "the pairs of angles on opposite sides of a transversal cutting two parallel lines but outside the two lines",
        "distractor_2": "the pairs of angles on one side of a transversal cutting two parallel lines but inside of the two lines",
        "distractor_3": "two nonadjacent angles formed by two intersecting lines "
      },
      {
        "id": "8025",
        "question": "What are alternate interior angles?",
        "answer": "the pairs of angles on opposite sides of a transversal cutting two parallel lines but inside the two lines",
        "distractor_1": "the pairs of angles on opposite sides of a transversal cutting two parallel lines but outside the two lines",
        "distractor_2": "the pairs of angles on one side of a transversal cutting two parallel lines but inside of the two lines",
        "distractor_3": "two nonadjacent angles in matching corners formed by a transversal intersecting two parallel lines "
      },
      {
        "id": "8026",
        "question": "What are alternate exterior angles?",
        "answer": "the pairs of angles on opposite sides of a transversal cutting two parallel lines but outside the two lines",
        "distractor_1": "the pairs of angles on opposite sides of a transversal cutting two parallel lines but inside the two lines",
        "distractor_2": "the pairs of angles on one side of a transversal cutting two parallel lines but inside of the two lines",
        "distractor_3": "two nonadjacent angles in matching corners formed by a transversal intersecting two parallel lines "
      },
      {
        "id": "8029",
        "question": "What does congruent mean?",
        "answer": "two figures that have the same size and shape ",
        "distractor_1": "two figures that have the same shape but not the same size",
        "distractor_2": "two figures in which the angle-angle-angle postulate holds",
        "distractor_3": "two figures in which each corresponding angle is the same"
      },
      {
        "id": "8030",
        "question": "What does SAS stand for?",
        "answer": "side-angle-side",
        "distractor_1": "angle-side-angle",
        "distractor_2": "side-side-side",
        "distractor_3": "side-angle-angle"
      },
      {
        "id": "8031",
        "question": "What does SSS stand for?",
        "answer": "side-side-side",
        "distractor_1": "angle-angle-angle",
        "distractor_2": "right-angle- hypotenuse-side",
        "distractor_3": "angle-angle-side"
      },
      {
        "id": "8032",
        "question": "What does ASA stand for?",
        "answer": "angle-side-angle",
        "distractor_1": "angle-angle-side",
        "distractor_2": "side-side-side",
        "distractor_3": "angle-angle-angle"
      },
      {
        "id": "8033",
        "question": "What does AAS stand for?",
        "answer": "angle-angle-side",
        "distractor_1": "angle-angle-angle",
        "distractor_2": "side-side-side",
        "distractor_3": "angle-angle-side"
      },
      {
        "id": "8034",
        "question": "What does RHS stand for?",
        "answer": "right-angle- hypotenuse-side",
        "distractor_1": "angle-side-angle",
        "distractor_2": "angle-angle-angle",
        "distractor_3": "side-side-side"
      },
      {
        "id": "8036",
        "question": "What are similar triangles?",
        "answer": "two triangles that have the same shape but one is a scale of the other",
        "distractor_1": "two triangles that have the same size and shape",
        "distractor_2": "two triangles in which the ASA postulate holds",
        "distractor_3": "two triangles in which the SSS postulate holds"
      },
      {
        "id": "8047",
        "question": "What is amplitude?",
        "answer": "the maximum distance a wave vibrates from its rest position",
        "distractor_1": "the distance between two adjacent crests in a wave",
        "distractor_2": "the number of waves found in a given amount of time",
        "distractor_3": "the speed at which a wave travels"
      },
      {
        "id": "8048",
        "question": "What is wavelength?",
        "answer": "the distance between two adjacent crests in a wave",
        "distractor_1": "the number of waves found in a given amount of time",
        "distractor_2": "the maximum distance a wave vibrates from its rest position",
        "distractor_3": "the direction that a wave travels"
      },
      {
        "id": "8049",
        "question": "What is frequency?",
        "answer": "the number of waves found in a given amount of time",
        "distractor_1": "the amount of time that it takes for a wave to complete one cycle",
        "distractor_2": "the distance between two adjacent crests in a wave",
        "distractor_3": "a bundle of light energy"
      },
      {
        "id": "8050",
        "question": "What is wave speed?",
        "answer": "the speed at which a wave travels",
        "distractor_1": "the amount of time that it takes for a wave to complete one cycle",
        "distractor_2": "the direction that a wave travels",
        "distractor_3": "the maximum distance a wave vibrates from its rest position"
      },
      {
        "id": "8051",
        "question": "What is a period?",
        "answer": "the amount of time that it takes for a wave to complete one cycle",
        "distractor_1": "the direction that a wave travels",
        "distractor_2": "the number of waves found in a given amount of time",
        "distractor_3": "the maximum distance a wave vibrates from its rest position"
      },
      {
        "id": "8052",
        "question": "What is propagation?",
        "answer": "the direction that a wave travels",
        "distractor_1": "the number of waves found in a given amount of time",
        "distractor_2": "the amount of time that it takes for a wave to complete one cycle",
        "distractor_3": "the distance between two adjacent crests in a wave"
      },
      {
        "id": "8061",
        "question": "What is a perpendicular bisector?",
        "answer": "a type of line that passes through the midpoint of a segment at a 90º angle",
        "distractor_1": "a type of line that passes through the midpoint of a segment at more than a 90º angle",
        "distractor_2": "a line that cuts another line into three equal parts",
        "distractor_3": "a type of line that passes through the midpoint of a segment at less than a 90º angle"
      },
      {
        "id": "8066",
        "question": "What is an angle bisector?",
        "answer": "a type of line that divides an angle into two angles with equal measures",
        "distractor_1": "a type of line that passes through the midpoint of a segment at a 90º angle",
        "distractor_2": "a type of line that divides an angle into two angles with measures that are not equal",
        "distractor_3": "a line that crosses through an angle"
      },
      {
        "id": "8067",
        "question": "What is a transversal?",
        "answer": "a line that crosses at least two other lines",
        "distractor_1": "a line that crosses through an angle",
        "distractor_2": "a type of line that divides an angle into two angles with measures that are not equal",
        "distractor_3": "a movement, or slide, of that object in any direction along a line"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "190",
    "name": "e-Design",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8276",
        "question": "Which of the following is a primary color?",
        "answer": "yellow",
        "distractor_1": "orange",
        "distractor_2": "green",
        "distractor_3": "purple"
      },
      {
        "id": "8277",
        "question": "Where are complementary colors located on a color wheel? ",
        "answer": "opposite one another",
        "distractor_1": "beside one another",
        "distractor_2": "on the same side",
        "distractor_3": "on top"
      },
      {
        "id": "8278",
        "question": "A balanced design on what format is a formal design? ",
        "answer": "central axis",
        "distractor_1": "white background",
        "distractor_2": "page",
        "distractor_3": "classical presentation"
      },
      {
        "id": "8279",
        "question": "Proportion is an important part of design. What is proportion considered? ",
        "answer": "principle",
        "distractor_1": "shape ",
        "distractor_2": "type",
        "distractor_3": "element"
      },
      {
        "id": "8280",
        "question": "Which of the following is an element of design? ",
        "answer": "color",
        "distractor_1": "rhythm",
        "distractor_2": "unity",
        "distractor_3": "contrast"
      },
      {
        "id": "8281",
        "question": "This occurs when all parts of a layout work together to achieve the intended message. ",
        "answer": "harmony",
        "distractor_1": "rhythm",
        "distractor_2": "proportion",
        "distractor_3": "balance"
      },
      {
        "id": "8282",
        "question": "A 2' x 8' rectangle would be proportional to what shape?",
        "answer": "1' x 4' rectangle",
        "distractor_1": "3' x 2' rectangle",
        "distractor_2": "4' x 5' rectangle",
        "distractor_3": "3' x 9' rectangle"
      },
      {
        "id": "8283",
        "question": "Which principle of design uses colors, texture, and lines to provide a point of emphasis in a layout?",
        "answer": "contrast",
        "distractor_1": "balance",
        "distractor_2": "rhythm",
        "distractor_3": "proportion"
      },
      {
        "id": "8284",
        "question": "What is a tertiary color? ",
        "answer": "the combination of a secondary and a primary color",
        "distractor_1": "a color on the lower third of the color wheel",
        "distractor_2": "the combination of two primary colors",
        "distractor_3": "the third color in a triad "
      },
      {
        "id": "8285",
        "question": "Which of the following terms is defined as an artistic arrangement used to put an idea together?",
        "answer": "design",
        "distractor_1": "portfolio",
        "distractor_2": "bouquet",
        "distractor_3": "principle"
      },
      {
        "id": "8288",
        "question": "A 3' x 4' rectangle would be proportional to what shape?",
        "answer": "6' x 8' rectangle",
        "distractor_1": "3' x 8' rectangle",
        "distractor_2": "1' x 2' triangle",
        "distractor_3": "3' circle"
      },
      {
        "id": "8298",
        "question": "Joe is creating a design, one-third of which will be white space. How much wihte space will be in the deisgn if it is placed on a 8.5 inch by 11 inch piece of paper?",
        "answer": "31.17 square inches",
        "distractor_1": "10.39 square inches",
        "distractor_2": "62.33 square inches",
        "distractor_3": "93.5 square inches"
      },
      {
        "id": "8289",
        "question": "Which design principle's function is to pull the total design together? ",
        "answer": "unity",
        "distractor_1": "proportion",
        "distractor_2": "contrast",
        "distractor_3": "rhythm"
      },
      {
        "id": "8291",
        "question": "Two identical objects lie horizontal to one another 5.37 centimeters apart. The design is formally balanced, and the center lies between the two objects. How far is the center from each object? ",
        "answer": "2.685 cm",
        "distractor_1": "2.185 cm ",
        "distractor_2": "3.185 cm",
        "distractor_3": "5.37 cm"
      },
      {
        "id": "8292",
        "question": "What is a formally balanced design called? ",
        "answer": "symmetrical",
        "distractor_1": "asymmetrical",
        "distractor_2": "proportional",
        "distractor_3": "orthogonal"
      },
      {
        "id": "8294",
        "question": "Two triangles will be placed on a design to balance a 3' x 4' rectangle. The combined area of the two triangles is equal to the area of the rectangle. What are the dimensions of the triangles? ",
        "answer": "1.5' x 4' and 3' x 2'",
        "distractor_1": "3' x 8' and 6' x 4'",
        "distractor_2": "3' x 4' and 4' x 3'",
        "distractor_3": "3' x 4' and 6' x 8'"
      },
      {
        "id": "8295",
        "question": "Which design principle's function is to draw the viewer's attention to specific parts of the design?",
        "answer": "contrast",
        "distractor_1": "unity",
        "distractor_2": "proportion",
        "distractor_3": "rhythm"
      },
      {
        "id": "8299",
        "question": "This principle is the result of placing elements on a page so that they appear secure and natural, either formally or informally.",
        "answer": "balance",
        "distractor_1": "unity",
        "distractor_2": "harmony",
        "distractor_3": "contrast"
      },
      {
        "id": "8300",
        "question": "This term is defined as the comparative relationship between layout elements with respect to size and visual weight.",
        "answer": "proportion",
        "distractor_1": "balance",
        "distractor_2": "unity",
        "distractor_3": "rhythm"
      },
      {
        "id": "8301",
        "question": "This term is defined as an exact division of the complete design elements into two identical halves.",
        "answer": "symmetrical",
        "distractor_1": "complementary",
        "distractor_2": "negative",
        "distractor_3": "horizontal"
      },
      {
        "id": "8302",
        "question": "A design is said to be this when it is uneven in reference to balance of elements; tone, size, and shape play major parts.",
        "answer": "asymmetrical",
        "distractor_1": "symmetrical",
        "distractor_2": "balanced",
        "distractor_3": "united"
      },
      {
        "id": "8303",
        "question": "A design is said to be this when all elements of the design are in precise relationship to one another.",
        "answer": "formal balance",
        "distractor_1": "informal balance",
        "distractor_2": "parallel",
        "distractor_3": "radial"
      },
      {
        "id": "8304",
        "question": "A design is said to be this when elements of similar weight are placed in relationship so that stability is achieved through dynamic rather than static control.",
        "answer": "informal balance",
        "distractor_1": "formal balance",
        "distractor_2": "parallel",
        "distractor_3": "radial"
      },
      {
        "id": "8305",
        "question": "These are colors found opposite each other on a 12-station color wheel; for example, red is this to green and is located directly across from it on the color wheel.",
        "answer": "complementary",
        "distractor_1": "contrasting",
        "distractor_2": "reflecting",
        "distractor_3": "absorbing"
      },
      {
        "id": "8306",
        "question": "This is obtained when difference in color is emphasized; for example, by adding light green text to a dark green background, you will grab the reader's attention.",
        "answer": "contrast",
        "distractor_1": "harmony",
        "distractor_2": "unity",
        "distractor_3": "balance"
      },
      {
        "id": "8307",
        "question": "This tool organizes colors by how they are made; for example, orange is between red and yellow; it also allows the artist to pick complementary and contrasting colors easily.",
        "answer": "color wheel",
        "distractor_1": "central axis",
        "distractor_2": "balance beam",
        "distractor_3": "element"
      },
      {
        "id": "8308",
        "question": "This occurs in a design when all parts of a layout work together to achieve their intended messages.",
        "answer": "harmony",
        "distractor_1": "unity",
        "distractor_2": "balance",
        "distractor_3": "contrast"
      },
      {
        "id": "8309",
        "question": "In design, this effect creates a striking difference between two or more objects using color, size, texture, or placement.",
        "answer": "contrast",
        "distractor_1": "proportion",
        "distractor_2": "harmony",
        "distractor_3": "unity"
      },
      {
        "id": "8310",
        "question": "This design principle is achieved when all the elements work together like a finely tuned machine.",
        "answer": "unity",
        "distractor_1": "balance",
        "distractor_2": "proportion",
        "distractor_3": "harmony"
      },
      {
        "id": "8311",
        "question": "This occurs in a design when a layout incorporates points, lines, shapes, textures, tones, and colors in a pleasing fashion.",
        "answer": "rhythm",
        "distractor_1": "scale",
        "distractor_2": "balance",
        "distractor_3": "emphasis"
      },
      {
        "id": "8312",
        "question": "Which of the following elements of design could be described as the way a surface feels or looks?",
        "answer": "texture",
        "distractor_1": "line",
        "distractor_2": "shape and form",
        "distractor_3": "color"
      },
      {
        "id": "8313",
        "question": "Color, an important part of design, is considered what part of design?",
        "answer": "element",
        "distractor_1": "principle",
        "distractor_2": "type",
        "distractor_3": "contrast"
      },
      {
        "id": "8314",
        "question": "Which of the following is a principle of design?",
        "answer": "proportion",
        "distractor_1": "shape",
        "distractor_2": "color",
        "distractor_3": "texture"
      },
      {
        "id": "8315",
        "question": "What is the color yellow considered?",
        "answer": "primary",
        "distractor_1": "secondary",
        "distractor_2": "tertiary",
        "distractor_3": "complementary"
      },
      {
        "id": "8316",
        "question": "What are two colors opposite one another on the color wheel called?",
        "answer": "complementary",
        "distractor_1": "warm",
        "distractor_2": "secondary",
        "distractor_3": "formal"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "182",
    "name": "Ideas & Innovations",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8463",
        "question": "What are the goals of science and technology?",
        "answer": "science: to understand the natural world; technology: to meet human needs",
        "distractor_1": "science: to test hypotheses through experimentation; technology: to obtain a patent",
        "distractor_2": "science: to ask questions; technology: to answer questions",
        "distractor_3": "science: to solve human problems; technology: to develop new products"
      },
      {
        "id": "8464",
        "question": "What are the two types of processes in the Universal Systems Model?",
        "answer": "management and production",
        "distractor_1": "systems and subsystems",
        "distractor_2": "design and test",
        "distractor_3": "inputs and outputs"
      },
      {
        "id": "8465",
        "question": "Complete this analogy: system is to subsystem as vehicle is to what? ",
        "answer": "propulsion",
        "distractor_1": "transportation",
        "distractor_2": "road",
        "distractor_3": "truck"
      },
      {
        "id": "8466",
        "question": "SCAMPER is a method of generating new ideas based on something that already exists. What does the A in SCAMPER stand for?",
        "answer": "adapt",
        "distractor_1": "analyze",
        "distractor_2": "arrange",
        "distractor_3": "attempt"
      },
      {
        "id": "8467",
        "question": "What type of engineer would be most likely to design and oversee the construction of a water-treatment facility?",
        "answer": "civil engineer",
        "distractor_1": "mechanical engineer",
        "distractor_2": "industrial engineer",
        "distractor_3": "electrical engineer"
      },
      {
        "id": "8468",
        "question": "What is an open system?",
        "answer": "a system that interacts with its environment and other systems",
        "distractor_1": "a system that has smaller systems within it",
        "distractor_2": "a system that runs and maintains itself",
        "distractor_3": "a system that automatically opens and closes doors"
      },
      {
        "id": "8469",
        "question": "Who was a major contributor to the invention of the television?",
        "answer": "Philo Farnsworth",
        "distractor_1": "Guglielmo Marconi",
        "distractor_2": "Charles Brush",
        "distractor_3": "Charles Babbage"
      },
      {
        "id": "8470",
        "question": "What are rules and limitations that must be followed when developing solutions to problems?",
        "answer": "constraints",
        "distractor_1": "trade-offs",
        "distractor_2": "patents",
        "distractor_3": "innovations"
      },
      {
        "id": "8471",
        "question": "In engineering, what is an exchange of one thing for something better?",
        "answer": "trade-off",
        "distractor_1": "constraint",
        "distractor_2": "system",
        "distractor_3": "patent"
      },
      {
        "id": "8472",
        "question": "What is the process of coming up with new ideas and ways to solve problems?",
        "answer": "ideation",
        "distractor_1": "systems thinking",
        "distractor_2": "Universal Systems Model",
        "distractor_3": "innovation"
      },
      {
        "id": "8473",
        "question": "What is the process of modifying or improving existing inventions or ways of doing things?",
        "answer": "innovation",
        "distractor_1": "invention",
        "distractor_2": "patenting",
        "distractor_3": "systems thinking"
      },
      {
        "id": "8474",
        "question": "What is an exclusive right to manufacture and sell an invention or innovation?",
        "answer": "patent",
        "distractor_1": "universal system",
        "distractor_2": "trade-off",
        "distractor_3": "constraint"
      },
      {
        "id": "8475",
        "question": "What is a smaller system that is part of a larger system?",
        "answer": "subsystem",
        "distractor_1": "supersystem",
        "distractor_2": "universal system",
        "distractor_3": "minisystem"
      },
      {
        "id": "8476",
        "question": "What is a group of parts that work together for a common purpose?",
        "answer": "system",
        "distractor_1": "patent",
        "distractor_2": "trade-off",
        "distractor_3": "constraint"
      },
      {
        "id": "8477",
        "question": "What is a way of looking at how things influence each other within a whole?",
        "answer": "systems thinking",
        "distractor_1": "trade-off",
        "distractor_2": "engineering",
        "distractor_3": "ideation"
      },
      {
        "id": "8478",
        "question": "A pulling force that stretches something is called what?",
        "answer": "tension",
        "distractor_1": "torque",
        "distractor_2": "compression",
        "distractor_3": "propulsion"
      },
      {
        "id": "8479",
        "question": "What is a tendency that causes things to want to turn or rotate?",
        "answer": "torque",
        "distractor_1": "tension",
        "distractor_2": "ideation",
        "distractor_3": "compression"
      },
      {
        "id": "8480",
        "question": "When engineers and technologists try to solve a problem, they often use a systems approach called what?",
        "answer": "Universal Systems Model",
        "distractor_1": "ideation",
        "distractor_2": "SCAMPER",
        "distractor_3": "innovation"
      },
      {
        "id": "8456",
        "question": "Jeremy is using the Ideas & Innovations problem-solving model to solve a challenge. He has identified the problem and proposed possible solutions. What is his next step?",
        "answer": "implement a solution",
        "distractor_1": "brainstorm",
        "distractor_2": "gather feedback",
        "distractor_3": "check the solution"
      },
      {
        "id": "8457",
        "question": "What is a constraint?",
        "answer": "a rule or limitation",
        "distractor_1": "the exclusive right to manufacture and sell an invention",
        "distractor_2": "a solution to a problem",
        "distractor_3": "a group of parts that work together for a common purpose"
      },
      {
        "id": "8458",
        "question": "Which of these statements is true about scientists?",
        "answer": "Scientists share new information openly so it can be confirmed by others.",
        "distractor_1": "Scientists keep new discoveries to themselves so they can get credit for the discovery.",
        "distractor_2": "Scientists and technologists are independent and do not work together.",
        "distractor_3": "Scientists fail when their hypotheses are proved wrong."
      },
      {
        "id": "8459",
        "question": "In engineering, when one attribute or quality is sacrificed for the sake of another, this is known as what?",
        "answer": "trade-off",
        "distractor_1": "patent",
        "distractor_2": "substitution",
        "distractor_3": "ideation"
      },
      {
        "id": "8460",
        "question": "Which is true about how science and technology spur each other on?",
        "answer": "Scientists often need new technology to make new discoveries.",
        "distractor_1": "Engineers work to disprove scientists.",
        "distractor_2": "Scientists and technologists compete with each other for new discoveries.",
        "distractor_3": "Scientists and technologists often race to patent their ideas."
      },
      {
        "id": "8461",
        "question": "What is the order of the Universal Systems Model?",
        "answer": "inputs, processes, outputs, feedback",
        "distractor_1": "inputs, feedback, outputs, processes",
        "distractor_2": "inputs, outputs, feedback, processes",
        "distractor_3": "processes, inputs, feedback, outputs"
      },
      {
        "id": "8462",
        "question": "Which of these discoveries would you be able to obtain a patent for?",
        "answer": "discovering how a car engine can run on water",
        "distractor_1": "discovering an asteroid",
        "distractor_2": "discovering a new species of fish",
        "distractor_3": "discovering a new buried civilization"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "183",
    "name": "Immunology",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8412",
        "question": "Which item best describes the function of the mucous membranes in the immune system?",
        "answer": "barrier",
        "distractor_1": "cell production",
        "distractor_2": "expulsion of bacteria",
        "distractor_3": "regulation"
      },
      {
        "id": "8413",
        "question": "The leukocytes that produce histamine are called what?",
        "answer": "basophils",
        "distractor_1": "neutrophils",
        "distractor_2": "B lymphocytes",
        "distractor_3": "T lymphocytes"
      },
      {
        "id": "8414",
        "question": "What type of immunity involves injecting a person with antibodies specific to a foreign antigen? This type of immunity is also passed from mother to infant during breastfeeding.",
        "answer": "passive immunity",
        "distractor_1": "active immunity",
        "distractor_2": "maternal immunity",
        "distractor_3": "community immunity"
      },
      {
        "id": "8415",
        "question": "When vaccination rates are high enough, a population can become immune to a disease. What is this called?",
        "answer": "community immunity",
        "distractor_1": "active immunity",
        "distractor_2": "passive immunity",
        "distractor_3": "maternal immunity"
      },
      {
        "id": "8416",
        "question": "Which name would be used to describe spherical-shaped bacteria?",
        "answer": "cocci",
        "distractor_1": "bacilli",
        "distractor_2": "spirilla",
        "distractor_3": "rodified"
      },
      {
        "id": "8417",
        "question": "Which term would best describe bacteria that appear pink in color, rod shaped, and in long chains of linked bacteria?",
        "answer": "Gram-negative streptobacilli",
        "distractor_1": "Gram-negative staphylococci",
        "distractor_2": "Gram-positive staphylococci",
        "distractor_3": "Gram-positive streptobacilli"
      },
      {
        "id": "8418",
        "question": "Which arrangement correctly orders the items named from smallest to largest?",
        "answer": "virus, bacteria, lymphocyte",
        "distractor_1": "bacteria, virus, lymphocyte",
        "distractor_2": "lymphocyte, bacteria, virus",
        "distractor_3": "lymphocyte, virus, bacteria"
      },
      {
        "id": "8419",
        "question": "On the surface of viruses are small proteins that project out and allow the virus to recognize and attach to a host cell. What are produced by B lymphocytes to attach to and neutralize these proteins?",
        "answer": "antibodies",
        "distractor_1": "antigens",
        "distractor_2": "basophils",
        "distractor_3": "neutrophils"
      },
      {
        "id": "8420",
        "question": "The disease athlete's foot is caused by what type of pathogen?",
        "answer": "fungus",
        "distractor_1": "bacteria ",
        "distractor_2": "virus ",
        "distractor_3": "protist"
      },
      {
        "id": "8421",
        "question": "Malaria is a protist infection that usually affects people when?",
        "answer": "when they are bitten by a mosquito that carries the protist",
        "distractor_1": "after a traumatic injury, when the deep tissue is exposed to the protist",
        "distractor_2": "after they have been treated with antibiotics for another illness",
        "distractor_3": "after they have been exposed to the body fluids of someone who has the condition"
      },
      {
        "id": "8422",
        "question": "Before birth, antibodies from the mother pass into the baby, protecting the baby for the first few months of life. What is this type of immunity called, in which antibodies from one person are transferred to another?",
        "answer": "passive immunity",
        "distractor_1": "active immunity",
        "distractor_2": "cellular immunity",
        "distractor_3": "maternal immunity"
      },
      {
        "id": "8425",
        "question": "A healthy person has about 0.1 percent as many white blood cells as red blood cells. How many white blood cells would be in a blood sample containing 25,000 red blood cells?",
        "answer": "25",
        "distractor_1": "2,500",
        "distractor_2": "250",
        "distractor_3": "2"
      },
      {
        "id": "8426",
        "question": "In 1931 two German scientists invented the first scanning electron microscope. What were their names?",
        "answer": "Max Knoll and Ernst Ruska",
        "distractor_1": "Max Webere and Johann Wincklemann",
        "distractor_2": "Rudolf Diesel and Felix Wankel",
        "distractor_3": "Roman Herzog and Johannes Rau"
      },
      {
        "id": "8427",
        "question": "Determining the magnification of a microscope is done by multiplying the power of the objective lens and the eyepiece lens. If a microscope has an objective lens of 40X and an eyepiece lens of 10X, how large would a cell with a diameter of 2 nanometers ap",
        "answer": "800 nanometers",
        "distractor_1": "80 nanometers",
        "distractor_2": "20 nanonmeters",
        "distractor_3": "2000 nanometers"
      },
      {
        "id": "8428",
        "question": "The last time someone contracted smallpox naturally was in 1975. However, in 1978, a medical photographer died from a case of smallpox contracted during a research accident. What was the name of the person who died in 1978?",
        "answer": "Janet Parker",
        "distractor_1": "Henry Bedson",
        "distractor_2": "Rahima Banu",
        "distractor_3": "Edward Jenner"
      },
      {
        "id": "8429",
        "question": "In 1958, the United States had 758,000 reported cases of measles and a population of 179,000,000. In 2008, fifty years later, the population was more than 300,000,000 and the major news was an outbreak of measles, which was only 131 cases, representing le",
        "answer": "0.4%",
        "distractor_1": "40%",
        "distractor_2": "4%",
        "distractor_3": "0.04%"
      },
      {
        "id": "8430",
        "question": "Which item best describes the function of the skin in the immune system?",
        "answer": "barrier",
        "distractor_1": "cell production",
        "distractor_2": "expulsion of bacteria",
        "distractor_3": "regulation"
      },
      {
        "id": "8431",
        "question": "The leukocytes that attack and engulf foreign bodies such as bacteria and viruses are called what?",
        "answer": "T lymphocytes",
        "distractor_1": "basophils",
        "distractor_2": "neutrophils",
        "distractor_3": "B lymphocytes"
      },
      {
        "id": "8432",
        "question": "What type of immunity do you have when your body produces antibodies specific to a certain foreign invader? You get this type of immunity when you are exposed to the invader.",
        "answer": "active immunity",
        "distractor_1": "passive immunity",
        "distractor_2": "maternal immunity",
        "distractor_3": "community immunity"
      },
      {
        "id": "8433",
        "question": "When a population is immune to the effects of an invader because a significant portion of the population is immune, but not necessarily all, which term is used to describe the situation?",
        "answer": "community immunity",
        "distractor_1": "active immunity",
        "distractor_2": "passive immunity",
        "distractor_3": "maternal immunity"
      },
      {
        "id": "8434",
        "question": "Which name would be used to describe rod-shaped bacteria?",
        "answer": "bacilli",
        "distractor_1": "cocci",
        "distractor_2": "spirilla",
        "distractor_3": "rodified"
      },
      {
        "id": "8435",
        "question": "Which term would best describe bacteria that appear purple in color, spherical in shape, and clustered in groups like grapes?",
        "answer": "Gram-positive staphylococci",
        "distractor_1": "Gram-negative staphylococci",
        "distractor_2": "Gram-negative streptobacilli",
        "distractor_3": "Gram-positive streptobacilli"
      },
      {
        "id": "8436",
        "question": "Which arrangement correctly orders the items named from largest to smallest?",
        "answer": "lymphocyte, bacteria, virus",
        "distractor_1": "bacteria, virus, lymphocyte",
        "distractor_2": "virus, bacteria, lymphocyte",
        "distractor_3": "lymphocyte, virus, bacteria"
      },
      {
        "id": "8437",
        "question": "On the surface of viruses are small proteins that project out and allow the virus to recognize and attach to a host cell. What are the proteins?",
        "answer": "antigens",
        "distractor_1": "antibodies",
        "distractor_2": "basophils",
        "distractor_3": "neutrophils"
      },
      {
        "id": "8438",
        "question": "The disease malaria is caused by what type of pathogen?",
        "answer": "protist",
        "distractor_1": "bacteria ",
        "distractor_2": "virus ",
        "distractor_3": "fungus"
      },
      {
        "id": "8439",
        "question": "Mucormycosis is a fungal infection that usually affects people when?",
        "answer": "after a traumatic injury, when the deep tissue is exposed to the fungus",
        "distractor_1": "after they have been treated with antibiotics for another illness",
        "distractor_2": "when they are bitten by a mosquito that carries the fungus",
        "distractor_3": "after being exposed to the body fluids of someone who has the condition"
      },
      {
        "id": "8440",
        "question": "The type of immunity you have because your body produces antibodies against a particular pathogen.",
        "answer": "active immunity ",
        "distractor_1": "passive immunity ",
        "distractor_2": "antigen",
        "distractor_3": "antibody "
      },
      {
        "id": "8441",
        "question": "A drug used to treat infection by a living organism, such as bacteria.",
        "answer": "antibiotic",
        "distractor_1": "active immunity ",
        "distractor_2": "vaccine",
        "distractor_3": "antibody "
      },
      {
        "id": "8442",
        "question": "A compound made by the B lymphocytes that attaches to the antigens on the surface of pathogens in the bloodstream.",
        "answer": "antibody ",
        "distractor_1": "protist",
        "distractor_2": "antibiotic",
        "distractor_3": "antigen"
      },
      {
        "id": "8443",
        "question": "Surface proteins on pathogens that when recognized by the immune system cause antibodies to be generated.",
        "answer": "antigen",
        "distractor_1": "virus",
        "distractor_2": "bacteria",
        "distractor_3": "protist"
      },
      {
        "id": "8444",
        "question": "A disorder in which the immune system fails to recognize normal body cells and destroys them, rheumatoid arthritis and lupus are examples.",
        "answer": "autoimmune disorder ",
        "distractor_1": "immunodeficiency disorder ",
        "distractor_2": "active immunity ",
        "distractor_3": "passive immunity "
      },
      {
        "id": "8445",
        "question": "Type of white blood cell that produces antibodies.",
        "answer": "B lymphocyte ",
        "distractor_1": "bacteria",
        "distractor_2": "T lymphocyte ",
        "distractor_3": "leukocyte"
      },
      {
        "id": "8446",
        "question": "Single celled organisms that can cause disease that are classified by how they stain, how they group, and their shape.",
        "answer": "bacteria",
        "distractor_1": "leukocyte",
        "distractor_2": "antigen",
        "distractor_3": "virus"
      },
      {
        "id": "8447",
        "question": "A disorder in which the immune system no longer recognizes any invader and so opportunistic infections can be life threatening, AIDS and SCID are examples.",
        "answer": "immunodeficiency disorder ",
        "distractor_1": "active immunity ",
        "distractor_2": "passive immunity ",
        "distractor_3": "autoimmune disorder "
      },
      {
        "id": "8448",
        "question": "Name for white blood cells.",
        "answer": "leukocyte",
        "distractor_1": "antigen",
        "distractor_2": "vaccine",
        "distractor_3": "passive immunity "
      },
      {
        "id": "8449",
        "question": "The type of immunity you have because of antibodies that you take into your body that are produced from an outside source.",
        "answer": "passive immunity ",
        "distractor_1": "immunodeficiency disorder ",
        "distractor_2": "autoimmune disorder ",
        "distractor_3": "active immunity "
      },
      {
        "id": "8450",
        "question": "Any disease causing agent.",
        "answer": "pathogen",
        "distractor_1": "B lymphocyte ",
        "distractor_2": "bacteria",
        "distractor_3": "antigen"
      },
      {
        "id": "8451",
        "question": "Single celled or multicellular organism that can cause a disease, the Plasmodium that causes malaria is an example.",
        "answer": "protist",
        "distractor_1": "pathogen",
        "distractor_2": "bacteria",
        "distractor_3": "B lymphocyte "
      },
      {
        "id": "8452",
        "question": "Type of white blood cell that finds and destroys foreign cells such as bacteria.",
        "answer": "T lymphocyte ",
        "distractor_1": "B lymphocyte ",
        "distractor_2": "virus",
        "distractor_3": "pathogen"
      },
      {
        "id": "8453",
        "question": "A drug that causes immunity to a pathogen.",
        "answer": "vaccine",
        "distractor_1": "antigen",
        "distractor_2": "antibiotic",
        "distractor_3": "antibody "
      },
      {
        "id": "8454",
        "question": "A non-living, protein-coated packet of genetic information that is pathogenic.",
        "answer": "virus",
        "distractor_1": "protist",
        "distractor_2": "pathogen",
        "distractor_3": "leukocyte"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "184",
    "name": "Investigating Careers",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8481",
        "question": "Why are careers listed in a cluster?",
        "answer": "Workers' interests and aptitudes are similar.",
        "distractor_1": "All of the careers need the same level of education.",
        "distractor_2": "All of the careers have the same median pay.",
        "distractor_3": "Workers are all employed by the same company."
      },
      {
        "id": "8383",
        "question": "Which term is used to describe the general path taken in one's professional life?",
        "answer": "career",
        "distractor_1": "assignment",
        "distractor_2": "avocation",
        "distractor_3": "job"
      },
      {
        "id": "8384",
        "question": "What term is used to describe a source of income that is one step in a professional career?",
        "answer": "job",
        "distractor_1": "avocation",
        "distractor_2": "career",
        "distractor_3": "profession"
      },
      {
        "id": "8385",
        "question": "Why are careers listed in a cluster?",
        "answer": "Workers have similar interests and aptitudes.",
        "distractor_1": "Workers perform a similar task.",
        "distractor_2": "Workers receive the same salary.",
        "distractor_3": "Workers are employed by similar companies."
      },
      {
        "id": "8386",
        "question": "An interest survey assesses which characteristic?",
        "answer": "personal enjoyment of an activity",
        "distractor_1": "physical ability to perform an activity",
        "distractor_2": "mental ability to perform an activity",
        "distractor_3": "college grades"
      },
      {
        "id": "8387",
        "question": "What type of survey assesses whether you like to work with others or by yourself?",
        "answer": "personality",
        "distractor_1": "attitude",
        "distractor_2": "interest",
        "distractor_3": "ability"
      },
      {
        "id": "8388",
        "question": "A résumé is a summary of all except which of the following?",
        "answer": "ethnicity",
        "distractor_1": "education",
        "distractor_2": "skills",
        "distractor_3": "work experience"
      },
      {
        "id": "8389",
        "question": "What is the common purpose of a letter of application and a résumé?",
        "answer": "convince an employer to interview you",
        "distractor_1": "provide proof of your skills",
        "distractor_2": "brag about your education",
        "distractor_3": "raise your salary"
      },
      {
        "id": "8390",
        "question": "Which of the following is an appropriate use of social networking?",
        "answer": "post conservative photos from your vacation",
        "distractor_1": "post critical comments about your current employer",
        "distractor_2": "post photos of inappropriate personal conduct",
        "distractor_3": "post comments using questionable language"
      },
      {
        "id": "8391",
        "question": "What percentage of job categories that appeared 25 years ago no longer exist?",
        "answer": "30%",
        "distractor_1": "5%",
        "distractor_2": "95%",
        "distractor_3": "70%"
      },
      {
        "id": "8392",
        "question": "What is an aptitude?",
        "answer": "your natural ability to complete a task",
        "distractor_1": "your positive or negative feeling about a task",
        "distractor_2": "your enjoyment or dislike of a task",
        "distractor_3": "your knowledge about how to complete a task"
      },
      {
        "id": "8393",
        "question": "How many Myers-Briggs personality-type combinations are possible?",
        "answer": "16",
        "distractor_1": "4",
        "distractor_2": "8",
        "distractor_3": "12"
      },
      {
        "id": "8394",
        "question": "Cindy works about 40 hours per week, 50 weeks per year. She earns an hourly wage of $9.45. What is Cindy’s approximate annual income?",
        "answer": "$18,900",
        "distractor_1": "$24,500",
        "distractor_2": "$37,800",
        "distractor_3": "$42,000"
      },
      {
        "id": "8395",
        "question": "Several scam artists are at work creating scams on the Internet. What is the objective of a job-offer scam?",
        "answer": "collect personal information about you",
        "distractor_1": "get you a job with better benefits",
        "distractor_2": "locate a high-paying job for you",
        "distractor_3": "connect you with companies looking for employees"
      },
      {
        "id": "8396",
        "question": "Jeff is retiring after spending 45 years as a member of the workforce. During this time, he held seven different jobs. About how many years did Jeff average per job?",
        "answer": "6 1/2 years",
        "distractor_1": "4 1/2 years",
        "distractor_2": "5 years",
        "distractor_3": "8 years"
      },
      {
        "id": "8397",
        "question": "What is the most important factor governing the size and composition of the labor force?",
        "answer": "population",
        "distractor_1": "economic growth",
        "distractor_2": "government",
        "distractor_3": "global trading"
      },
      {
        "id": "8398",
        "question": "Melvin works four 10-hour days per week for 50 weeks in a year. During the 50 weeks he works, he also receives 10 paid holidays. About what percentage of total days in a year does Melvin work? (Hint: There are 365 days in a calendar year.)",
        "answer": "52%",
        "distractor_1": "60%",
        "distractor_2": "55%",
        "distractor_3": "73%"
      },
      {
        "id": "8399",
        "question": "Jennifer is paid $19.60 per hour and works 40 hours per week. What will be her weekly pay if she receives an increase of 5 percent per hour?",
        "answer": "$823.20",
        "distractor_1": "$392.75",
        "distractor_2": "$920.00",
        "distractor_3": "$784.50"
      },
      {
        "id": "8400",
        "question": "How is a career defined?",
        "answer": "the general path taken in one's professional life",
        "distractor_1": "an activity done to earn an income",
        "distractor_2": "the hobbies participated in during a lifetime",
        "distractor_3": "a single work assignment"
      },
      {
        "id": "8401",
        "question": "What types of questions will appear on an interest survey?",
        "answer": "questions about how much you enjoy specific activities",
        "distractor_1": "questions about your physical abilities",
        "distractor_2": "questions about your mental abilities",
        "distractor_3": "questions about your grades in classes associated with specific careers"
      },
      {
        "id": "8402",
        "question": "What document is a summary of your education, skills, and work experience?",
        "answer": "résumé",
        "distractor_1": "letter of introduction",
        "distractor_2": "resignation",
        "distractor_3": "personnel file"
      },
      {
        "id": "8403",
        "question": "Which of the following is an inappropriate use of social networking?",
        "answer": "post critical comments about your current employer",
        "distractor_1": "post original poetry that you have written",
        "distractor_2": "post conservative videos that you have created",
        "distractor_3": "post conservative photos from your vacation"
      },
      {
        "id": "8404",
        "question": "What term is used to describe the natural ability to complete a task associated with a job?",
        "answer": "aptitude",
        "distractor_1": "attitude",
        "distractor_2": "soft skill",
        "distractor_3": "career"
      },
      {
        "id": "8405",
        "question": "What is known as a group of jobs related by the worker's interests and aptitudes?",
        "answer": "career cluster",
        "distractor_1": "job",
        "distractor_2": "career",
        "distractor_3": "avocation"
      },
      {
        "id": "8406",
        "question": "Which type of personality tends to focus their attention and energy on the world outside of themselves?",
        "answer": "extrovert",
        "distractor_1": "introvert",
        "distractor_2": "judger",
        "distractor_3": "intuitive"
      },
      {
        "id": "8407",
        "question": "What term describes technical skills that are necessary to complete work you are assigned?",
        "answer": "hard skills",
        "distractor_1": "soft skills",
        "distractor_2": "aptitude",
        "distractor_3": "attitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "8408",
        "question": "Which type of personality describes people who prefer to work and spend time alone?",
        "answer": "introvert",
        "distractor_1": "extrovert",
        "distractor_2": "persuader",
        "distractor_3": "intuitive"
      },
      {
        "id": "8409",
        "question": "Which document is used to express interest in a specific job, sell yourself as the the best person for the job, and ask for an interview?",
        "answer": "letter of application",
        "distractor_1": "résumé",
        "distractor_2": "letter of resignation",
        "distractor_3": "letter of retirement"
      },
      {
        "id": "8410",
        "question": "Which document summarizes your skills, work experience, and education?",
        "answer": "résumé",
        "distractor_1": "letter of retirement",
        "distractor_2": "letter of resignation",
        "distractor_3": "letter of application"
      },
      {
        "id": "8411",
        "question": "Which term describes the way you behave and how you treat other people?",
        "answer": "soft skills",
        "distractor_1": "hard skills",
        "distractor_2": "aptitude",
        "distractor_3": "attitude"
      },
      {
        "id": "8455",
        "question": "Mike loves to read books about astronomy. He wants to find an occupation in this field, but he also wants to make a lot of money. Which salary range contains the median salary for an astronomer?",
        "answer": "$80,000 to $95,000",
        "distractor_1": "$30,000 to $45,000",
        "distractor_2": "$50,000 to $65,000",
        "distractor_3": "$120,000 to $135,000"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "185",
    "name": "Money Management",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8342",
        "question": "This term is defined as the original amount borrowed or deposited. ",
        "answer": "principal",
        "distractor_1": "collateral",
        "distractor_2": "finance charges",
        "distractor_3": "interest"
      },
      {
        "id": "8343",
        "question": "What term describes checks that have been written but have not yet been received by the bank?",
        "answer": "outstanding",
        "distractor_1": "cashier's",
        "distractor_2": "canceled",
        "distractor_3": "overdraft"
      },
      {
        "id": "8344",
        "question": "What tool is used to help manage spending?",
        "answer": "budget",
        "distractor_1": "calculator",
        "distractor_2": "expense estimator",
        "distractor_3": "parents"
      },
      {
        "id": "8347",
        "question": "Identify the term defined as how much you will earn on an investment or how much you will pay for borrowing money.",
        "answer": "interest",
        "distractor_1": "principal ",
        "distractor_2": "collateral",
        "distractor_3": "insufficient funds"
      },
      {
        "id": "8348",
        "question": "This type of credit must be paid back within a given time period after the purchase, usually 30 days.",
        "answer": "open",
        "distractor_1": "revolving",
        "distractor_2": "30 day ",
        "distractor_3": "installment"
      },
      {
        "id": "8351",
        "question": "What is the fee charged for lending money called?",
        "answer": "interest",
        "distractor_1": "co-pay",
        "distractor_2": "down payment",
        "distractor_3": "investment"
      },
      {
        "id": "8352",
        "question": "If Bridget worked 22 hours at $9.35 per hour and 15% of her gross pay was deducted for taxes, what was her actual take-home pay? ",
        "answer": "$174.84",
        "distractor_1": "$30.86 ",
        "distractor_2": "$236.56",
        "distractor_3": "$205.70"
      },
      {
        "id": "8353",
        "question": "Which of the terms listed is defined as the record of use of debt?",
        "answer": "credit history",
        "distractor_1": "stock market",
        "distractor_2": "check register",
        "distractor_3": "balance sheet "
      },
      {
        "id": "8354",
        "question": "Hunter has an annual income of $52,000.00. He pays 7.5% of his annual income to Social Security. How much does Hunter pay in Social Security taxes each year?",
        "answer": "$3,900.00",
        "distractor_1": "$75.00 ",
        "distractor_2": "$48,100.00",
        "distractor_3": "$55,900.00"
      },
      {
        "id": "8355",
        "question": "Use the rule of 72 formula to determine how many years it will take to double your money given a 9.5% interest rate.",
        "answer": "7.6 years",
        "distractor_1": "6.8 years",
        "distractor_2": "9.5 years",
        "distractor_3": "7.2 years"
      },
      {
        "id": "8356",
        "question": "Julie borrowed $5,000.00 to be paid back in four years at an annual interest rate of 7.5%. How much interest will she have paid at the end of the loan?",
        "answer": "$1,500.00",
        "distractor_1": "$375.00",
        "distractor_2": "$75.00 ",
        "distractor_3": "$6,500.00"
      },
      {
        "id": "8357",
        "question": "Which of the following is a savings plan established by employers to which eligible employees may make salary contributions on a posttax and/or pretax basis?",
        "answer": "401(k)",
        "distractor_1": "IRA",
        "distractor_2": "Social Security",
        "distractor_3": "W2"
      },
      {
        "id": "8358",
        "question": "Sarah borrowed $2,400.00 to be paid back in one year at an annual interest rate of 9%. How much interest will she have paid at the end of the loan?",
        "answer": "$216.00",
        "distractor_1": "$18.00 ",
        "distractor_2": "$21.60",
        "distractor_3": "$180.00"
      },
      {
        "id": "8361",
        "question": "This occurs when money is withdrawn from your account, making the available balance go below zero. ",
        "answer": "overdraft ",
        "distractor_1": "cancelation",
        "distractor_2": "forgery",
        "distractor_3": "reconciliation"
      },
      {
        "id": "8363",
        "question": "This term is defined as a short period of time that you can pay your total credit card bill and not be charged interest.",
        "answer": "grace period",
        "distractor_1": "maturation period",
        "distractor_2": "trial period",
        "distractor_3": "target period "
      },
      {
        "id": "8366",
        "question": "This number represents your creditworthiness and is generated by a mathematical formula based on information in your credit report.",
        "answer": "credit score",
        "distractor_1": "SAT score",
        "distractor_2": "ACT score",
        "distractor_3": "bank score"
      },
      {
        "id": "8367",
        "question": "Identify the term for balancing a checking account.",
        "answer": "reconciling ",
        "distractor_1": "endorsing",
        "distractor_2": "overdrafting",
        "distractor_3": "budgeting"
      },
      {
        "id": "8368",
        "question": "This computerized process initiates an electronic transfer of funds into a bank account. ",
        "answer": "direct deposit",
        "distractor_1": "forgery ",
        "distractor_2": "certificate of deposit",
        "distractor_3": "merger"
      },
      {
        "id": "8369",
        "question": "This term is defined as a decrease in the value of purchasing power as the result of demand for more goods than producers can supply.",
        "answer": "inflation",
        "distractor_1": "forgery",
        "distractor_2": "interest",
        "distractor_3": "insufficient funds"
      },
      {
        "id": "8370",
        "question": "This term is defined as a fee that is charged for lending money.",
        "answer": "interest",
        "distractor_1": "principal",
        "distractor_2": "installment",
        "distractor_3": "target period"
      },
      {
        "id": "8371",
        "question": "This term is defined as a fee calculated by multiplying the interest rate times the principal times the length of the loan/investment, or I = prn.",
        "answer": "simple interest",
        "distractor_1": "compound interest",
        "distractor_2": "credit history",
        "distractor_3": "overdraft"
      },
      {
        "id": "8372",
        "question": "This term is defined as the interest gained would be added to the principal, and future interest would be calculated on the principal plus the interest, or A = P(1 + r)^n.",
        "answer": "compound interest",
        "distractor_1": "simple interest",
        "distractor_2": "budget",
        "distractor_3": "balance sheet"
      },
      {
        "id": "8374",
        "question": "This term is defined as the monetary payment received for goods or services or from other sources, such as rents or investments.",
        "answer": "income",
        "distractor_1": "interest",
        "distractor_2": "merger",
        "distractor_3": "collateral"
      },
      {
        "id": "8375",
        "question": "This term is defined as costs or charges.",
        "answer": "expenses",
        "distractor_1": "outstanding",
        "distractor_2": "credit score",
        "distractor_3": "investment"
      },
      {
        "id": "8376",
        "question": "This term is defined as an estimate, often itemized, of expected income and expense for a given period in the future.",
        "answer": "budget",
        "distractor_1": "finance",
        "distractor_2": "interest",
        "distractor_3": "co-pay"
      },
      {
        "id": "8377",
        "question": "This term is defined as security pledged for the payment of a loan.",
        "answer": "collateral",
        "distractor_1": "investment",
        "distractor_2": "credit",
        "distractor_3": "installment"
      },
      {
        "id": "8378",
        "question": "This term is defined as a plan in which salaries or other payments are transferred by the paying agency directly to the accounts of the recipients.",
        "answer": "direct deposit",
        "distractor_1": "endorsement",
        "distractor_2": "overdraft",
        "distractor_3": "forgery"
      },
      {
        "id": "8379",
        "question": "This term is defined as an act or instance of overdrawing a checking account.",
        "answer": "overdraft",
        "distractor_1": "reconcile",
        "distractor_2": "outstanding",
        "distractor_3": "merger"
      },
      {
        "id": "8380",
        "question": "This term is defined as when you compare your bank statement with your check register to make sure you have accurately been tracking your checking account balance.",
        "answer": "reconciliation",
        "distractor_1": "overdraft",
        "distractor_2": "maturation",
        "distractor_3": "investment"
      },
      {
        "id": "8381",
        "question": "This formula is used to determine the number of years it will take to double an investment; divide the interest rate into 72 to determine the number of years it will take.",
        "answer": "rule of 72",
        "distractor_1": "credit score",
        "distractor_2": "finance charge",
        "distractor_3": "maturation period"
      },
      {
        "id": "8382",
        "question": "This term is defined as a savings plan through your employer that you can access after you retire.",
        "answer": "401(k)",
        "distractor_1": "rule of 72",
        "distractor_2": "credit history",
        "distractor_3": "direct deposit"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "186",
    "name": "Intelligent Homes",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8525",
        "question": "Define the term sound environment.",
        "answer": "physical characteristics that make up a room",
        "distractor_1": "an event in which a performer or group of performers behave in a particular way for another group of people",
        "distractor_2": "mechanical vibrations transmitted through an elastic medium",
        "distractor_3": "the social and cultural forces that shape the life of a person or a population"
      },
      {
        "id": "8526",
        "question": "This term refers to how clear or pleasing a sound is. ",
        "answer": "sound quality",
        "distractor_1": "sound volume",
        "distractor_2": "sound condition",
        "distractor_3": "sound lyrics"
      },
      {
        "id": "8527",
        "question": "One of the first units manufactured of a product, which is tested and retested so that it can be changed if necessary before the product is manufactured commercially, is referred to as what?",
        "answer": "prototype",
        "distractor_1": "original",
        "distractor_2": "ancestral",
        "distractor_3": "vintage"
      },
      {
        "id": "8528",
        "question": "The ability to control equipment or a device from a distance is known as what?",
        "answer": "remote control",
        "distractor_1": "electrical control",
        "distractor_2": "conditional control",
        "distractor_3": "telepathy control"
      },
      {
        "id": "8529",
        "question": "This type of network has more than one way for messages to get to their destination.",
        "answer": "dual mesh network",
        "distractor_1": "X10",
        "distractor_2": "Z-Wave",
        "distractor_3": "sensor"
      },
      {
        "id": "8531",
        "question": "Someone who takes technology for granted, grew up surrounded by technology, and never lived without the Internet, mobile phones, or computer games is referred to as what?",
        "answer": "digital native",
        "distractor_1": "digital immigrant",
        "distractor_2": "tech savvy",
        "distractor_3": "nerd"
      },
      {
        "id": "8532",
        "question": "This type of sensor measures the amount of humidity, or water vapor, in the air. ",
        "answer": "hygrometer",
        "distractor_1": "motion",
        "distractor_2": "leak",
        "distractor_3": "thermostat"
      },
      {
        "id": "8533",
        "question": "Which term is defined as the protection, preservation, and careful management of natural resources and of the environment?",
        "answer": "conservation",
        "distractor_1": "reservation",
        "distractor_2": "regulation",
        "distractor_3": "enforcement"
      },
      {
        "id": "8534",
        "question": "Which of the following terms is defined as a mechanical device that measures a physical condition and then converts the information into a signal that can be measured electrically?",
        "answer": "sensor",
        "distractor_1": "dual mesh network",
        "distractor_2": "prototype",
        "distractor_3": "circuit"
      },
      {
        "id": "8535",
        "question": "Opposition to electrical flow is called resistance. What are the SI units for resistance?",
        "answer": "ohms",
        "distractor_1": "voltage",
        "distractor_2": "electrons",
        "distractor_3": "amperes "
      },
      {
        "id": "8536",
        "question": "In electronic systems, the flow of electricity is called current. What SI unit is used to measure current?",
        "answer": "amperes",
        "distractor_1": "voltage ",
        "distractor_2": "electrons",
        "distractor_3": "ohms"
      },
      {
        "id": "8537",
        "question": "A continuous path along which electricity flows is known as what?",
        "answer": "circuit",
        "distractor_1": "watt",
        "distractor_2": "volt",
        "distractor_3": "power"
      },
      {
        "id": "8538",
        "question": "What type of camera has its own IP address and is connected directly to a network?",
        "answer": "IP camera",
        "distractor_1": "Polaroid camera",
        "distractor_2": "portrait camera",
        "distractor_3": "host camera"
      },
      {
        "id": "8539",
        "question": "What does a hygrometer measure?",
        "answer": "water vapor in the air ",
        "distractor_1": "movement",
        "distractor_2": "temperature",
        "distractor_3": "liquid, gas, or light lost through a hole or crack"
      },
      {
        "id": "8540",
        "question": "This term is defined as the physical characteristics that make up a room.",
        "answer": "sound environment ",
        "distractor_1": "sound lyrics",
        "distractor_2": "sound regulation",
        "distractor_3": "sound theory"
      },
      {
        "id": "8541",
        "question": "What does a home automation system do?",
        "answer": "It connects a home's smart electrical devices with each other.",
        "distractor_1": "It provides a home's warmth and coolness.",
        "distractor_2": "It gauges and records a home's audio and video.",
        "distractor_3": "It circulates the electrical current within a home."
      },
      {
        "id": "8542",
        "question": "Define the term conservation.",
        "answer": "the protection, preservation, and careful management of natural resources and of the environment",
        "distractor_1": "to emphasize or reinforce",
        "distractor_2": "the percentage difference in some quantity related to the operation of an apparatus or machine",
        "distractor_3": "the act of keeping back, withholding, or setting apart"
      },
      {
        "id": "8543",
        "question": "What term is defined as a residence that uses various appliances, devices, or technologies capable of communicating with one another and can be controlled remotely from any room in the home?",
        "answer": "smart home",
        "distractor_1": "electric company",
        "distractor_2": "magic",
        "distractor_3": "network"
      },
      {
        "id": "8544",
        "question": "This digital control protocol allows smart-home products to communicate with each other.",
        "answer": "X10",
        "distractor_1": "ZigBee",
        "distractor_2": "Wi-Fi",
        "distractor_3": "electrons"
      },
      {
        "id": "8545",
        "question": "What term is defined as a system of interconnected components or circuits?",
        "answer": "network",
        "distractor_1": "sensor",
        "distractor_2": "management",
        "distractor_3": "technology"
      },
      {
        "id": "8546",
        "question": "This type of system connects smart electrical devices in a house with each other.",
        "answer": "home automation",
        "distractor_1": "social network",
        "distractor_2": "HVAC",
        "distractor_3": "conditional"
      },
      {
        "id": "8547",
        "question": "What term is defined as electric current used as a power source?",
        "answer": "electricity",
        "distractor_1": "technology",
        "distractor_2": "chemistry",
        "distractor_3": "static"
      },
      {
        "id": "8548",
        "question": "This term is defined as anything that receives a signal or stimulus and responds to it.",
        "answer": "sensor",
        "distractor_1": "circuitry",
        "distractor_2": "software",
        "distractor_3": "trigger"
      },
      {
        "id": "8549",
        "question": "Which of the following terms is defined as a series of INSTEON, timer, and/or e-mail actions executed upon a trigger, which is subject to certain conditions?",
        "answer": "event",
        "distractor_1": "condition",
        "distractor_2": "trigger",
        "distractor_3": "action"
      },
      {
        "id": "8550",
        "question": "Anything that initiates a reaction or series of reactions can be called what?",
        "answer": "a trigger",
        "distractor_1": "a verdict",
        "distractor_2": "a responsibility",
        "distractor_3": "an action"
      },
      {
        "id": "8551",
        "question": "What term is defined as a particular state of being or existence such as the state of a device, certain days of the week, certain times of the day, and/or if it is light or dark outside?",
        "answer": "condition",
        "distractor_1": "constraint",
        "distractor_2": "consideration",
        "distractor_3": "conclusion"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "187",
    "name": "Mobile Apps",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8553",
        "question": "In the WIMP interface, the W in the acronym stands for what device that enables the user to control the pointer?",
        "answer": "window",
        "distractor_1": "widget",
        "distractor_2": "working",
        "distractor_3": "worm"
      },
      {
        "id": "8554",
        "question": "Which of the elements listed describes information the user receives from the program as the program is running?",
        "answer": "feedback",
        "distractor_1": "appearance",
        "distractor_2": "screen arrangement",
        "distractor_3": "brightness"
      },
      {
        "id": "8555",
        "question": "When does user experience begin?",
        "answer": "when the user is first introduced to the program",
        "distractor_1": "when a program starts",
        "distractor_2": "after the user completes the tutorials to the program",
        "distractor_3": "when the program is installing"
      },
      {
        "id": "8556",
        "question": "Which of the following statements about copyright laws is true?",
        "answer": "Copyright laws vary from country to country.",
        "distractor_1": "Copyright laws in the US expire after one year.",
        "distractor_2": "Copyright laws do not apply to certain fields such as education.",
        "distractor_3": "Copyright laws do not apply if you make any change to the created material."
      },
      {
        "id": "8557",
        "question": "A program that a user provides information for that acts as a tool to get the computer to do what the user wants done is called what?",
        "answer": "application software",
        "distractor_1": "operating system",
        "distractor_2": "communications software",
        "distractor_3": "navigation system"
      },
      {
        "id": "8558",
        "question": "A line in a program reads, 'If A > B or C > A go to line seven else go to line one.' If A = 7, B = 3, and C = 5, which line will the program go to?",
        "answer": "line seven",
        "distractor_1": "line one",
        "distractor_2": "line seven first then line one",
        "distractor_3": "line one first then line seven"
      },
      {
        "id": "8559",
        "question": "What is it called if a file is moved from a computer to a remote storage location such as over the Internet?",
        "answer": "upload",
        "distractor_1": "sideload",
        "distractor_2": "download",
        "distractor_3": "unload"
      },
      {
        "id": "8560",
        "question": "Which letter describes the best screen arrangement of items in a computer program based on their importance?",
        "answer": "Z",
        "distractor_1": "N",
        "distractor_2": "M",
        "distractor_3": "C"
      },
      {
        "id": "8561",
        "question": "Which of the following items would be useful feedback to the user of a game app?",
        "answer": "the score in the corner updating",
        "distractor_1": "the program adding features",
        "distractor_2": "real-time updates of the app",
        "distractor_3": "an end-user license agreement "
      },
      {
        "id": "8562",
        "question": "A picture is posted on a commercial Web site that you would like to use. The site is a public access site, but users must register and pay a fee. Which of the listed statements best describes your right to use the picture?",
        "answer": "You may not use the picture unless you get specific permission from the creator of the picture.",
        "distractor_1": "You may use it if you register and pay the fee.",
        "distractor_2": "You may use it after it has been on the site for one calendar year.",
        "distractor_3": "You may use it if you make some minor changes such as cropping the picture."
      },
      {
        "id": "8563",
        "question": "Which of the listed items is considered the forerunner of the modern Internet?",
        "answer": "ARPANET",
        "distractor_1": "Intercon",
        "distractor_2": "World Wide Web",
        "distractor_3": "Hypertext"
      },
      {
        "id": "8565",
        "question": "2011 was the first full year for tablet sales after the introduction of the iPad by Apple. How many tablet computers sold during 2011?",
        "answer": "50 to 75 million",
        "distractor_1": "25 to 50 million",
        "distractor_2": "75 to 100 million",
        "distractor_3": "more than 100 million"
      },
      {
        "id": "8566",
        "question": "If a 280,000-pixel screen has 700 pixels in each horizontal row, how many pixels are in each vertical column?",
        "answer": "400",
        "distractor_1": "40",
        "distractor_2": "4",
        "distractor_3": "40,000"
      },
      {
        "id": "8567",
        "question": "The Android operating system was developed by Android, Inc. and later purchased by which of these corporations?",
        "answer": "Google ",
        "distractor_1": "Apple",
        "distractor_2": "Microsoft",
        "distractor_3": "Amazon"
      },
      {
        "id": "8569",
        "question": "The Android operating system is a type of software that is freely distributed and encourages the sharing of design details in the software. Which of the following terms best describes this type of software?",
        "answer": "open source",
        "distractor_1": "free market",
        "distractor_2": "communal",
        "distractor_3": "freeware"
      },
      {
        "id": "8571",
        "question": "In the WIMP interface model, the M in the acronym stands for what device that enables the user to control the pointer?",
        "answer": "mouse",
        "distractor_1": "minisystem",
        "distractor_2": "microcomputer",
        "distractor_3": "macro"
      },
      {
        "id": "8572",
        "question": "Which of the elements listed are most effective at setting the overall tone of a program?",
        "answer": "appearance",
        "distractor_1": "feedback",
        "distractor_2": "screen arrangement",
        "distractor_3": "brightness"
      },
      {
        "id": "8573",
        "question": "Which of the following best describes the idea of user experience as it relates to a computer program?",
        "answer": "the total of all of the experiences the user will have from first introduction until the program is no longer in use",
        "distractor_1": "the type of feedback the user receives as he or she uses the program",
        "distractor_2": "the ease of navigation for the user as he or she uses the program",
        "distractor_3": "the number of times the user experiences the program measured by how often he or she accesses the program"
      },
      {
        "id": "8574",
        "question": "When is the creator of an original work legally allowed to claim a copyright for that work in the United States?",
        "answer": "from the moment the work is created",
        "distractor_1": "when he or she first conceives of the idea",
        "distractor_2": "when the proper documents are filed with the copyright office",
        "distractor_3": "from when the work is created until it is first put up for public display"
      },
      {
        "id": "8575",
        "question": "A program that communicates directly with the hardware of the program and with other programs to allow those programs to use hardware components is called what?",
        "answer": "operating system",
        "distractor_1": "application software",
        "distractor_2": "communications software",
        "distractor_3": "navigation system"
      },
      {
        "id": "8576",
        "question": "A line in a program reads: 'If A > B and C > A go to line seven else go to line one.' If A = 7, B = 3, and C = 5, which line will the program go to?",
        "answer": "line one",
        "distractor_1": "line seven",
        "distractor_2": "line seven first then line one",
        "distractor_3": "line one first then line seven"
      },
      {
        "id": "8577",
        "question": "What is it called if a file is moved from one computer to a second computer over a physical connection such as a USB cable?",
        "answer": "sideload",
        "distractor_1": "upload",
        "distractor_2": "download",
        "distractor_3": "unload"
      },
      {
        "id": "8578",
        "question": "The answer to the question 'What do you want an app to look like?' is usually driven by which of the following?",
        "answer": "the purpose of the app",
        "distractor_1": "how much it will cost",
        "distractor_2": "what will fit",
        "distractor_3": "what's pretty"
      },
      {
        "id": "8579",
        "question": "Which of the following items would be useful feedback to the user of a banking app?",
        "answer": "the balance turning red when the account is overdrawn",
        "distractor_1": "the program adding his or her checks ",
        "distractor_2": "real-time updates of the app",
        "distractor_3": "an end-user license agreement "
      },
      {
        "id": "8580",
        "question": "A picture is posted on a social media site that you would like to use. The site is a public access site where anyone can see the picture without registering or paying a fee. Which of the listed statements best describes your right to use the picture?",
        "answer": "You may not use the picture unless you get specific permission from the creator of the picture.",
        "distractor_1": "Your right to use it depends on whether the creator is a professional in the field of graphics.",
        "distractor_2": "You may use it after it has been on the site for one calendar year.",
        "distractor_3": "You may use it if you make some minor changes such as cropping the picture."
      },
      {
        "id": "8581",
        "question": "Software that communicates between the user and the operating system software on a computer",
        "answer": "application software",
        "distractor_1": "user software",
        "distractor_2": "appops software",
        "distractor_3": "communications software"
      },
      {
        "id": "8582",
        "question": "This grants the creator of any intellectual property the rights to control the property.",
        "answer": "copyright",
        "distractor_1": "intellectual right",
        "distractor_2": "creation right",
        "distractor_3": "property right"
      },
      {
        "id": "8583",
        "question": "The process of deciding on the look and function of a program before it is built",
        "answer": "design",
        "distractor_1": "execution",
        "distractor_2": "describing",
        "distractor_3": "resolution"
      },
      {
        "id": "8584",
        "question": "Transferring a file from a remote location to a local device.",
        "answer": "download",
        "distractor_1": "sideload",
        "distractor_2": "upload",
        "distractor_3": "unload"
      },
      {
        "id": "8585",
        "question": "Information that is received from a program that makes the user aware of a change in the program",
        "answer": "feedback",
        "distractor_1": "appearance",
        "distractor_2": "infomatics",
        "distractor_3": "update"
      },
      {
        "id": "8586",
        "question": "Small graphical representation used as a shortcut to an application",
        "answer": "icon",
        "distractor_1": "pictograph",
        "distractor_2": "typeface",
        "distractor_3": "vector"
      },
      {
        "id": "8587",
        "question": "The arrangement of elements of a program on the screen",
        "answer": "layout",
        "distractor_1": "elemental course",
        "distractor_2": "piecework",
        "distractor_3": "constraint"
      },
      {
        "id": "8588",
        "question": "Device used to control the pointer",
        "answer": "mouse",
        "distractor_1": "application  ",
        "distractor_2": "pictograph",
        "distractor_3": "vector"
      },
      {
        "id": "8589",
        "question": "Software that communicates between the hardware and the applications software",
        "answer": "operating system software",
        "distractor_1": "communication software",
        "distractor_2": "opsapp software",
        "distractor_3": "applications software"
      },
      {
        "id": "8590",
        "question": "Graphical representation of a location on the screen where the user can affect the application",
        "answer": "pointer",
        "distractor_1": "icon",
        "distractor_2": "infomatic",
        "distractor_3": "locator"
      },
      {
        "id": "8591",
        "question": "A description of the number of pixels in a certain area on a device screen",
        "answer": "resolution",
        "distractor_1": "pixelation",
        "distractor_2": "aspect ratio",
        "distractor_3": "pixel area"
      },
      {
        "id": "8592",
        "question": "Transferring a file from one device to another through a physical connection",
        "answer": "sideload",
        "distractor_1": "download",
        "distractor_2": "upload",
        "distractor_3": "unload"
      },
      {
        "id": "8593",
        "question": "Transferring a file from a device to a remote location",
        "answer": "upload",
        "distractor_1": "sideload",
        "distractor_2": "download",
        "distractor_3": "unload"
      },
      {
        "id": "8594",
        "question": "The sum total of all of the interations a user has with a program",
        "answer": "user experience",
        "distractor_1": "interactive path",
        "distractor_2": "user application",
        "distractor_3": "communication path"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "188",
    "name": "Composites",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8624",
        "question": "Select the best definition of a composite.",
        "answer": "a material that physically bonds two materials, creating a material with more desirable properties",
        "distractor_1": "a material that chemically bonds two materials into one, creating a new material",
        "distractor_2": "a material made from a solid and a liquid that creates a chemical bond",
        "distractor_3": "a material that is used to improve soil"
      },
      {
        "id": "8625",
        "question": "Which of the following materials is considered a natural composite?",
        "answer": "bone",
        "distractor_1": "concrete",
        "distractor_2": "Kevlar",
        "distractor_3": "fiberglass"
      },
      {
        "id": "8626",
        "question": "Which of the following is a disadvantage of using a composite material?",
        "answer": "higher material cost",
        "distractor_1": "prone to corrode",
        "distractor_2": "difficult to form complex parts",
        "distractor_3": "lighter weight"
      },
      {
        "id": "8627",
        "question": "Choose the most commonly used composite material.",
        "answer": "concrete",
        "distractor_1": "fiberglass",
        "distractor_2": "carbon fiber",
        "distractor_3": "epoxy resin"
      },
      {
        "id": "8628",
        "question": "What function does the matrix perform in a composite?",
        "answer": "adhesive",
        "distractor_1": "lubricant",
        "distractor_2": "reinforcement",
        "distractor_3": "filler"
      },
      {
        "id": "8638",
        "question": "What is the largest all-carbon fiber aircraft that has been built?",
        "answer": "White Knight Two",
        "distractor_1": "Boeing 787 Dreamliner",
        "distractor_2": "C5A Cargo Plane",
        "distractor_3": "Airbus A380"
      },
      {
        "id": "8639",
        "question": "As the thickness of a resin increases, the amount of heat it generates increases. What type of reaction causes this heat to be generated?",
        "answer": "exothermic",
        "distractor_1": "endothermic",
        "distractor_2": "exoskeletal",
        "distractor_3": "endotrophic"
      },
      {
        "id": "8640",
        "question": "An empty Boeing 787 Dreamliner weighs around 242,000 pounds, and 50% of the weight is a composite material. How many pounds of composites are in the Dreamliner?",
        "answer": "121,000 lb",
        "distractor_1": "1,210,000 lb",
        "distractor_2": "12,100 lb",
        "distractor_3": "4,840 lb"
      },
      {
        "id": "8641",
        "question": "Which of the following is an advantage of using a composite material?",
        "answer": "lighter weight",
        "distractor_1": "prone to corrode",
        "distractor_2": "difficult to form complex parts",
        "distractor_3": "higher material cost"
      },
      {
        "id": "8642",
        "question": "What function does the glass fiber perform in fiberglass?",
        "answer": "reinforcement",
        "distractor_1": "lubricant",
        "distractor_2": "adhesive",
        "distractor_3": "filler"
      },
      {
        "id": "8643",
        "question": "During which build-up process are sheets or mats soaked with resin and rolled into a form?",
        "answer": "hand lay-up",
        "distractor_1": "pouring",
        "distractor_2": "resin infusion",
        "distractor_3": "spray-up"
      },
      {
        "id": "8644",
        "question": "Which type of plastic material cannot be reformed by heating it?",
        "answer": "thermoset",
        "distractor_1": "epoxy",
        "distractor_2": "reinforced",
        "distractor_3": "thermoplastic"
      },
      {
        "id": "8645",
        "question": "Which manufacturing process pulls reinforcing material through a die to infuse the resin and shape a part?",
        "answer": "pultrusion",
        "distractor_1": "filament winding",
        "distractor_2": "spray-up",
        "distractor_3": "vacuum infusion"
      },
      {
        "id": "8646",
        "question": "What material initiates or accelerates a chemical reaction?",
        "answer": "catalyst",
        "distractor_1": "Kevlar",
        "distractor_2": "polyester",
        "distractor_3": "epoxy resin"
      },
      {
        "id": "8647",
        "question": "Which term describes a production method in which a soft plastic is forced through a die to create a shape?",
        "answer": "extrusion",
        "distractor_1": "pultrusion",
        "distractor_2": "injection molding",
        "distractor_3": "vacuum infusion"
      },
      {
        "id": "8648",
        "question": "Which term describes a method of gluing layers of material together to form a thicker part?",
        "answer": "lamination",
        "distractor_1": "molding",
        "distractor_2": "filament winding",
        "distractor_3": "pouring"
      },
      {
        "id": "8649",
        "question": "Which term describes the material used as an adhesive in a composite?",
        "answer": "resin",
        "distractor_1": "vinyl ester",
        "distractor_2": "fiberglass",
        "distractor_3": "reinforcement"
      },
      {
        "id": "8650",
        "question": "Which term describes a fiber made almost entirely of pure carbon?",
        "answer": "carbon fiber",
        "distractor_1": "fiberglass",
        "distractor_2": "filament",
        "distractor_3": "natural fiber"
      },
      {
        "id": "8651",
        "question": "Which term describes a thermosetting adhesive used with carbon fiber to create a strong, lightweight material?",
        "answer": "epoxy",
        "distractor_1": "latex",
        "distractor_2": "polyester",
        "distractor_3": "vinyl ester"
      },
      {
        "id": "8629",
        "question": "Plywood is an example of which kind of fiber arrangement?",
        "answer": "laminated layers with fibers perpendicular",
        "distractor_1": "random fiber arrangement",
        "distractor_2": "laminated layers with fibers parallel",
        "distractor_3": "natural arrangement"
      },
      {
        "id": "8630",
        "question": "During which build-up process are long fibers chopped and mixed with resin while being placed in a form?",
        "answer": "spray-up",
        "distractor_1": "resin infusion",
        "distractor_2": "hand lay-up",
        "distractor_3": "pouring"
      },
      {
        "id": "8631",
        "question": "Which type of plastic material can be heated to soften it for forming?",
        "answer": "thermoplastic",
        "distractor_1": "epoxy",
        "distractor_2": "reinforced",
        "distractor_3": "thermoset"
      },
      {
        "id": "8632",
        "question": "Which manufacturing process uses a mandrel to build large, hollow composite tubes?",
        "answer": "filament winding",
        "distractor_1": "spray-up",
        "distractor_2": "pultrusion",
        "distractor_3": "vacuum infusion"
      },
      {
        "id": "8633",
        "question": "Which type of software enables a manufacturer to test a product before creating a prototype?",
        "answer": "simulation",
        "distractor_1": "virtual reality",
        "distractor_2": "CAM",
        "distractor_3": "prototyping"
      },
      {
        "id": "8634",
        "question": "What is the name of the chemical process that occurs when cement hardens into concrete?",
        "answer": "hydration",
        "distractor_1": "hardening",
        "distractor_2": "compaction",
        "distractor_3": "bonding"
      },
      {
        "id": "8635",
        "question": "A cubic yard of concrete contains 27 cubic feet. How many yards of concrete would be needed to pour a column of concrete 18 inches by 18 inches by 24 feet?",
        "answer": "2 cu yd",
        "distractor_1": "54 cu yd",
        "distractor_2": "0.2 cu yd",
        "distractor_3": "5.4 cu yd"
      },
      {
        "id": "8636",
        "question": "What type of resin should be used with a carbon fiber reinforcing cloth?",
        "answer": "epoxy",
        "distractor_1": "polyester",
        "distractor_2": "vinyl ester",
        "distractor_3": "latex"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "500",
    "name": "ITC Orientation",
    "weight": "100",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "8656",
        "question": "In which session(s) is the Post Test completed?",
        "answer": "Session 7 ",
        "distractor_1": "Sessions 2-5",
        "distractor_2": "Session 6",
        "distractor_3": "Session 1"
      },
      {
        "id": "8657",
        "question": "In which session(s) is the Module Guide completed?",
        "answer": "Session 1",
        "distractor_1": "Sessions 2-5",
        "distractor_2": "Session 6",
        "distractor_3": "Session 7"
      },
      {
        "id": "8658",
        "question": "Module activities are performed in what area?",
        "answer": "workstation",
        "distractor_1": "hall ",
        "distractor_2": "seating",
        "distractor_3": "lecture"
      },
      {
        "id": "8666",
        "question": "What term is defined as introductory instruction concerning a new situation?",
        "answer": "orientation",
        "distractor_1": "performance ",
        "distractor_2": "goal",
        "distractor_3": "cooperation"
      },
      {
        "id": "8667",
        "question": "What term is defined as the interaction of two or more forces so that their combined effect is greater than the sum of their individual effects?",
        "answer": "synergy",
        "distractor_1": "goal",
        "distractor_2": "performance",
        "distractor_3": "cooperation"
      },
      {
        "id": "8668",
        "question": "What activity is completed at the beginning of Session 1?",
        "answer": "Module Guide",
        "distractor_1": "Research, Challenge, and Application",
        "distractor_2": "Test Review",
        "distractor_3": "Post Test"
      },
      {
        "id": "8669",
        "question": "What activity is completed at the beginning of Session 7?",
        "answer": "Post Test",
        "distractor_1": "Research, Challenge, and Application",
        "distractor_2": "Test Review",
        "distractor_3": "Module Guide "
      },
      {
        "id": "8670",
        "question": "What activity takes about 45 minutes to complete and covers a group of closely related ideas that are explained in a series of pages?",
        "answer": "session",
        "distractor_1": "Module",
        "distractor_2": "rotation",
        "distractor_3": "application "
      },
      {
        "id": "8671",
        "question": "What term is defined as a group of elements or parts that interact to form a complex whole?",
        "answer": "system",
        "distractor_1": "cooperation",
        "distractor_2": "performance",
        "distractor_3": "partnership"
      },
      {
        "id": "8672",
        "question": "What term is defined as an interactive competition completed during Session 6 in order to review Module Guide questions and Module-specific vocabulary words?",
        "answer": "Test Review",
        "distractor_1": "Module Guide",
        "distractor_2": "Post Test",
        "distractor_3": "Enrichments"
      },
      {
        "id": "8673",
        "question": "What term is defined as a consequence taken for misbehavior in a Module lab?",
        "answer": "personal step",
        "distractor_1": "demerit",
        "distractor_2": "blemish",
        "distractor_3": "virus"
      },
      {
        "id": "8674",
        "question": "This term is defined as a folder specially designed for students in a Module lab used to record personal information and store Module documents.",
        "answer": "student portfolio",
        "distractor_1": "grade book",
        "distractor_2": "Student Module Notebook",
        "distractor_3": "Module Guide"
      },
      {
        "id": "8675",
        "question": "This term is defined as a movable window used whenever third-party software instructions are given.",
        "answer": "Agent",
        "distractor_1": "Coach",
        "distractor_2": "Windows",
        "distractor_3": "Explorer"
      },
      {
        "id": "8676",
        "question": "This term is defined as a Module feature that offers additional hints on a page in addition to the instructions already presented.",
        "answer": "Student Tip",
        "distractor_1": "Bonus round",
        "distractor_2": "Test Review",
        "distractor_3": "Freebies"
      },
      {
        "id": "8659",
        "question": "What activities are typically completed after finishing a session?",
        "answer": "enrichments",
        "distractor_1": "RCAs",
        "distractor_2": "Module Guide",
        "distractor_3": "Post Test"
      },
      {
        "id": "8660",
        "question": "Answering an RCA question correctly on the first attempt is worth how many points?",
        "answer": "10",
        "distractor_1": "5",
        "distractor_2": "30",
        "distractor_3": "120"
      },
      {
        "id": "8661",
        "question": "Answering an RCA question correctly on the second attempt is worth how many points?",
        "answer": "5",
        "distractor_1": "10",
        "distractor_2": "30",
        "distractor_3": "120"
      },
      {
        "id": "8662",
        "question": "RCA is the acronym for which of the following?",
        "answer": "Research, Challenge, and Application",
        "distractor_1": "Resource, Challenge, and Application",
        "distractor_2": "Research, Chart, and Application ",
        "distractor_3": "Research, Challenge, and Approximation"
      },
      {
        "id": "8663",
        "question": "What term refers to the time spent learning the information in one Module and is made up of seven sessions or class periods?",
        "answer": "rotation",
        "distractor_1": "session ",
        "distractor_2": "application",
        "distractor_3": "semester"
      },
      {
        "id": "8664",
        "question": "What term refers to seven sessions of engaging activities designed to teach concepts related to a specific topic",
        "answer": "Module",
        "distractor_1": "application",
        "distractor_2": "session ",
        "distractor_3": "semester"
      },
      {
        "id": "8665",
        "question": "What term is defined as the act of working together toward a common end or purpose?",
        "answer": "cooperation",
        "distractor_1": "partnership",
        "distractor_2": "orientation",
        "distractor_3": "goal"
      }
    ]
  }
]
